<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Greatest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 21:05:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>tensorflow</title>
      <link>https://github.com/tensorflow/tensorflow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An Open Source Machine Learning Framework for Everyone]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/tensorflow/tensorflow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>transformers</title>
      <link>https://github.com/huggingface/transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ Transformers: State-of-the-art Machine Learning for Pytorch, TensorFlow, and JAX.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/huggingface/transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-mixing: Mitigating Backdoors in Fine-tuned Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-mixing-mitigating-backdoors-in-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we take the first step to exploit the pre-trained (unfine-tuned) weights to mitigate backdoors in fine-tuned language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-mixing-mitigating-backdoors-in-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parsing as Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parsing-as-pretraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first cast constituent and dependency parsing as sequence tagging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parsing-as-pretraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>models</title>
      <link>https://github.com/tensorflow/models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Models and examples built with TensorFlow]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/tensorflow/models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pytorch</title>
      <link>https://github.com/pytorch/pytorch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tensors and Dynamic neural networks in Python with strong GPU acceleration]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/pytorch/pytorch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ConvNet for the 2020s</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-convnet-for-the-2020s</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The "Roaring 20s" of visual recognition began with the introduction of Vision Transformers (ViTs), which quickly superseded ConvNets as the state-of-the-art image classification model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-convnet-for-the-2020s</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RegNet: Self-Regulated Network for Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regnet-self-regulated-network-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ResNet and its variants have achieved remarkable successes in various computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regnet-self-regulated-network-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaskNet: Introducing Feature-Wise Multiplication to CTR Ranking Models by Instance-Guided Mask</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masknet-introducing-feature-wise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also turn the feed-forward layer in DNN model into a mixture of addictive and multiplicative feature interactions by proposing MaskBlock in this paper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masknet-introducing-feature-wise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gender Classification and Bias Mitigation in Facial Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gender-classification-and-bias-mitigation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We worked to increase classification accuracy and mitigate algorithmic biases on our baseline model trained on the augmented benchmark database.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gender-classification-and-bias-mitigation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gender Classification from Iris Texture Images Using a New Set of Binary Statistical Image Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gender-classification-from-iris-texture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the use of a Binary Statistical Features (BSIF) algorithm for classifying gender from iris texture images captured with NIR sensors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gender-classification-from-iris-texture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Covariate Influence on Gender and Race Prediction from Near-Infrared Ocular Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-covariate-influence-on-gender-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research has explored the possibility of automatically deducing information such as gender, age and race of an individual from their biometric data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-covariate-influence-on-gender-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Resolution Image Synthesis with Latent Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-image-synthesis-with-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By decomposing the image formation process into a sequential application of denoising autoencoders, diffusion models (DMs) achieve state-of-the-art synthesis results on image data and beyond.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-image-synthesis-with-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAGA: A Fast Incremental Gradient Method With Support for Non-Strongly Convex Composite Objectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saga-a-fast-incremental-gradient-method-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we introduce a new optimisation method called SAGA in the spirit of SAG, SDCA, MISO and SVRG, a set of recently proposed incremental gradient algorithms with fast linear convergence rates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saga-a-fast-incremental-gradient-method-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scikit-learn: Machine Learning in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scikit-learn-machine-learning-in-python</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scikit-learn is a Python module integrating a wide range of state-of-the-art machine learning algorithms for medium-scale supervised and unsupervised problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scikit-learn-machine-learning-in-python</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting the Tesseract Open Source OCR Engine for Multilingual OCR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-the-tesseract-open-source-ocr-engine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe efforts to adapt the Tesseract open source OCR engine for multiple scripts and languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-the-tesseract-open-source-ocr-engine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politeness Transfer: A Tag and Generate Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/politeness-transfer-a-tag-and-generate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a new task of politeness transfer which involves converting non-polite sentences to polite sentences while preserving the meaning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/politeness-transfer-a-tag-and-generate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrossWOZ: A Large-Scale Chinese Cross-Domain Task-Oriented Dialogue Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crosswoz-a-large-scale-chinese-cross-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To advance multi-domain (cross-domain) dialogue modeling as well as alleviate the shortage of Chinese task-oriented datasets, we propose CrossWOZ, the first large-scale Chinese Cross-Domain Wizard-of-Oz task-oriented dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crosswoz-a-large-scale-chinese-cross-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepFaceLab: Integrated, flexible and extensible face-swapping framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepfacelab-a-simple-flexible-and-extensible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deepfake defense not only requires the research of detection but also requires the efforts of generation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepfacelab-a-simple-flexible-and-extensible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepFakes and Beyond: A Survey of Face Manipulation and Fake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepfakes-and-beyond-a-survey-of-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The free access to large-scale public databases, together with the fast progress of deep learning techniques, in particular Generative Adversarial Networks, have led to the generation of very realistic fake content with its corresponding implications towards society in this era of fake news.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepfakes-and-beyond-a-survey-of-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time-Voice-Cloning</title>
      <link>https://github.com/CorentinJ/Real-Time-Voice-Cloning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clone a voice in 5 seconds to generate arbitrary speech in real-time]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/CorentinJ/Real-Time-Voice-Cloning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Path Aggregation Network for Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/path-aggregation-network-for-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The way that information propagates in neural networks is of great importance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/path-aggregation-network-for-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Contribution of Per-ICD Attention Mechanisms to Classify Health Records in Languages with Fewer Resources than English</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-contribution-of-per-icd-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a multi-label text classifier with per-label attention for the classification of Electronic Health Records according to the International Classification of Diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-contribution-of-per-icd-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Well-Read Students Learn Better: On the Importance of Pre-training Compact Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/well-read-students-learn-better-the-impact-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent developments in natural language representations have been accompanied by large and expensive models that leverage vast amounts of general-domain text through self-supervised pre-training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/well-read-students-learn-better-the-impact-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caffe: Convolutional Architecture for Fast Feature Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caffe-convolutional-architecture-for-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The framework is a BSD-licensed C++ library with Python and MATLAB bindings for training and deploying general-purpose convolutional neural networks and other deep models efficiently on commodity architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caffe-convolutional-architecture-for-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAssistant Conversations -- Democratizing Large Language Model Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openassistant-conversations-democratizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The corpus is a product of a worldwide crowd-sourcing effort involving over 13, 500 volunteers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openassistant-conversations-democratizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training language models to follow instructions with human feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-language-models-to-follow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show an avenue for aligning language models with user intent on a wide range of tasks by fine-tuning with human feedback.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-language-models-to-follow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-code LLM: Visual Programming over LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-code-llm-visual-programming-over-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed Low-code LLM framework consists of a Planning LLM that designs a structured planning workflow for complex tasks, which can be correspondingly edited and confirmed by users through low-code visual programming operations, and an Executing LLM that generates responses following the user-confirmed workflow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-code-llm-visual-programming-over-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual ChatGPT: Talking, Drawing and Editing with Visual Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-chatgpt-talking-drawing-and-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, We build a system called \textbf{Visual ChatGPT}, incorporating different Visual Foundation Models, to enable the user to interact with ChatGPT by 1) sending and receiving not only languages but also images 2) providing complex visual questions or visual editing instructions that require the collaboration of multiple AI models with multi-steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-chatgpt-talking-drawing-and-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding Conditional Control to Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adding-conditional-control-to-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, training a ControlNet is as fast as fine-tuning a diffusion model, and the model can be trained on a personal devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adding-conditional-control-to-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
