<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 21:07:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Training and Tuning Generative Neural Radiance Fields for Attribute-Conditional 3D-Aware Face Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-tuning-generative-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce a conditional GNeRF model that uses specific attribute labels as input in order to improve the controllabilities and disentangling abilities of 3D-aware generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-tuning-generative-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-lingual Transfer Learning for Fake News Detector in a Low-Resource Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-transfer-learning-for-fake-news</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Development of methods to detect fake news (FN) in low-resource languages has been impeded by a lack of training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-transfer-learning-for-fake-news</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User-Controllable Latent Transformer for StyleGAN Image Layout Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-controllable-latent-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our framework, the user annotates a StyleGAN image with locations they want to move or not and specifies a movement direction by mouse dragging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-controllable-latent-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Automated Imbalanced Learning with Deep Hierarchical Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-automated-imbalanced-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, we investigate developing a learning-based over-sampling algorithm to optimize the classification performance, which is a challenging task because of the huge and hierarchical decision space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-automated-imbalanced-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Mini-Batch Consistency for Set Encoding Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-mini-batch-consistency-for-set</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous works have established solid foundations for neural set functions, as well as effective architectures which preserve the necessary properties for operating on sets, such as being invariant to permutations of the set elements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-mini-batch-consistency-for-set</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arbitrary Shape Text Detection via Segmentation with Probability Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbitrary-shape-text-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To be concrete, we adopt a Sigmoid Alpha Function (SAF) to transfer the distances between boundaries and their inside pixels to a probability map.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbitrary-shape-text-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVD-GCN: A Simplified Graph Convolution Paradigm for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svd-gcn-a-simplified-graph-convolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the tremendous success of Graph Convolutional Networks (GCNs), they have been widely applied to recommender systems and have shown promising performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svd-gcn-a-simplified-graph-convolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partially Relevant Video Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partially-relevant-video-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill the gap, we propose in this paper a novel T2VR subtask termed Partially Relevant Video Retrieval (PRVR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partially-relevant-video-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoQGS: Auto-Prompt for Low-Resource Knowledge-based Question Generation from SPARQL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoqgs-auto-prompt-for-low-resource</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the task of knowledge-based question generation (KBQG).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoqgs-auto-prompt-for-low-resource</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuralSI: Structural Parameter Identification in Nonlinear Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralsi-structural-parameter-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Structural monitoring for complex built environments often suffers from mismatch between design, laboratory testing, and actual built parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralsi-structural-parameter-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Lingual Cross-Modal Retrieval with Noise-Robust Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-cross-modal-retrieval-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a noise-robust cross-lingual cross-modal retrieval method for low-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-cross-modal-retrieval-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laplacian Pyramid-like Autoencoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplacian-pyramid-like-autoencoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LPAE decomposes an image into the approximation image and the detail image in the encoder part and then tries to reconstruct the original image in the decoder part using the two components.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplacian-pyramid-like-autoencoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORI-RAN: Multi-view Robust Representation Learning via Hybrid Contrastive Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mori-ran-multi-view-robust-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, in this paper, we proposed a hybrid contrastive fusion algorithm to extract robust view-common representation from unlabeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mori-ran-multi-view-robust-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Bandits for Linear Structural Equation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-bandits-for-linear-structural-equation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two linear mechanisms, one soft intervention and one observational, are assumed for each node, giving rise to $2^N$ possible interventions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-bandits-for-linear-structural-equation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Auto-Differentiable Digitally Reconstructed Radiographs for Solving Inverse Problems in Intraoperative Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-auto-differentiable-digitally</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To make DRRs interoperable with gradient-based optimization and deep learning frameworks, we have reformulated Siddon's method, the most popular ray-tracing algorithm used in DRR generation, as a series of vectorized tensor operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-auto-differentiable-digitally</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Spike Depth Estimation via Cross-modality Cross-domain Knowledge Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-spike-depth-estimation-via-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key challenges for such problem lie in the modality gap between RGB and spike modalities, and the domain gap between labeled source RGB and unlabeled target spike domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-spike-depth-estimation-via-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Framework for Inherently Interpretable Optimization Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-inherently-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One major barrier is that the optimization software can be perceived as a black box, which may produce solutions of high quality, but can create completely different solutions when circumstances change leading to low acceptance of optimized solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-inherently-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMD: Self-supervised 3D Action Representation Learning with Cross-modal Mutual Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmd-self-supervised-3d-action-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we formulate the cross-modal interaction as a bidirectional knowledge distillation problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmd-self-supervised-3d-action-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image augmentation improves few-shot classification performance in plant disease recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-augmentation-improves-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the world population projected to near 10 billion by 2050, minimizing crop damage and guaranteeing food security has never been more important.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-augmentation-improves-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variance Reduction based Experience Replay for Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variance-reduction-based-experience-replay</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For reinforcement learning on complex stochastic systems where many factors dynamically impact the output trajectories, it is desirable to effectively leverage the information from historical samples collected in previous iterations to accelerate policy optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variance-reduction-based-experience-replay</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Relational Causal Models with Cycles through Relational Acyclification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-relational-causal-models-with-cycles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce \textit{relational acyclification}, an operation specifically designed for relational models that enables reasoning about the identifiability of cyclic relational causal models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-relational-causal-models-with-cycles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Truncated Linear Regression with Unknown Noise Variance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-truncated-linear-regression-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide the first computationally and statistically efficient estimators for truncated linear regression when the noise variance is unknown, estimating both the linear model and the variance of the noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-truncated-linear-regression-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pix4Point: Image Pretrained Transformers for 3D Point Cloud Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pix4point-image-pretrained-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of 3D point clouds, the availability of large datasets is a challenge, which exacerbates the issue of training Transformers for 3D tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pix4point-image-pretrained-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Perception Transformer for Temporal Action Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-perception-transformer-for-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, their multi-stage designs cannot generate action boundaries and categories straightforwardly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-perception-transformer-for-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A deep learning approach to predict the number of k-barriers for intrusion detection over a circular region using wireless sensor networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-approach-to-predict-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the crucial applications of WSNs is intrusion detection and surveillance at the border areas and in the defense establishments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-approach-to-predict-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Audio-Language Learning for Music</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-audio-language-learning-for-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore cross-modal learning in an attempt to bridge audio and language in the music domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-audio-language-learning-for-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Series Clustering with an EM algorithm for Mixtures of Linear Gaussian State Space Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-clustering-with-an-em-algorithm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we propose a novel model-based time series clustering method with mixtures of linear Gaussian state space models, which have high flexibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-clustering-with-an-em-algorithm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-driven Predictive Tracking Control based on Koopman Operators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-predictive-tracking-control-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We seek to combine the nonlinear modeling capabilities of a wide class of neural networks with the safety guarantees of model predictive control (MPC) in a rigorous and online computationally tractable framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-predictive-tracking-control-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAXFit: Trust Region Method for Nonlinear Least-Squares Curve Fitting on the GPU</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jaxfit-trust-region-method-for-nonlinear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We implement a trust region method on the GPU for nonlinear least squares curve fitting problems using a new deep learning Python library called JAX.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jaxfit-trust-region-method-for-nonlinear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Autoencoders Enable Efficient Knowledge Distillers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-enable-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, by distilling the knowledge from an MAE pre-trained ViT-L into a ViT-B, our method achieves 84. 0% ImageNet top-1 accuracy, outperforming the baseline of directly distilling a fine-tuned ViT-L by 1. 2%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-enable-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparison of Reinforcement Learning Frameworks for Software Testing Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-of-reinforcement-learning-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we empirically investigate the applications of carefully selected RL algorithms on two important software testing tasks: test case prioritization in the context of Continuous Integration (CI) and game testing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-of-reinforcement-learning-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refine and Represent: Region-to-Object Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refine-and-represent-region-to-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works in self-supervised learning have demonstrated strong performance on scene-level dense prediction tasks by pretraining with object-centric or region-based correspondence objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refine-and-represent-region-to-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity-Sensitive Knowledge Propagation for Cloth-Changing Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identity-sensitive-knowledge-propagation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the resolution degradation issue and mine identity-sensitive cues from human faces, we propose to restore the missing facial details using prior facial knowledge, which is then propagated to a smaller network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identity-sensitive-knowledge-propagation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unbiased Multi-Modality Guidance for Image Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-multi-modality-guidance-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image inpainting is an ill-posed problem to recover missing or damaged image content based on incomplete images with masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-multi-modality-guidance-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Construct 3D Building Wireframes from 3D Line Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-construct-3d-building-wireframes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Line clouds, though under-investigated in the previous work, potentially encode more compact structural information of buildings than point clouds extracted from multi-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-construct-3d-building-wireframes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polarimetric Inverse Rendering for Transparent Shapes Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polarimetric-inverse-rendering-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We build a polarization dataset for multi-view transparent shapes reconstruction to verify our method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polarimetric-inverse-rendering-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning-based approaches for automatic detection of shell nouns and evaluation on WikiText-2</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-approaches-for-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[All discovered shell nouns as well as pre-trained models and code are available on GitHub.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-approaches-for-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Analysis of the Efficacy of Different Sampling Techniques for Imbalanced Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-analysis-of-the-efficacy-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are numerous approaches to dealing with imbalanced data, but the efficacy of such techniques or an experimental comparison among those techniques has not been conducted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-analysis-of-the-efficacy-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSR: Towards Drone Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsr-towards-drone-image-super-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It would enable drones to fly higher covering larger fields of view, while maintaining a high image quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsr-towards-drone-image-super-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Light-weight probing of unsupervised representations for Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/light-weight-probing-of-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised visual representation learning offers the opportunity to leverage large corpora of unlabeled trajectories to form useful visual representations, which can benefit the training of reinforcement learning (RL) algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/light-weight-probing-of-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Dimensionality Reduction and Classification with Convolutional Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-dimensionality-reduction-and-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It turned out that this methodology can also be greatly beneficial in enforcing explainability of deep learning architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-dimensionality-reduction-and-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skeleton Prototype Contrastive Learning with Multi-Level Graph Relation Modeling for Unsupervised Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-prototype-contrastive-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lastly, we propose a skeleton prototype contrastive learning scheme that clusters feature-correlative instances of unlabeled graph representations and contrasts their inherent similarity with representative skeleton features ("skeleton prototypes") to learn discriminative skeleton representations for person re-ID.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-prototype-contrastive-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Multimodal Emotion Recognition using Hybrid Fusion of Speech and Image Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-multimodal-emotion-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A new interpretability technique has been developed to identify the important speech & image features leading to the prediction of particular emotion classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-multimodal-emotion-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Contrastive Learning for Affect Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-contrastive-learning-for-affect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Affect modeling is viewed, traditionally, as the process of mapping measurable affect manifestations from multiple modalities of user input to affect labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-contrastive-learning-for-affect</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ReprGesture entry to the GENEA Challenge 2022</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-reprgesture-entry-to-the-genea-challenge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes the ReprGesture entry to the Generation and Evaluation of Non-verbal Behaviour for Embodied Agents (GENEA) challenge 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-reprgesture-entry-to-the-genea-challenge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Deep Learning Approach Using Masked Image Modeling for Reconstruction of Undersampled K-spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-approach-using-masked-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model was evaluated through L1 loss, gradient normalization, and structural similarity values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-approach-using-masked-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EEG4Students: An Experimental Design for EEG Data Collection and Machine Learning Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eeg4students-an-experimental-design-for-eeg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, during the COVID-19 pandemic, data collection and analysis could be more challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eeg4students-an-experimental-design-for-eeg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secondary Protein Structure Prediction Using Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secondary-protein-structure-prediction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, we test the impact of varying the length of protein sequence we input into the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secondary-protein-structure-prediction-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing Token Uniformity in Transformers via Singular Value Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-token-uniformity-in-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to use the distribution of singular values of outputs of each transformer layer to characterise the phenomenon of token uniformity and empirically illustrate that a less skewed singular value distribution can alleviate the `token uniformity' problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-token-uniformity-in-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symbolic Replay: Scene Graph as Prompt for Continual Learning on VQA Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-replay-scene-graph-as-prompt-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, CL on VQA involves not only the expansion of label sets (new Answer sets).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-replay-scene-graph-as-prompt-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
