<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 21:07:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Temporal Action Localization: Advanced S6 Modeling with Recurrent Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-temporal-action-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal Action Localization (TAL) is a critical task in video analysis, identifying precise start and end times of actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-temporal-action-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Investigation Into the Time and Frequency Response Characteristics of Hopf Resonators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-investigation-into-the-time-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an empirical investigation of software developed by the Science and Music Research Group at the University of Glasgow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-investigation-into-the-time-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPSFormer: A Global Perception and Local Structure Fitting-based Transformer for Point Cloud Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpsformer-a-global-perception-and-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core of GPSFormer is the Global Perception Module (GPM) and the Local Structure Fitting Convolution (LSFConv).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpsformer-a-global-perception-and-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SA-DVAE: Improving Zero-Shot Skeleton-Based Action Recognition by Disentangled Variational Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-dvae-improving-zero-shot-skeleton-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing zero-shot skeleton-based action recognition methods utilize projection networks to learn a shared latent space of skeleton features and semantic embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-dvae-improving-zero-shot-skeleton-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANHALTEN: Cross-Lingual Transfer for German Token-Level Reference-Free Hallucination Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anhalten-cross-lingual-transfer-for-german</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Research on token-level reference-free hallucination detection has predominantly focused on English, primarily due to the scarcity of robust datasets in other languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anhalten-cross-lingual-transfer-for-german</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Language of Infographics: Toward Understanding Conceptual Metaphor Use in Scientific Storytelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-language-of-infographics-toward</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our classification of the visual conceptual mappings within scientific representations is based on the breakdown of visual components in existing scientific infographics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-language-of-infographics-toward</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scikit-fingerprints: easy and efficient computation of molecular fingerprints in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scikit-fingerprints-easy-and-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present \textit{scikit-fingerprints}, a Python package for computation of molecular fingerprints for applications in chemoinformatics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scikit-fingerprints-easy-and-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heart-Mind Harmony: Predicting Stress from Heart Rate</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heart-mind-harmony-predicting-stress-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[in the end, the findings of this research may additionally have broader implications for improving the satisfactory of existence and basic properly-being of individuals via permitting early pressure detection and intervention thru the analysis of heart price statistics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heart-mind-harmony-predicting-stress-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Sight and Sound: Advanced Sound Source Localization Through Audio-Visual Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-sight-and-sound-advanced-sound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we introduce new evaluation metrics to rigorously assess sound source localization methods, focusing on accurately evaluating both localization performance and cross-modal interaction ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-sight-and-sound-advanced-sound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using LLMs to Investigate Correlations of Conversational Follow-up Queries with User Satisfaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-llms-to-investigate-correlations-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From qualitative analysis of 250 conversational turns from an in-lab user evaluation of Naver Cue:, a commercial conversational search engine, we propose a taxonomy of 18 users' follow-up query patterns from conversational search, comprising two major axes: (1) users' motivations behind continuing conversations (N = 7) and (2) actions of follow-up queries (N = 11).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-llms-to-investigate-correlations-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCNv3: Towards Next Generation Deep Cross Network for CTR Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcnv3-towards-next-generation-deep-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep & Cross Network and its derivative models have become an important paradigm in click-through rate (CTR) prediction due to their effective balance between computational cost and performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcnv3-towards-next-generation-deep-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HPix: Generating Vector Maps from Satellite Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hpix-generating-vector-maps-from-satellite</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vector maps find widespread utility across diverse domains due to their capacity to not only store but also represent discrete data boundaries such as building footprints, disaster impact analysis, digitization, urban planning, location points, transport links, and more.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hpix-generating-vector-maps-from-satellite</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TXL-PBC: a freely accessible labeled peripheral blood cell dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/txl-pbc-a-freely-accessible-labeled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we used the YOLOv8n model to train these three datasets, the performance of the TXL-PBC dataset surpass the original two datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/txl-pbc-a-freely-accessible-labeled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmark Agreement Testing Done Right: A Guide for LLM Benchmark Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-agreement-testing-done-right-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the crucial role of BAT for benchmark builders and consumers, there are no standardized procedures for such agreement testing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-agreement-testing-done-right-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fixed and Adaptive Simultaneous Machine Translation Strategies Using Adapters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fixed-and-adaptive-simultaneous-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The wait-$k$ policy offers a solution by starting to translate after consuming $k$ words, where the choice of the number $k$ directly affects the latency and quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fixed-and-adaptive-simultaneous-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlcLaM: Arabic Dialectal Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alclam-arabic-dialectal-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Arabic-specific PLMs are trained predominantly on modern standard Arabic, which compromises their performance on regional dialects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alclam-arabic-dialectal-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating 3D House Wireframes with Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-3d-house-wireframes-with-semantics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new approach for generating 3D house wireframes with semantic enrichment using an autoregressive model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-3d-house-wireframes-with-semantics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Calibration with Energy Based Instance-wise Scaling in the Wild Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-calibration-with-energy-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate robust post-hoc uncertainty calibration methods for DNNs within the context of multi-class classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-calibration-with-energy-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoME: Mixture of Multimodal Experts for Generalist Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mome-mixture-of-multimodal-experts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a mixture of multimodal experts (MoME) to mitigate task interference and obtain a generalist MLLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mome-mixture-of-multimodal-experts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HGL: Hierarchical Geometry Learning for Test-time Adaptation in 3D Point Cloud Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgl-hierarchical-geometry-learning-for-test</link>
      <description><![CDATA[HGL comprises three complementary modules from local, global to temporal learning in a bottom-up manner. Technically, we first construct a local geometry learning module for pseudo-label generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgl-hierarchical-geometry-learning-for-test</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Dependency Framework for Enhancing Discourse Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-dependency-framework-for-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By converting both PDTB and RST annotations for the same texts into dependencies, this study also applies ``dependency distance'' metrics to examine the correlation between RST dependencies and PDTB dependencies in English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-dependency-framework-for-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Case2Code: Learning Inductive Reasoning with Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/case2code-learning-inductive-reasoning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we hope to focus on evaluating and teaching LLMs to conduct inductive reasoning, that is, LLMs are supposed to infer underlying rules by observing examples or sequential transformations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/case2code-learning-inductive-reasoning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Better Angels of Machine Personality: How Personality Relates to LLM Safety</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-better-angels-of-machine-personality-how</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we discover that LLMs' personality traits are closely related to their safety abilities, i. e., toxicity, privacy, and fairness, based on the reliable MBTI-M scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-better-angels-of-machine-personality-how</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging the Mahalanobis Distance to enhance Unsupervised Brain MRI Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-the-mahalanobis-distance-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised Anomaly Detection (UAD) methods rely on healthy data distributions to identify anomalies as outliers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-the-mahalanobis-distance-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoSIGN: Few-Step Guidance of ConSIstency Model to Solve General INverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosign-few-step-guidance-of-consistency-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within comparable NFEs, our method achieves new state-of-the-art in diffusion-based inverse problem solving, showcasing the significant potential of employing prior-based inverse problem solvers for real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosign-few-step-guidance-of-consistency-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Models for Parabolic Partial Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/base-models-for-parabolic-partial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is often necessary to compute the solutions or a function of the solutions to a parametric PDE in multiple scenarios corresponding to different parameters of this PDE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/base-models-for-parabolic-partial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving Adaptive Re-Identification without Image Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-adaptive-re-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Re-Identification systems (Re-ID) are crucial for public safety but face the challenge of having to adapt to environments that differ from their training distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-adaptive-re-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dirac--Bianconi Graph Neural Networks -- Enabling Non-Diffusive Long-Range Graph Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dirac-bianconi-graph-neural-networks-enabling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The geometry of a graph is encoded in dynamical processes on the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dirac-bianconi-graph-neural-networks-enabling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global-Local Similarity for Efficient Fine-Grained Image Recognition with Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-local-similarity-for-efficient-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-grained recognition involves the classification of images from subordinate macro-categories, and it is challenging due to small inter-class differences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-local-similarity-for-efficient-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlimFlow: Training Smaller One-Step Diffusion Models with Rectified Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slimflow-training-smaller-one-step-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rectified flow framework trains one-step generative models using two operations, reflow and distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slimflow-training-smaller-one-step-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ER-FSL: Experience Replay with Feature Subspace Learning for Online Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/er-fsl-experience-replay-with-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing replay-based methods mitigate forgetting by replaying buffered samples from old data and learning current samples of new data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/er-fsl-experience-replay-with-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Context-Based Low-Light Image Enhancement via Neural Implicit Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-context-based-low-light-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current deep learning-based low-light image enhancement methods often struggle with high-resolution images, and fail to meet the practical demands of visual perception across diverse and unseen scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-context-based-low-light-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-level Adaptive Self-Labeling for Novel Class Discovery in Point Cloud Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-level-adaptive-self-labeling-for-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We tackle the novel class discovery in point cloud segmentation, which discovers novel classes based on the semantic knowledge of seen classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-level-adaptive-self-labeling-for-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaLog: Post-Training Quantization for Vision Transformers with Adaptive Logarithm Quantizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adalog-post-training-quantization-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose a novel non-uniform quantizer, dubbed the Adaptive Logarithm AdaLog (AdaLog) quantizer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adalog-post-training-quantization-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ActionSwitch: Class-agnostic Detection of Simultaneous Actions in Streaming Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actionswitch-class-agnostic-detection-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online Temporal Action Localization (On-TAL) is a critical task that aims to instantaneously identify action instances in untrimmed streaming videos as soon as an action concludes -- a major leap from frame-based Online Action Detection (OAD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actionswitch-class-agnostic-detection-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBAD: A Dataset and Benchmark for Retinal Vessels Branching Angle Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rbad-a-dataset-and-benchmark-for-retinal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting retinal image analysis, particularly the geometrical features of branching points, plays an essential role in diagnosing eye diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rbad-a-dataset-and-benchmark-for-retinal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Architecture Design for Efficient Generic Event Boundary Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-architecture-design-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generic event boundary detection (GEBD), inspired by human visual cognitive behaviors of consistently segmenting videos into meaningful temporal chunks, finds utility in various applications such as video editing and.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-architecture-design-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProcTag: Process Tagging for Assessing the Efficacy of Document Instruction Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proctag-process-tagging-for-assessing-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An effective evaluation method for document instruction data is crucial in constructing instruction data with high efficacy, which, in turn, facilitates the training of LLMs and MLLMs for document VQA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proctag-process-tagging-for-assessing-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NavGPT-2: Unleashing Navigational Reasoning Capability for Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navgpt-2-unleashing-navigational-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Capitalizing on the remarkable advancements in Large Language Models (LLMs), there is a burgeoning initiative to harness LLMs for instruction following robotic navigation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navgpt-2-unleashing-navigational-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Individualized Federated Learning for Traffic Prediction with Error Driven Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individualized-federated-learning-for-traffic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-latency traffic prediction is vital for smart city traffic management.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individualized-federated-learning-for-traffic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentPoison: Red-teaming LLM Agents via Poisoning Memory or Knowledge Bases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentpoison-red-teaming-llm-agents-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we form the trigger generation process as a constrained optimization to optimize backdoor triggers by mapping the triggered instances to a unique embedding space, so as to ensure that whenever a user instruction contains the optimized backdoor trigger, the malicious demonstrations are retrieved from the poisoned memory or knowledge base with high probability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentpoison-red-teaming-llm-agents-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeneralAD: Anomaly Detection Across Domains by Attending to Distorted Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalad-anomaly-detection-across-domains-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These features are fed to an attention-based discriminator, which is trained to score every patch in the image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalad-anomaly-detection-across-domains-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E5-V: Universal Embeddings with Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e5-v-universal-embeddings-with-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a single modality training approach for E5-V, where the model is trained exclusively on text pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e5-v-universal-embeddings-with-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VCP-CLIP: A visual context prompting model for zero-shot anomaly segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vcp-clip-a-visual-context-prompting-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this end, we propose a visual context prompting model (VCP-CLIP) for ZSAS task based on CLIP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vcp-clip-a-visual-context-prompting-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SG-NeRF: Neural Surface Reconstruction with Scene Graph Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sg-nerf-neural-surface-reconstruction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this challenge, we present a novel approach that optimizes radiance fields with scene graphs to mitigate the influence of outlier poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sg-nerf-neural-surface-reconstruction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Robust Self-Supervised Learning Across Diverse Downstream Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-robust-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale vision models have become integral in many applications due to their unprecedented performance and versatility across downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-robust-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PersLLM: A Personified Training Approach for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persllm-a-personified-training-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models exhibit aspects of human-level intelligence that catalyze their application as human-like agents in domains such as social simulations, human-machine interactions, and collaborative multi-agent systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persllm-a-personified-training-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EmoFace: Audio-driven Emotional 3D Face Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emoface-audio-driven-emotional-3d-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach can generate facial expressions with multiple emotions, and has the ability to generate random yet natural blinks and eye movements, while maintaining accurate lip synchronization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emoface-audio-driven-emotional-3d-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Wrist Abnormality Detection with YOLO: Analysis of State-of-the-art Single-stage Detection Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-wrist-abnormality-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diagnosing and treating abnormalities in the wrist, specifically distal radius, and ulna fractures, is a crucial concern among children, adolescents, and young adults, with a higher incidence rate during puberty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-wrist-abnormality-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy-Guided Diffusion Sampling for Offline-to-Online Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-guided-diffusion-sampling-for-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combining offline and online reinforcement learning (RL) techniques is indeed crucial for achieving efficient and safe learning where data acquisition is expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-guided-diffusion-sampling-for-offline</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
