<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 21:07:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dense Interspecies Face Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-interspecies-face-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are three main obstacles for interspecies face understanding: (1) lack of animal data compared to human, (2) ambiguous connection between faces of various animals, and (3) extreme shape and style variance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-interspecies-face-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Smoothing: Unsupervised Graph Representation Learning with Edge Heterophily Discriminating</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-smoothing-unsupervised-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Node representations are learned through contrasting the dual-channel encodings obtained from the discriminated homophilic and heterophilic edges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-smoothing-unsupervised-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAEDAY: MAE for few and zero shot AnomalY-Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maeday-mae-for-few-and-zero-shot-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that MAEDAY performs surprisingly well at this task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maeday-mae-for-few-and-zero-shot-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BeLFusion: Latent Diffusion for Behavior-Driven Human Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/belfusion-latent-diffusion-for-behavior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we present BeLFusion, a model that, for the first time, leverages latent diffusion models in HMP to sample from a latent space where behavior is disentangled from pose and motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/belfusion-latent-diffusion-for-behavior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCOOP: Self-Supervised Correspondence and Optimization-Based Scene Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scoop-self-supervised-correspondence-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scene flow estimation is a long-standing problem in computer vision, where the goal is to find the 3D motion of a scene from its consecutive observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scoop-self-supervised-correspondence-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Domain Ensemble Distillation for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-ensemble-distillation-for-domain-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain generalization is the task of learning models that generalize to unseen target domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-ensemble-distillation-for-domain-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Source Skull Reconstruction with MONAI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-skull-reconstruction-with-monai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The primary goal of this paper lies in the investigation of open-sourcing codes and pre-trained deep learning models under the MONAI framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-skull-reconstruction-with-monai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSIED: A Benchmark for Event Detection from Multi-Source Heterogeneous Informal Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musied-a-benchmark-for-event-detection-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a pioneering exploration that expands event detection to the scenarios involving informal and heterogeneous texts, we propose a new large-scale Chinese event detection dataset based on user reviews, text conversations, and phone conversations in a leading e-commerce platform for food service.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musied-a-benchmark-for-event-detection-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning General Audio Representations with Large-Scale Training of Patchout Audio Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-general-audio-representations-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we will show that transformers trained on Audioset can be extremely effective representation extractors for a wide range of downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-general-audio-representations-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FFHQ-UV: Normalized Facial UV-Texture Dataset for 3D Face Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ffhq-uv-normalized-facial-uv-texture-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our pipeline utilizes the recent advances in StyleGAN-based facial image editing approaches to generate multi-view normalized face images from single-image inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ffhq-uv-normalized-facial-uv-texture-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Convolutional Network-based Feature Selection for High-dimensional and Low-sample Size Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-convolutional-network-based-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Feature selection is a powerful dimension reduction technique which selects a subset of relevant features for model construction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-convolutional-network-based-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group Buying Recommendation Model Based on Multi-task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/group-buying-recommendation-model-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose two auxiliary losses corresponding to the two sub-tasks, to refine the representation learning in our model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/group-buying-recommendation-model-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Competency-Aware Neural Machine Translation: Can Machine Translation Know its Own Translation Quality?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/competency-aware-neural-machine-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The lack of competency awareness makes NMT untrustworthy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/competency-aware-neural-machine-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuzzy clustering for the within-season estimation of cotton phenology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fuzzy-clustering-for-the-within-season</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new approach for the within-season phenology estimation for cotton at the field level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fuzzy-clustering-for-the-within-season</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIP: Positional-encoding Image Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pip-positional-encoding-image-prior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Deep Image Prior (DIP), a Convolutional Neural Network (CNN) is fitted to map a latent space to a degraded (e. g. noisy) image but in the process learns to reconstruct the clean image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pip-positional-encoding-image-prior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MorphPool: Efficient Non-linear Pooling &amp; Unpooling in CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphpool-efficient-non-linear-pooling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pooling is essentially an operation from the field of Mathematical Morphology, with max pooling as a limited special case.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphpool-efficient-non-linear-pooling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial-Spectral Transformer for Hyperspectral Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-spectral-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperspectral image (HSI) denoising is a crucial preprocessing procedure for the subsequent HSI applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-spectral-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Positive unlabeled learning with tensor networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/positive-unlabeled-learning-with-tensor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Positive unlabeled learning is a binary classification problem with positive and unlabeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/positive-unlabeled-learning-with-tensor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Stochastic Optimization with Energy-Based Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-stochastic-optimization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decision-focused learning (DFL) was recently proposed for stochastic optimization problems that involve unknown parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-stochastic-optimization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild-Time: A Benchmark of in-the-Wild Distribution Shift over Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wild-time-a-benchmark-of-in-the-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal shifts -- distribution shifts arising from the passage of time -- often occur gradually and have the additional structure of timestamp metadata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wild-time-a-benchmark-of-in-the-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoET: Pose Estimation Transformer for Single-View, Multi-Object 6D Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poet-pose-estimation-transformer-for-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is a challenging task due to object symmetries, clutter and occlusion, but it becomes more challenging when additional information, such as depth and 3D models, is not provided.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poet-pose-estimation-transformer-for-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-Assisted 3D Feature Learning for Semantic Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-assisted-3d-feature-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To guide 3D feature learning toward important geometric attributes and scene context, we explore the help of textual scene descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-assisted-3d-feature-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAD2Render: A Modular Toolkit for GPU-accelerated Photorealistic Synthetic Data Generation for the Manufacturing Industry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cad2render-a-modular-toolkit-for-gpu</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The use of computer vision for product and assembly quality control is becoming ubiquitous in the manufacturing industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cad2render-a-modular-toolkit-for-gpu</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assistive Teaching of Motor Control Tasks to Humans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assistive-teaching-of-motor-control-tasks-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on the problem of assistive teaching of motor control tasks such as parking a car or landing an aircraft.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assistive-teaching-of-motor-control-tasks-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copy-Pasting Coherent Depth Regions Improves Contrastive Learning for Urban-Scene Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copy-pasting-coherent-depth-regions-improves</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For unsupervised semantic segmentation of urban scenes, our method surpasses the previous state-of-the-art baseline by +7. 14% in mIoU on Cityscapes and +6. 65% on KITTI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copy-pasting-coherent-depth-regions-improves</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifying Incorrect Annotations in Multi-Label Classification Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-incorrect-annotations-in-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In multi-label classification, each example in a dataset may be annotated as belonging to one or more classes (or none of the classes).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-incorrect-annotations-in-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSSL: Weighted Self-supervised Learning Framework For Image-inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wssl-weighted-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the performance of our framework and produce more visually appealing images, we also present a novel loss function for image inpainting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wssl-weighted-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Dimensional Causal Discovery: Learning from Inverse Covariance via Independence-based Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-causal-discovery-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed algorithm, called ICID (inverse covariance estimation and {\it independence-based} decomposition), searches for a decomposition of the inverse covariance matrix that preserves its nonzero patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-causal-discovery-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy-Adaptive Estimator Selection for Off-Policy Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-adaptive-estimator-selection-for-off</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although many estimators have been developed, there is no single estimator that dominates the others, because the estimators' accuracy can vary greatly depending on a given OPE task such as the evaluation policy, number of actions, and noise level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-adaptive-estimator-selection-for-off</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DATE: Dual Assignment for End-to-End Fully Convolutional Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/date-dual-assignment-for-end-to-end-fully</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we revisit these two assignment methods and find that bringing one-to-many assignment back to end-to-end fully convolutional detectors helps with model convergence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/date-dual-assignment-for-end-to-end-fully</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Good Practices for Missing Modality Robust Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-good-practices-for-missing-modality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We ask: how can we train a model that is robust to missing modalities?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-good-practices-for-missing-modality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiverse: Multilingual Evidence for Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiverse-multilingual-evidence-for-fake</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose Multiverse -- a new feature based on multilingual evidence that can be used for fake news detection and improve existing approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiverse-multilingual-evidence-for-fake</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Weight Search for Scalable Task Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-weight-search-for-scalable-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Task incremental learning aims to enable a system to maintain its performance on previously learned tasks while learning new tasks, solving the problem of catastrophic forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-weight-search-for-scalable-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More comprehensive facial inversion for more effective expression recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-comprehensive-facial-inversion-for-more</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extensively evaluate ASIT on facial datasets such as FFHQ and CelebA-HQ, showing that our approach achieves state-of-the-art facial inversion performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-comprehensive-facial-inversion-for-more</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-label Few-shot ICD Coding as Autoregressive Generation with Prompt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-label-few-shot-icd-coding-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This task is challenging due to the high-dimensional space of multi-label assignment (155, 000+ ICD code candidates) and the long-tail challenge - Many ICD codes are infrequently assigned yet infrequent ICD codes are important clinically.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-label-few-shot-icd-coding-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Practical Control of Singular Values of Convolutional Layers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-practical-control-of-singular-values</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the improved properties of modern CNNs with our method and analyze its impact on the model performance, calibration, and adversarial robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-practical-control-of-singular-values</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint segmentation and discontinuity-preserving deformable registration: Application to cardiac cine-MR images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-segmentation-and-discontinuity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In such scenarios, enforcing smooth, globally continuous deformation fields leads to incorrect/implausible registration results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-segmentation-and-discontinuity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Short-Term Predictability of Returns in Order Book Markets: a Deep Learning Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-short-term-predictability-of-returns-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of the deep learning models is strongly dependent on the choice of order book representation, and in this respect, the volume representation appears to have multiple practical advantages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-short-term-predictability-of-returns-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Importance of Image Encoding in Automated Chest X-Ray Report Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-importance-of-image-encoding-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chest X-ray is one of the most popular medical imaging modalities due to its accessibility and effectiveness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-importance-of-image-encoding-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyTAIL: Interactive and Incremental Learning of NLP Models with Human in the Loop for Online Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytail-interactive-and-incremental-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For natural language processing (NLP) tasks that utilize a collection of features based on lexicons and rules, it is important to adapt these features to the changing data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytail-interactive-and-incremental-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross Aggregation Transformer for Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-aggregation-transformer-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core of our CAT is the Rectangle-Window Self-Attention (Rwin-SA), which utilizes horizontal and vertical rectangle window attention in different heads parallelly to expand the attention area and aggregate the features cross different windows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-aggregation-transformer-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Partial Labels from Semi-supervised Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-partial-labels-from-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the impressive success of deep Semi-Supervised (SS) learning, we transform the PL learning problem into the SS learning problem, and propose a novel PL learning method, namely Partial Label learning with Semi-supervised Perspective (PLSP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-partial-labels-from-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reduction Algorithms for Persistence Diagrams of Networks: CoralTDA and PrunIT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduction-algorithms-for-persistence-diagrams</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we introduce a pruning algorithm for graphs to compute their persistence diagrams by removing the dominated vertices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduction-algorithms-for-persistence-diagrams</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GA-cal software for the automatic calibration of soil constitutive laws: a tutorial and a user manual</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ga-cal-software-for-the-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The calibration of an advanced constitutive law for soil is a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ga-cal-software-for-the-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised vision-language pretraining for Medical visual question answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-vision-language-pretraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image visual question answering (VQA) is a task to answer clinical questions, given a radiographic image, which is a challenging problem that requires a model to integrate both vision and language information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-vision-language-pretraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable and Safe Reinforcement Learning for Autonomous Air Mobility</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-and-safe-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although DRL has achieved important advancements in this field, the existing works pay little attention to the explainability and safety issues related to DRL controllers, particularly the safety under adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-and-safe-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go Beyond Point Pairs: A General and Accurate Sim2Real Object Pose Voting Method with Efficient Online Synthetic Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/go-beyond-point-pairs-a-general-and-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel method for sim-to-real pose estimation, which is effective on both instance-level and category-level settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/go-beyond-point-pairs-a-general-and-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immersive Neural Graphics Primitives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/immersive-neural-graphics-primitives</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present and evaluate a NeRF-based framework that is capable of rendering scenes in immersive VR allowing users to freely move their heads to explore complex real-world scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/immersive-neural-graphics-primitives</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Physics-Based Object Pose Tracking during Non-Prehensile Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-physics-based-object-pose-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At any given time during the manipulation of the object, we assume access to the robot joint controls and an image from a camera looking at the scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-physics-based-object-pose-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Shot General Object Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-general-object-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, our proposed OneLoc algorithm efficiently finds the object center and bounding box size by a special voting scheme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-general-object-localization</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
