<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:08:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Ultra-High-Definition Image Deraining: A Benchmark and An Efficient Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-ultra-high-definition-image-deraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on the task of UHD image deraining, and contribute the first large-scale UHD image deraining dataset, 4K-Rain13k, that contains 13, 000 image pairs at 4K resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-ultra-high-definition-image-deraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content-Style Decoupling for Unsupervised Makeup Transfer without Generating Pseudo Ground Truth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/content-style-decoupling-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This assumption allows CSD-MT to decouple the content and makeup style information in each face image through the frequency decomposition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/content-style-decoupling-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survival of the Fittest Representation: A Case Study with Modular Addition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survival-of-the-fittest-representation-a-case</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To investigate this Survival of the Fittest hypothesis, we conduct a case study on neural networks performing modular addition, and find that these networks' multiple circular representations at different Fourier frequencies undergo such competitive dynamics, with only a few circles surviving at the end.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survival-of-the-fittest-representation-a-case</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoformalizing Euclidean Geometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoformalizing-euclidean-geometry</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One challenge in Euclidean geometry is that informal proofs rely on diagrams, leaving gaps in texts that are hard to formalize.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoformalizing-euclidean-geometry</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformers Can Do Arithmetic with the Right Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-can-do-arithmetic-with-the-right</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The poor performance of transformers on arithmetic tasks seems to stem in large part from their inability to keep track of the exact position of each digit inside of a large span of digits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-can-do-arithmetic-with-the-right</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMPlug: A Plug-in Method for Solving Inverse Problems with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dmplug-a-plug-in-method-for-solving-inverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, such interleaving methods struggle to produce final results that look like natural objects of interest (i. e., manifold feasibility) and fit the measurement (i. e., measurement feasibility), especially for nonlinear IPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dmplug-a-plug-in-method-for-solving-inverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Linear Probing then Fine-tuning Language Models from NTK Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-linear-probing-then-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments with a Transformer-based model on natural language processing tasks across multiple benchmarks confirm our theoretical analysis and demonstrate the effectiveness of LP-FT in fine-tuning language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-linear-probing-then-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoCV: Empowering Reasoning with Automated Process Labeling via Confidence Variation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autocv-empowering-reasoning-with-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We experimentally validate that the confidence variations learned by the verification model trained on the final answer correctness can effectively identify errors in the reasoning steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autocv-empowering-reasoning-with-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Performance of Continuous-Time Dynamic Link Prediction Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-performance-of-continuous-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, a single metric is not sufficient to fully capture the differences between DLP algorithms, and is prone to overly optimistic performance evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-performance-of-continuous-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVMS-RCN: A Dual-Domain Unfolding CT Reconstruction with Multi-sparse-view and Multi-scale Refinement-correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvms-rcn-a-dual-domain-unfolding-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel dual-domain deep unfolding unified framework that offers a great deal of flexibility for multi-sparse-view CT reconstruction with different sampling views through a single model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvms-rcn-a-dual-domain-unfolding-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PatchScaler: An Efficient Patch-independent Diffusion Model for Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchscaler-an-efficient-patch-independent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models significantly improve the quality of super-resolved images with their impressive content generation capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchscaler-an-efficient-patch-independent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling Rate, Distortion, and Realism: Towards a Single Comprehensive Neural Image Compression Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-rate-distortion-and-realism</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A critical obstacle of these generative NIC methods is that each model is optimized for a single bit rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-rate-distortion-and-realism</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GTA: Generative Trajectory Augmentation with Guidance for Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gta-generative-trajectory-augmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that GTA, as a general data augmentation strategy, enhances the performance of widely used offline RL algorithms in both dense and sparse reward settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gta-generative-trajectory-augmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Data-aware and Parameter-aware Robustness for Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-data-aware-and-parameter-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of Continual Learning (CL) task is to continuously learn multiple new tasks sequentially while achieving a balance between the plasticity and stability of new and old knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-data-aware-and-parameter-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Transformers in Solving POMDPs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-transformers-in-solving-pomdps</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sequential decision-making algorithms such as reinforcement learning (RL) in real-world scenarios inevitably face environments with partial observability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-transformers-in-solving-pomdps</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RLAIF-V: Aligning MLLMs through Open-Source AI Feedback for Super GPT-4V Trustworthiness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlaif-v-aligning-mllms-through-open-source-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While traditional methods rely on labor-intensive and time-consuming manual labeling, recent approaches employing models as automatic labelers have shown promising results without human intervention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlaif-v-aligning-mllms-through-open-source-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EF-Calib: Spatiotemporal Calibration of Event- and Frame-Based Cameras Using Continuous-Time Trajectories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ef-calib-spatiotemporal-calibration-of-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging the asynchronous nature of events, a derivable piece-wise B-spline to represent camera pose continuously is introduced, enabling calibration for intrinsic parameters, extrinsic parameters, and time offset, with analytical Jacobians provided.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ef-calib-spatiotemporal-calibration-of-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing the significance of longitudinal data in Alzheimer's Disease forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-significance-of-longitudinal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we employ a transformer encoder model to characterize the significance of longitudinal patient data for forecasting the progression of Alzheimer's Disease (AD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-significance-of-longitudinal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match, Compare, or Select? An Investigation of Large Language Models for Entity Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/match-compare-or-select-an-investigation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our findings, we further design a compositional entity matching (ComEM) framework that leverages the composition of multiple strategies and LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/match-compare-or-select-an-investigation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phase Transitions in the Output Distribution of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phase-transitions-in-the-output-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analogous phenomena have recently been observed in large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phase-transitions-in-the-output-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaussian Embedding of Temporal Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-embedding-of-temporal-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representing the nodes of continuous-time temporal graphs in a low-dimensional latent space has wide-ranging applications, from prediction to visualization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-embedding-of-temporal-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Retrospective of the Tutorial on Opportunities and Challenges of Online Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-retrospective-of-the-tutorial-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is done with the use of online learning or continuous ML technologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-retrospective-of-the-tutorial-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HDC: Hierarchical Semantic Decoding with Counting Assistance for Generalized Referring Expression Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hdc-hierarchical-semantic-decoding-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The newly proposed Generalized Referring Expression Segmentation (GRES) amplifies the formulation of classic RES by involving multiple/non-target scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hdc-hierarchical-semantic-decoding-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Optimization with Human Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-optimization-with-human-feedback</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply our APOHF algorithm to various tasks, including optimizing user instructions, prompt optimization for text-to-image generative models, and response optimization with human feedback (i. e., further refining the response using a variant of our APOHF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-optimization-with-human-feedback</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KSW: Khmer Stop Word based Dictionary for Keyword Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ksw-khmer-stop-word-based-dictionary-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces KSW, a Khmer-specific approach to keyword extraction that leverages a specialized stop word dictionary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ksw-khmer-stop-word-based-dictionary-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VoCoT: Unleashing Visually Grounded Multi-Step Reasoning in Large Multi-Modal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vocot-unleashing-visually-grounded-multi-step</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While large multi-modal models (LMMs) have exhibited impressive capabilities across diverse tasks, their effectiveness in handling complex tasks has been limited by the prevailing single-step reasoning paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vocot-unleashing-visually-grounded-multi-step</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCSim: A Realistic Spike Cameras Simulator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scsim-a-realistic-spike-cameras-simulator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale synthetic datasets have significantly accelerated the development of these cameras, particularly in reconstruction and optical flow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scsim-a-realistic-spike-cameras-simulator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look at Time Steps is Worthy of Triple Speed-Up for Diffusion Model Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-time-steps-is-worthy-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training diffusion models is always a computation-intensive task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-time-steps-is-worthy-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PP-SAM: Perturbed Prompts for Robust Adaptation of Segment Anything Model for Polyp Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pp-sam-perturbed-prompts-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we utilize variable perturbed bounding box prompts (BBP) to enrich the learning context and enhance the model's robustness to BBP perturbations during inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pp-sam-perturbed-prompts-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Large Language Models to Set up a Knowledge Retrieval Indexer via Self-Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-large-language-models-to-set-up-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) offers a cost-effective approach to injecting real-time knowledge into large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-large-language-models-to-set-up-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiOOD: Scaling Out-of-Distribution Detection for Multiple Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiood-scaling-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on MultiOOD demonstrate that training with A2D and NP-Mix improves existing OOD detection algorithms by a large margin.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiood-scaling-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoSLight: Co-optimizing Collaborator Selection and Decision-making to Enhance Traffic Signal Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coslight-co-optimizing-collaborator-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Effective multi-intersection collaboration is pivotal for reinforcement-learning-based traffic signal control to alleviate congestion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coslight-co-optimizing-collaborator-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Ensembling for Constrained Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-ensembling-for-constrained-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we further investigate these themes by considering a setting in which we wish to ensemble models for multidimensional output predictions that are in turn used for downstream optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-ensembling-for-constrained-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superpixelwise Low-rank Approximation based Partial Label Learning for Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superpixelwise-low-rank-approximation-based-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel superpixelwise low-rank approximation (LRA)-based partial label learning method, namely SLAP, which is the first to take into account partial label learning in HSI classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superpixelwise-low-rank-approximation-based-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Layer Pruning Through Similarity Metric Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-layer-pruning-through-similarity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, layer pruning often hurts the network predictive ability (i. e., accuracy) at high compression rates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-layer-pruning-through-similarity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Language Model-based Translator for  English-Vietnamese Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advanced-language-model-based-translator-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a transformative approach to English-Vietnamese translation, leveraging the cutting edge capabilities of the Gemma-7B-IT (Gemma Team et al. 2024) model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advanced-language-model-based-translator-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OED: Towards One-stage End-to-End Dynamic Scene Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oed-towards-one-stage-end-to-end-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic Scene Graph Generation (DSGG) focuses on identifying visual relationships within the spatial-temporal domain of videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oed-towards-one-stage-end-to-end-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPN: Decoupling Partition and Navigation for Neural Solvers of Min-max Vehicle Routing Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpn-decoupling-partition-and-navigation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The min-max vehicle routing problem (min-max VRP) traverses all given customers by assigning several routes and aims to minimize the length of the longest route.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpn-decoupling-partition-and-navigation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixture of Modality Knowledge Experts for Robust Multi-modal Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-modality-knowledge-experts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal knowledge graph completion (MMKGC) aims to automatically discover new knowledge triples in the given multi-modal knowledge graphs (MMKGs), which is achieved by collaborative modeling the structural information concealed in massive triples and the multi-modal features of the entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-modality-knowledge-experts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reason3D: Searching and Reasoning 3D Segmentation via Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reason3d-searching-and-reasoning-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This foundational estimation facilitates a detailed, coarse-to-fine segmentation strategy that significantly enhances the precision of object identification and segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reason3d-searching-and-reasoning-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReflectionCoder: Learning from Reflection Sequence for Enhanced One-off Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reflectioncoder-learning-from-reflection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by this, we present ReflectionCoder, a novel approach that effectively leverages reflection sequences constructed by integrating compiler feedback to improve one-off code generation performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reflectioncoder-learning-from-reflection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoRA: Enhancing Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning with Dynamic Rank Distribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dora-enhancing-parameter-efficient-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning large-scale pre-trained models is inherently a resource-intensive task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dora-enhancing-parameter-efficient-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking and Improving Bird's Eye View Perception Robustness in Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-and-improving-bird-s-eye-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we present RoboBEV, an extensive benchmark suite designed to evaluate the resilience of BEV algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-and-improving-bird-s-eye-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vista: A Generalizable Driving World Model with High Fidelity and Versatile Controllability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vista-a-generalizable-driving-world-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present Vista, a generalizable driving world model with high fidelity and versatile controllability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vista-a-generalizable-driving-world-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardness-Aware Scene Synthesis for Semi-Supervised 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardness-aware-scene-synthesis-for-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While conventional methods focus on generating pseudo-labels for unlabeled samples as supplements for training, the structural nature of 3D point cloud data facilitates the composition of objects and backgrounds to synthesize realistic scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardness-aware-scene-synthesis-for-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think Before You Act: A Two-Stage Framework for Mitigating Gender Bias Towards Vision-Language Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/think-before-you-act-a-two-stage-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During answer inference, GAMA integrates the image, generated narrative, and a task-specific question prompt to infer answers for different vision-language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/think-before-you-act-a-two-stage-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Various Lengths, Constant Speed: Efficient Language Modeling with Lightning Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/various-lengths-constant-speed-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This eliminates the need for cumsum in the linear attention calculation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/various-lengths-constant-speed-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balancing User Preferences by Social Networks: A Condition-Guided Social Recommendation Model for Mitigating Popularity Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-user-preferences-by-social-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More specifically, CGSoRec first includes a Condition-Guided Social Denoising Model (CSD) to remove redundant social relations in the social network for capturing users' social preferences with items more precisely.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-user-preferences-by-social-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectral-Refiner: Fine-Tuning of Accurate Spatiotemporal Neural Operator for Turbulent Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-refiner-fine-tuning-of-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new Spatiotemporal Fourier Neural Operator (SFNO) that learns maps between Bochner spaces, and a new learning framework to address these issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-refiner-fine-tuning-of-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GaussianFormer: Scene as Gaussians for Vision-Based 3D Semantic Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussianformer-scene-as-gaussians-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose an object-centric representation to describe 3D scenes with sparse 3D semantic Gaussians where each Gaussian represents a flexible region of interest and its semantic features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussianformer-scene-as-gaussians-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
