<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 21:07:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>GPU-accelerated SIFT-aided source identification of stabilized videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpu-accelerated-sift-aided-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video stabilization is an in-camera processing commonly applied by modern acquisition devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpu-accelerated-sift-aided-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimal Neural Atlas: Parameterizing Complex Surfaces with Minimal Charts and Distortion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimal-neural-atlas-parameterizing-complex</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, our representation can learn a minimal atlas of 3 charts with distortion-minimal parameterization for surfaces of arbitrary topology, including closed and open surfaces with arbitrary connected components.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimal-neural-atlas-parameterizing-complex</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content-Aware Differential Privacy with Conditional Invertible Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/content-aware-differential-privacy-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Manipulation of the latent space leads to a modified image while preserving important details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/content-aware-differential-privacy-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiFeat: Supercharge GNN Training via Graph Feature Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bifeat-supercharge-gnn-training-via-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We identify the main accuracy impact factors in graph feature quantization and theoretically prove that BiFeat training converges to a network where the loss is within $\epsilon$ of the optimal loss of uncompressed network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bifeat-supercharge-gnn-training-via-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Comment Inconsistency Detection with BERT and Longformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/code-comment-inconsistency-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comments, or natural language descriptions of source code, are standard practice among software developers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/code-comment-inconsistency-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egret Swarm Optimization Algorithm: An Evolutionary Computation Approach for Model Free Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egret-swarm-optimization-algorithm-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A novel meta-heuristic algorithm, Egret Swarm Optimization Algorithm (ESOA), is proposed in this paper, which is inspired by two egret species' (Great Egret and Snowy Egret) hunting behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egret-swarm-optimization-algorithm-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive UCB: Provably Efficient Contrastive Self-Supervised Learning in Online Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-ucb-provably-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, under the online setting, we propose novel upper confidence bound (UCB)-type algorithms that incorporate such a contrastive loss with online RL algorithms for MDPs or MGs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-ucb-provably-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Identification in X-ray Diffraction Data using Machine Learning Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artifact-identification-in-x-ray-diffraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Depending on the material's form, one may observe different characteristics other than the typical Debye Scherrer rings for a realistic sample and its environments, such as textures or preferred orientations and single crystal diffraction spots in the 2D XRD image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artifact-identification-in-x-ray-diffraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLEAN: Generative Latent Bank for Image Super-Resolution and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glean-generative-latent-bank-for-image-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While most existing perceptual-oriented approaches attempt to generate realistic outputs through learning with adversarial loss, our method, Generative LatEnt bANk (GLEAN), goes beyond existing practices by directly leveraging rich and diverse priors encapsulated in a pre-trained GAN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glean-generative-latent-bank-for-image-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Prototype via Placeholder for Zero-shot Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-prototype-via-placeholder-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we combine seen classes to hallucinate new classes which play as placeholders of the unseen classes in the visual and semantic space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-prototype-via-placeholder-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WISE: Whitebox Image Stylization by Example-based Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wise-whitebox-image-stylization-by-example</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image-based artistic rendering can synthesize a variety of expressive styles using algorithmic image filtering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wise-whitebox-image-stylization-by-example</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Shuffling Video Benefit Temporal Bias Problem: A Novel Training Framework for Temporal Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-shuffling-video-benefit-temporal-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our framework introduces two auxiliary tasks, cross-modal matching and temporal order discrimination, to promote the grounding model training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-shuffling-video-benefit-temporal-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centrality and Consistency: Two-Stage Clean Samples Identification for Learning with Instance-Dependent Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centrality-and-consistency-two-stage-clean</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a two-stage clean samples identification method to address the aforementioned challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centrality-and-consistency-two-stage-clean</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Domain-agnostic Depth Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-domain-agnostic-depth-completion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method leverages a data driven prior in the form of a single image depth prediction network trained on large-scale datasets, the output of which is used as an input to our model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-domain-agnostic-depth-completion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models Can Teach Themselves to Program Better</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-can-teach-themselves-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we show how generating synthetic programming puzzles and solutions, verified for correctness by a Python interpreter, can be used to improve performance in solving test puzzles from P3, a public benchmark set of Python Programming Puzzles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-can-teach-themselves-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A One-Shot Reparameterization Method for Reducing the Loss of Tile Pruning on DNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-one-shot-reparameterization-method-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a one-shot reparameterization method, called TileTrans, to reduce the loss of tile pruning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-one-shot-reparameterization-method-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GTrans: Grouping and Fusing Transformer Layers for Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gtrans-grouping-and-fusing-transformer-layers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer structure, stacked by a sequence of encoder and decoder network layers, achieves significant development in neural machine translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gtrans-grouping-and-fusing-transformer-layers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal SuperCon: Classifier for Drivers of Deforestation in Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-supercon-classifier-for-drivers-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a contrastive learning architecture, called Multimodal SuperCon, for classifying drivers of deforestation in Indonesia using satellite images obtained from Landsat 8.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-supercon-classifier-for-drivers-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restoring Vision in Adverse Weather Conditions with Patch-Based Denoising Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/restoring-vision-in-adverse-weather</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image restoration under adverse weather conditions has been of significant interest for various computer vision applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/restoring-vision-in-adverse-weather</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning idempotent representation for subspace clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-idempotent-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The critical point for the successes of spectral-type subspace clustering algorithms is to seek reconstruction coefficient matrices which can faithfully reveal the subspace structures of data sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-idempotent-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Density-Distance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-density-distance-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, it is difficult to achieve high localization performance by only density fields-based methods such as Neural Radiance Field (NeRF) since they do not provide density gradient in most empty regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-density-distance-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Design of Physical Objects using Modular Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-design-of-physical-objects-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we formulate general approach to an arbitrary generative design problem and propose novel framework called GEFEST (Generative Evolution For Encoded STructure) on its basis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-design-of-physical-objects-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reference-Guided Texture and Structure Inference for Image Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reference-guided-texture-and-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing learning-based image inpainting methods are still in challenge when facing complex semantic environments and diverse hole patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reference-guided-texture-and-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Deformable 3D Caricatures with Learned Shape Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-deformable-3d-caricatures-with-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve the goal, we propose an MLP-based framework for building a deformable surface model, which takes a latent code and produces a 3D surface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-deformable-3d-caricatures-with-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleLight: HDR Panorama Generation for Lighting Estimation and Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylelight-hdr-panorama-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, we propose a coupled dual-StyleGAN panorama synthesis network (StyleLight) that integrates LDR and HDR panorama synthesis into a unified framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylelight-hdr-panorama-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Specific Wav2vec 2.0 Fine-tuning For The SE&amp;R 2022 Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-specific-wav2vec-2-0-fine-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents our efforts to build a robust ASR model for the shared task Automatic Speech Recognition for spontaneous and prepared speech & Speech Emotion Recognition in Portuguese (SE&R 2022).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-specific-wav2vec-2-0-fine-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Hypergraph Transformer for Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-hypergraph-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the distilled global context, a cross-view generative self-supervised learning component is proposed for data augmentation over the user-item interaction graph, so as to enhance the robustness of recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-hypergraph-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Aligned Matching for Enhanced DETR Convergence and Multi-Scale Feature Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aligned-matching-for-enhanced-detr</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recently proposed DEtection TRansformer (DETR) has established a fully end-to-end paradigm for object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aligned-matching-for-enhanced-detr</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rewriting Geometric Rules of a GAN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rewriting-geometric-rules-of-a-gan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method allows a user to create a model that synthesizes endless objects with defined geometric changes, enabling the creation of a new generative model without the burden of curating a large-scale dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rewriting-geometric-rules-of-a-gan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Limited Annotations: A Survey on Deep Semi-Supervised Learning for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-limited-annotations-a-survey-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image segmentation is a fundamental and critical step in many image-guided clinical approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-limited-annotations-a-survey-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dive into Machine Learning Algorithms for Influenza Virus Host Prediction with Hemagglutinin Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dive-into-machine-learning-algorithms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Influenza viruses mutate rapidly and can pose a threat to public health, especially to those in vulnerable groups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dive-into-machine-learning-algorithms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequence to sequence pretraining for a less-resourced Slovenian language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequence-to-sequence-pretraining-for-a-less</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large pretrained language models have recently conquered the area of natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequence-to-sequence-pretraining-for-a-less</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Training of Language Models to Fill in the Middle</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-training-of-language-models-to-fill</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we run a series of ablations on key hyperparameters, such as the data transformation frequency, the structure of the transformation, and the method of selecting the infill span.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-training-of-language-models-to-fill</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety-Enhanced Autonomous Driving Using Interpretable Sensor Fusion Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-enhanced-autonomous-driving-using-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale deployment of autonomous vehicles has been continually delayed due to safety concerns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-enhanced-autonomous-driving-using-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Recognition by Request</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-recognition-by-request</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel protocol of annotation and evaluation for visual recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-recognition-by-request</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EEG2Mel: Reconstructing Sound from Brain Responses to Music</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eeg2mel-reconstructing-sound-from-brain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Information retrieval from brain responses to auditory and visual stimuli has shown success through classification of song names and image classes presented to participants while recording EEG signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eeg2mel-reconstructing-sound-from-brain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans disagree with the IoU for measuring object detector localization error</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humans-disagree-with-the-iou-for-measuring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work is the first to evaluate IoU with humans and makes it clear that relying on IoU scores alone to evaluate localization errors might not be sufficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humans-disagree-with-the-iou-for-measuring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the Output Structure of Sparse Matrix Multiplication with Sampled Compression Ratio</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-output-structure-of-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose a reference design of the existing sampling-based method with optimized computing overheads to demonstrate the better accuracy of the proposed method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-output-structure-of-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Syntactic Modelling Structures in Biomedical Ontologies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-syntactic-modelling-structures-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the large-scale uptake of semantic technologies in the biomedical domain, little is known about common modelling practices in published ontologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-syntactic-modelling-structures-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Step Deductive Reasoning Over Natural Language: An Empirical Study on Out-of-Distribution Generalisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-step-deductive-reasoning-over-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our model, reasoning is performed using an iterative memory neural network based on RNN with a gate attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-step-deductive-reasoning-over-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A general framework for multi-step ahead adaptive conformal heteroscedastic time series forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-framework-for-multi-step-ahead</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The exponential growth of machine learning (ML) has prompted a great deal of interest in quantifying the uncertainty of each prediction for a user-defined level of confidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-framework-for-multi-step-ahead</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utterance-by-utterance overlap-aware neural diarization with Graph-PIT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utterance-by-utterance-overlap-aware-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we argue that such an approach involving the segmentation has several issues; for example, it inevitably faces a dilemma that larger segment sizes increase both the context available for enhancing the performance and the number of speakers for the local EEND module to handle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utterance-by-utterance-overlap-aware-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning-Based Acoustic Mosquito Detection in Noisy Conditions Using Trainable Kernels and Augmentations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-acoustic-mosquito</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we demonstrate a unique recipe to enhance the effectiveness of audio machine learning approaches by fusing pre-processing techniques into a deep learning model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-acoustic-mosquito</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HelixFold-Single: MSA-free Protein Structure Prediction by Using Protein Language Model as an Alternative</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helixfold-single-msa-free-protein-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed method, HelixFold-Single, first pre-trains a large-scale protein language model (PLM) with thousands of millions of primary sequences utilizing the self-supervised learning paradigm, which will be used as an alternative to MSAs and templates for learning the co-evolution information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helixfold-single-msa-free-protein-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Performance of Robust Control through Event-Triggered Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-performance-of-robust-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in practice, many systems also exhibit uncertainty in the form of changes over time, e. g., due to weight shifts or wear and tear, leading to decreased performance or instability of the learning-based controller.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-performance-of-robust-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MonteBoxFinder: Detecting and Filtering Primitives to Fit a Noisy Point Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monteboxfinder-detecting-and-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present MonteBoxFinder, a method that, given a noisy input point cloud, fits cuboids to the input scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monteboxfinder-detecting-and-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HorNet: Efficient High-Order Spatial Interactions with Recursive Gated Convolutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hornet-efficient-high-order-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show that the key ingredients behind the vision Transformers, namely input-adaptive, long-range and high-order spatial interactions, can also be efficiently implemented with a convolution-based framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hornet-efficient-high-order-spatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mining Cross-Person Cues for Body-Part Interactiveness Learning in HOI Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-cross-person-cues-for-body-part</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though significant progress has been made, interactiveness learning remains a challenging problem in HOI detection: existing methods usually generate redundant negative H-O pair proposals and fail to effectively extract interactive pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-cross-person-cues-for-body-part</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supplementing Recurrent Neural Network Wave Functions with Symmetry and Annealing to Improve Accuracy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supplementing-recurrent-neural-network-wave</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use symmetry and annealing to obtain accurate estimates of ground state energies of the two-dimensional (2D) Heisenberg model, on the square lattice and on the triangular lattice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supplementing-recurrent-neural-network-wave</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Recommender System for Equitable Public Art Curation and Installation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-recommender-system-for-equitable-public-art</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a cost matrix by drawing on Schelling's model of segregation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-recommender-system-for-equitable-public-art</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
