<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 21:06:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Semantic-Aware Knowledge Guidance for Low-Light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-semantic-aware-knowledge-guidance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel semantic-aware knowledge-guided framework (SKF) that can assist a low-light enhancement model in learning rich and diverse priors encapsulated in a semantic segmentation model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-semantic-aware-knowledge-guidance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimpLex: a lexical text simplification architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplex-a-lexical-text-simplification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, the main contributions of this paper are: (1) We propose a new Word Embedding and Transformer based algorithm for text simplification; (2) We design \textsc{SimpLex} -- a modular novel text simplification system -- that can provide a baseline for further research; and (3) We perform an in-depth analysis of our solution and compare our results with two state-of-the-art models, i. e., LightLS [19] and NTS-w2v [44].]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplex-a-lexical-text-simplification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance-aware Dynamic Prompt Tuning for Pre-trained Point Cloud Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-aware-dynamic-prompt-tuning-for-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose an Instance-aware Dynamic Prompt Tuning (IDPT) for point cloud pre-trained models, which utilizes a prompt module to perceive the semantic prior features of each instance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-aware-dynamic-prompt-tuning-for-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DINOv2: Learning Robust Visual Features without Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dinov2-learning-robust-visual-features</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent breakthroughs in natural language processing for model pretraining on large quantities of data have opened the way for similar foundation models in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dinov2-learning-robust-visual-features</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectral Transfer Guided Active Domain Adaptation For Thermal Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-transfer-guided-active-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an active domain adaptation method in order to examine the efficiency of combining the visible spectrum and thermal imagery modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-transfer-guided-active-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weighted Siamese Network to Predict the Time to Onset of Alzheimer's Disease from MRI Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-siamese-network-to-predict-the-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We train a siamese network model to predict the time to onset of AD based on MRI brain images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-siamese-network-to-predict-the-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitstream-Corrupted JPEG Images are Restorable: Two-stage Compensation and Alignment Framework for Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitstream-corrupted-jpeg-images-are</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study a real-world JPEG image restoration problem with bit errors on the encrypted bitstream.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitstream-corrupted-jpeg-images-are</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn What Is Possible, Then Choose What Is Best: Disentangling One-To-Many Relations in Language Through Text-based Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-what-is-possible-then-choose-what-is</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models pre-trained on large self-supervised corpora, followed by task-specific fine-tuning has become the dominant paradigm in NLP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-what-is-possible-then-choose-what-is</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoSplice: A Text-prompt Manipulated Image Dataset for Media Forensics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autosplice-a-text-prompt-manipulated-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this, we propose a new approach that leverages the DALL-E2 language-image model to automatically generate and splice masked regions guided by a text prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autosplice-a-text-prompt-manipulated-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Byte Sequence is Worth an Image: CNN for File Fragment Classification Using Bit Shift and n-Gram Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-byte-sequence-is-worth-an-image-cnn-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[File fragment classification (FFC) on small chunks of memory is essential in memory forensics and Internet security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-byte-sequence-is-worth-an-image-cnn-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signal Novelty Detection as an Intrinsic Reward for Robotics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/signal-novelty-detection-as-an-intrinsic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In advanced robot control, reinforcement learning is a common technique used to transform sensor data into signals for actuators, based on feedback from the robot’s environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/signal-novelty-detection-as-an-intrinsic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L1BSR: Exploiting Detector Overlap for Self-Supervised Single-Image Super-Resolution of Sentinel-2 L1B Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l1bsr-exploiting-detector-overlap-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately the lack of reliable high-resolution (HR) ground truth limits the application of deep learning methods to this task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l1bsr-exploiting-detector-overlap-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Learning based Depth Estimation from Monocular Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-based-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Depth Estimation has wide reaching applications in the field of Computer vision such as target tracking, augmented reality, and self-driving cars.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-based-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HuaTuo: Tuning LLaMA Model with Chinese Medical Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/huatuo-tuning-llama-model-with-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs), such as the LLaMA model, have demonstrated their effectiveness in various general-domain natural language processing (NLP) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/huatuo-tuning-llama-model-with-chinese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WYTIWYR: A User Intent-Aware Framework with Multi-modal Inputs for Visualization Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wytiwyr-a-user-intent-aware-framework-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieving charts from a large corpus is a fundamental task that can benefit numerous applications such as visualization recommendations. The retrieved results are expected to conform to both explicit visual attributes (e. g., chart type, colormap) and implicit user intents (e. g., design style, context information) that vary upon application scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wytiwyr-a-user-intent-aware-framework-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cultural-aware Machine Learning based Analysis of COVID-19 Vaccine Hesitancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cultural-aware-machine-learning-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings show that Hispanic and African American are most likely impacted by cultural characteristics such as religions and ethnic affiliation, whereas the vaccine trust and approval influence the Asian communities the most.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cultural-aware-machine-learning-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performative Prediction with Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performative-prediction-with-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we instead assume that the data distribution is Lipschitz continuous with respect to the model's predictions, a more natural assumption for performative systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performative-prediction-with-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Aware Null Space Networks for Data-Consistent Image Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-null-space-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This can be achieved either by iterative network architectures or by a subsequent projection of the network reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-null-space-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BCE-Net: Reliable Building Footprints Change Extraction based on Historical Map and Up-to-Date Images using Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bce-net-reliable-building-footprints-change</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This contrastive learning strategy allowed us to inject the semantics of buildings into a pipeline for the detection of changes, which is achieved by increasing the distinguishability of features of buildings from those of non-buildings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bce-net-reliable-building-footprints-change</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Study on Generative Models for High Resolution Solar Observation Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-on-generative-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Starting from StyleGAN-based methods, we uncover severe deficits of this model family in handling fine-scale details of solar images when training on high resolution samples, contrary to training on natural face images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-on-generative-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Real-Time Image Annotation Using Marginalized Coupled Dictionary Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-real-time-image-annotation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We have employed a marginalized loss function in our method to leverage a simple and effective method of prototype updating.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-real-time-image-annotation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal C4: An Open, Billion-scale Corpus of Images Interleaved With Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-c4-an-open-billion-scale-corpus-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We release Multimodal C4 (mmc4), an augmentation of the popular text-only c4 corpus with images interleaved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-c4-an-open-billion-scale-corpus-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TUM-FAÇADE: Reviewing and enriching point cloud benchmarks for façade segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tum-facade-reviewing-and-enriching-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Point clouds are widely regarded as one of the best dataset types for urban mapping purposes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tum-facade-reviewing-and-enriching-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEA: A Scalable Entity Alignment System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sea-a-scalable-entity-alignment-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enhance the usability of GNN-based EA models in real-world applications, we present SEA, a scalable entity alignment system that enables to (i) train large-scale GNNs for EA, (ii) speed up the normalization and the evaluation process, and (iii) report clear results for users to estimate different models and parameter settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sea-a-scalable-entity-alignment-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARFormer: Transformer-based Multi-Task Network for Pedestrian Attribute Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parformer-transformer-based-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pedestrian attribute recognition (PAR) has received increasing attention because of its wide application in video surveillance and pedestrian analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parformer-transformer-based-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FairRec: Fairness Testing for Deep Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairrec-fairness-testing-for-deep-recommender</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the testing report, by adopting a simple re-ranking mitigation strategy on these identified disadvantaged groups, we show that the fairness of DRSs can be significantly improved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairrec-fairness-testing-for-deep-recommender</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCFace: Synthetic Face Generation with Dual Condition Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcface-synthetic-face-generation-with-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our novel Patch-wise style extractor and Time-step dependent ID loss enables DCFace to consistently produce face images of the same subject under different styles with precise control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcface-synthetic-face-generation-with-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the State of the Art in Legal QA Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-state-of-the-art-in-legal-qa</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At this time, there is a lack of surveys that discuss legal question answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-state-of-the-art-in-legal-qa</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STU-Net: Scalable and Transferable Medical Image Segmentation Models Empowered by Large-Scale Supervised Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stu-net-scalable-and-transferable-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the state-of-the-art models for medical image segmentation are still small-scale, with their parameters only in the tens of millions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stu-net-scalable-and-transferable-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGIEval: A Human-Centric Benchmark for Evaluating Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agieval-a-human-centric-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Impressively, GPT-4 surpasses average human performance on SAT, LSAT, and math competitions, attaining a 95% accuracy rate on the SAT Math test and a 92. 5% accuracy on the English test of the Chinese national college entrance exam.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agieval-a-human-centric-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDT: Dual-branch Deformable Transformer for Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddt-dual-branch-deformable-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer is beneficial for image denoising tasks since it can model long-range dependencies to overcome the limitations presented by inductive convolutional biases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddt-dual-branch-deformable-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segment Everything Everywhere All at Once</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-everything-everywhere-all-at-once</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the development of prompt-based universal interfaces for LLMs, this paper presents SEEM, a promptable, interactive model for Segmenting Everything Everywhere all at once in an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-everything-everywhere-all-at-once</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canonical and Noncanonical Hamiltonian Operator Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/canonical-and-noncanonical-hamiltonian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A method for the nonintrusive and structure-preserving model reduction of canonical and noncanonical Hamiltonian systems is presented.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/canonical-and-noncanonical-hamiltonian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priors for symbolic regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/priors-for-symbolic-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we develop methods to incorporate detailed prior information on both functions and their parameters into SR. Our prior on the structure of a function is based on a $n$-gram language model, which is sensitive to the arrangement of operators relative to one another in addition to the frequency of occurrence of each operator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/priors-for-symbolic-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural State-Space Models: Empirical Evaluation of Uncertainty Quantification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-state-space-models-empirical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Effective quantification of uncertainty is an essential and still missing step towards a greater adoption of deep-learning approaches in different applications, including mission-critical ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-state-space-models-empirical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards hypergraph cognitive networks as feature-rich models of knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-hypergraph-cognitive-networks-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic networks provide a useful tool to understand how related concepts are retrieved from memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-hypergraph-cognitive-networks-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VISION DIFFMASK: Faithful Interpretation of Vision Transformers with Differentiable Patch Masking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-diffmask-faithful-interpretation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The lack of interpretability of the Vision Transformer may hinder its use in critical real-world applications despite its effectiveness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-diffmask-faithful-interpretation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging triplet loss for unsupervised action segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-triplet-loss-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel fully unsupervised framework that learns action representations suitable for the action segmentation task from the single input video itself, without requiring any training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-triplet-loss-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Robustness of Interpretability Methods through Explanation Invariance and Equivariance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-robustness-of-interpretability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through this rigorous formalism, we derive (1) two metrics to measure the robustness of any interpretability method with respect to the model symmetry group; (2) theoretical robustness guarantees for some popular interpretability methods and (3) a systematic approach to increase the invariance of any interpretability method with respect to a symmetry group.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-robustness-of-interpretability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LasUIE: Unifying Information Extraction with Latent Adaptive Structure-aware Generative Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lasuie-unifying-information-extraction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Universally modeling all typical information extraction tasks (UIE) with one generative language model (GLM) has revealed great potential by the latest study, where various IE predictions are unified into a linearized hierarchical expression under a GLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lasuie-unifying-information-extraction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Study of Biologically Plausible Neural Network: The Role and Interactions of Brain-Inspired Mechanisms in Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-study-of-biologically-plausible-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Humans excel at continually acquiring, consolidating, and retaining information from an ever-changing environment, whereas artificial neural networks (ANNs) exhibit catastrophic forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-study-of-biologically-plausible-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Sensing Change Detection With Transformers Trained from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remote-sensing-change-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current transformer-based change detection (CD) approaches either employ a pre-trained model trained on large-scale image classification ImageNet dataset or rely on first pre-training on another CD dataset and then fine-tuning on the target benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remote-sensing-change-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DGNN-Booster: A Generic FPGA Accelerator Framework For Dynamic Graph Neural Network Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgnn-booster-a-generic-fpga-accelerator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experiment results demonstrate that DGNN-Booster can achieve a speedup of up to 5. 6x compared to the CPU baseline (6226R), 8. 4x compared to the GPU baseline (A6000) and 2. 1x compared to the FPGA baseline without applying optimizations proposed in this paper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgnn-booster-a-generic-fpga-accelerator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Level generation for rhythm VR games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/level-generation-for-rhythm-vr-games</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The assignment is broken down into three parts: determining the timing of the beats (action placement), determining where in space the runes connected with the chosen beats should be placed (action selection) and web-application creation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/level-generation-for-rhythm-vr-games</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoSDA: Continual Source-Free Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosda-continual-source-free-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, SFDA has gained popularity due to the need to protect the data privacy of the source domain, but it suffers from catastrophic forgetting on the source domain due to the lack of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosda-continual-source-free-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soundini: Sound-Guided Diffusion for Natural Video Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soundini-sound-guided-diffusion-for-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method for adding sound-guided visual effects to specific regions of videos with a zero-shot setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soundini-sound-guided-diffusion-for-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shall We Pretrain Autoregressive Language Models with Retrieval? A Comprehensive Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shall-we-pretrain-autoregressive-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To answer it, we perform a comprehensive study on a scalable pre-trained retrieval-augmented LM (i. e., RETRO) compared with standard GPT and retrieval-augmented GPT incorporated at fine-tuning or inference stages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shall-we-pretrain-autoregressive-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diagnostic Benchmark and Iterative Inpainting for Layout-Guided Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnostic-benchmark-and-iterative-inpainting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose LayoutBench, a diagnostic benchmark for layout-guided image generation that examines four categories of spatial control skills: number, position, size, and shape.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnostic-benchmark-and-iterative-inpainting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PGTask: Introducing the Task of Profile Generation from Dialogues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgtask-introducing-the-task-of-profile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent approaches have attempted to personalize dialogue systems by leveraging profile information into models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgtask-introducing-the-task-of-profile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoboBEV: Towards Robust Bird's Eye View Perception under Corruptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robobev-towards-robust-bird-s-eye-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments further demonstrate that pre-training and depth-free BEV transformation has the potential to enhance out-of-distribution robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robobev-towards-robust-bird-s-eye-view</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
