<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 21:06:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Nerfbusters: Removing Ghostly Artifacts from Casually Captured NeRFs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerfbusters-removing-ghostly-artifacts-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Casually captured Neural Radiance Fields (NeRFs) suffer from artifacts such as floaters or flawed geometry when rendered outside the camera trajectory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerfbusters-removing-ghostly-artifacts-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CKBP v2: An Expert-Annotated Evaluation Set for Commonsense Knowledge Base Population</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ckbp-v2-an-expert-annotated-evaluation-set</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Populating Commonsense Knowledge Bases (CSKB) is an important yet hard task in NLP, as it tackles knowledge from external sources with unseen events and entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ckbp-v2-an-expert-annotated-evaluation-set</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety Assessment of Chinese Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-assessment-of-chinese-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further promote the safe deployment of LLMs, we develop a Chinese LLM safety assessment benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-assessment-of-chinese-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Manipulating Tokenization Aid Cross-Lingual Transfer? A Study on POS Tagging for Non-Standardized Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-manipulating-tokenization-aid-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This can for instance be observed when finetuning PLMs on one language and evaluating them on data in a closely related language variety with no standardized orthography.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-manipulating-tokenization-aid-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Program with Natural Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-program-with-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we further propose the Learning to Program (LP) method to ask LLMs themselves to learn natural language programs from the training dataset of complex tasks and then use the learned program to guide inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-program-with-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Cellular Coverage from Real Network Configurations using GNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-cellular-coverage-from-real-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cellular coverage quality estimation has been a critical task for self-organized networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-cellular-coverage-from-real-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PED-ANOVA: Efficiently Quantifying Hyperparameter Importance in Arbitrary Subspaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ped-anova-efficiently-quantifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent rise in popularity of Hyperparameter Optimization (HPO) for deep learning has highlighted the role that good hyperparameter (HP) space design can play in training strong models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ped-anova-efficiently-quantifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Bottleneck Concepts in Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-bottleneck-concepts-in-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using some image classification tasks as our testbed, we demonstrate BotCL's potential to rebuild neural networks for better interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-bottleneck-concepts-in-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A geometry-aware deep network for depth estimation in monocular endoscopy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-geometry-aware-deep-network-for-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we introduce a gradient loss to penalize edge fluctuations ambiguous around stepped edge structures and a normal loss to explicitly express the sensitivity to frequently small structures, and propose a geometric consistency loss to spreads the spatial information across the sample grids to constrain the global geometric anatomy structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-geometry-aware-deep-network-for-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards replacing precipitation ensemble predictions systems using machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-replacing-precipitation-ensemble</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the feasibility of generating realistic precipitation ensemble members on unseen higher resolutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-replacing-precipitation-ensemble</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omni Aggregation Networks for Lightweight Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omni-aggregation-networks-for-lightweight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While lightweight ViT framework has made tremendous progress in image super-resolution, its uni-dimensional self-attention modeling, as well as homogeneous aggregation scheme, limit its effective receptive field (ERF) to include more comprehensive interactions from both spatial and channel dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omni-aggregation-networks-for-lightweight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image-text Retrieval via preserving main Semantics of Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-text-retrieval-via-preserving-main</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, this paper presents a semantic optimization approach, implemented as a Visual Semantic Loss (VSL), to assist the model in focusing on an image's main content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-text-retrieval-via-preserving-main</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Implicit Neural Representations in Low-Level Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-implicit-neural-representations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implicit Neural Representation (INR) has been emerging in computer vision in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-implicit-neural-representations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature-compatible Progressive Learning for Video Copy Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-compatible-progressive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video Copy Detection (VCD) has been developed to identify instances of unauthorized or duplicated video content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-compatible-progressive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Censoring chemical data to mitigate dual use risk</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/censoring-chemical-data-to-mitigate-dual-use</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dual use of machine learning applications, where models can be used for both beneficial and malicious purposes, presents a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/censoring-chemical-data-to-mitigate-dual-use</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noisy Universal Domain Adaptation via Divergence Optimization for Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisy-universal-domain-adaptation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To transfer the knowledge learned from a labeled source domain to an unlabeled target domain, many studies have worked on universal domain adaptation (UniDA), where there is no constraint on the label sets of the source domain and target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisy-universal-domain-adaptation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Open Intent Classification with K-center Contrastive Learning and Adjustable Decision Boundary</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-open-intent-classification-with-k</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce novel K-center contrastive learning and adjustable decision boundary learning (CLAB) to improve the effectiveness of open intent classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-open-intent-classification-with-k</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt-Learning for Cross-Lingual Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-learning-for-cross-lingual-relation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on WMT17-EnZh XRE also show the effectiveness of our Prompt-XRE against other competitive baselines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-learning-for-cross-lingual-relation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-NER: Named Entity Recognition via Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-ner-named-entity-recognition-via-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GPT-NER bridges the gap by transforming the sequence labeling task to a generation task that can be easily adapted by LLMs e. g., the task of finding location entities in the input text "Columbus is a city" is transformed to generate the text sequence "@@Columbus## is a city", where special tokens @@## marks the entity to extract.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-ner-named-entity-recognition-via-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road Genome: A Topology Reasoning Benchmark for Scene Understanding in Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/road-genome-a-topology-reasoning-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By introducing Road Genome (OpenLane-V2), we intend to shift the community's attention and take a step further beyond perception - to the task of topology reasoning for scene structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/road-genome-a-topology-reasoning-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperTuner: A Cross-Layer Multi-Objective Hyperparameter Auto-Tuning Framework for Data Analytic Services</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypertuner-a-cross-layer-multi-objective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, experiments with different training datasets, different optimization objectives and different machine learning platforms verify that HyperTuner can well adapt to various data analytic service scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypertuner-a-cross-layer-multi-objective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularizing Second-Order Influences for Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-second-order-influences-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual learning aims to learn on non-stationary data streams without catastrophically forgetting previous knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-second-order-influences-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Neural Networks with Knapsack Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/securing-neural-networks-with-knapsack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The second way to accelerate Secure Inference is based on cutting the number of bit comparisons required for a secure ReLU operation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/securing-neural-networks-with-knapsack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTIRE 2023 Challenge on Light Field Image Super-Resolution: Dataset, Methods and Results</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntire-2023-challenge-on-light-field-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we summarize the first NTIRE challenge on light field (LF) image super-resolution (SR), which aims at super-resolving LF images under the standard bicubic degradation with a magnification factor of 4.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntire-2023-challenge-on-light-field-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Paracrawl for Document-level Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-paracrawl-for-document-level-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that document-level NMT models trained with only parallel paragraphs from Paracrawl can be used to translate real documents from TED, News and Europarl, outperforming sentence-level NMT models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-paracrawl-for-document-level-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StoManager1: Automated, High-throughput Tool to Measure Leaf Stomata Using Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stomanager1-automated-high-throughput-tool-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stomatal characteristics of leaves are crucial for plant physiological performance and ecological functioning in regulating global water and carbon cycling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stomanager1-automated-high-throughput-tool-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architectures of Topological Deep Learning: A Survey on Topological Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/architectures-of-topological-deep-learning-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The natural world is full of complex systems characterized by intricate relations between their components: from social interactions between individuals in a social network to electrostatic interactions between atoms in a protein.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/architectures-of-topological-deep-learning-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix: Democratizing ChatGPT across Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phoenix-democratizing-chatgpt-across</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents our efforts to democratize ChatGPT across language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phoenix-democratizing-chatgpt-across</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angle based dynamic learning rate for gradient descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/angle-based-dynamic-learning-rate-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our work, we propose a novel yet simple approach to obtain an adaptive learning rate for gradient-based descent methods on classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/angle-based-dynamic-learning-rate-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Temporal Modeling with Learnable Alignment for Video Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-temporal-modeling-with-learnable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While modeling temporal information within straight through tube is widely adopted in literature, we find that simple frame alignment already provides enough essence without temporal attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-temporal-modeling-with-learnable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Dynamic Bayesian Networks for Predicting Acute Kidney Injury Before Onset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-dynamic-bayesian-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Ranking Approaches for Unknown Structures (RAUS), an automated framework to systematically inform variable ordering and learn networks end-to-end.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-dynamic-bayesian-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Deep Reinforcement Learning Scheduling via Weight Anchoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-deep-reinforcement-learning-scheduling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Questions remain on the robustness of data-driven learning methods when crossing the gap from simulation to reality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-deep-reinforcement-learning-scheduling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA3: Efficient Label-Aware AutoAugment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/la3-efficient-label-aware-autoaugment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated augmentation is an emerging and effective technique to search for data augmentation policies to improve generalizability of deep neural network training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/la3-efficient-label-aware-autoaugment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Tuning: A Little Help to Make Masked Autoencoders Forget</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-tuning-a-little-help-to-make</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study how to combine the efficiency and scalability of MIM with the ability of ID to perform downstream classification in the absence of large amounts of labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-tuning-a-little-help-to-make</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certified Adversarial Robustness Within Multiple Perturbation Bounds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certified-adversarial-robustness-within</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further propose a novel \textit{training noise distribution} along with a \textit{regularized training scheme} to improve the certification within both $\ell_1$ and $\ell_2$ perturbation norms simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certified-adversarial-robustness-within</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Diffusion for Multi-Modal Face Generation and Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-diffusion-for-multi-modal-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Collaborative Diffusion, where pre-trained uni-modal diffusion models collaborate to achieve multi-modal face generation and editing without re-training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-diffusion-for-multi-modal-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer-Based Visual Segmentation: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-visual-segmentation-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, transformers, a type of neural network based on self-attention originally designed for natural language processing, have considerably surpassed previous convolutional or recurrent approaches in various vision processing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-visual-segmentation-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolving Constrained Reinforcement Learning Policy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolving-constrained-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evolutionary algorithms have been used to evolve a population of actors to generate diverse experiences for training reinforcement learning agents, which helps to tackle the temporal credit assignment problem and improves the exploration efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolving-constrained-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rank-Based Learning and Local Model Based Evolutionary Algorithm for High-Dimensional Expensive Multi-Objective Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rank-based-learning-and-local-model-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, a novel Classifier-assisted rank-based learning and Local Model based multi-objective Evolutionary Algorithm (CLMEA) is proposed for high-dimensional expensive multi-objective optimization problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rank-based-learning-and-local-model-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon: Plug-and-Play Compositional Reasoning with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chameleon-plug-and-play-compositional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have achieved remarkable progress in various natural language processing tasks with emergent abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chameleon-plug-and-play-compositional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the Nature of 3D Generalization in Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-nature-of-3d-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern deep learning architectures for object recognition generalize well to novel views, but the mechanisms are not well understood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-nature-of-3d-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LipsFormer: Introducing Lipschitz Continuity to Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lipsformer-introducing-lipschitz-continuity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to previous practical tricks that address training instability by learning rate warmup, layer normalization, attention formulation, and weight initialization, we show that Lipschitz continuity is a more essential property to ensure training stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lipsformer-introducing-lipschitz-continuity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pointerformer: Deep Reinforced Multi-Pointer Transformer for the Traveling Salesman Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointerformer-deep-reinforced-multi-pointer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traveling Salesman Problem (TSP), as a classic routing optimization problem originally arising in the domain of transportation and logistics, has become a critical task in broader domains, such as manufacturing and biology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointerformer-deep-reinforced-multi-pointer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rehabilitation Exercise Repetition Segmentation and Counting using Skeletal Body Joints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rehabilitation-exercise-repetition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel approach for segmenting and counting the repetitions of rehabilitation exercises performed by patients, based on their skeletal body joints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rehabilitation-exercise-repetition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Representative Trajectories of Dynamical Systems via Domain-Adaptive Imitation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representative-trajectories-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain-adaptive trajectory imitation is a skill that some predators learn for survival, by mapping dynamic information from one domain (their speed and steering direction) to a different domain (current position of the moving prey).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representative-trajectories-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Resource Scheduling with High Priority Users using Deep Deterministic Policy Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-resource-scheduling-with-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advances in mobile communication capabilities open the door for closer integration of pre-hospital and in-hospital care processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-resource-scheduling-with-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive-Hint Prompting Improves Reasoning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/https-arxiv-org-abs-2304-09797</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of Large Language Models (LLMs) in reasoning tasks depends heavily on prompt design, with Chain-of-Thought (CoT) and self-consistency being critical methods that enhance this ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/https-arxiv-org-abs-2304-09797</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A robust and interpretable deep learning framework for multi-modal registration via keypoints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-robust-and-interpretable-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our core insight which addresses these shortcomings is that corresponding keypoints between images can be used to obtain the optimal transformation via a differentiable closed-form expression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-robust-and-interpretable-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Face of Populism: Examining Differences in Facial Emotional Expressions of Political Leaders Using Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-face-of-populism-examining-differences-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online media has revolutionized the way political information is disseminated and consumed on a global scale, and this shift has compelled political figures to adopt new strategies of capturing and retaining voter attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-face-of-populism-examining-differences-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMT: All-Pairs Multi-Field Transforms for Efficient Frame Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amt-all-pairs-multi-field-transforms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is based on two essential designs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amt-all-pairs-multi-field-transforms-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
