<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 21:06:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Combining deep learning on order books with reinforcement learning for profitable trading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-deep-learning-on-order-books-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-frequency trading is prevalent, where automated decisions must be made quickly to take advantage of price imbalances and patterns in price action that forecast near-future movements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-deep-learning-on-order-books-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Named Entity Recognition without Catastrophic Forgetting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-named-entity-recognition-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This issue is intensified in CNER due to the consolidation of old entity types from previous steps into the non-entity type at each step, leading to what is known as the semantic shift problem of the non-entity type.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-named-entity-recognition-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Word-Level Auto-Completion in Computer-Aided Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-word-level-auto-completion-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Word-Level Auto-Completion (WLAC) plays a crucial role in Computer-Assisted Translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-word-level-auto-completion-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeMask: Synthetic Images with Dense Annotations Make Stronger Segmentation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freemask-synthetic-images-with-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we investigate the role of synthetic images by joint training with real images, or pre-training for real images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freemask-synthetic-images-with-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We are Who We Cite: Bridges of Influence Between Natural Language Processing and Other Academic Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/we-are-who-we-cite-bridges-of-influence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyzed ~77k NLP papers, ~3. 1m citations from NLP papers to other papers, and ~1. 8m citations from other papers to NLP papers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/we-are-who-we-cite-bridges-of-influence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALCUNA: Large Language Models Meet New Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alcuna-large-language-models-meet-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid development of NLP, large-scale language models (LLMs) excel in various tasks across multiple domains now.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alcuna-large-language-models-meet-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Regression Markets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-regression-markets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning tasks are vulnerable to the quality of data used as input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-regression-markets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air-Decoding: Attribute Distribution Reconstruction for Decoding-Time Controllable Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/air-decoding-attribute-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then we design a novel attribute distribution reconstruction method to balance the obtained distributions and use the reconstructed distributions to guide language models for generation, effectively avoiding the issue of Attribute Collapse.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/air-decoding-attribute-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Don't Get Too Technical with Me': A Discourse Structure-Based Framework for Science Journalism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-get-too-technical-with-me-a-discourse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Science journalism refers to the task of reporting technical findings of a scientific paper as a less technical news article to the general public audience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-get-too-technical-with-me-a-discourse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Heterogeneous Graph Learning via Random Projection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-heterogeneous-graph-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve low information loss, we introduce a Relation-wise Neighbor Collection component with an Even-odd Propagation Scheme, which aims to collect information from neighbors in a finer-grained way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-heterogeneous-graph-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adam through a Second-Order Lens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adam-through-a-second-order-lens</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Research into optimisation for deep learning is characterised by a tension between the computational efficiency of first-order, gradient-based methods (such as SGD and Adam) and the theoretical efficiency of second-order, curvature-based methods (such as quasi-Newton methods and K-FAC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adam-through-a-second-order-lens</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Study on Knowledge Graph Embeddings and Graph Neural Networks for Web Of Things</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-study-on-knowledge-graph-embeddings-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph data structures are widely used to store relational information between several entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-study-on-knowledge-graph-embeddings-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-in-the-loop: Leveraging Large Language Model for Thematic Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-in-the-loop-leveraging-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thematic analysis (TA) has been widely used for analyzing qualitative data in many disciplines and fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-in-the-loop-leveraging-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S3Eval: A Synthetic, Scalable, Systematic Evaluation Suite for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s3eval-a-synthetic-scalable-systematic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of Large Language Models (LLMs) has led to great strides in model capabilities like reasoning and long-context understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s3eval-a-synthetic-scalable-systematic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transparency at the Source: Evaluating and Interpreting Language Models With Access to the True Distribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transparency-at-the-source-evaluating-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With access to the underlying true source, our results show striking differences and outcomes in learning dynamics between different classes of words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transparency-at-the-source-evaluating-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affective and Dynamic Beam Search for Story Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affective-and-dynamic-beam-search-for-story</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Storytelling's captivating potential makes it a fascinating research area, with implications for entertainment, education, therapy, and cognitive studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affective-and-dynamic-beam-search-for-story</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrisisMatch: Semi-Supervised Few-Shot Learning for Fine-Grained Disaster Tweet Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crisismatch-semi-supervised-few-shot-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The shared real-time information about natural disasters on social media platforms like Twitter and Facebook plays a critical role in informing volunteers, emergency managers, and response organizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crisismatch-semi-supervised-few-shot-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paraphrase Types for Generation and Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paraphrase-types-for-generation-and-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current approaches in paraphrase generation and detection heavily rely on a single general similarity score, ignoring the intricate linguistic properties of language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paraphrase-types-for-generation-and-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning of Large Language Models with Parameter-Efficient Prompt Tuning and Adaptive Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-of-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a Parameter-efficient prompt Tuning approach with Adaptive Optimization, i. e., FedPepTAO, to enable efficient and effective FL of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-of-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Language Models Fall in Love: Animacy Processing in Transformer Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-language-models-fall-in-love-animacy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we also show that even when presented with stories about atypically animate entities, such as a peanut in love, LMs adapt: they treat these entities as animate, though they do not adapt as well as humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-language-models-fall-in-love-animacy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fidelity-Enriched Contrastive Search: Reconciling the Faithfulness-Diversity Trade-Off in Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fidelity-enriched-contrastive-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we address the hallucination problem commonly found in natural language generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fidelity-enriched-contrastive-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can ChatGPT Perform Reasoning Using the IRAC Method in Analyzing Legal Scenarios Like a Lawyer?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-chatgpt-perform-reasoning-using-the-irac</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Each scenario in the corpus is annotated with a complete IRAC analysis in a semi-structured format so that both machines and legal professionals are able to interpret and understand the annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-chatgpt-perform-reasoning-using-the-irac</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta- (out-of-context) learning in neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-out-of-context-learning-in-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Brown et al. (2020) famously introduced the phenomenon of in-context learning in large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-out-of-context-learning-in-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linking Surface Facts to Large-Scale Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linking-surface-facts-to-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open Information Extraction (OIE) methods extract facts from natural language text in the form of ("subject"; "relation"; "object") triples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linking-surface-facts-to-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-autoregressive Streaming Transformer for Simultaneous Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-autoregressive-streaming-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Simultaneous machine translation (SiMT) models are trained to strike a balance between latency and translation quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-autoregressive-streaming-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Converting Depth Images and Point Clouds for Feature-based Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/converting-depth-images-and-point-clouds-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to Bearing Angle images, our method yields brighter, higher-contrast images with more visible contours and more details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/converting-depth-images-and-point-clouds-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond VaR and CVaR: Topological Risk Measures in Derivative Markets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-var-and-cvar-topological-risk-measures</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel approach to financial risk assessment by incorporating topological data analysis (TDA), specifically cohomology groups, into the evaluation of derivatives portfolios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-var-and-cvar-topological-risk-measures</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characterizing how 'distributional' NLP corpora distance metrics are</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-how-distributional-nlp-corpora</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We quantify this quality by constructing a Known-Similarity Corpora set from two paraphrase corpora and calculating the distance between paired corpora from it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-how-distributional-nlp-corpora</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Detection of Image-Scaling Attacks in Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-detection-of-image-scaling-attacks-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, this preprocessing step is vulnerable to so-called image-scaling attacks where an attacker makes unnoticeable changes to an image so that it becomes a new image after scaling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-detection-of-image-scaling-attacks-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The continued usefulness of vocabulary tests for evaluating large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-continued-usefulness-of-vocabulary-tests</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that their Test of English as a Foreign Language (TOEFL) test remains informative for contemporary major language models, since none of the models was perfect and made errors on divergent items.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-continued-usefulness-of-vocabulary-tests</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penalty Decoding: Well Suppress the Self-Reinforcement Effect in Open-Ended Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/penalty-decoding-well-suppress-the-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the self-reinforcement effect in text generation and the effectiveness of a repetition penalty to mitigate it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/penalty-decoding-well-suppress-the-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Frame Mechanism For Efficient Conformer Based End-to-end Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/key-frame-mechanism-for-efficient-conformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Following the initial encoder, we introduce an intermediate CTC loss function to compute the label frame, enabling us to extract the key frames and blank frames for KFSA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/key-frame-mechanism-for-efficient-conformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing Step-by-Step Reasoning against Lexical Negation: A Case Study on Syllogism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-step-by-step-reasoning-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) take advantage of step-by-step reasoning instructions, e. g., chain-of-thought (CoT) prompting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-step-by-step-reasoning-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tree of Clarifications: Answering Ambiguous Questions with Retrieval-Augmented Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-of-clarifications-answering-ambiguous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To cope with the challenge, we propose a novel framework, Tree of Clarifications (ToC): It recursively constructs a tree of disambiguations for the AQ -- via few-shot prompting leveraging external knowledge -- and uses it to generate a long-form answer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-of-clarifications-answering-ambiguous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Conceptualization in Bottleneck Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-conceptualization-in-bottleneck</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concept Bottleneck Models (CBMs) assume that training examples (e. g., x-ray images) are annotated with high-level concepts (e. g., types of abnormalities), and perform classification by first predicting the concepts, followed by predicting the label relying on these concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-conceptualization-in-bottleneck</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoboDepth: Robust Out-of-Distribution Depth Estimation under Corruptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robodepth-robust-out-of-distribution-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Depth estimation from monocular images is pivotal for real-world visual perception systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robodepth-robust-out-of-distribution-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero123++: a Single Image to Consistent Multi-view Diffusion Base Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero123-a-single-image-to-consistent-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We report Zero123++, an image-conditioned diffusion model for generating 3D-consistent multi-view images from a single input view.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero123-a-single-image-to-consistent-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FD-Align: Feature Discrimination Alignment for Fine-tuning Pre-Trained Models in Few-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fd-align-feature-discrimination-alignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the limited availability of data, existing few-shot learning methods trained from scratch fail to achieve satisfactory performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fd-align-feature-discrimination-alignment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Seq2Seq Grammatical Error Correction via Decoding Interventions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-seq2seq-grammatical-error</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a unified decoding intervention framework that employs an external critic to assess the appropriateness of the token to be generated incrementally, and then dynamically influence the choice of the next token.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-seq2seq-grammatical-error</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handling Data Heterogeneity via Architectural Design for Federated Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handling-data-heterogeneity-via-architectural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings emphasize the importance of architectural design for computer vision tasks in practical scenarios, effectively narrowing the performance gap between federated and centralized learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handling-data-heterogeneity-via-architectural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeleQnA: A Benchmark Dataset to Assess Large Language Models Telecommunications Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teleqna-a-benchmark-dataset-to-assess-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Afterwards, using the provided dataset, an evaluation is conducted to assess the capabilities of LLMs, including GPT-3. 5 and GPT-4.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teleqna-a-benchmark-dataset-to-assess-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINC: A Neurosymbolic Approach for Logical Reasoning by Combining Language Models with First-Order Logic Provers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linc-a-neurosymbolic-approach-for-logical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Logical reasoning, i. e., deductively inferring the truth value of a conclusion from a set of premises, is an important task for artificial intelligence with wide potential impacts on science, mathematics, and society.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linc-a-neurosymbolic-approach-for-logical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESVAE: An Efficient Spiking Variational Autoencoder with Reparameterizable Poisson Spiking Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/esvae-an-efficient-spiking-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an efficient spiking variational autoencoder (ESVAE) that constructs an interpretable latent space distribution and design a reparameterizable spiking sampling method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/esvae-an-efficient-spiking-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novel-View Acoustic Synthesis from 3D Reconstructed Rooms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-view-acoustic-synthesis-from-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given audio recordings from 2-4 microphones and the 3D geometry and material of a scene containing multiple unknown sound sources, we estimate the sound anywhere in the scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-view-acoustic-synthesis-from-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEsignBench: Exploring and Benchmarking DALL-E 3 for Imagining Visual Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designbench-exploring-and-benchmarking-dall-e</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For DEsignBench benchmarking, we perform human evaluations on generated images in DEsignBench gallery, against the criteria of image-text alignment, visual aesthetic, and design creativity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designbench-exploring-and-benchmarking-dall-e</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical Deep Dispersed Watermarking with Synchronization and Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-deep-dispersed-watermarking-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared with state-of-the-art approaches, our blind watermarking can achieve better performance: averagely improve the bit accuracy by 5. 28\% and 5. 93\% against single and combined attacks, respectively, and show less file size increment and better visual quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-deep-dispersed-watermarking-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-Med3D</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-med3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These issues can hardly be addressed by fine-tuning SAM on medical data because the original 2D structure of SAM neglects 3D spatial information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-med3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E4S: Fine-grained Face Swapping via Editing With Regional GAN Inversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e4s-fine-grained-face-swapping-via-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this disentanglement, face swapping can be simplified as style and mask swapping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e4s-fine-grained-face-swapping-via-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpEL: Structured Prediction for Entity Linking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spel-structured-prediction-for-entity-linking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entity linking is a prominent thread of research focused on structured data creation by linking spans of text to an ontology or knowledge source.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spel-structured-prediction-for-entity-linking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards LLM-driven Dialogue State Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-llm-driven-dialogue-state-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we conduct an initial examination of ChatGPT's capabilities in DST.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-llm-driven-dialogue-state-tracking</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
