<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 21:09:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>RuDSI: graph-based word sense induction dataset for Russian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rudsi-graph-based-word-sense-induction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present RuDSI, a new benchmark for word sense induction (WSI) in Russian.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rudsi-graph-based-word-sense-induction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartMocap: Joint Estimation of Human and Camera Motion using Uncalibrated RGB Cameras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartmocap-joint-estimation-of-human-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we learn a probability distribution of short human motion sequences ($\sim$1sec) relative to the ground plane and leverage it to disambiguate between the camera and human motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartmocap-joint-estimation-of-human-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>METS-CoV: A Dataset of Medical Entity and Targeted Sentiment on COVID-19 Related Tweets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mets-cov-a-dataset-of-medical-entity-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further investigate tweet users' attitudes toward specific entities, 4 types of entities (Person, Organization, Drug, and Vaccine) are selected and annotated with user sentiments, resulting in a targeted sentiment dataset with 9, 101 entities (in 5, 278 tweets).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mets-cov-a-dataset-of-medical-entity-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TVLT: Textless Vision-Language Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tvlt-textless-vision-language-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present the Textless Vision-Language Transformer (TVLT), where homogeneous transformer blocks take raw visual and audio inputs for vision-and-language representation learning with minimal modality-specific design, and do not use text-specific modules such as tokenization or automatic speech recognition (ASR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tvlt-textless-vision-language-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Retrieval with WavText5K and CLAP Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-retrieval-with-wavtext5k-and-clap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new collection of web audio-text pairs and a new framework for retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-retrieval-with-wavtext5k-and-clap</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion Transformer for Unsupervised Image Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-transformer-for-unsupervised-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image animation aims to animate a source image by using motion learned from a driving video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-transformer-for-unsupervised-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Proxy Models for Concept-Based Model Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-proxy-models-for-concept-based-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core of our proposal is the Causal Proxy Model (CPM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-proxy-models-for-concept-based-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Right: Multimodal Retrieval on Representation of ImaGe witH Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mr-right-multimodal-retrieval-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce Multimodal Retrieval on Representation of ImaGe witH Text (Mr.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mr-right-multimodal-retrieval-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Compressed Sensing with Multi-scale Dilated Convolutional Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-compressed-sensing-with-multi-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During the measurement period, we directly obtain all measurements from a trained measurement network, which employs fully convolutional structures and is jointly trained with the reconstruction network from the input image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-compressed-sensing-with-multi-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-scale Attention Network for Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-attention-network-for-image-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a CNN-based multi-scale attention network (MAN), which consists of multi-scale large kernel attention (MLKA) and a gated spatial attention unit (GSAU), to improve the performance of convolutional SR networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-attention-network-for-image-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ArNLI: Arabic Natural Language Inference for Entailment and Contradiction Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arnli-arabic-natural-language-inference-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We proposed an approach to detect contradictions between pairs of sentences in Arabic language using contradiction vector combined with language model vector as an input to machine learning model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arnli-arabic-natural-language-inference-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Neural Sculpting (3DNS): Editing Neural Signed Distance Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-neural-sculpting-3dns-editing-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, implicit surface representations through neural networks that encode the signed distance have gained popularity and have achieved state-of-the-art results in various tasks (e. g. shape representation, shape reconstruction, and learning shape priors).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-neural-sculpting-3dns-editing-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEMICON: A Learning-to-hash Solution for Large-scale Fine-grained Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semicon-a-learning-to-hash-solution-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Suppression-Enhancing Mask based attention and Interactive Channel transformatiON (SEMICON) to learn binary hash codes for dealing with large-scale fine-grained image retrieval tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semicon-a-learning-to-hash-solution-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weighted Contrastive Hashing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-contrastive-hashing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of unsupervised hashing is advanced by the recent popular contrastive learning paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-contrastive-hashing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTU-Net: Multi-level TransUNet for Space-based Infrared Tiny Ship Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtu-net-multi-level-transunet-for-space-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the extremely large image coverage area (e. g., thousands square kilometers), candidate targets in these images are much smaller, dimer, more changeable than those targets observed by aerial-based and land-based imaging devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtu-net-multi-level-transunet-for-space-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLink: Linking Black-Box Models from Multiple Domains for Collaborative Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlink-linking-black-box-models-from-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The cost efficiency of model inference is critical to real-world machine learning (ML) applications, especially for delay-sensitive tasks and resource-limited devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlink-linking-black-box-models-from-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guiding Safe Exploration with Weakest Preconditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-safe-exploration-with-weakest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In reinforcement learning for safety-critical settings, it is often desirable for the agent to obey safety constraints at all points in time, including during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-safe-exploration-with-weakest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Video Temporal Action Segmentation In Real Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-video-temporal-action-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the real-time action segmentation task is different from TAS task, we define it as streaming video real-time temporal action segmentation (SVTAS) task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-video-temporal-action-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising of 3D MR images using a voxel-wise hybrid residual MLP-CNN model to improve small lesion diagnostic confidence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-of-3d-mr-images-using-a-voxel-wise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate the proposed method on 720 T2-FLAIR brain images with small lesions at different noise levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-of-3d-mr-images-using-a-voxel-wise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LL-GNN: Low Latency Graph Neural Networks on FPGAs for Particle Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ll-gnn-low-latency-graph-neural-networks-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we introduce an outer-product based matrix multiplication approach which is enhanced by the strength reduction for low latency design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ll-gnn-low-latency-graph-neural-networks-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Prediction of Spontaneous Humour: A Novel Dataset and First Results</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-prediction-of-spontaneous-humour-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings suggest that for the automatic analysis of humour and its sentiment, facial expressions are most promising, while humour direction can be best modelled via text-based features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-prediction-of-spontaneous-humour-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Asynchronous and Error-prone Longitudinal Data via Functional Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-asynchronous-and-error-prone</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many longitudinal settings, time-varying covariates may not be measured at the same time as responses and are often prone to measurement error.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-asynchronous-and-error-prone</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YATO: Yet Another deep learning based Text analysis Open toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yato-yet-another-deep-learning-based-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designed in a hierarchical structure, YATO supports free combinations of three types of features including 1) traditional neural networks (CNN, RNN, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yato-yet-another-deep-learning-based-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Parameter-free Nonconvex Low-rank Tensor Completion Model for Spatiotemporal Traffic Data Recovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-parameter-free-nonconvex-low-rank-tensor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we proposed a Parameter-Free Non-Convex Tensor Completion model (TC-PFNC) for traffic data recovery, in which a log-based relaxation term was designed to approximate tensor algebraic rank.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-parameter-free-nonconvex-low-rank-tensor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient block contrastive learning via parameter-free meta-node approximation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-block-contrastive-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a meta-node based approximation technique that can (a) proxy all negative combinations (b) in quadratic cluster size time complexity, (c) at graph level, not node level, and (d) exploit graph sparsity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-block-contrastive-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strong Instance Segmentation Pipeline for MMSports Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strong-instance-segmentation-pipeline-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of ACM MMSports2022 DeepSportRadar Instance Segmentation Challenge is to tackle the segmentation of individual humans including players, coaches and referees on a basketball court.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strong-instance-segmentation-pipeline-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debiasing Graph Neural Networks via Learning Disentangled Causal Substructure</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-graph-neural-networks-via-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, by presenting a graph classification investigation on the training graphs with severe bias, surprisingly, we discover that GNNs always tend to explore the spurious correlations to make decision, even if the causal correlation always exists.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-graph-neural-networks-via-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experimental study of time series forecasting methods for groundwater level prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/experimental-study-of-time-series-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Each time series is made of daily measurements of groundwater levels and two exogenous variables, rainfall and evapotranspiration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/experimental-study-of-time-series-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obj2Seq: Formatting Objects as Sequences with Class Prompt for Visual Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/obj2seq-formatting-objects-as-sequences-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Obj2Seq is able to flexibly determine input categories to satisfy customized requirements, and be easily extended to different visual tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/obj2seq-formatting-objects-as-sequences-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPNet: Dual-Path Network for Real-time Object Detection with Lightweight Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpnet-dual-path-network-for-real-time-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent advances of compressing high-accuracy convolution neural networks (CNNs) have witnessed remarkable progress for real-time object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpnet-dual-path-network-for-real-time-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual Search with Subword TF-IDF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-search-with-subword-tf-idf</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multilingual search can be achieved with subword tokenization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-search-with-subword-tf-idf</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Target Features Affect Visual Search, A Study of Eye Fixations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-features-affect-visual-search-a-study</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Search is referred to the task of finding a target object among a set of distracting objects in a visual display.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-features-affect-visual-search-a-study</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InFi: End-to-End Learning to Filter Input for Resource-Efficiency in Mobile-Centric Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infi-end-to-end-learning-to-filter-input-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous efforts have tailored effective solutions for many applications, but left two essential questions unanswered: (1) theoretical filterability of an inference workload to guide the application of input filtering techniques, thereby avoiding the trial-and-error cost for resource-constrained mobile applications; (2) robust discriminability of feature embedding to allow input filtering to be widely effective for diverse inference tasks and input content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infi-end-to-end-learning-to-filter-input-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inducing Data Amplification Using Auxiliary Datasets in Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inducing-data-amplification-using-auxiliary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several recent studies have shown that the use of extra in-distribution data can lead to a high level of adversarial robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inducing-data-amplification-using-auxiliary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LapGM: A Multisequence MR Bias Correction and Normalization Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lapgm-a-multisequence-mr-bias-correction-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A spatially regularized Gaussian mixture model, LapGM, is proposed for the bias field correction and magnetic resonance normalization problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lapgm-a-multisequence-mr-bias-correction-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrossDTR: Cross-view and Depth-guided Transformers for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crossdtr-cross-view-and-depth-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve accurate 3D object detection at a low cost for autonomous driving, many multi-camera methods have been proposed and solved the occlusion problem of monocular approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crossdtr-cross-view-and-depth-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embracing Consistency: A One-Stage Approach for Spatio-Temporal Video Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embracing-consistency-a-one-stage-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatio-Temporal video grounding (STVG) focuses on retrieving the spatio-temporal tube of a specific object depicted by a free-form textual expression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embracing-consistency-a-one-stage-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion Transformer with Global Intention Localization and Local Movement Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-transformer-with-global-intention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments show that MTR achieves state-of-the-art performance on both the marginal and joint motion prediction challenges, ranking 1st on the leaderboards of Waymo Open Motion Dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-transformer-with-global-intention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Laws For Deep Learning Based Image Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-laws-for-deep-learning-based-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current methods are only trained on a few hundreds or thousands of images as opposed to the millions of examples deep networks are trained on in other domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-laws-for-deep-learning-based-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing Digital Language Support on a Global Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-digital-language-support-on-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The users of endangered languages struggle to thrive in a digitally-mediated world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-digital-language-support-on-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WeightedSHAP: analyzing and improving Shapley based feature attributions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weightedshap-analyzing-and-improving-shapley</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On several real-world datasets, we demonstrate that the influential features identified by WeightedSHAP are better able to recapitulate the model's predictions compared to the features identified by the Shapley value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weightedshap-analyzing-and-improving-shapley</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAIR-FATE: Fair Federated Learning with Momentum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-fate-fair-federated-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While fairness-aware machine learning algorithms have been receiving increasing attention, the focus has been on centralized machine learning, leaving decentralized methods underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-fate-fair-federated-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IdeaReader: A Machine Reading System for Understanding the Idea Flow of Scientific Publications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ideareader-a-machine-reading-system-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the origin and influence of the publication's idea is critical to conducting scientific research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ideareader-a-machine-reading-system-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiDes: A Wikipedia-Based Dataset for Generating Short Descriptions from Paragraphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikides-a-wikipedia-based-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce WikiDes, a novel dataset to generate short descriptions of Wikipedia articles for the problem of text summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikides-a-wikipedia-based-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Counter: Stochastic Feature-based Learning for Diverse Counterfactual Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-counter-stochastic-feature-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interpretable machine learning seeks to understand the reasoning process of complex black-box systems that are long notorious for lack of explainability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-counter-stochastic-feature-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Globally Optimal Event-Based Divergence Estimation for Ventral Landing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/globally-optimal-event-based-divergence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is achieved by estimating divergence (inverse TTC), which is the rate of radial optic flow, from the event stream generated during landing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/globally-optimal-event-based-divergence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publication Bias in Asset Pricing Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/publication-bias-in-asset-pricing-research</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These facts are easily misinterpreted as evidence of publication bias effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/publication-bias-in-asset-pricing-research</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Network Panning: Screening the Optimal Sparse Network Before Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-panning-screening-the-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pruning on neural networks before training not only compresses the original models, but also accelerates the network training phase, which has substantial application value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-panning-screening-the-optimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural parameter calibration for large-scale multi-agent models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-parameter-calibration-for-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computational models have become a powerful tool in the quantitative sciences to understand the behaviour of complex systems that evolve in time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-parameter-calibration-for-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Draw Your Art Dream: Diverse Digital Art Synthesis with Multimodal Guided Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/draw-your-art-dream-diverse-digital-art</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experimental results on the quality and quantity of the generated digital art paintings confirm the effectiveness of the combination of the diffusion model and multimodal guidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/draw-your-art-dream-diverse-digital-art</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
