<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 21:06:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-modality transrectal ultrasound vudei classification for identification of clinically significant prostate cancer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modality-transrectal-ultrasound-vudei</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the aim of effectively identifying prostate cancer, we propose a framework for the classification of clinically significant prostate cancer (csPCa) from multi-modality TRUS videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modality-transrectal-ultrasound-vudei</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEL: Efficient Multi-Task Evolutionary Learning for High-Dimensional Feature Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mel-efficient-multi-task-evolutionary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating information sharing between different feature selection tasks, MEL achieves enhanced learning ability and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mel-efficient-multi-task-evolutionary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Negative Transfer on Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-negative-transfer-on-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate this, we bring a new insight: for semantically similar graphs, although structural differences lead to significant distribution shift in node embeddings, their impact on subgraph embeddings could be marginal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-negative-transfer-on-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Vocabulary Segmentation with Unpaired Mask-Text Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-segmentation-with-unpaired</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With this unpaired mask-text supervision, we propose a new weakly-supervised open-vocabulary segmentation framework (Uni-OVSeg) that leverages confident pairs of mask predictions and entities in text descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-segmentation-with-unpaired</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPIrigen: MPI Code Generation through Domain-Specific Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpirigen-mpi-code-generation-through-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study first investigates the performance of state-of-the-art language models in generating MPI-based parallel programs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpirigen-mpi-code-generation-through-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Sharpness in Grokking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-sharpness-in-grokking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks sometimes exhibit grokking, a phenomenon where perfect or near-perfect performance is achieved on a validation set well after the same performance has been obtained on the corresponding training set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-sharpness-in-grokking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Portrait Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-portrait-quality-assessment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated and robust portrait quality assessment (PQA) is of paramount importance in high-impact applications such as smartphone photography.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-portrait-quality-assessment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LlaSMol: Advancing Large Language Models for Chemistry with a Large-Scale, Comprehensive, High-Quality Instruction Tuning Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llasmol-advancing-large-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chemistry plays a crucial role in many domains, such as drug discovery and material science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llasmol-advancing-large-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformers, parallel computation, and logarithmic depth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-parallel-computation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that a constant number of self-attention layers can efficiently simulate, and be simulated by, a constant number of communication rounds of Massively Parallel Computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-parallel-computation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crop and Couple: cardiac image segmentation using interlinked specialist networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crop-and-couple-cardiac-image-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diagnosis of cardiovascular disease using automated methods often relies on the critical task of cardiac image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crop-and-couple-cardiac-image-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient One-stage Video Object Detection by Exploiting Temporal Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-one-stage-video-object-detection-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the analysis, we present a simple yet efficient framework to address the computational bottlenecks and achieve efficient one-stage VOD by exploiting the temporal consistency in video frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-one-stage-video-object-detection-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Machine Learning techniques in the management of harmful algal blooms impact</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-machine-learning-techniques-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Harmful algal blooms (HABs) are episodes of high concentrations of algae that are potentially toxic for human consumption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-machine-learning-techniques-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entropy-regularized Point-based Value Iteration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropy-regularized-point-based-value</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, model-based planners may be brittle under these types of uncertainty because they rely on an exact model and tend to commit to a single optimal behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropy-regularized-point-based-value</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depth-aware Volume Attention for Texture-less Stereo Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-aware-volume-attention-for-texture-less</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose a more rigorous evaluation metric that considers depth-wise relative error, providing comprehensive evaluations for universal stereo matching and depth estimation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-aware-volume-attention-for-texture-less</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLEB: Streamlining LLMs through Redundancy Verification and Elimination of Transformer Blocks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sleb-streamlining-llms-through-redundancy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce SLEB, a novel approach designed to streamline LLMs by eliminating redundant transformer blocks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sleb-streamlining-llms-through-redundancy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PC-NeRF: Parent-Child Neural Radiance Fields Using Sparse LiDAR Frames in Autonomous Driving Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pc-nerf-parent-child-neural-radiance-fields-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With extensive experiments, PC-NeRF is proven to achieve high-precision novel LiDAR view synthesis and 3D reconstruction in large-scale scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pc-nerf-parent-child-neural-radiance-fields-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOv8-AM: YOLOv8 with Attention Mechanisms for Pediatric Wrist Fracture Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov8-am-yolov8-with-attention-mechanisms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we respectively employ four attention modules, Convolutional Block Attention Module (CBAM), Global Attention Mechanism (GAM), Efficient Channel Attention (ECA), and Shuffle Attention (SA), to design the improved models and train them on GRAZPEDWRI-DX dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov8-am-yolov8-with-attention-mechanisms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Into the Unknown: Self-Learning Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/into-the-unknown-self-learning-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It facilitates the creation of a self-learning loop that focuses exclusively on the knowledge gap in Points in The Unknown, resulting in a reduced hallucination score.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/into-the-unknown-self-learning-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Deep Learning Based Channel Estimation for Extremely Large-Scale Massive MIMO Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-deep-learning-based-channel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extremely large-scale massive multiple-input multiple-output (XL-MIMO) systems introduce the much higher channel dimensionality and incur the additional near-field propagation effect, aggravating the computation load and the difficulty to acquire the prior knowledge for channel estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-deep-learning-based-channel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pyramid Attention Network for Medical Image Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyramid-attention-network-for-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advent of deep-learning-based registration networks has addressed the time-consuming challenge in traditional iterative methods. However, the potential of current registration networks for comprehensively capturing spatial relationships has not been fully explored, leading to inadequate performance in large-deformation image registration. The pure convolutional neural networks (CNNs) neglect feature enhancement, while current Transformer-based networks are susceptible to information redundancy. To alleviate these issues, we propose a pyramid attention network (PAN) for deformable medical image registration. Specifically, the proposed PAN incorporates a dual-stream pyramid encoder with channel-wise attention to boost the feature representation. Moreover, a multi-head local attention Transformer is introduced as decoder to analyze motion patterns and generate deformation fields. Extensive experiments on two public brain magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) datasets and one abdominal MRI dataset demonstrate that our method achieves favorable registration performance, while outperforming several CNN-based and Transformer-based registration networks. Our code is publicly available at https://github. com/JuliusWang-7/PAN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyramid-attention-network-for-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing ID and Text Fusion via Alternative Training in Session-based Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-id-and-text-fusion-via-alternative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To integrate text information, various methods have been introduced, mostly following a naive fusion framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-id-and-text-fusion-via-alternative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Video Compression with Pre-trained Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extreme-video-compression-with-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results showcase the potential of exploiting the temporal relations in video data using generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extreme-video-compression-with-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-MUSED: CLIP-Guided Multi-Subject Visual Neural Information Semantic Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-mused-clip-guided-multi-subject-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although prior multi-subject decoding methods have made significant progress, they still suffer from several limitations, including difficulty in extracting global neural response features, linear scaling of model parameters with the number of subjects, and inadequate characterization of the relationship between neural responses of different subjects to various stimuli.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-mused-clip-guided-multi-subject-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraSSRep: Graph-Based Self-Supervised Learning for Repeat Detection in Metagenomic Assembly</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grassrep-graph-based-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, our experiments with synthetic metagenomic datasets reveal that incorporating the graph structure and the GNN enhances our detection performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grassrep-graph-based-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Inference Acceleration by Learning MLPs on Graphs without Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-inference-acceleration-by-learning-mlps</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have demonstrated effectiveness in various graph learning tasks, yet their reliance on message-passing constraints their deployment in latency-sensitive applications such as financial fraud detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-inference-acceleration-by-learning-mlps</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Training Induces Information Bottleneck through Layer-Role Differentiation: A Comparative Analysis with Layer-wise Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-training-induces-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[End-to-end (E2E) training, optimizing the entire model through error backpropagation, fundamentally supports the advancements of deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-training-induces-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(Ir)rationality and Cognitive Biases in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ir-rationality-and-cognitive-biases-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Do large language models (LLMs) display rational reasoning?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ir-rationality-and-cognitive-biases-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AQA-Bench: An Interactive Benchmark for Evaluating LLMs' Sequential Reasoning Ability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aqa-bench-an-interactive-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces AQA-Bench, a novel benchmark to assess the sequential reasoning capabilities of large language models (LLMs) in algorithmic contexts, such as depth-first search (DFS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aqa-bench-an-interactive-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedSiKD: Clients Similarity and Knowledge Distillation: Addressing Non-i.i.d. and Constraints in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedsikd-clients-similarity-and-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, federated learning (FL) has emerged as a promising technique for training machine learning models in a decentralized manner while also preserving data privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedsikd-clients-similarity-and-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthesizing Knowledge-enhanced Features for Real-world Zero-shot Food Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesizing-knowledge-enhanced-features-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The complexity of food semantic attributes further makes it more difficult for current ZSD methods to distinguish various food categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesizing-knowledge-enhanced-features-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TDViT: Temporal Dilated Video Transformer for Dense Video Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tdvit-temporal-dilated-video-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep video models, for example, 3D CNNs or video transformers, have achieved promising performance on sparse video tasks, i. e., predicting one result per video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tdvit-temporal-dilated-video-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less is More: Fewer Interpretable Region via Submodular Subset Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-fewer-interpretable-region-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For incorrectly predicted samples, our method achieves gains of 81. 0% and 18. 4% compared to the HSIC-Attribution algorithm in the average highest confidence and Insertion score respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-fewer-interpretable-region-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BdSLW60: A Word-Level Bangla Sign Language Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bdslw60-a-word-level-bangla-sign-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sign language discourse is an essential mode of daily communication for the deaf and hard-of-hearing people.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bdslw60-a-word-level-bangla-sign-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dense Reward View on Aligning Text-to-Image Diffusion with Preference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dense-reward-view-on-aligning-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aligning text-to-image diffusion model (T2I) with preference has been gaining increasing research attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dense-reward-view-on-aligning-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Generative AI for De Novo Drug Design: New Frontiers in Molecule and Protein Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-generative-ai-for-de-novo-drug</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within each theme, we identify a variety of subtasks and applications, highlighting important datasets, benchmarks, and model architectures and comparing the performance of top models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-generative-ai-for-de-novo-drug</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pix2Code: Learning to Compose Neural Visual Concepts as Programs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pix2code-learning-to-compose-neural-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The challenge in learning abstract concepts from images in an unsupervised fashion lies in the required integration of visual perception and generalizable relational reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pix2code-learning-to-compose-neural-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompted Contextual Vectors for Spear-Phishing Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompted-contextual-vectors-for-spear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spear-phishing attacks present a significant security challenge, with large language models (LLMs) escalating the threat by generating convincing emails and facilitating target reconnaissance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompted-contextual-vectors-for-spear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Discovery under Off-Target Interventions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-under-off-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal graph discovery is a significant problem with applications across various disciplines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-under-off-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatCell: Facilitating Single-Cell Analysis with Natural Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatcell-facilitating-single-cell-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As Large Language Models (LLMs) rapidly evolve, their influence in science is becoming increasingly prominent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatcell-facilitating-single-cell-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Logical Approach to Criminal Case Investigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-logical-approach-to-criminal-case</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We created an ontology of motives and methods of murder from dictionaries and dictionaries, added it to the knowledge graph of ``The Adventure of the Speckled Band'', and applied scripts to determine motives, opportunities, and methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-logical-approach-to-criminal-case</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concept-1K: A Novel Benchmark for Instance Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-1k-a-novel-benchmark-for-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing IL scenarios and datasets are unqualified for assessing forgetting in PLMs, giving an illusion that PLMs do not suffer from catastrophic forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-1k-a-novel-benchmark-for-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verified Multi-Step Synthesis using Large Language Models and Monte Carlo Tree Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verified-multi-step-synthesis-using-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The base model with VMCTS is even competitive with ChatGPT4 augmented with plugins and multiple re-tries on these problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verified-multi-step-synthesis-using-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaGA: Large Language and Graph Assistant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llaga-large-language-and-graph-assistant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have empowered the advance in graph-structured data analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llaga-large-language-and-graph-assistant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional Neural Expert Processes for Learning from Demonstration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-neural-expert-processes-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we compare the performance of CNEP with another LfD framework, namely Conditional Neural Movement Primitives (CNMP), on a range of tasks, including experiments on a real robot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-neural-expert-processes-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSC-CPI: Multi-Scale Protein Sequence-Structure Contrasting for Efficient and Generalizable Compound-Protein Interaction Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psc-cpi-multi-scale-protein-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compound-Protein Interaction (CPI) prediction aims to predict the pattern and strength of compound-protein interactions for rational drug discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psc-cpi-multi-scale-protein-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Effect of Data Poisoning on Counterfactual Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-data-poisoning-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterfactual explanations provide a popular method for analyzing the predictions of black-box systems, and they can offer the opportunity for computational recourse by suggesting actionable changes on how to change the input to obtain a different (i. e. more favorable) system output.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-data-poisoning-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Mamba: Towards Learning on Graphs with State Space Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-mamba-towards-learning-on-graphs-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the recent success of State Space Models (SSMs), such as Mamba, we present Graph Mamba Networks (GMNs), a general framework for a new class of GNNs based on selective SSMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-mamba-towards-learning-on-graphs-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLD-Attack: Jailbreaking LLMs with Stealthiness and Controllability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cold-attack-jailbreaking-llms-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this connection, we adapt the Energy-based Constrained Decoding with Langevin Dynamics (COLD), a state-of-the-art, highly efficient algorithm in controllable text generation, and introduce the COLD-Attack framework which unifies and automates the search of adversarial LLM attacks under a variety of control requirements such as fluency, stealthiness, sentiment, and left-right-coherence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cold-attack-jailbreaking-llms-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ant Colony Optimization for Cooperative Inspection Path Planning Using Multiple Unmanned Aerial Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ant-colony-optimization-for-cooperative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new swarm intelligence-based approach to deal with the cooperative path planning problem of unmanned aerial vehicles (UAVs), which is essential for the automatic inspection of infrastructure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ant-colony-optimization-for-cooperative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disambiguated Node Classification with Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disambiguated-node-classification-with-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have demonstrated significant success in learning from graph-structured data across various domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disambiguated-node-classification-with-graph</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
