<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 09:12:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation of Fractional Brownian Motion and Related Stochastic Processes in Practice: A Straightforward Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-of-fractional-brownian-motion-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fractional Brownian motion, with its long-time correlated increments, has been applied in many fields in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-of-fractional-brownian-motion-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QAGait: Revisit Gait Recognition from a Quality Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qagait-revisit-gait-recognition-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gait recognition is a promising biometric method that aims to identify pedestrians from their unique walking patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qagait-revisit-gait-recognition-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DenoSent: A Denoising Objective for Self-Supervised Sentence Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denosent-a-denoising-objective-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These methods regularize the representation space by pulling similar sentence representations closer and pushing away the dissimilar ones and have been proven effective in various NLP tasks, e. g., semantic textual similarity (STS) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denosent-a-denoising-objective-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatterBox: Multi-round Multimodal Referring and Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatterbox-multi-round-multimodal-referring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we establish a baseline for a new task named multimodal multi-round referring and grounding (MRG), opening up a promising direction for instance-level multimodal dialogues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatterbox-multi-round-multimodal-referring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Definitive Guide to Policy Gradients in Deep Reinforcement Learning: Theory, Algorithms and Implementations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-definitive-guide-to-policy-gradients-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, various powerful policy gradient algorithms have been proposed in deep reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-definitive-guide-to-policy-gradients-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debiased Sample Selection for Combating Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiased-sample-selection-for-combating-noisy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose a noIse-Tolerant Expert Model (ITEM) for debiased learning in sample selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiased-sample-selection-for-combating-noisy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compositional Generative Inverse Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-generative-inverse-design</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an N-body interaction task and a challenging 2D multi-airfoil design task, we demonstrate that by composing the learned diffusion model at test time, our method allows us to design initial states and boundary shapes that are more complex than those in the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-generative-inverse-design</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructDoc: A Dataset for Zero-Shot Generalization of Visual Document Understanding with Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructdoc-a-dataset-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of completing various visual document understanding (VDU) tasks, e. g., question answering and information extraction, on real-world documents through human-written instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructdoc-a-dataset-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified-Width Adaptive Dynamic Network for All-In-One Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-width-adaptive-dynamic-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to traditional image restoration methods, all-in-one image restoration techniques are gaining increased attention for their ability to restore images affected by diverse and unknown corruption types and levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-width-adaptive-dynamic-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFMatch: Aligning Automated Answer Equivalence Evaluation with Expert Judgments For Open-Domain Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfmatch-aligning-automated-answer-equivalence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Question answering (QA) can only make progress if we know if an answer is correct, but for many of the most challenging and interesting QA examples, current evaluation metrics to determine answer equivalence (AE) often do not align with human judgments, particularly more verbose, free-form answers from large language models (LLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfmatch-aligning-automated-answer-equivalence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning Model Reuse in the HuggingFace Community: Challenges, Benefit and Trends</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-model-reuse-in-the-huggingface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our qualitative analysis, we present a taxonomy of the challenges and benefits associated with PTM reuse within this community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-model-reuse-in-the-huggingface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentBoard: An Analytical Evaluation Board of Multi-turn LLM Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentboard-an-analytical-evaluation-board-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating large language models (LLMs) as general-purpose agents is essential for understanding their capabilities and facilitating their integration into practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentboard-an-analytical-evaluation-board-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Explainable Harmful Meme Detection through Multimodal Debate between Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explainable-harmful-meme-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then we propose to fine-tune a small language model as the debate judge for harmfulness inference, to facilitate multimodal fusion between the harmfulness rationales and the intrinsic multimodal information within memes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explainable-harmful-meme-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Forget Clients in Federated Online Learning to Rank?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-forget-clients-in-federated-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a FOLTR system, a ranker is learned by aggregating local updates to the global ranking model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-forget-clients-in-federated-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Synthetic Health Sensor Data for Privacy-Preserving Wearable Stress Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-synthetic-health-sensor-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Smartwatch health sensor data is increasingly utilized in smart health applications and patient monitoring, including stress detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-synthetic-health-sensor-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADMap: Anti-disturbance framework for reconstructing online vectorized HD map</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/admap-anti-disturbance-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, this paper proposes the Anti-disturbance Map reconstruction framework (ADMap).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/admap-anti-disturbance-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Generalized Multiscale Bundle-Based Hyperspectral Sparse Unmixing Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generalized-multiscale-bundle-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In hyperspectral sparse unmixing, a successful approach employs spectral bundles to address the variability of the endmembers in the spatial domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generalized-multiscale-bundle-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDI-CoCo: A Dataset For Understanding The Effect Of Color Contrast In Machine-Assisted Skin Disease Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddi-coco-a-dataset-for-understanding-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We take another angle to investigate color contrast's impact, beyond skin tones, on malignancy detection in skin disease datasets: We hypothesize that in addition to skin tones, the color difference between the lesion area and skin also plays a role in malignancy detection performance of dermatology AI models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddi-coco-a-dataset-for-understanding-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Supervised Coupled Thin-Plate Spline Model for Rotation Correction and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-coupled-thin-plate-spline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To break this bottleneck, we propose the coupled thin-plate spline model (CoupledTPS), which iteratively couples multiple TPS with limited control points into a more flexible and powerful transformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-coupled-thin-plate-spline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Big Data Architecture for Early Identification and Categorization of Dark Web Sites</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-big-data-architecture-for-early</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dark web has become notorious for its association with illicit activities and there is a growing need for systems to automate the monitoring of this space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-big-data-architecture-for-early</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Cost-Sensitive Meta-Learning Strategy for Fair Provider Exposure in Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cost-sensitive-meta-learning-strategy-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When devising recommendation services, it is important to account for the interests of all content providers, encompassing not only newcomers but also minority demographic groups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cost-sensitive-meta-learning-strategy-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multitask Active Learning for Graph Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multitask-active-learning-for-graph-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, by coupling node classification tasks, MITIGATE obtains the capability to detect out-of-distribution nodes without known anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multitask-active-learning-for-graph-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-bayesian-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In industry, Bayesian optimization (BO) is widely applied in the human-AI collaborative parameter tuning of cyber-physical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-bayesian-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SegMamba: Long-range Sequential Modeling Mamba For 3D Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmamba-long-range-sequential-modeling-mamba</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our SegMamba, in contrast to Transformer-based methods, excels in whole volume feature modeling from a state space model standpoint, maintaining superior processing speed, even with volume features at a resolution of {$64\times 64\times 64$}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmamba-long-range-sequential-modeling-mamba</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Representations for Clustering via Partial Information Discrimination and Cross-Level Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-for-clustering-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel deep image clustering approach termed PICI, which enforces the partial information discrimination and the cross-level interaction in a joint learning framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-for-clustering-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpeechGPT-Gen: Scaling Chain-of-Information Speech Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechgpt-gen-scaling-chain-of-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It comprises an autoregressive model based on LLM for semantic information modeling and a non-autoregressive model employing flow matching for perceptual information modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechgpt-gen-scaling-chain-of-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiTA: Bi-Directional Tuning for Lossless Acceleration in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bita-bi-directional-tuning-for-lossless</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) commonly employ autoregressive generation during inference, leading to high memory bandwidth demand and consequently extended latency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bita-bi-directional-tuning-for-lossless</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SGTR+: End-to-end Scene Graph Generation with Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgtr-end-to-end-scene-graph-generation-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we design a graph assembling module to infer the connectivity of the bipartite scene graph based on our entity-aware structure, enabling us to generate the scene graph in an end-to-end manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgtr-end-to-end-scene-graph-generation-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shift-ConvNets: Small Convolutional Kernel with Large Kernel Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shift-convnets-small-convolutional-kernel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results show that our shift-wise operator significantly improves the accuracy of a regular CNN while markedly reducing computational requirements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shift-convnets-small-convolutional-kernel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PA-SAM: Prompt Adapter SAM for High-Quality Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pa-sam-prompt-adapter-sam-for-high-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel prompt-driven adapter into SAM, namely Prompt Adapter Segment Anything Model (PA-SAM), aiming to enhance the segmentation mask quality of the original SAM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pa-sam-prompt-adapter-sam-for-high-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClipSAM: CLIP and SAM Collaboration for Zero-Shot Anomaly Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clipsam-clip-and-sam-collaboration-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, foundational models such as CLIP and SAM have shown promising performance for the task of Zero-Shot Anomaly Segmentation (ZSAS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clipsam-clip-and-sam-collaboration-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMCheckup: Conversational Examination of Large Language Models via Interpretability Tools</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmcheckup-conversational-examination-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interpretability tools that offer explanations in the form of a dialogue have demonstrated their efficacy in enhancing users' understanding, as one-off explanations may occasionally fall short in providing sufficient information to the user.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmcheckup-conversational-examination-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemanticSLAM: Learning based Semantic Map Construction and Robust Camera Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semanticslam-learning-based-semantic-map</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach enables the creation of a semantic map of the environment and ensures reliable camera localization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semanticslam-learning-based-semantic-map</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Spatiotemporal Clutter Filtering of Transthoracic Echocardiographic Images Using a 3D Convolutional Auto-Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-spatiotemporal-clutter-filtering-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To train the deep network, a diverse set of artifact patterns was simulated and the simulated patterns were superimposed onto artifact-free ultra-realistic synthetic TTE sequences of six ultrasound vendors to generate input of the filtering network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-spatiotemporal-clutter-filtering-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seed-Guided Fine-Grained Entity Typing in Science and Engineering Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seed-guided-fine-grained-entity-typing-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the task of seed-guided fine-grained entity typing in science and engineering domains, which takes the name and a few seed entities for each entity type as the only supervision and aims to classify new entity mentions into both seen and unseen types (i. e., those without seed entities).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seed-guided-fine-grained-entity-typing-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy-based Automated Model Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-based-automated-model-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The conventional evaluation protocols on machine learning models rely heavily on a labeled, i. i. d-assumed testing dataset, which is not often present in real world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-based-automated-model-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DREditor: An Time-efficient Approach for Building a Domain-specific Dense Retrieval Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreditor-an-time-efficient-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, we develop a time-efficient approach called DREditor to edit the matching rule of an off-the-shelf dense retrieval model to suit a specific domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreditor-an-time-efficient-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Initialization for Data-Efficient Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-initialization-for-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training vision transformer networks on small datasets poses challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-initialization-for-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffMoog: a Differentiable Modular Synthesizer for Sound Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffmoog-a-differentiable-modular-synthesizer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an open-source platform that comprises DiffMoog and an end-to-end sound matching framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffmoog-a-differentiable-modular-synthesizer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIV-SSD: Neighbor IoU-Voting Single-Stage Object Detector From Point Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/niv-ssd-neighbor-iou-voting-single-stage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NIV strategy can serve as a bridge between classification and regression branches by calculating two types of statistical data from the regression output to correct the classification confidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/niv-ssd-neighbor-iou-voting-single-stage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Domain Coarse-to-Fine Progressive Estimation Network for Simultaneous Denoising, Limited-View Reconstruction, and Attenuation Correction of Cardiac SPECT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-domain-coarse-to-fine-progressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, Computed Tomography (CT) is commonly used to derive attenuation maps ($\mu$-maps) for attenuation correction (AC) of cardiac SPECT, but it will introduce additional radiation exposure and SPECT-CT misalignments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-domain-coarse-to-fine-progressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCA: Collaborative Competitive Agents for Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cca-collaborative-competitive-agents-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel generative model, Collaborative Competitive Agents (CCA), which leverages the capabilities of multiple Large Language Models (LLMs) based agents to execute complex tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cca-collaborative-competitive-agents-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAZARD Challenge: Embodied Decision Making in Dynamically Changing Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hazard-challenge-embodied-decision-making-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in high-fidelity virtual environments serve as one of the major driving forces for building intelligent embodied agents to perceive, reason and interact with the physical world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hazard-challenge-embodied-decision-making-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAST: Video Polyp Segmentation with a Mixture-Attention Siamese Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mast-video-polyp-segmentation-with-a-mixture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, our MAST is the first transformer model dedicated to video polyp segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mast-video-polyp-segmentation-with-a-mixture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon: Fair Active Learning using Multi-armed Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/falcon-fair-active-learning-using-multi-armed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a user-specified group fairness measure, Falcon identifies samples from "target groups" (e. g., (attribute=female, label=positive)) that are the most informative for improving fairness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/falcon-fair-active-learning-using-multi-armed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Icy Moon Surface Simulation and Stereo Depth Estimation for Sampling Autonomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icy-moon-surface-simulation-and-stereo-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The surface reflectance properties of icy moon terrains (Enceladus and Europa) are inferred from multispectral datasets of previous missions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icy-moon-surface-simulation-and-stereo-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSAvatar: A Point-based Morphable Shape Model for Real-Time Head Avatar Creation with 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psavatar-a-point-based-morphable-shape-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce PSAvatar, a novel framework for animatable head avatar creation that utilizes discrete geometric primitive to create a parametric morphable shape model and employs 3D Gaussian for fine detail representation and high fidelity rendering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psavatar-a-point-based-morphable-shape-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Review of Deep Learning Methods for Photoplethysmography Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-deep-learning-methods-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this review, we systematically reviewed papers that applied deep learning models to process PPG data between January 1st of 2017 and July 31st of 2023 from Google Scholar, PubMed and Dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-deep-learning-methods-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Prompting: Enhancing Language Models with Task-Agnostic Scaffolding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-prompting-enhancing-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This collaborative prompting approach empowers a single LM to simultaneously act as a comprehensive orchestrator and a panel of diverse experts, significantly enhancing its performance across a wide array of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-prompting-enhancing-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TroVE: Inducing Verifiable and Efficient Toolboxes for Solving Programmatic Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trove-inducing-verifiable-and-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models (LMs) can solve tasks such as answering questions about tables or images by writing programs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trove-inducing-verifiable-and-efficient</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
