<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 09:16:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SCA: Highly Efficient Semantic-Consistent Unrestricted Adversarial Attack</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sca-highly-efficient-semantic-consistent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unrestricted adversarial attacks typically manipulate the semantic content of an image (e. g., color or texture) to create adversarial examples that are both effective and photorealistic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sca-highly-efficient-semantic-consistent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BadCM: Invisible Backdoor Attack Against Cross-Modal Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badcm-invisible-backdoor-attack-against-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel bilateral backdoor to fill in the missing pieces of the puzzle in the cross-modal backdoor and propose a generalized invisible backdoor framework against cross-modal learning (BadCM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badcm-invisible-backdoor-attack-against-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog-IQA: Standard-guided Zero-shot MLLM for Mix-grained Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dog-iqa-standard-guided-zero-shot-mllm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image quality assessment (IQA) serves as the golden standard for all models' performance in nearly all computer vision fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dog-iqa-standard-guided-zero-shot-mllm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Models are Evolutionary Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-are-evolutionary-algorithms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a convergence of machine learning and biology, we reveal that diffusion models are evolutionary algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-are-evolutionary-algorithms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning-Based Prediction of Suspension Dynamics Performance in Multi-Axle Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-prediction-of-suspension</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a deep learning-based framework for predicting the dynamic performance of suspension systems in multi-axle vehicles, emphasizing the integration of machine learning with traditional vehicle dynamics modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-prediction-of-suspension</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard Negative Sample Mining for Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-negative-sample-mining-for-whole-slide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly supervised whole slide image (WSI) classification is challenging due to the lack of patch-level labels and high computational costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-negative-sample-mining-for-whole-slide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs Know More Than They Show: On the Intrinsic Representation of LLM Hallucinations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-know-more-than-they-show-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show that the internal representations of LLMs encode much more information about truthfulness than previously recognized.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-know-more-than-they-show-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BACKTIME: Backdoor Attacks on Multivariate Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backtime-backdoor-attacks-on-multivariate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multivariate Time Series (MTS) forecasting is a fundamental task with numerous real-world applications, such as transportation, climate, and epidemiology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backtime-backdoor-attacks-on-multivariate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer-aided Colorization State-of-the-science: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computer-aided-colorization-state-of-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper reviews published research in the field of computer-aided colorization technology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computer-aided-colorization-state-of-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom Non-Linear Model Predictive Control for Obstacle Avoidance in Indoor and Outdoor Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/custom-non-linear-model-predictive-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Navigating complex environments requires Unmanned Aerial Vehicles (UAVs) and autonomous systems to perform trajectory tracking and obstacle avoidance in real-time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/custom-non-linear-model-predictive-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter Competition Balancing for Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-competition-balancing-for-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently developed model merging techniques enable the direct integration of multiple models, each fine-tuned for distinct tasks, into a single model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-competition-balancing-for-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Comprehensive Detection of Chinese Harmful Memes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-comprehensive-detection-of-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Harmful memes have proliferated on the Chinese Internet, while research on detecting Chinese harmful memes significantly lags behind due to the absence of reliable datasets and effective detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-comprehensive-detection-of-chinese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-based Extreme Image Compression with Compressed Feature Initialization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-extreme-image-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we design a novel relay residual diffusion that reconstructs the raw image by iteratively removing the added noise and the residual between the compressed and target latent features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-extreme-image-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Survey of Mamba Architectures for Medical Image Analysis: Classification, Segmentation, Restoration and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-survey-of-mamba-architectures</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This review aims to demonstrate the transformative potential of Mamba in overcoming existing barriers within medical imaging while paving the way for innovative advancements in the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-survey-of-mamba-architectures</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Med-TTT: Vision Test-Time Training model for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/med-ttt-vision-test-time-training-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image segmentation plays a crucial role in clinical diagnosis and treatment planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/med-ttt-vision-test-time-training-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Regression 2D-3D Ultrasound Registration for Liver Motion Correction in Focal Tumor Thermal Ablation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-regression-2d-3d-ultrasound-registration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose a 2D-3D US registration approach to enable intra-procedural alignment that mitigates errors caused by liver motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-regression-2d-3d-ultrasound-registration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Memorization In Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-memorization-in-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models (LMs) can "memorize" information, i. e., encode training data in their weights in such a way that inference-time queries can lead to verbatim regurgitation of that data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-memorization-in-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Light or Light Traffic? Investigating Phrasal Semantics in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-light-or-light-traffic-investigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Phrases are fundamental linguistic units through which humans convey semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-light-or-light-traffic-investigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeJudge: Evaluating Code Generation with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codejudge-evaluating-code-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents CodeJudge, a code evaluation framework that leverages LLMs to evaluate the semantic correctness of generated code without the need for test cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codejudge-evaluating-code-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Channel-aware Contrastive Conditional Diffusion for Multivariate Probabilistic Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/channel-aware-contrastive-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we devise an ad-hoc denoising-based temporal contrastive learning to explicitly amplify the predictive mutual information between past observations and future forecasts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/channel-aware-contrastive-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Train Long-Context Language Models (Effectively)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-train-long-context-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study continued training and supervised fine-tuning (SFT) of a language model (LM) to make effective use of long-context information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-train-long-context-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Searching for Efficient Linear Layers over a Continuous Space of Structured Matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/searching-for-efficient-linear-layers-over-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To analyze the framework, we develop a taxonomy of all such operators based on their computational and algebraic properties and show that differences in the compute-optimal scaling laws are mostly governed by a small number of variables that we introduce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/searching-for-efficient-linear-layers-over-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measurements with Noise: Bayesian Optimization for Co-optimizing Noise and Property Discovery in Automated Experiments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measurements-with-noise-bayesian-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We have developed a Bayesian optimization (BO) workflow that integrates intra-step noise optimization into automated experimental cycles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measurements-with-noise-bayesian-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Efficient Inference Frame for SMLM (Single-Molecule Localization Microscopy)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-inference-frame-for-smlm-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Single-molecule localization microscopy (SMLM) surpasses the diffraction limit, achieving subcellular resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-inference-frame-for-smlm-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Preference Modeling with Preference Representations for Aligning Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-preference-modeling-with-preference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce preference representation learning, an approach that embeds responses into a latent space to capture intricate preference structures efficiently, achieving linear query complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-preference-modeling-with-preference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collective Critics for Creative Story Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collective-critics-for-creative-story</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating a long story of several thousand words with narrative coherence using Large Language Models (LLMs) has been a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collective-critics-for-creative-story</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Large Language Models Grasp Legal Theories? Enhance Legal Reasoning with Insights from Multi-Agent Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-grasp-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) could struggle to fully understand legal theories and perform complex legal reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-grasp-legal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTARR: A fast and robust method for identifying anatomical regions on CT images via atlas registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ctarr-a-fast-and-robust-method-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The method serves as a pre-processing step for any deep learning-based CT image analysis pipeline by automatically identifying the pre-defined anatomical region that is relevant for the follow-up task and removing the rest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ctarr-a-fast-and-robust-method-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RelChaNet: Neural Network Feature Selection using Relative Change Scores</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relchanet-neural-network-feature-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce RelChaNet, a novel and lightweight feature selection algorithm that uses neuron pruning and regrowth in the input layer of a dense neural network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relchanet-neural-network-feature-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ControlAR: Controllable Image Generation with Autoregressive Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlar-controllable-image-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we explore control encoding for AR models and propose a lightweight control encoder to transform spatial inputs (e. g., canny edges or depth maps) into control tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlar-controllable-image-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReLIC: A Recipe for 64k Steps of In-Context Reinforcement Learning for Embodied AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relic-a-recipe-for-64k-steps-of-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intelligent embodied agents need to quickly adapt to new scenarios by integrating long histories of experience into decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relic-a-recipe-for-64k-steps-of-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent Security Bench (ASB): Formalizing and Benchmarking Attacks and Defenses in LLM-based Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-security-bench-asb-formalizing-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our benchmark results reveal critical vulnerabilities in different stages of agent operation, including system prompt, user prompt handling, tool usage, and memory retrieval, with the highest average attack success rate of 84. 30\%, but limited effectiveness shown in current defenses, unveiling important works to be done in terms of agent security for the community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-security-bench-asb-formalizing-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vinoground: Scrutinizing LMMs over Dense Temporal Reasoning with Short Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vinoground-scrutinizing-lmms-over-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There has been growing sentiment recently that modern large multimodal models (LMMs) have addressed most of the key challenges related to short video comprehension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vinoground-scrutinizing-lmms-over-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pseudo-Stereo Inputs: A Solution to the Occlusion Challenge in Self-Supervised Stereo Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-stereo-inputs-a-solution-to-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed pseudo-stereo inputs strategy, due to its simplicity and effectiveness, has the potential to serve as a new paradigm for direct self-supervised stereo matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-stereo-inputs-a-solution-to-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlphaEdit: Null-Space Constrained Knowledge Editing for Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alphaedit-null-space-constrained-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce AlphaEdit, a novel solution that projects perturbation onto the null space of the preserved knowledge before applying it to the parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alphaedit-null-space-constrained-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leray-Schauder Mappings for Operator Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leray-schauder-mappings-for-operator-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an algorithm for learning operators between Banach spaces, based on the use of Leray-Schauder mappings to learn a finite-dimensional approximation of compact subspaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leray-schauder-mappings-for-operator-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extending Context Window of Large Language Models from a Distributional Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-context-window-of-large-language-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing scaling methods often rely on empirical approaches and lack a profound understanding of the internal distribution within RoPE, resulting in suboptimal performance in extending the context window length.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-context-window-of-large-language-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Taylor Expansion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-taylor-expansion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Statistical Taylor expansion replaces the input precise variables in a conventional Taylor expansion with random variables each with known mean and deviation, to calculate the result mean and deviation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-taylor-expansion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-LDM: Multi-Modal Latent Diffusion Model for Sounding Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-ldm-multi-modal-latent-diffusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sounding Video Generation (SVG) is an audio-video joint generation task challenged by high-dimensional signal spaces, distinct data formats, and different patterns of content information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-ldm-multi-modal-latent-diffusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlashMask: Efficient and Rich Mask Extension of FlashAttention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashmask-efficient-and-rich-mask-extension</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose FlashMask, an extension of FlashAttention that introduces a column-wise sparse representation of attention masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashmask-efficient-and-rich-mask-extension</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Zero-Shot Learning for Visual Dehazing of Urological Surgical Robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-zero-shot-learning-for-visual-dehazing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we organize and propose a dehaze dataset for robotic vision in urological surgery (USRobot-Dehaze dataset).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-zero-shot-learning-for-visual-dehazing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perceptual Piercing: Human Visual Cue-based Object Detection in Low Visibility Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perceptual-piercing-human-visual-cue-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The findings offer a viable solution for enhancing object detection in poor visibility and contribute to the broader understanding of integrating human visual principles into deep learning algorithms for intricate visual recognition challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perceptual-piercing-human-visual-cue-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Codev-Bench: How Do LLMs Understand Developer-Centric Code Completion?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codev-bench-how-do-llms-understand-developer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Code completion, a key downstream task in code generation, is one of the most frequent and impactful methods for enhancing developer productivity in software development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codev-bench-how-do-llms-understand-developer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EUFCC-CIR: a Composed Image Retrieval Dataset for GLAM Collections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eufcc-cir-a-composed-image-retrieval-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The intersection of Artificial Intelligence and Digital Humanities enables researchers to explore cultural heritage collections with greater depth and scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eufcc-cir-a-composed-image-retrieval-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiraGe: Editable 2D Images using Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mirage-editable-2d-images-using-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach improves the rendering quality and allows realistic image modifications, including human-inspired perception of photos in the 3D world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mirage-editable-2d-images-using-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake It Until You Break It: On the Adversarial Robustness of AI-generated Image Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fake-it-until-you-break-it-on-the-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While generative AI (GenAI) offers countless possibilities for creative and productive tasks, artificially generated media can be misused for fraud, manipulation, scams, misinformation campaigns, and more.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fake-it-until-you-break-it-on-the-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EAB-FL: Exacerbating Algorithmic Bias through Model Poisoning Attacks in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eab-fl-exacerbating-algorithmic-bias-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new type of model poisoning attack, EAB-FL, with a focus on exacerbating group unfairness while maintaining a good level of model utility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eab-fl-exacerbating-algorithmic-bias-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Spark of Vision-Language Intelligence: 2-Dimensional Autoregressive Transformer for Efficient Finegrained Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-spark-of-vision-language-intelligence-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work tackles the information loss bottleneck of vector-quantization (VQ) autoregressive image generation by introducing a novel model architecture called the 2-Dimensional Autoregression (DnD) Transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-spark-of-vision-language-intelligence-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depth Pro: Sharp Monocular Metric Depth in Less Than a Second</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-pro-sharp-monocular-metric-depth-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a foundation model for zero-shot metric monocular depth estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-pro-sharp-monocular-metric-depth-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Visual and Textual Inputs for Searching Large-Scale Map Collections with CLIP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-visual-and-textual-inputs-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the prevalence and historical importance of maps in digital collections, current methods of navigating and exploring map collections are largely restricted to catalog records and structured metadata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-visual-and-textual-inputs-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
