<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 21:07:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>LTE4G: Long-Tail Experts for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lte4g-long-tail-experts-for-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After having trained an expert for each balanced subset, we adopt knowledge distillation to obtain two class-wise students, i. e., Head class student and Tail class student, each of which is responsible for classifying nodes in the head classes and tail classes, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lte4g-long-tail-experts-for-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FairDisCo: Fairer AI in Dermatology via Disentanglement Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairdisco-fairer-ai-in-dermatology-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning models have achieved great success in automating skin lesion diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairdisco-fairer-ai-in-dermatology-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuro-Symbolic Visual Dialog</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-visual-dialog</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Neuro-Symbolic Visual Dialog (NSVD) -the first method to combine deep learning and symbolic program execution for multi-round visually-grounded reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-visual-dialog</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Temporal Structures of Cyclostationary Signals for Data-Driven Single-Channel Source Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-temporal-structures-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of single-channel source separation (SCSS), and focus on cyclostationary signals, which are particularly suitable in a variety of application domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-temporal-structures-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorporating Rivalry in Reinforcement Learning for a Competitive Game</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-rivalry-in-reinforcement-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in reinforcement learning with social agents have allowed such models to achieve human-level performance on specific interaction tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-rivalry-in-reinforcement-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient-level Microsatellite Stability Assessment from Whole Slide Images By Combining Momentum Contrast Learning and Group Patch Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patient-level-microsatellite-stability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the high resolution of WSI practically prevent direct classification of the entire WSI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patient-level-microsatellite-stability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Adaptive Threshold based Learning for Noisy Annotations Robust Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-adaptive-threshold-based-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To handle noisy annotations, we propose a dynamic FER learning framework (DNFER) in which clean samples are selected based on dynamic class specific threshold during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-adaptive-threshold-based-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repurposing Knowledge Graph Embeddings for Triple Representation via Weak Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repurposing-knowledge-graph-embeddings-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The majority of knowledge graph embedding techniques treat entities and predicates as separate embedding matrices, using aggregation functions to build a representation of the input triple.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repurposing-knowledge-graph-embeddings-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-supervised classification using a supervised autoencoder for biomedical applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-classification-using-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments show that the SSAE outperforms Label Propagation and Spreading and the Fully Connected Neural Network both on a synthetic dataset and on two real-world biological datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-classification-using-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-quality Task Division for Large-scale Entity Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-quality-task-division-for-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To include in the EA subtasks a high proportion of the potential mappings originally present in the large EA task, we devise a counterpart discovery method that exploits the locality principle of the EA task and the power of trained EA models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-quality-task-division-for-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Granularity Distillation Scheme Towards Lightweight Semi-Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-distillation-scheme-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consequently, we offer the first attempt to provide lightweight SSSS models via a novel multi-granularity distillation (MGD) scheme, where multi-granularity is captured from three aspects: i) complementary teacher structure; ii) labeled-unlabeled data cooperative distillation; iii) hierarchical and multi-levels loss setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-distillation-scheme-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inductive Knowledge Graph Reasoning for Multi-batch Emerging Entities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inductive-knowledge-graph-reasoning-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a walk-based inductive reasoning model to tackle the new setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inductive-knowledge-graph-reasoning-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Baseline for Multi-Camera 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-baseline-for-multi-camera-3d-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we extract multi-scale features and generate the perspective object proposals on each monocular image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-baseline-for-multi-camera-3d-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A simple learning agent interacting with an agent-based market model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-learning-agent-interacting-with-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the learning dynamics of a single reinforcement learning optimal execution trading agent when it interacts with an event driven agent-based financial market model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-learning-agent-interacting-with-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProtoPFormer: Concentrating on Prototypical Parts in Vision Transformers for Interpretable Image Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/protopformer-concentrating-on-prototypical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The global prototypes are adopted to provide the global view of objects to guide local prototypes to concentrate on the foreground while eliminating the influence of the background.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/protopformer-concentrating-on-prototypical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Calibrated Hyper-Sphere Representation via Distribution Overlap Coefficient for Long-tailed Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-calibrated-hyper-sphere</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our knowledge, this is the first work to measure representation quality of classifiers and features from the perspective of distribution overlap coefficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-calibrated-hyper-sphere</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shapelet-Based Counterfactual Explanations for Multivariate Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapelet-based-counterfactual-explanations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we take advantage of the inherent interpretability of shapelets to develop a model agnostic multivariate time series (MTS) counterfactual explanation algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapelet-based-counterfactual-explanations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GENEA Challenge 2022: A large evaluation of data-driven co-speech gesture generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-genea-challenge-2022-a-large-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, all synthetic motion is found to be vastly less appropriate for the speech than the original motion-capture recordings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-genea-challenge-2022-a-large-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Branched Fusion and Orthogonal Projection for Face-Voice Association</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-branched-fusion-and-orthogonal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we leverage cross-modal verification and matching tasks to analyze the impact of multiple languages on face-voice association.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-branched-fusion-and-orthogonal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVD-NAS: Coupling Low-Rank Approximation and Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svd-nas-coupling-low-rank-approximation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of compressing pre-trained Deep Neural Networks has attracted wide interest of the research community due to its great benefits in freeing practitioners from data access requirements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svd-nas-coupling-low-rank-approximation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Hypergraph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-hypergraph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many problems in computer vision and machine learning can be cast as learning on hypergraphs that represent higher-order relations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-hypergraph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoseBERT: A Generic Transformer Module for Temporal 3D Human Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posebert-a-generic-transformer-module-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is simple, generic and versatile, as it can be plugged on top of any image-based model to transform it in a video-based model leveraging temporal information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posebert-a-generic-transformer-module-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Easy to Hard: A Dual Curriculum Learning Framework for Context-Aware Document Ranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-easy-to-hard-a-dual-curriculum-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a curriculum learning framework for context-aware document ranking, in which the ranking model learns matching signals between the search context and the candidate document in an easy-to-hard manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-easy-to-hard-a-dual-curriculum-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image as a Foreign Language: BEiT Pretraining for All Vision and Vision-Language Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-as-a-foreign-language-beit-pretraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A big convergence of language, vision, and multimodal pretraining is emerging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-as-a-foreign-language-beit-pretraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Knowledge Distillation via Cross-Entropy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-knowledge-distillation-via-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we smooth students' target output to treat it as the soft target for training without teachers and propose a teacher-free new KD loss (tf-NKD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-knowledge-distillation-via-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survey of Machine Learning Techniques To Predict Heartbeat Arrhythmias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survey-of-machine-learning-techniques-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many works in biomedical computer science research use machine learning techniques to give accurate results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survey-of-machine-learning-techniques-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survey of Machine Learning Techniques To Predict Heartbeat Arrhythmias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survey-of-machine-learning-techniques-to-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many works in biomedical computer science research use machine learning techniques to give accurate results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survey-of-machine-learning-techniques-to-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWEM: Towards Real-Time Video Object Segmentation with Sequential Weighted Expectation-Maximization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swem-towards-real-time-video-object-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Matching-based methods, especially those based on space-time memory, are significantly ahead of other solutions in semi-supervised video object segmentation (VOS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swem-towards-real-time-video-object-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Multi-Task Learning Approach for Context-Sensitive Compound Type Identification in Sanskrit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-multi-task-learning-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The phenomenon of compounding is ubiquitous in Sanskrit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-multi-task-learning-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recent Advances in Text-to-SQL: A Survey of What We Have and What We Expect</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recent-advances-in-text-to-sql-a-survey-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-SQL has attracted attention from both the natural language processing and database communities because of its ability to convert the semantics in natural language into SQL queries and its practical application in building natural language interfaces to database systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recent-advances-in-text-to-sql-a-survey-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DP-Rewrite: Towards Reproducibility and Transparency in Differentially Private Text Rewriting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dp-rewrite-towards-reproducibility-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text rewriting with differential privacy (DP) provides concrete theoretical guarantees for protecting the privacy of individuals in textual documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dp-rewrite-towards-reproducibility-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locate Then Ask: Interpretable Stepwise Reasoning for Multi-hop Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locate-then-ask-interpretable-stepwise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an interpretable stepwise reasoning framework to incorporate both single-hop supporting sentence identification and single-hop question generation at each intermediate step, and utilize the inference of the current hop for the next until reasoning out the final result.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locate-then-ask-interpretable-stepwise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twin Papers: A Simple Framework of Causal Inference for Citations via Coupling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/twin-papers-a-simple-framework-of-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main difficulty in investigating the effects is that we need to know counterfactual results, which are not available in reality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/twin-papers-a-simple-framework-of-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Aspects of SHAP: Functional ANOVA for Model Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-aspects-of-shap-functional-anova</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use this connection to show that challenges in SHAP approximations largely relate to the choice of a feature distribution and the number of $2^p$ ANOVA terms estimated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-aspects-of-shap-functional-anova</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Graphical Model for Fusing Diverse Microbiome Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-graphical-model-for-fusing-diverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a computationally scalable variational Expectation-Maximization (EM) algorithm for inferring the latent variables and the parameters of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-graphical-model-for-fusing-diverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Node Classification on Graphs: Jointly from Bayesian Label Transition and Topology-based Label Propagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-node-classification-on-graphs-jointly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new label inference model, namely LInDT, which integrates both Bayesian label transition and topology-based label propagation for improving the robustness of GNNs against topological perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-node-classification-on-graphs-jointly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyche: A library for probabilistic reasoning and belief modelling in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tyche-a-library-for-probabilistic-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents Tyche, a Python library to facilitate probabilistic reasoning in uncertain worlds through the construction, querying, and learning of belief models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tyche-a-library-for-probabilistic-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparison-based Conversational Recommender System with Relative Bandit Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-based-conversational-recommender</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enable users to provide comparative preferences during conversational interactions, we propose a novel comparison-based conversational recommender system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-based-conversational-recommender</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring Sensitive Attributes from Model Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-sensitive-attributes-from-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We focus on the specific privacy risk of attribute inference attack wherein an adversary infers sensitive attributes of an input (e. g., race and sex) given its model explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-sensitive-attributes-from-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Know What You Do Not Know: Knowledge Graph Embedding via Co-distillation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-know-what-you-do-not-know-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose CoLE, a Co-distillation Learning method for KG Embedding that exploits the complementarity of graph structures and text information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-know-what-you-do-not-know-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MolGraph: a Python package for the implementation of small molecular graphs and graph neural networks with TensorFlow and Keras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molgraph-a-python-package-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Molecular machine learning (ML) has proven important for tackling various molecular problems, including the prediction of protein-drug interactions and blood brain-barrier permeability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molgraph-a-python-package-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastCPH: Efficient Survival Analysis for Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastcph-efficient-survival-analysis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Cox proportional hazards model is a canonical method in survival analysis for prediction of the life expectancy of a patient given clinical or genetic covariates -- it is a linear model in its original form.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastcph-efficient-survival-analysis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRETEL: Graph Contrastive Topic Enhanced Language Model for Long Document Extractive Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gretel-graph-contrastive-topic-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, neural topic models (NTMs) have been incorporated into pre-trained language models (PLMs), to capture the global semantic information for text summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gretel-graph-contrastive-topic-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Objects Can Move: 3D Change Detection by Geometric Transformation Constistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/objects-can-move-3d-change-detection-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AR/VR applications and robots need to know when the scene has changed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/objects-can-move-3d-change-detection-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A semi-supervised Teacher-Student framework for surgical tool detection and localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semi-supervised-teacher-student-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, in this paper we introduce a semi-supervised learning (SSL) framework in surgical tool detection paradigm which aims to mitigate the scarcity of training data and the data imbalance through a knowledge distillation approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semi-supervised-teacher-student-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Principled User-side Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-principled-user-side-recommender</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach opens the door to user-defined fair systems even if the official recommender system of the service is not fair.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-principled-user-side-recommender</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MockingBERT: A Method for Retroactively Adding Resilience to NLP Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mockingbert-a-method-for-retroactively-adding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Protecting NLP models against misspellings whether accidental or adversarial has been the object of research interest for the past few years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mockingbert-a-method-for-retroactively-adding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Weak-to-Strong Consistency in Semi-Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-weak-to-strong-consistency-in-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we revisit the weak-to-strong consistency framework, popularized by FixMatch from semi-supervised classification, where the prediction of a weakly perturbed image serves as supervision for its strongly perturbed version.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-weak-to-strong-consistency-in-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOV: Making Still Image Object Detectors Great at Video Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov-making-still-image-object-detectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the positive side, the detection in a certain frame of a video, compared with in a still image, can draw support from other frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov-making-still-image-object-detectors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persuasion Strategies in Advertisements: Dataset, Modeling, and Baselines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persuasion-strategies-in-advertisements</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by persuasion literature in social psychology and marketing, we introduce an extensive vocabulary of persuasion strategies and build the first ad image corpus annotated with persuasion strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persuasion-strategies-in-advertisements</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
