<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 21:07:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MMFN: Multi-Modal-Fusion-Net for End-to-End Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmfn-multi-modal-fusion-net-for-end-to-end-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the fact that humans use diverse sensory organs to perceive the world, sensors with different modalities are deployed in end-to-end driving to obtain the global context of the 3D scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmfn-multi-modal-fusion-net-for-end-to-end-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TopicFM: Robust and Interpretable Feature Matching with Topic-assisted</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topicfm-robust-and-interpretable-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an architecture for image matching which is efficient, robust, and interpretable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topicfm-robust-and-interpretable-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer-aided Tuberculosis Diagnosis with Attribute Reasoning Assistance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computer-aided-tuberculosis-diagnosis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although deep learning algorithms have been intensively developed for computer-aided tuberculosis diagnosis (CTD), they mainly depend on carefully annotated datasets, leading to much time and resource consumption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computer-aided-tuberculosis-diagnosis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modular Lifelong Reinforcement Learning via Neural Composition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modular-lifelong-reinforcement-learning-via-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirically, we demonstrate that neural composition indeed captures the underlying structure of this space of problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modular-lifelong-reinforcement-learning-via-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Understanding-Oriented Robust Machine Reading Comprehension Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-understanding-oriented-robust-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an understanding-oriented machine reading comprehension model to address three kinds of robustness issues, which are over sensitivity, over stability and generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-understanding-oriented-robust-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MotionMixer: MLP-based 3D Human Body Pose Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motionmixer-mlp-based-3d-human-body-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a stacked sequence of 3D body poses, a spatial-MLP extracts fine grained spatial dependencies of the body joints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motionmixer-mlp-based-3d-human-body-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Explainers: Black-Box Explainable Machine Learning for Student Success Prediction in MOOCs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-explainers-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks are ubiquitous in applied machine learning for education.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-explainers-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pile of Law: Learning Responsible Data Filtering from the Law and a 256GB Open-Source Legal Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pile-of-law-learning-responsible-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One concern with the rise of large language models lies with their potential for significant harm, particularly from pretraining on biased, obscene, copyrighted, and private information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pile-of-law-learning-responsible-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local manifold learning and its link to domain-based physics knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-manifold-learning-and-its-link-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show that PCA applied in local clusters of data (local PCA) is capable of detecting the intrinsic parameterization of the thermo-chemical state-space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-manifold-learning-and-its-link-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-features based Semantic Augmentation Networks for Named Entity Recognition in Threat Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-features-based-semantic-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extracting cybersecurity entities such as attackers and vulnerabilities from unstructured network texts is an important part of security analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-features-based-semantic-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VL-CheckList: Evaluating Pre-trained Vision-Language Models with Objects, Attributes and Relations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vl-checklist-evaluating-pre-trained-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the CheckList for testing natural language processing, we introduce VL-CheckList, a novel framework to understand the capabilities of VLP models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vl-checklist-evaluating-pre-trained-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video + CLIP Baseline for Ego4D Long-term Action Anticipation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-clip-baseline-for-ego4d-long-term</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The CLIP embedding provides fine-grained understanding of objects relevant for an action whereas the slowfast network is responsible for modeling temporal information within a video clip of few frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-clip-baseline-for-ego4d-long-term</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FitHuBERT: Going Thinner and Deeper for Knowledge Distillation of Speech Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fithubert-going-thinner-and-deeper-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method reduces the model to 23. 8% in size and 35. 9% in inference time compared to HuBERT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fithubert-going-thinner-and-deeper-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offset equivariant networks and their applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offset-equivariant-networks-and-their</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present a framework for the design and implementation of offset equivariant networks, that is, neural networks that preserve in their output uniform increments in the input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offset-equivariant-networks-and-their</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIAFusion: A progressive infrared and visible image fusion network based on illumination aware</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/piafusion-a-progressive-infrared-and-visible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we utilize the illumination probability to construct an illumination-aware loss to guide the training of the fusion network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/piafusion-a-progressive-infrared-and-visible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting the Mean Teacher for keypoint-based lung registration under geometric domain shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-the-mean-teacher-for-keypoint-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We build on a keypoint-based registration model, combining graph convolutions for geometric feature learning with loopy belief optimization, and propose to reduce the domain shift through self-ensembling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-the-mean-teacher-for-keypoint-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Far Can I Go ? : A Self-Supervised Approach for Deterministic Video Depth Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-can-i-go-a-self-supervised-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike previous methods, we model the depth estimation of the unobserved frame as a view-synthesis problem, which treats the depth estimate of the unseen video frame as an auxiliary task while synthesizing back the views using learned pose.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-can-i-go-a-self-supervised-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Dataset and A Baseline Model for Breast Lesion Detection in Ultrasound Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-dataset-and-a-baseline-model-for-breast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we learn video-level features to classify the breast lesions of the original video as benign or malignant lesions to further enhance the final breast lesion detection performance in ultrasound videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-dataset-and-a-baseline-model-for-breast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing cluster analysis via topological manifold learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-cluster-analysis-via-topological</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discuss topological aspects of cluster analysis and show that inferring the topological structure of a dataset before clustering it can considerably enhance cluster detection: theoretical arguments and empirical evidence show that clustering embedding vectors, representing the structure of a data manifold instead of the observed feature vectors themselves, is highly beneficial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-cluster-analysis-via-topological</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifelong Inverse Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelong-inverse-reinforcement-learning-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods for learning from demonstration (LfD) have shown success in acquiring behavior policies by imitating a user.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelong-inverse-reinforcement-learning-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Speech Enhancement through Fine-Grained Speech Characteristics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-speech-enhancement-through-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first identify key acoustic parameters that have been found to correlate well with voice quality (e. g. jitter, shimmer, and spectral flux) and then propose objective functions which are aimed at reducing the difference between clean speech and enhanced speech with respect to these features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-speech-enhancement-through-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modelling Users with Item Metadata for Explainable and Interactive Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelling-users-with-item-metadata-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The more interpretable the profile and this "matching function" are, the easier it is to provide users with accurate and intuitive explanations, and also to let them interact with the system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelling-users-with-item-metadata-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable MCMC Sampling for Nonsymmetric Determinantal Point Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-mcmc-sampling-for-nonsymmetric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop a scalable MCMC sampling algorithm for $k$-NDPPs with low-rank kernels, thus enabling runtime that is sublinear in $n$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-mcmc-sampling-for-nonsymmetric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is neural language acquisition similar to natural? A chronological probing study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-neural-language-acquisition-similar-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The probing methodology allows one to obtain a partial representation of linguistic phenomena stored in the inner layers of the neural network, using external classifiers and statistical analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-neural-language-acquisition-similar-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Pre-training for Navigation: What Can We Learn from Noise?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-pre-training-for-navigation-what-can</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hypothesize a sufficient representation of the current view and the goal view for a navigation policy can be learned by predicting the location and size of a crop of the current view that corresponds to the goal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-pre-training-for-navigation-what-can</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Unsupervised Domain Adaptation for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-unsupervised-domain-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The existing studies stick to the basic assumption that no labeled sample is available for the new domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-unsupervised-domain-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performative Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performative-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the framework of performative reinforcement learning where the policy chosen by the learner affects the underlying reward and transition dynamics of the environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performative-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color-aware two-branch DCNN for efficient plant disease classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-aware-two-branch-dcnn-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep convolutional neural networks (DCNNs) have been successfully applied to plant disease detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-aware-two-branch-dcnn-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Learning with Deep Tabular Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-with-deep-tabular-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we demonstrate that upstream data gives tabular neural networks a decisive advantage over widely used GBDT models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-with-deep-tabular-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BigBIO: A Framework for Data-Centric Biomedical Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bigbio-a-framework-for-data-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training and evaluating language models increasingly requires the construction of meta-datasets --diverse collections of curated data with clear provenance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bigbio-a-framework-for-data-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Instance-Level Impact of Fairness Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-instance-level-impact-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A variety of fairness constraints have been proposed in the literature to mitigate group-level statistical bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-instance-level-impact-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Copilot AI pair programmer: Asset or Liability?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/github-copilot-ai-pair-programmer-asset-or</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the capabilities of Copilot in two different programming tasks: (1) generating (and reproducing) correct and efficient solutions for fundamental algorithmic problems, and (2) comparing Copilot's proposed solutions with those of human programmers on a set of programming tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/github-copilot-ai-pair-programmer-asset-or</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Functions on Multiple Sets using Multi-Set Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-functions-on-multiple-sets-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a general deep architecture for learning functions on multiple permutation-invariant sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-functions-on-multiple-sets-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuASK -- Quantum Advantage Seeker with Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quask-quantum-advantage-seeker-with-kernels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[QuASK is a quantum machine learning software written in Python that supports researchers in designing, experimenting, and assessing different quantum and classical kernels performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quask-quantum-advantage-seeker-with-kernels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Learning and Learnablity of Quasimetrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-learning-and-learnablity-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, our proposed Poisson Quasimetric Embedding (PQE) is the first quasimetric learning formulation that both is learnable with gradient-based optimization and enjoys strong performance guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-learning-and-learnablity-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoised MDPs: Learning World Models Better Than the World Itself</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoised-mdps-learning-world-models-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to separate signal from noise, and reason with clean abstractions, is critical to intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoised-mdps-learning-world-models-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking the Robustness of Deep Neural Networks to Common Corruptions in Digital Pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-the-robustness-of-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluated on two resulting benchmark datasets, we find that (1) a variety of deep neural network models suffer from a significant accuracy decrease (double the error on clean images) and the unreliable confidence estimation on corrupted images; (2) A low correlation between the validation and test errors while replacing the validation set with our benchmark can increase the correlation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-the-robustness-of-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting Future World Events with Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-future-world-events-with-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We test language models on our forecasting task and find that performance is far below a human expert baseline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-future-world-events-with-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZeroC: A Neuro-Symbolic Model for Zero-shot Concept Recognition and Acquisition at Inference Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zeroc-a-neuro-symbolic-model-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Zero-shot Concept Recognition and Acquisition (ZeroC), a neuro-symbolic architecture that can recognize and acquire novel concepts in a zero-shot way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zeroc-a-neuro-symbolic-model-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Part-Of-Speech Model: Does Modeling Long Context Help Unsupervised POS-tagging?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-part-of-speech-model-does-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MPoSM can model arbitrary tag dependency and perform POS induction through the objective of masked POS reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-part-of-speech-model-does-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmark Dataset for Precipitation Forecasting by Post-Processing the Numerical Weather Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-dataset-for-precipitation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a hybrid NWP-DL workflow to fill the gap between standalone NWP and DL approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-dataset-for-precipitation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnoShift: A Distribution Shift Benchmark for Unsupervised Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anoshift-a-distribution-shift-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We validate the performance degradation over time with diverse models (MLM to classical Isolation Forest).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anoshift-a-distribution-shift-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable K-FAC Training for Deep Neural Networks with Distributed Preconditioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-k-fac-training-for-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The second-order optimization methods, notably the D-KFAC (Distributed Kronecker Factored Approximate Curvature) algorithms, have gained traction on accelerating deep neural network (DNN) training on GPU clusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-k-fac-training-for-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Ensemble Distillation With Weight Averaging and Diversifying Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-ensemble-distillation-with-weight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ensembles of deep neural networks have demonstrated superior performance, but their heavy computational cost hinders applying them for resource-limited environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-ensemble-distillation-with-weight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laplacian Autoencoders for Learning Stochastic Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplacian-autoencoders-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representation learning has become a practical family of methods for building rich parametric codifications of massive high-dimensional data while succeeding in the reconstruction side.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplacian-autoencoders-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Randomized K-FACs: Speeding up K-FAC with Randomized Numerical Linear Algebra</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randomized-k-facs-speeding-up-k-fac-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we theoretically show that, owing to the exponential-average construction paradigm of the Kronecker factors that is typically used, their eigen-spectrum must decay.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randomized-k-facs-speeding-up-k-fac-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEAD: A Multi-Armed Approach for Evaluation of Adversarial Examples Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mead-a-multi-armed-approach-for-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detection of adversarial examples has been a hot topic in the last years due to its importance for safely deploying machine learning algorithms in critical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mead-a-multi-armed-approach-for-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HRFuser: A Multi-resolution Sensor Fusion Architecture for 2D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrfuser-a-multi-resolution-sensor-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides standard cameras, autonomous vehicles typically include multiple additional sensors, such as lidars and radars, which help acquire richer information for perceiving the content of the driving scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrfuser-a-multi-resolution-sensor-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Anomaly Detection in Echocardiograms with Dynamic Variational Trajectory Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-anomaly-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel anomaly detection method for echocardiogram videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-anomaly-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified End-to-End Retriever-Reader Framework for Knowledge-based VQA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-end-to-end-retriever-reader</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, pertaining to the implicit knowledge, the multi-modal implicit knowledge for knowledge-based VQA still remains largely unexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-end-to-end-retriever-reader</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
