<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 21:08:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>GNN Applied to Ego-nets for Friend Suggestions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnn-applied-to-ego-nets-for-friend</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we develop the WalkGNN model which is capable of working effectively in the social network domain, where these graph-level link prediction tasks are heterogeneous, dynamic and featureless.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnn-applied-to-ego-nets-for-friend</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMI-Net: Adaptive Mask Inpainting Network for Industrial Anomaly Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ami-net-adaptive-mask-inpainting-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this manner, the model can leverage the visible normal global contextual information to restore the masked anomalous regions, thereby effectively suppressing the reconstruction of defects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ami-net-adaptive-mask-inpainting-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vertical Federated Unlearning via Backdoor Certification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vertical-federated-unlearning-via-backdoor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an innovative modification to traditional VFL by employing a mechanism that inverts the typical learning trajectory with the objective of extracting specific data contributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vertical-federated-unlearning-via-backdoor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VersaGen: Unleashing Versatile Visual Control for Text-to-Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/versagen-unleashing-versatile-visual-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the rapid advancements in text-to-image (T2I) synthesis, enabling precise visual control remains a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/versagen-unleashing-versatile-visual-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RL-LLM-DT: An Automatic Decision Tree Generation Method Based on RL Evaluation and LLM Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-llm-dt-an-automatic-decision-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After iterative refinements, our curling AI based on the decision tree ranks first on the Jidi platform among 34 curling AIs in total, which demonstrates that LLMs can significantly enhance the robustness and adaptability of decision trees, representing a substantial advancement in the field of Game AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-llm-dt-an-automatic-decision-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just a Simple Transformation is Enough for Data Protection in Vertical Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/just-a-simple-transformation-is-enough-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vertical Federated Learning (VFL) aims to enable collaborative training of deep learning models while maintaining privacy protection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/just-a-simple-transformation-is-enough-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Domain Adaptive Object Detection via Dual Probabilistic Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-domain-adaptive-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[IDSA utilizes instance-level sampling to mine domain-shared category samples and calculates alignment weight through Gaussian distribution to conduct the domain-shared category domain alignment to address the feature heterogeneity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-domain-adaptive-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biased or Flawed? Mitigating Stereotypes in Generative Language Models by Addressing Task-Specific Flaws</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biased-or-flawed-mitigating-stereotypes-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, when a model misinterprets a text and produces a response that reinforces a stereotype, it becomes difficult to determine whether the issue arises from inherent bias or from a misunderstanding of the given content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biased-or-flawed-mitigating-stereotypes-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D$^2$-Actor: Learning Pose-Conditioned 3D-Aware Denoiser for Realistic Gaussian Avatar Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-2-actor-learning-pose-conditioned-3d-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advancements in neural implicit representations and differentiable rendering have markedly improved the ability to learn animatable 3D avatars from sparse multi-view RGB videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-2-actor-learning-pose-conditioned-3d-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Semantic Consistency and Style Diversity for Domain Generalized Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-semantic-consistency-and-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we introduce a novel framework, named SCSD for Semantic Consistency prediction and Style Diversity generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-semantic-consistency-and-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual and Explainable Text Detoxification with Parallel Corpora</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-and-explainable-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even with various regulations in place across countries and social media platforms (Government of India, 2021; European Parliament and Council of the European Union, 2022, digital abusive speech remains a significant issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-and-explainable-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPGL: Enhancing Session-based Recommendation with Single Positive Graph Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spgl-enhancing-session-based-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It also takes into account the reverse positional information of items when constructing session representations to incorporate temporal information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spgl-enhancing-session-based-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-View Geo-Localization with Street-View and VHR Satellite Imagery in Decentrality Settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-view-geo-localization-with-street-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BIM uses bird's-eye view images derived from street-view panoramas as an intermediary, simplifying the cross-view challenge with decentrality to a cross-view problem and a decentrality problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-view-geo-localization-with-street-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skip Tuning: Pre-trained Vision-Language Models are Effective and Efficient Adapters Themselves</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skip-tuning-pre-trained-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompt tuning (PT) has long been recognized as an effective and efficient paradigm for transferring large pre-trained vision-language models (VLMs) to downstream tasks by learning a tiny set of context vectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skip-tuning-pre-trained-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Mapper Algorithm with implicit intervals and its optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mapper-algorithm-with-implicit-intervals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Variants of the standard Mapper algorithms have been developed to address these limitations, yet most of them still require manual tuning of parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mapper-algorithm-with-implicit-intervals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future Sight and Tough Fights: Revolutionizing Sequential Recommendation with FENRec</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/future-sight-and-tough-fights-revolutionizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sequential recommendation (SR) systems predict user preferences by analyzing time-ordered interaction sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/future-sight-and-tough-fights-revolutionizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmark and Robustness Study of In-Context-Learning with Large Language Models in Music Entity Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-and-robustness-study-of-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advent of large language models (LLMs), these outperform SLMs in a variety of downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-and-robustness-study-of-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constructing Confidence Intervals for Average Treatment Effects from Multiple Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-confidence-intervals-for-average</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Constructing confidence intervals (CIs) for the average treatment effect (ATE) from patient records is crucial to assess the effectiveness and safety of drugs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-confidence-intervals-for-average</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Random Features for Scalable Interpolation of Spatiotemporal Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-random-features-for-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While deep GPs can overcome this issue, training and making inference with them are difficult, again requiring crude approximations via inducing points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-random-features-for-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No More Adam: Learning Rate Scaling at Initialization is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-more-adam-learning-rate-scaling-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By adjusting learning rates without relying on adaptive second-order momentum, SGD-SaI helps prevent training imbalances from the very first iteration and cuts the optimizer's memory usage by half compared to AdamW.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-more-adam-learning-rate-scaling-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Slow Gradient Approximation for Binary Neural Network Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-slow-gradient-approximation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, hypernetwork based methods, which utilize neural networks to learn the gradients of non-differentiable quantization functions, have emerged as a promising approach due to their adaptive learning capabilities to reduce estimation errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-slow-gradient-approximation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Re-Attentional Controllable Video Diffusion Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-attentional-controllable-video-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, the controllability of video editing remains a formidable challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-attentional-controllable-video-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asymmetric Learning for Spectral Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymmetric-learning-for-spectral-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on eighteen benchmark datasets show that asymmetric learning consistently improves the performance of spectral GNNs for both heterophilic and homophilic graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymmetric-learning-for-spectral-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPQ-DM: Mixed Precision Quantization for Extremely Low Bit Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpq-dm-mixed-precision-quantization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the existing quantization methods for diffusion models still cause severe degradation in performance, especially under extremely low bit-widths (2-4 bit).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpq-dm-mixed-precision-quantization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SepLLM: Accelerate Large Language Models by Compressing One Segment into One Separator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sepllm-accelerate-large-language-models-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This observation suggests that information of the segments between these separator tokens can be effectively condensed into the separator tokens themselves without significant information loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sepllm-accelerate-large-language-models-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Flow Is All You Need to Sample Out-of-Distribution Chemical Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-flow-is-all-you-need-to-sample-out</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating novel molecules with higher properties than the training space, namely the out-of-distribution generation, is important for ${de~novo}$ drug design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-flow-is-all-you-need-to-sample-out</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Unscented Kalman Filter Architecture for Sensor Fusion in Water Networks Leak Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-unscented-kalman-filter-architecture-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leakage in water systems results in significant daily water losses, degrading service quality, increasing costs, and aggravating environmental problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-unscented-kalman-filter-architecture-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the Original Appearance of Damaged Historical Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-original-appearance-of-damaged</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Historical documents encompass a wealth of cultural treasures but suffer from severe damages including character missing, paper damage, and ink erosion over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-original-appearance-of-damaged</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making FETCH! Happen: Finding Emergent Dog Whistles Through Common Habitats</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-fetch-happen-finding-emergent-dog</link>
      <description><![CDATA[WARNING: This paper contains content that maybe upsetting or offensive to some readers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-fetch-happen-finding-emergent-dog</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HGSFusion: Radar-Camera Fusion with Hybrid Generation and Synchronization for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgsfusion-radar-camera-fusion-with-hybrid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, in this paper, we present the radar-camera fusion network with Hybrid Generation and Synchronization (HGSFusion), designed to better fuse radar potentials and image features for 3D object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgsfusion-radar-camera-fusion-with-hybrid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoothness Really Matters: A Simple yet Effective Approach for Unsupervised Graph Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smoothness-really-matters-a-simple-yet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the sensitivity of GNNs to local structural features, even slight discrepancies between source and target graphs could lead to significant shifts in node embeddings, thereby reducing the effectiveness of knowledge transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smoothness-really-matters-a-simple-yet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VG-TVP: Multimodal Procedural Planning via Visually Grounded Text-Video Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vg-tvp-multimodal-procedural-planning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[They allow LLMs to guide the generation of visually-grounded text plans and textual-grounded video plans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vg-tvp-multimodal-procedural-planning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StrandHead: Text to Strand-Disentangled 3D Head Avatars Using Hair Geometric Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strandhead-text-to-strand-disentangled-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose StrandHead, a novel text to 3D head avatar generation method capable of generating disentangled 3D hair with strand representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strandhead-text-to-strand-disentangled-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Writer Retrieval with Chinese Handwritten Phrases: A Synergistic Temporal-Frequency Representation Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-writer-retrieval-with-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, to address data deficit, we introduce OLIWER, a large-scale online writer retrieval dataset encompassing over 670, 000 Chinese handwritten phrases from 1, 731 individuals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-writer-retrieval-with-chinese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DriveGazen: Event-Based Driving Status Recognition using Conventional Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivegazen-event-based-driving-status</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, our method is the first to utilize guide attention spiking neural networks and eye-based event frames generated from conventional cameras for driving status recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivegazen-event-based-driving-status</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhysAug: A Physical-guided and Frequency-based Data Augmentation for Single-Domain Generalized Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physaug-a-physical-guided-and-frequency-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Single-Domain Generalized Object Detection~(S-DGOD) aims to train on a single source domain for robust performance across a variety of unseen target domains by taking advantage of an object detector.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physaug-a-physical-guided-and-frequency-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Findings of the WMT 2024 Shared Task on Discourse-Level Literary Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/findings-of-the-wmt-2024-shared-task-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Following last year, we have continued to host the WMT translation shared task this year, the second edition of the Discourse-Level Literary Translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/findings-of-the-wmt-2024-shared-task-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One for Dozens: Adaptive REcommendation for All Domains with Counterfactual Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-for-dozens-adaptive-recommendation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AREAD employs a hierarchical structure with a limited number of expert networks at several layers, to effectively capture domain knowledge at different granularities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-for-dozens-adaptive-recommendation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCITAT: A Question Answering Benchmark for Scientific Tables and Text Covering Diverse Reasoning Types</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scitat-a-question-answering-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose a QA benchmark for scientific tables and text with diverse reasoning types (SciTaT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scitat-a-question-answering-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are the Latent Representations of Foundation Models for Pathology Invariant to Rotation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-the-latent-representations-of-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised foundation models for digital pathology encode small patches from H\&E whole slide images into latent representations used for downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-the-latent-representations-of-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SegMAN: Omni-scale Context Modeling with State Space Models and Local Attention for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segman-omni-scale-context-modeling-with-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-quality semantic segmentation relies on three key capabilities: global context modeling, local detail encoding, and multi-scale feature extraction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segman-omni-scale-context-modeling-with-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emma-X: An Embodied Multimodal Action Model with Grounded Chain of Thought and Look-ahead Spatial Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emma-x-an-embodied-multimodal-action-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional reinforcement learning-based robotic control methods are often task-specific and fail to generalize across diverse environments or unseen objects and instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emma-x-an-embodied-multimodal-action-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glimpse: Enabling White-Box Methods to Use Proprietary Models for Zero-Shot LLM-Generated Text Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glimpse-enabling-white-box-methods-to-use</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advanced large language models (LLMs) can generate text almost indistinguishable from human-written text, highlighting the importance of LLM-generated text detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glimpse-enabling-white-box-methods-to-use</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runtime Analysis for Multi-Objective Evolutionary Algorithms in Unbounded Integer Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/runtime-analysis-for-multi-objective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, the vast majority of these results regard problems with binary or continuous decision variables -- the theoretical analysis of randomized search heuristics for unbounded integer domains is almost nonexistent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/runtime-analysis-for-multi-objective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Inter-Intra Heterogeneity for Graph Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-inter-intra-heterogeneity-for-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose a novel Federated learning method by integrally modeling the Inter-Intra Heterogeneity (FedIIH).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-inter-intra-heterogeneity-for-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicit and Implicit Graduated Optimization in Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-and-implicit-graduated-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graduated optimization is a global optimization technique that is used to minimize a multimodal nonconvex function by smoothing the objective function with noise and gradually refining the solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-and-implicit-graduated-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Does ChatGPT "Delve" So Much? Exploring the Sources of Lexical Overrepresentation in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-does-chatgpt-delve-so-much-exploring-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then pose "the puzzle of lexical overrepresentation": WHY are such words overused by LLMs?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-does-chatgpt-delve-so-much-exploring-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUENCH: Measuring the gap between Indic and Non-Indic Contextual General Reasoning in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quench-measuring-the-gap-between-indic-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise of large language models (LLMs) has created a need for advanced benchmarking systems beyond traditional setups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quench-measuring-the-gap-between-indic-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BioBridge: Unified Bio-Embedding with Bridging Modality in Code-Switched EMR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biobridge-unified-bio-embedding-with-bridging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pediatric Emergency Department (PED) overcrowding presents a significant global challenge, prompting the need for efficient solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biobridge-unified-bio-embedding-with-bridging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining Large Language Models with Tutoring System Intelligence: A Case Study in Caregiver Homework Support</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-large-language-models-with-tutoring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We contribute insights into how tutoring systems can best be merged with LLMs to support hybrid tutoring settings through conversational assistance, facilitating effective caregiver involvement in tutoring systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-large-language-models-with-tutoring</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
