<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:06:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing social network hate detection using back translation and GPT-3 augmentations during training and test-time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-social-network-hate-detection-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Social media platforms have become an essential means of communication, but they also serve as a breeding ground for hateful content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-social-network-hate-detection-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Quantification via Spatial-Temporal Tweedie Model for Zero-inflated and Long-tail Travel Demand Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-via-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[crucial for transportation management.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-via-spatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jumanji: a Diverse Suite of Scalable Reinforcement Learning Environments in JAX</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jumanji-a-diverse-suite-of-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-source reinforcement learning (RL) environments have played a crucial role in driving progress in the development of AI algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jumanji-a-diverse-suite-of-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheffield's Submission to the AmericasNLP Shared Task on Machine Translation into Indigenous Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sheffield-s-submission-to-the-americasnlp</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we describe the University of Sheffield's submission to the AmericasNLP 2023 Shared Task on Machine Translation into Indigenous Languages which comprises the translation from Spanish to eleven indigenous languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sheffield-s-submission-to-the-americasnlp</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listener Model for the PhotoBook Referential Game with CLIPScores as Implicit Reference Chain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/listener-model-for-the-photobook-referential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PhotoBook is a collaborative dialogue game where two players receive private, partially-overlapping sets of images and resolve which images they have in common.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/listener-model-for-the-photobook-referential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full Parameter Fine-tuning for Large Language Models with Limited Resources</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/full-parameter-fine-tuning-for-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have revolutionized Natural Language Processing (NLP) but demand massive GPU resources for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/full-parameter-fine-tuning-for-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED$^{\rm FM}$: a Filtered and Multilingual Relation Extraction Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/red-rm-fm-a-filtered-and-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Relation Extraction (RE) is a task that identifies relationships between entities in a text, enabling the acquisition of relational facts and bridging the gap between natural language and structured knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/red-rm-fm-a-filtered-and-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LabelBench: A Comprehensive Framework for Benchmarking Label-Efficient Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/labelbench-a-comprehensive-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Labeled data are critical to modern machine learning applications, but obtaining labels can be expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/labelbench-a-comprehensive-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-Resolution Radar Imaging with Sparse Arrays Using a Deep Neural Network Trained with Enhanced Virtual Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolution-radar-imaging-with-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key to this performance is that the DNN is trained using realistic simulation data that perfectly mimic a given sparse antenna radar array hardware as the input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolution-radar-imaging-with-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Hypergraph Energy Functions to Hypergraph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-hypergraph-energy-functions-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hypergraphs are a powerful abstraction for representing higher-order interactions between entities of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-hypergraph-energy-functions-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FewSAR: A Few-shot SAR Image Classification Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fewsar-a-few-shot-sar-image-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this observation, we propose a novel few-shot SAR image classification benchmark (FewSAR) to address this issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fewsar-a-few-shot-sar-image-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FETNet: Feature Erasing and Transferring Network for Scene Text Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fetnet-feature-erasing-and-transferring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these problems, we propose a novel Feature Erasing and Transferring (FET) mechanism to reconfigure the encoded features for STR in this paper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fetnet-feature-erasing-and-transferring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using DUCK-Net for polyp image segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-duck-net-for-polyp-image-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel supervised convolutional neural network architecture, “DUCK-Net”, capable of effectively learning and generalizing from small amounts of medical images to perform accurate segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-duck-net-for-polyp-image-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient is All You Need?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-is-all-you-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The fundamental value of such link between CBO and SGD lies in the fact that CBO is provably globally convergent to global minimizers for ample classes of nonsmooth and nonconvex objective functions, hence, on the one side, offering a novel explanation for the success of stochastic relaxations of gradient descent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-is-all-you-need</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HomoGCL: Rethinking Homophily in Graph Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/homogcl-rethinking-homophily-in-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive learning (CL) has become the de-facto learning paradigm in self-supervised learning on graphs, which generally follows the "augmenting-contrasting" learning scheme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/homogcl-rethinking-homophily-in-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Domain Toxic Spans Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-toxic-spans-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the dynamic nature of toxic language use, automated methods for detecting toxic spans are likely to encounter distributional shift.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-toxic-spans-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP2Protect: Protecting Facial Privacy using Text-Guided Makeup via Adversarial Latent Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip2protect-protecting-facial-privacy-using-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel two-step approach for facial privacy protection that relies on finding adversarial latent codes in the low-dimensional manifold of a pretrained generative model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip2protect-protecting-facial-privacy-using-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Framework and Benchmarks for Combinatorial and Mixed-variable Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/framework-and-benchmarks-for-combinatorial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a modular framework for Mixed-variable and Combinatorial Bayesian Optimization (MCBO) to address the lack of systematic benchmarking and standardized evaluation in the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/framework-and-benchmarks-for-combinatorial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Hierarchical Bayesian Model for Deep Few-Shot Meta Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hierarchical-bayesian-model-for-deep-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel hierarchical Bayesian model for learning with a large (possibly infinite) number of tasks/episodes, which suits well the few-shot meta learning problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hierarchical-bayesian-model-for-deep-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly-Optimal Hierarchical Clustering for Well-Clustered Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nearly-optimal-hierarchical-clustering-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents two efficient hierarchical clustering (HC) algorithms with respect to Dasgupta's cost function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nearly-optimal-hierarchical-clustering-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discourse Representation Structure Parsing for Chinese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discourse-representation-structure-parsing-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous work has predominantly focused on monolingual English semantic parsing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discourse-representation-structure-parsing-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FALL-E: A Foley Sound Synthesis Model and Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fall-e-a-foley-sound-synthesis-model-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces FALL-E, a foley synthesis system and its training/inference strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fall-e-a-foley-sound-synthesis-model-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squeezing nnU-Nets with Knowledge Distillation for On-Board Cloud Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/squeezing-nnu-nets-with-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cloud detection is a pivotal satellite image pre-processing step that can be performed both on the ground and on board a satellite to tag useful images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/squeezing-nnu-nets-with-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subset Selection Based On Multiple Rankings in the Presence of Bias: Effectiveness of Fairness Constraints for Multiwinner Voting Score Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subset-selection-based-on-multiple-rankings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of subset selection where one is given multiple rankings of items and the goal is to select the highest ``quality'' subset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subset-selection-based-on-multiple-rankings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politeness Stereotypes and Attack Vectors: Gender Stereotypes in Japanese and Korean Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/politeness-stereotypes-and-attack-vectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Non-English bias research, however, is still in its infancy with most work focusing on English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/politeness-stereotypes-and-attack-vectors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amortized Inference for Gaussian Process Hyperparameters of Structured Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amortized-inference-for-gaussian-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose amortizing kernel parameter inference over a complete kernel-structure-family rather than a fixed kernel structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amortized-inference-for-gaussian-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphSHA: Synthesizing Harder Samples for Class-Imbalanced Node Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphsha-synthesizing-harder-samples-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Class imbalance is the phenomenon that some classes have much fewer instances than others, which is ubiquitous in real-world graph-structured scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphsha-synthesizing-harder-samples-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fedstellar: A Platform for Decentralized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedstellar-a-platform-for-decentralized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these challenges, this paper presents Fedstellar, a novel platform designed to train FL models in a decentralized, semi-decentralized, and centralized fashion across diverse federations of physical or virtualized devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedstellar-a-platform-for-decentralized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group Orthogonalization Regularization For Vision Models Adaptation and Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/group-orthogonalization-regularization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As neural networks become deeper, the redundancy within their parameters increases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/group-orthogonalization-regularization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BISCUIT: Causal Representation Learning from Binary Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biscuit-causal-representation-learning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identifying the causal variables of an environment and how to intervene on them is of core value in applications such as robotics and embodied AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biscuit-causal-representation-learning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do different tokenizers perform on downstream tasks in scriptio continua languages?: A case study in Japanese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-do-different-tokenizers-perform-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the effect of tokenizers on the downstream performance of pretrained language models (PLMs) in scriptio continua languages where no explicit spaces exist between words, using Japanese as a case study.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-do-different-tokenizers-perform-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structured Cooperative Learning with Graphical Model Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-cooperative-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose "Structured Cooperative Learning (SCooL)", in which a cooperation graph across devices is generated by a graphical model prior to automatically coordinate mutual learning between devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-cooperative-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of Speech Representations for MOS prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-speech-representations-for-mos</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Among the supervised and self-supervised learning models using BRSpeechMOS, Whisper-Small achieved the best linear correlation of 0. 6980, and the speaker verification model, SpeakerNet, had linear correlation of 0. 6963.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-speech-representations-for-mos</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MagicBrush: A Manually Annotated Dataset for Instruction-Guided Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magicbrush-a-manually-annotated-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we introduce MagicBrush (https://osu-nlp-group. github. io/MagicBrush/), the first large-scale, manually annotated dataset for instruction-guided real image editing that covers diverse scenarios: single-turn, multi-turn, mask-provided, and mask-free editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magicbrush-a-manually-annotated-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMS-DPM: Optimizing the Model Schedule for Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oms-dpm-optimizing-the-model-schedule-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion probabilistic models (DPMs) are a new class of generative models that have achieved state-of-the-art generation quality in various domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oms-dpm-optimizing-the-model-schedule-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QH9: A Quantum Hamiltonian Prediction Benchmark for QM9 Molecules</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qh9-a-quantum-hamiltonian-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Supervised machine learning approaches have been increasingly used in accelerating electronic structure prediction as surrogates of first-principle computational methods, such as density functional theory (DFT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qh9-a-quantum-hamiltonian-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuadSwarm: A Modular Multi-Quadrotor Simulator for Deep Reinforcement Learning with Direct Thrust Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quadswarm-a-modular-multi-quadrotor-simulator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to speed, such simulators need to model the physics of the robots and their interaction with the environment to a level acceptable for transferring policies learned in simulation to reality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quadswarm-a-modular-multi-quadrotor-simulator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore, Establish, Exploit: Red Teaming Language Models from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explore-establish-exploit-red-teaming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The red team is expected to refine/extend this specification and identify methods to elicit this behavior from the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explore-establish-exploit-red-teaming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Social Navigation with Non-Cooperative Robots via Bi-Level Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-social-navigation-with-non</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a fully decentralized approach for realtime non-cooperative multi-robot navigation in social mini-games, such as navigating through a narrow doorway or negotiating right of way at a corridor intersection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-social-navigation-with-non</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pragmatic Inference with a CLIP Listener for Contrastive Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pragmatic-inference-with-a-clip-listener-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a simple yet effective and robust method for contrastive captioning: generating discriminative captions that distinguish target images from very similar alternative distractor images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pragmatic-inference-with-a-clip-listener-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic HELM: An Interpretable Memory for Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-helm-an-interpretable-memory-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then we feed these tokens to a pretrained language model that serves the agent as memory and provides it with a coherent and interpretable representation of the past.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-helm-an-interpretable-memory-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and Mitigating Extrapolation Failures in Physics-Informed Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-mitigating-extrapolation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By analyzing the Fourier spectra of the solution functions, we characterize the PDEs that yield favorable extrapolation behavior, and show that the presence of high frequencies in the solution function is not to blame for poor extrapolation behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-mitigating-extrapolation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIGHT: A Large Annotated Dataset on Student Insights Gathered from Higher Education Transcripts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sight-a-large-annotated-dataset-on-student</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this challenge, we propose a set of best practices for using large language models (LLMs) to cheaply classify the comments at scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sight-a-large-annotated-dataset-on-student</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural models for Factual Inconsistency Classification with Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-models-for-factual-inconsistency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed system first predicts inconsistent spans from claim and context; and then uses them to predict inconsistency types and inconsistent entity types (when inconsistency is due to entities).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-models-for-factual-inconsistency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation and Optimization of Gradient Compression for Distributed Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-and-optimization-of-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To accelerate distributed training, many gradient compression methods have been proposed to alleviate the communication bottleneck in synchronous stochastic gradient descent (S-SGD), but their efficacy in real-world applications still remains unclear.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-and-optimization-of-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relation-Aware Diffusion Model for Controllable Poster Layout Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relation-aware-diffusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To advance research in this field, we have constructed a poster layout dataset named CGL-Dataset V2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relation-aware-diffusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Split Matters: Flat Minima Methods for Improving the Performance of GNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-split-matters-flat-minima-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate flat minima methods and combinations of those methods for training graph neural networks (GNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-split-matters-flat-minima-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical confusion matrix for classification performance evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-confusion-matrix-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we use measures based on the novel confusion matrix to evaluate models within a benchmark for three real world hierarchical classification applications and compare the results to established evaluation measures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-confusion-matrix-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Self-Supervised Miniature One-Shot Texture Segmentation (MOSTS) Model for Real-Time Robot Navigation and Embedded Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-self-supervised-miniature-one-shot-texture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Determining the drivable area, or free space segmentation, is critical for mobile robots to navigate indoor environments safely.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-self-supervised-miniature-one-shot-texture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FFB: A Fair Fairness Benchmark for In-Processing Group Fairness Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ffb-a-fair-fairness-benchmark-for-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the Fair Fairness Benchmark (\textsf{FFB}), a benchmarking framework for in-processing group fairness methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ffb-a-fair-fairness-benchmark-for-in</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
