<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 09:12:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Transferable Models for Bioacoustics with Human Language Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferable-models-for-bioacoustics-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After training on this dataset to connect language and audio representations, our model can identify over a thousand species' calls across taxa, complete bioacoustic tasks zero-shot, and retrieve animal vocalization recordings from natural text queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferable-models-for-bioacoustics-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AspectMMKG: A Multi-modal Knowledge Graph with Aspect-aware Entities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aspectmmkg-a-multi-modal-knowledge-graph-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal knowledge graphs (MMKGs) combine different modal data (e. g., text and image) for a comprehensive understanding of entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aspectmmkg-a-multi-modal-knowledge-graph-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volumetric Fast Fourier Convolution for Detecting Ink on the Carbonized Herculaneum Papyri</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volumetric-fast-fourier-convolution-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in Digital Document Restoration (DDR) have led to significant breakthroughs in analyzing highly damaged written artifacts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volumetric-fast-fourier-convolution-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Density Crop-guided Semi-supervised Object Detection in Aerial Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/density-crop-guided-semi-supervised-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the important bottlenecks in training modern object detectors is the need for labeled images where bounding box annotations have to be produced for each object present in the image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/density-crop-guided-semi-supervised-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Modulation Transformer: Cross-Refinement of Global Representation via High-Frequency Prior for Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-modulation-transformer-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based methods have exhibited remarkable potential in single image super-resolution (SISR) by effectively extracting long-range dependencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-modulation-transformer-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint-Relation Transformer for Multi-Person Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-relation-transformer-for-multi-person</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-person motion prediction is a challenging problem due to the dependency of motion on both individual past movements and interactions with other people.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-relation-transformer-for-multi-person</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIFD: A Generative Gradient Inversion Method with Feature Domain Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gifd-a-generative-gradient-inversion-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) has recently emerged as a promising distributed machine learning framework to preserve clients' privacy, by allowing multiple clients to upload the gradients calculated from their local data to a central server.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gifd-a-generative-gradient-inversion-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Induction Network: Audio-Visual Modality Gap-Bridging for Self-Supervised Sound Source Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/induction-network-audio-visual-modality-gap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By decoupling the gradients of visual and audio modalities, the discriminative visual representations of sound sources can be learned with the designed Induction Vector in a bootstrap manner, which also enables the audio modality to be aligned with the visual modality consistently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/induction-network-audio-visual-modality-gap</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Separate Anything You Describe</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/separate-anything-you-describe</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce AudioSep, a foundation model for open-domain audio source separation with natural language queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/separate-anything-you-describe</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A degree of image identification at sub-human scales could be possible with more advanced clusters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-degree-of-image-identification-at-sub-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The purpose of the research is to determine if currently available self-supervised learning techniques can accomplish human level comprehension of visual images using the same degree and amount of sensory input that people acquire from.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-degree-of-image-identification-at-sub-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Perturbation Analysis for Probabilistic Black-Box Anomaly Attribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-perturbation-analysis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then propose a novel framework for probabilistic anomaly attribution that allows us to not only compute attribution scores as the predictive mean but also quantify the uncertainty of those scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-perturbation-analysis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreground Object Search by Distilling Composite Image Feature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foreground-object-search-by-distilling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, previous works did not release their datasets, so we contribute two datasets for FOS task: S-FOSD dataset with synthetic composite images and R-FOSD dataset with real composite images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foreground-object-search-by-distilling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperCoil-Recon: A Hypernetwork-based Adaptive Coil Configuration Task Switching Network for MRI Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypercoil-recon-a-hypernetwork-based-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments reveal that our approach 1) adapts on the fly to various unseen configurations up to 32 coils when trained on lower numbers (i. e. 7 to 11) of randomly varying coils, and to 120 deviated unseen configurations when trained on 18 configurations in a single model, 2) matches the performance of coil configuration-specific models, and 3) outperforms configuration-invariant models with improvement margins of around 1 dB / 0. 03 and 0. 3 dB / 0. 02 in PSNR / SSIM for knee and brain data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypercoil-recon-a-hypernetwork-based-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decorrelating neurons using persistence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decorrelating-neurons-using-persistence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel way to improve the generalisation capacity of deep learning models by reducing high correlations between neurons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decorrelating-neurons-using-persistence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Learning From Distributed Data With Differentially Private Synthetic Twin Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-learning-from-distributed-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consider a setting where multiple parties holding sensitive data aim to collaboratively learn population level statistics, but pooling the sensitive data sets is not possible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-learning-from-distributed-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards true discovery of the differential equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-true-discovery-of-the-differential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Differential equation discovery, a machine learning subfield, is used to develop interpretable models, particularly in nature-related applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-true-discovery-of-the-differential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kairos: : Practical Intrusion Detection and Investigation using Whole-system Provenance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kairos-practical-intrusion-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sifting through their design documents, we identify four common dimensions that drive the development of provenance-based intrusion detection systems (PIDSes): scope (can PIDSes detect modern attacks that infiltrate across application boundaries?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kairos-practical-intrusion-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance Analysis of Transformer Based Models (BERT, ALBERT and RoBERTa) in Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-analysis-of-transformer-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, some studies suggest the performance can be improved with the use of improved BERT models known as ALBERT and RoBERTa.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-analysis-of-transformer-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When and How Does Known Class Help Discover Unknown Ones? Provable Understanding Through Spectral Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-and-how-does-known-class-help-discover</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper bridges the gap by providing an analytical framework to formalize and investigate when and how known classes can help discover novel classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-and-how-does-known-class-help-discover</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Class Deep SVDD: Anomaly Detection Approach in Astronomy with Distinct Inlier Categories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-class-deep-svdd-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results demonstrate the efficacy of MCDSVDD in detecting anomalous sources while leveraging the presence of different inlier categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-class-deep-svdd-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resource Constrained Model Compression via Minimax Optimization for Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resource-constrained-model-compression-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an improved end-to-end Minimax optimization method for this sparse learning problem to better balance the model performance and the computation efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resource-constrained-model-compression-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMeBench: A Flexible Framework for Accelerating LLMs Benchmarking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmebench-a-flexible-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Initially developed to evaluate Arabic NLP tasks using OpenAI's GPT and BLOOM models; it can be seamlessly customized for any NLP task and model, regardless of language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmebench-a-flexible-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SelectNAdapt: Support Set Selection for Few-Shot Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selectnadapt-support-set-selection-for-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few-shot domain adaptation mitigates this issue by adapting deep neural networks pre-trained on the source domain to the target domain using a randomly selected and annotated support set from the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selectnadapt-support-set-selection-for-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiVa: An Iterative Framework to Harvest More Diverse and Valid Labels from User Comments for Music</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diva-an-iterative-framework-to-harvest-more</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the observation that such missing information may already be presented in user comments, we propose to study the automated music labeling in an essential but under-explored setting, where the model is required to harvest more diverse and valid labels from the users' comments given limited gold labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diva-an-iterative-framework-to-harvest-more</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Intents Graph Modeling for User-centric Group Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-intents-graph-modeling-for-user-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, user-centric group discovery task, i. e., recommending groups to users can help both users' online experiences and platforms' long-term developments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-intents-graph-modeling-for-user-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUnAA: Sparse Unmixing using Archetypal Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sunaa-sparse-unmixing-using-archetypal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike most conventional sparse unmixing methods, here the minimization problem is non-convex.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sunaa-sparse-unmixing-using-archetypal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Bipartite Graph is All We Need for Enhancing Emotional Reasoning with Commonsense Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bipartite-graph-is-all-we-need-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most previous knowledge infusion methods perform empirical knowledge filtering and design highly customized architectures for knowledge interaction with the utterances, which can discard useful knowledge aspects and limit their generalizability to different knowledge sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bipartite-graph-is-all-we-need-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parallel Knowledge Enhancement based Framework for Multi-behavior Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-knowledge-enhancement-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the fusion step, advanced neural networks are used to model the hierarchical correlations between user behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-knowledge-enhancement-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Directed differential equation discovery using modified mutation and cross-over operators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/directed-differential-equation-discovery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The discovery of equations with knowledge of the process origin is a tempting prospect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/directed-differential-equation-discovery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SILO Language Models: Isolating Legal Risk In a Nonparametric Datastore</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/silo-language-models-isolating-legal-risk-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SILO is built by (1) training a parametric LM on Open License Corpus (OLC), a new corpus we curate with 228B tokens of public domain and permissively licensed text and (2) augmenting it with a more general and easily modifiable nonparametric datastore (e. g., containing copyrighted books or news) that is only queried during inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/silo-language-models-isolating-legal-risk-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Augmentation with Large-scale Unconditional Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-augmentation-with-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further reduce the dependency on annotated data, we propose a synthetic augmentation method called HistoDiffusion, which can be pre-trained on large-scale unlabeled datasets and later applied to a small-scale labeled dataset for augmented training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-augmentation-with-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lossy and Lossless (L$^2$) Post-training Model Size Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lossy-and-lossless-l-2-post-training-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, a dedicated differentiable counter is introduced to guide the optimization of lossy compression to arrive at a more suitable point for later lossless compression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lossy-and-lossless-l-2-post-training-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single-Sentence Reader: A Novel Approach for Addressing Answer Position Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-sentence-reader-a-novel-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine Reading Comprehension (MRC) models tend to take advantage of spurious correlations (also known as dataset bias or annotation artifacts in the research community).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-sentence-reader-a-novel-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLEM: Machine Learning for Path Modeling and Causal Inference with Super Learner Equation Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slem-machine-learning-for-path-modeling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal inference is a crucial goal of science, enabling researchers to arrive at meaningful conclusions regarding the predictions of hypothetical interventions using observational data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slem-machine-learning-for-path-modeling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards an AI to Win Ghana's National Science and Maths Quiz</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-ai-to-win-ghana-s-national-science</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Can an AI win Ghana's National Science and Maths Quiz (NSMQ)?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-ai-to-win-ghana-s-national-science</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Monotonic Aggregation for Open-domain QA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-monotonic-aggregation-for-open-domain-qa</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments show that our framework not only ensures monotonicity, but also outperforms state-of-the-art multi-source QA methods on Natural Questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-monotonic-aggregation-for-open-domain-qa</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Distillation-enhanced Multi-modal Transformer for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-distillation-enhanced-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To be specific, we first introduce an ID-aware Multi-modal Transformer module in the item representation learning stage to facilitate information interaction among different features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-distillation-enhanced-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MindDiffuser: Controlled Image Reconstruction from Human Brain Activity with Semantic and Structural Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minddiffuser-controlled-image-reconstruction-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Stage 2, we utilize the CLIP visual feature decoded from fMRI as supervisory information, and continually adjust the two feature vectors decoded in Stage 1 through backpropagation to align the structural information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minddiffuser-controlled-image-reconstruction-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPCFormer: Expression Prompt Collaboration Transformer for Universal Referring Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epcformer-expression-prompt-collaboration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, we propose an Expression Alignment (EA) mechanism for audio and text expressions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epcformer-expression-prompt-collaboration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial Prior Based First Order Motion Model for Micro-expression Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facial-prior-based-first-order-motion-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve this problem, this paper tries to formulate a new task called micro-expression generation and then presents a strong baseline which combines the first order motion model with facial prior knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facial-prior-based-first-order-motion-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class-level Structural Relation Modelling and Smoothing for Visual Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-level-structural-relation-modelling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representation learning for images has been advanced by recent progress in more complex neural models such as the Vision Transformers and new learning theories such as the structural causal models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-level-structural-relation-modelling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding CNN Hidden Neuron Activations Using Structured Background Knowledge and Deductive Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-cnn-hidden-neuron-activations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A major challenge in Explainable AI is in correctly interpreting activations of hidden neurons: accurate interpretations would provide insights into the question of what a deep learning system has internally detected as relevant on the input, demystifying the otherwise black-box character of deep learning systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-cnn-hidden-neuron-activations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSTFormer: Bridging Spiking Neural Network and Memory Support Transformer for Frame-Event based Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sstformer-bridging-spiking-neural-network-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, they adopt either Spiking Neural Networks (SNN) for energy-efficient recognition with suboptimal results, or Artificial Neural Networks (ANN) for energy-intensive, high-performance recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sstformer-bridging-spiking-neural-network-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAIF: Perception-Aware Infrared-Visible Image Fusion for Attack-Tolerant Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paif-perception-aware-infrared-visible-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first conduct systematic analyses about the components of image fusion, investigating the correlation with segmentation robustness under adversarial perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paif-perception-aware-infrared-visible-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DialogRE^C+: An Extension of DialogRE to Investigate How Much Coreference Helps Relation Extraction in Dialogs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialogre-c-an-extension-of-dialogre-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dialogue relation extraction (DRE) that identifies the relations between argument pairs in dialogue text, suffers much from the frequent occurrence of personal pronouns, or entity and speaker coreference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialogre-c-an-extension-of-dialogre-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-Scale Multi-Hypotheses Cell Tracking Using Ultrametric Contours Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-hypotheses-cell-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we describe a method for large-scale 3D cell-tracking through a segmentation selection approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-hypotheses-cell-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUG: Photorealistic and Semantically Controllable Synthetic Data for Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pug-photorealistic-and-semantically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthetic image datasets offer unmatched advantages for designing and evaluating deep neural networks: they make it possible to (i) render as many data samples as needed, (ii) precisely control each scene and yield granular ground truth labels (and captions), (iii) precisely control distribution shifts between training and testing to isolate variables of interest for sound experimentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pug-photorealistic-and-semantically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coarse-to-Fine: Learning Compact Discriminative Representation for Single-Stage Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse-to-fine-learning-compact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image retrieval targets to find images from a database that are visually similar to the query image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse-to-fine-learning-compact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top K Relevant Passage Retrieval for Biomedical Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/top-k-relevant-passage-retrieval-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we work on the existing DPR framework for the biomedical domain and retrieve answers from the Pubmed articles which is a reliable source to answer medical questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/top-k-relevant-passage-retrieval-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collective Human Opinions in Semantic Textual Similarity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collective-human-opinions-in-semantic-textual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the subjective nature of semantic textual similarity (STS) and pervasive disagreements in STS annotation, existing benchmarks have used averaged human ratings as the gold standard.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collective-human-opinions-in-semantic-textual</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
