<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 21:06:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of RLHF in Large Language Models Part II: Reward Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secrets-of-rlhf-in-large-language-models-part-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a series of novel methods to mitigate the influence of incorrect and ambiguous preferences in the dataset and fully leverage high-quality preference data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secrets-of-rlhf-in-large-language-models-part-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-as-a-Coauthor: The Challenges of Detecting LLM-Human Mixcase</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-as-a-coauthor-the-challenges-of-detecting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the remarkable development and widespread applications of large language models (LLMs), the use of machine-generated text (MGT) is becoming increasingly common.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-as-a-coauthor-the-challenges-of-detecting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Boosting Many-to-Many Multilingual Machine Translation with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-boosting-many-to-many-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The training paradigm for machine translation has gradually shifted, from learning neural machine translation (NMT) models with extensive parallel corpora to instruction finetuning on pretrained multilingual large language models (LLMs) with high-quality translation pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-boosting-many-to-many-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transforming Image Super-Resolution: A ConvFormer-based Efficient Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transforming-image-super-resolution-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in single-image super-resolution (SISR) has achieved remarkable performance, yet the computational costs of these methods remain a challenge for deployment on resource-constrained devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transforming-image-super-resolution-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeekMoE: Towards Ultimate Expert Specialization in Mixture-of-Experts Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseekmoe-towards-ultimate-expert</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, we scale up DeepSeekMoE to 16B parameters and show that it achieves comparable performance with LLaMA2 7B, with only about 40% of computations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseekmoe-towards-ultimate-expert</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention to detail: inter-resolution knowledge distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-to-detail-inter-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of computer vision solutions for gigapixel images in digital pathology is hampered by significant computational limitations due to the large size of whole slide images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-to-detail-inter-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the representation and methodology for wide and short range head pose estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-representation-and-methodology-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose a generalization of the geodesic angular distance metric that enables the construction of a loss that controls the contribution of each training sample to the optimization of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-representation-and-methodology-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Personality Recognition in Dialogue by Data Augmentation and Heterogeneous Conversational Graph Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-personality-recognition-in-dialogue</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personality recognition is useful for enhancing robots' ability to tailor user-adaptive responses, thus fostering rich human-robot interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-personality-recognition-in-dialogue</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manipulating Feature Visualizations with Gradient Slingshots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manipulating-feature-visualizations-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Neural Networks (DNNs) are capable of learning complex and versatile representations, however, the semantic nature of the learned concepts remains unknown.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manipulating-feature-visualizations-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pushing the Pareto front of band gap and permittivity: ML-guided search for dielectric materials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pushing-the-pareto-front-of-band-gap-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, we report the first high-purity synthesis and dielectric characterization of Bi2Zr2O7 with a band gap of 2. 27 eV and a permittivity of 20. 5, meeting all target metrics of our multi-objective search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pushing-the-pareto-front-of-band-gap-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Detecting Cherry-picking in News Coverage Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-detecting-cherry-picking-in-news-coverage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study introduces Cherry, an innovative approach for automatically detecting cherry-picked statements in news articles by finding missing important statements in the target news story.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-detecting-cherry-picking-in-news-coverage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Low-rank Subspaces for Language-agnostic Multilingual Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-low-rank-subspaces-for-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While these results are promising, follow-up works found that, within the multilingual embedding spaces, there exists strong language identity information which hinders the expression of linguistic factors shared across languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-low-rank-subspaces-for-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of a Concise Chain of Thought on Problem-Solving in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-benefits-of-a-concise-chain-of-thought-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluated this using GPT-3. 5 and GPT-4 with a multiple-choice question-and-answer (MCQA) benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-benefits-of-a-concise-chain-of-thought-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEGO:Language Enhanced Multi-modal Grounding Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lego-language-enhanced-multi-modal-grounding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Beyond capturing global information like other multi-modal models, our proposed model excels at tasks demanding a detailed understanding of local information within the input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lego-language-enhanced-multi-modal-grounding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look at AUROC and AUPRC under Class Imbalance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-auroc-and-auprc-under-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In machine learning (ML), a widespread adage is that the area under the precision-recall curve (AUPRC) is a superior metric for model comparison to the area under the receiver operating characteristic (AUROC) for binary classification tasks with class imbalance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-auroc-and-auprc-under-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An experimental evaluation of Deep Reinforcement Learning algorithms for HVAC control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-experimental-evaluation-of-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Heating, Ventilation, and Air Conditioning (HVAC) systems are a major driver of energy consumption in commercial and residential buildings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-experimental-evaluation-of-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GE-AdvGAN: Improving the transferability of adversarial samples by gradient editing-based adversarial generative model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ge-advgan-improving-the-transferability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the functional and characteristic similarity analysis, we introduce a novel gradient editing (GE) mechanism and verify its feasibility in generating transferable samples on various models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ge-advgan-improving-the-transferability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REBUS: A Robust Evaluation Benchmark of Understanding Symbols</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rebus-a-robust-evaluation-benchmark-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new benchmark evaluating the performance of multimodal large language models on rebus puzzles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rebus-a-robust-evaluation-benchmark-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe reinforcement learning in uncertain contexts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-reinforcement-learning-in-uncertain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we drop this assumption and show how we can perform safe learning when we cannot directly measure the context variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-reinforcement-learning-in-uncertain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Image Deblurring Networks based on Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-image-deblurring-networks-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article introduces a sliding window model for defocus deblurring that achieves the best performance to date with extremely low memory usage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-image-deblurring-networks-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiCMAE: Hierarchical Contrastive Masked Autoencoder for Self-Supervised Audio-Visual Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hicmae-hierarchical-contrastive-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Audio-Visual Emotion Recognition (AVER) has garnered increasing attention in recent years for its critical role in creating emotion-ware intelligent machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hicmae-hierarchical-contrastive-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining Normalizing Flows and Quasi-Monte Carlo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-normalizing-flows-and-quasi-monte</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in machine learning have led to the development of new methods for enhancing Monte Carlo methods such as Markov chain Monte Carlo (MCMC) and importance sampling (IS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-normalizing-flows-and-quasi-monte</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Vulnerabilities in Large Language Models: In-context Learning Backdoor Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-vulnerabilities-in-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experimental results across several language models, ranging in size from 1. 3B to 40B parameters, demonstrate the effectiveness of our attack method, exemplified by a high average attack success rate of 95. 0% across the three datasets on OPT models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-vulnerabilities-in-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-end Learnable Clustering for Intent Learning in Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-learnable-clustering-for-intent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, the separation of representation learning and clustering optimization within a generalized expectation maximization (EM) framework often results in sub-optimal performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-learnable-clustering-for-intent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgical-DINO: Adapter Learning of Foundation Model for Depth Estimation in Endoscopic Surgery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgical-dino-adapter-learning-of-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is clear evidence in the results that zero-shot prediction on pre-trained weights in computer vision datasets or naive fine-tuning is not sufficient to use the foundation model in the surgical domain directly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgical-dino-adapter-learning-of-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Translation: A New Pathway for Model Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-translation-a-new-pathway-for-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning has witnessed significant advancements in recent years at the cost of increasing training, inference, and model storage overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-translation-a-new-pathway-for-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An attempt to generate new bridge types from latent space of PixelCNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attempt-to-generate-new-bridge-types-from-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal models should be the way to achieve artificial general intelligence in the future.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attempt-to-generate-new-bridge-types-from-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DREQ: Document Re-Ranking Using Entity-based Query Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreq-document-re-ranking-using-entity-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While entity-oriented neural IR models have advanced significantly, they often overlook a key nuance: the varying degrees of influence individual entities within a document have on its overall relevance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreq-document-re-ranking-using-entity-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAT-LLM: Prompting Large Language Models with Text Style Definition for Chinese Article-style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-llm-prompting-large-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text style transfer is increasingly prominent in online entertainment and social media.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-llm-prompting-large-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wavelet-Inspired Multiscale Graph Convolutional Recurrent Network for Traffic Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavelet-inspired-multiscale-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traffic forecasting is the foundation for intelligent transportation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavelet-inspired-multiscale-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HaltingVT: Adaptive Token Halting Transformer for Efficient Video Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/haltingvt-adaptive-token-halting-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Action recognition in videos poses a challenge due to its high computational cost, especially for Joint Space-Time video transformers (Joint VT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/haltingvt-adaptive-token-halting-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Population Graph Cross-Network Node Classification for Autism Detection Across Sample Groups</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/population-graph-cross-network-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNN) are a powerful tool for combining imaging and non-imaging medical information for node classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/population-graph-cross-network-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closed-Form Interpretation of Neural Network Classifiers with Symbolic Regression Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closed-form-interpretation-of-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[I introduce a unified framework for interpreting neural network classifiers tailored toward automated scientific discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closed-form-interpretation-of-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuantumSEA: In-Time Sparse Exploration for Noise Adaptive Quantum Circuits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantumsea-in-time-sparse-exploration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these two pain points, we propose QuantumSEA, an in-time sparse exploration for noise-adaptive quantum circuits, aiming to achieve two key objectives: (1) implicit circuits capacity during training - by dynamically exploring the circuit's sparse connectivity and sticking a fixed small number of quantum gates throughout the training which satisfies the coherence time and enjoy light noises, enabling feasible executions on real quantum devices; (2) noise robustness - by jointly optimizing the topology and parameters of quantum circuits under real device noise models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantumsea-in-time-sparse-exploration-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Audio Concepts from Counterfactual Natural Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-audio-concepts-from-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional audio classification relied on predefined classes, lacking the ability to learn from free-form text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-audio-concepts-from-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASA: Causality-driven Argument Sufficiency Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/casa-causality-driven-argument-sufficiency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the probability of sufficiency (PS) definition in the causal literature, we propose CASA, a zero-shot causality-driven argument sufficiency assessment framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/casa-causality-driven-argument-sufficiency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divide and Conquer for Large Language Models Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divide-and-conquer-for-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown impressive performance in various reasoning benchmarks with the emergence of Chain-of-Thought (CoT) and its derivative methods, particularly in tasks involving multi-choice questions (MCQs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divide-and-conquer-for-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Hardness Negative Sampling for Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-hardness-negative-sampling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Negative sampling is essential for implicit collaborative filtering to provide proper negative training signals so as to achieve desirable performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-hardness-negative-sampling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal LLM Agents: Insights and Survey about the Capability, Efficiency and Security</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personal-llm-agents-insights-and-survey-about</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, we discuss several key challenges to achieve intelligent, efficient and secure Personal LLM Agents, followed by a comprehensive survey of representative solutions to address these challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personal-llm-agents-insights-and-survey-about</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Online Sign Language Recognition and Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-online-sign-language-recognition-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach comprises three phases: 1) developing a sign language dictionary encompassing all glosses present in a target sign language dataset; 2) training an isolated sign language recognition model on augmented signs using both conventional classification loss and our novel saliency loss; 3) employing a sliding window approach on the input sign sequence and feeding each sign clip to the well-optimized model for online recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-online-sign-language-recognition-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Causal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-causal-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists often want to learn about cause and effect from hierarchical data, collected from subunits nested inside units.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-causal-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REACT 2024: the Second Multiple Appropriate Facial Reaction Generation Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/react-2024-the-second-multiple-appropriate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In dyadic interactions, humans communicate their intentions and state of mind using verbal and non-verbal cues, where multiple different facial reactions might be appropriate in response to a specific speaker behaviour.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/react-2024-the-second-multiple-appropriate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-trained Large Language Models for Financial Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-trained-large-language-models-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Financial sentiment analysis refers to classifying financial text contents into sentiment categories (e. g. positive, negative, and neutral).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-trained-large-language-models-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISS: Multiclass Interpretable Scoring Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miss-multiclass-interpretable-scoring-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a novel, machine-learning approach for constructing Multiclass Interpretable Scoring Systems (MISS) - a fully data-driven methodology for generating single, sparse, and user-friendly scoring systems for multiclass classification problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miss-multiclass-interpretable-scoring-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full-frequency dynamic convolution: a physical frequency-dependent convolution for sound event detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/full-frequency-dynamic-convolution-a-physical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, 2D convolution has been found unqualified in sound event detection (SED).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/full-frequency-dynamic-convolution-a-physical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inconsistency-Based Data-Centric Active Open-Set Annotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inconsistency-based-data-centric-active-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The presence of unknown classes in the data can significantly impact the performance of existing active learning methods due to the uncertainty they introduce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inconsistency-based-data-centric-active-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleeper Agents: Training Deceptive LLMs that Persist Through Safety Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sleeper-agents-training-deceptive-llms-that</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that such backdoored behavior can be made persistent, so that it is not removed by standard safety training techniques, including supervised fine-tuning, reinforcement learning, and adversarial training (eliciting unsafe behavior and then training to remove it).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sleeper-agents-training-deceptive-llms-that</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Influence of Reading Sequences on Knowledge Gain during Web Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-influence-of-reading-sequences-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use publicly available study data from a web-based learning task to examine the relationship between our feature set and the participants' test scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-influence-of-reading-sequences-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECC-PolypDet: Enhanced CenterNet with Contrastive Learning for Automatic Polyp Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecc-polypdet-enhanced-centernet-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate polyp detection is critical for early colorectal cancer diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecc-polypdet-enhanced-centernet-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modelling Species Distributions with Deep Learning to Predict Plant Extinction Risk and Assess Climate Change Impacts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelling-species-distributions-with-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-validation yields average accuracies of 0. 61 for status classification and 0. 78 for binary classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelling-species-distributions-with-deep</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
