<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:11:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>RSpell: Retrieval-augmented Framework for Domain Adaptive Chinese Spelling Check</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rspell-retrieval-augmented-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a retrieval-augmented spelling check framework called RSpell, which searches corresponding domain terms and incorporates them into CSC models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rspell-retrieval-augmented-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Membrane Potential Batch Normalization for Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membrane-potential-batch-normalization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[All these BNs are suggested to be used after the convolution layer as usually doing in CNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membrane-potential-batch-normalization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ref-DVGO: Reflection-Aware Direct Voxel Grid Optimization for an Improved Quality-Efficiency Trade-Off in Reflective Scene Reconstructio</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ref-dvgo-reflection-aware-direct-voxel-grid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we investigate an implicit-explicit approach based on conventional volume rendering to enhance the reconstruction quality and accelerate the training and rendering processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ref-dvgo-reflection-aware-direct-voxel-grid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDDial: A Multi-turn Differential Diagnosis Dialogue Dataset with Reliability Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mddial-a-multi-turn-differential-diagnosis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a unified score for the ADD system that takes into account the interplay between symptoms and diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mddial-a-multi-turn-differential-diagnosis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaBrowse: Adaptive Video Browser for Efficient Continuous Sign Language Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adabrowse-adaptive-video-browser-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then these features are fed into a policy network to intelligently select a subsequence to process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adabrowse-adaptive-video-browser-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising Diffusion Probabilistic Model for Retinal Image Generation and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-probabilistic-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We developed a Retinal Trees (ReTree) dataset consisting of retinal images, corresponding vessel trees, and a segmentation network based on DDPM trained with images from the ReTree dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-probabilistic-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inherent Redundancy in Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inherent-redundancy-in-spiking-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we pose and focus on three key questions regarding the inherent redundancy in SNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inherent-redundancy-in-spiking-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expressivity of Graph Neural Networks Through the Lens of Adversarial Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressivity-of-graph-neural-networks-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We perform the first adversarial robustness study into Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) that are provably more powerful than traditional Message Passing Neural Networks (MPNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressivity-of-graph-neural-networks-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Independent Distribution Regularization for Private Graph Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/independent-distribution-regularization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we introduce a novel regularization to enforce the independence of the encoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/independent-distribution-regularization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoencoding a Soft Touch to Learn Grasping from On-land to Underwater</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoding-a-soft-touch-to-learn-grasping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robots play a critical role as the physical agent of human operators in exploring the ocean.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoding-a-soft-touch-to-learn-grasping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characteristics of networks generated by kernel growing neural gas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characteristics-of-networks-generated-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research aims to develop kernel GNG, a kernelized version of the growing neural gas (GNG) algorithm, and to investigate the features of the networks generated by the kernel GNG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characteristics-of-networks-generated-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detoxify Language Model Step-by-Step</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detoxify-language-model-step-by-step</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detoxification for LLMs is challenging since it requires models to avoid generating harmful content while maintaining the generation capability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detoxify-language-model-step-by-step</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Neural Network Generalization for Grammar Induction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-neural-network-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How well do neural networks generalize?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-neural-network-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Visual and Semantic Similarity Using Hierarchies for Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-visual-and-semantic-similarity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most of the research in content-based image retrieval (CBIR) focus on developing robust feature representations that can effectively retrieve instances from a database of images that are visually similar to a query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-visual-and-semantic-similarity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S-Mixup: Structural Mixup for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-mixup-structural-mixup-for-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing studies for applying the mixup technique on graphs mainly focus on graph classification tasks, while the research in node classification is still under-explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-mixup-structural-mixup-for-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Multi-View Deep Networks Methodology for Experimental Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-multi-view-deep-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we suggest different multi-view architectures for the vision domain, each suited to another problem, and we also present a methodology for explaining these models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-multi-view-deep-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endogenous Macrodynamics in Algorithmic Recourse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/endogenous-macrodynamics-in-algorithmic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing work on Counterfactual Explanations (CE) and Algorithmic Recourse (AR) has largely focused on single individuals in a static environment: given some estimated model, the goal is to find valid counterfactuals for an individual instance that fulfill various desiderata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/endogenous-macrodynamics-in-algorithmic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeDoDe: Detect, Don't Describe -- Describe, Don't Detect for Local Feature Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dedode-detect-don-t-describe-describe-don-t</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To train a descriptor, we maximize the mutual nearest neighbour objective over the keypoints with a separate network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dedode-detect-don-t-describe-describe-don-t</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDPK: A Framework to Synthesise Process Data and Corresponding Procedural Knowledge for Manufacturing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdpk-a-framework-to-synthesise-process-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, no real-world datasets containing process data and corresponding procedural knowledge are publicly available, possibly due to corporate apprehensions regarding the loss of knowledge advances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdpk-a-framework-to-synthesise-process-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALIP: Adaptive Language-Image Pre-training with Synthetic Caption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alip-adaptive-language-image-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the presence of intrinsic noise and unmatched image-text pairs in web data can potentially affect the performance of representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alip-adaptive-language-image-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Cap: Leveraging a Frozen Vision-Language Model for Hateful Meme Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pro-cap-leveraging-a-frozen-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we prompt a frozen PVLM by asking hateful content-related questions and use the answers as image captions (which we call Pro-Cap), so that the captions contain information critical for hateful content detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pro-cap-leveraging-a-frozen-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Domain Adaptive Detection with Network Stability Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptive-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, drawing inspiration from the concept of stability from the control theory that a robust system requires to remain consistent both externally and internally regardless of disturbances, we propose a novel framework that achieves unsupervised domain adaptive detection through stability analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptive-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Likelihood-Based Text-to-Image Evaluation with Patch-Level Perceptual and Semantic Credit Assignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/likelihood-based-text-to-image-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to evaluate text-to-image generation performance by directly estimating the likelihood of the generated images using a pre-trained likelihood-based text-to-image generative model, i. e., a higher likelihood indicates better perceptual quality and better text-image alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/likelihood-based-text-to-image-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPA-3D: Geometry-aware Prototype Alignment for Unsupervised Domain Adaptive 3D Object Detection from Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpa-3d-geometry-aware-prototype-alignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LiDAR-based 3D detection has made great progress in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpa-3d-geometry-aware-prototype-alignment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering User Interest from Biased and Noised Watch Time in Video Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-user-interest-from-biased-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the video recommendation, watch time is commonly adopted as an indicator of user interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-user-interest-from-biased-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diagnosing Human-object Interaction Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnosing-human-object-interaction-detectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although we have witnessed significant progress in human-object interaction (HOI) detection with increasingly high mAP (mean Average Precision), a single mAP score is too concise to obtain an informative summary of a model's performance and to understand why one approach is better than another.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnosing-human-object-interaction-detectors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Expert's Guide to Training Physics-informed Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-expert-s-guide-to-training-physics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Physics-informed neural networks (PINNs) have been popularized as a deep learning framework that can seamlessly synthesize observational data and partial differential equation (PDE) constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-expert-s-guide-to-training-physics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KernelWarehouse: Towards Parameter-Efficient Dynamic Convolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernelwarehouse-towards-parameter-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic convolution learns a linear mixture of $n$ static kernels weighted with their sample-dependent attentions, demonstrating superior performance compared to normal convolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernelwarehouse-towards-parameter-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeViS: A Large-scale Benchmark for Video Segmentation with Motion Expressions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mevis-a-large-scale-benchmark-for-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To investigate the feasibility of using motion expressions to ground and segment objects in videos, we propose a large-scale dataset called MeViS, which contains numerous motion expressions to indicate target objects in complex environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mevis-a-large-scale-benchmark-for-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Reference Deep Adaptive Curve Estimation for Low-Light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-reference-deep-adaptive-curve-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a 2-stage low-light image enhancement method called Self-Reference Deep Adaptive Curve Estimation (Self-DACE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-reference-deep-adaptive-curve-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety Filter Design for Neural Network Systems via Convex Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-filter-design-for-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increase in data availability, it has been widely demonstrated that neural networks (NN) can capture complex system dynamics precisely in a data-driven manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-filter-design-for-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid model-guided design of organ-scale synthetic vasculature for biomanufacturing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-model-guided-design-of-organ-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate rapid generation, simulation, and 3D printing of synthetic vasculature in complex geometries, from small tissue constructs to organ scale networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-model-guided-design-of-organ-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riemannian geometry for efficient analysis of protein dynamics data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/riemannian-geometry-for-efficient-analysis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, it comes with a rich structure to account for a wide range of geometries that can be modelled after an energy landscape.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/riemannian-geometry-for-efficient-analysis-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anaphoric Structure Emerges Between Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anaphoric-structure-emerges-between-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pragmatics is core to natural language, enabling speakers to communicate efficiently with structures like ellipsis and anaphora that can shorten utterances without loss of meaning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anaphoric-structure-emerges-between-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Commit Message Generation to History-Aware Commit Message Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-commit-message-generation-to-history</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use this dataset to evaluate the completion setting and the usefulness of the historical context for state-of-the-art CMG models and GPT-3. 5-turbo.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-commit-message-generation-to-history</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Genetic Algorithm Meta-Heuristic for a Generalized Quadratic Assignment Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-genetic-algorithm-meta-heuristic-for-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The GQAP addressed in this work is defined as the task of minimizing the assignment and transportation costs of assigning a set of facilities to a set of locations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-genetic-algorithm-meta-heuristic-for-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ske2Grid: Skeleton-to-Grid Representation Learning for Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ske2grid-skeleton-to-grid-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents Ske2Grid, a new representation learning framework for improved skeleton-based action recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ske2grid-skeleton-to-grid-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Identify Critical States for Reinforcement Learning from Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-identify-critical-states-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work on deep reinforcement learning (DRL) has pointed out that algorithmic information about good policies can be extracted from offline data which lack explicit information about executed actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-identify-critical-states-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EQ-Net: Elastic Quantization Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eq-net-elastic-quantization-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore a one-shot network quantization regime, named Elastic Quantization Neural Networks (EQ-Net), which aims to train a robust weight-sharing quantization supernet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eq-net-elastic-quantization-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning to Learn: A Novel Algorithm for Active Learning during Model-Based Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planning-to-learn-a-novel-algorithm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we compare performance of SI to Bayesian reinforcement learning (RL) schemes designed to solve similar problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planning-to-learn-a-novel-algorithm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness and Privacy in Federated Learning and Their Implications in Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-and-privacy-in-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper endeavors to outline the typical lifecycle of fair federated learning in research as well as provide an updated taxonomy to account for the current state of fairness in implementations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-and-privacy-in-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Scalable Epistemic Uncertainty Quantification in Organ Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-scalable-epistemic-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning based methods for automatic organ segmentation have shown promise in aiding diagnosis and treatment planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-scalable-epistemic-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Machine Unlearning Without Retraining Through Selective Synaptic Dampening</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-machine-unlearning-without-retraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Selective Synaptic Dampening (SSD), a novel two-step, post hoc, retrain-free approach to machine unlearning which is fast, performant, and does not require long-term storage of the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-machine-unlearning-without-retraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniTR: A Unified and Efficient Multi-Modal Transformer for Bird's-Eye-View Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitr-a-unified-and-efficient-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Jointly processing information from multiple sensors is crucial to achieving accurate and robust perception for reliable autonomous driving systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitr-a-unified-and-efficient-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Interest Network for Click-Through Rate Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-interest-network-for-click-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed TIN outperforms the best-performing baselines by 0. 43\% and 0. 29\% on two datasets, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-interest-network-for-click-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Reinforcement Learning Approach for Performance-aware Reduction in Power Consumption of Data Center Compute Nodes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reinforcement-learning-approach-for-8</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Employing a Proximal Policy Optimization (PPO) agent to learn an optimal policy on a mathematical model of the compute nodes, we demonstrate and evaluate using the STREAM benchmark how a trained agent running on actual hardware can take actions by balancing power consumption and application performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reinforcement-learning-approach-for-8</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Link-Context Learning for Multimodal LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-context-learning-for-multimodal-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to learn from context with novel concepts, and deliver appropriate responses are essential in human conversations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-context-learning-for-multimodal-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Foundation LAnguage-Image model of the Retina (FLAIR): Encoding expert knowledge in text supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-foundation-language-image-model-of-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foundation vision-language models are currently transforming computer vision, and are on the rise in medical imaging fueled by their very promising generalization capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-foundation-language-image-model-of-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity-Consistent Aggregation for Video Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identity-consistent-aggregation-for-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Video Object Detection (VID), a common practice is to leverage the rich temporal contexts from the video to enhance the object representations in each frame.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identity-consistent-aggregation-for-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Switch: Efficient CLIP Adaptation for Text-Video Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-switch-efficient-clip-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In text-video retrieval, recent works have benefited from the powerful learning capabilities of pre-trained text-image foundation models (e. g., CLIP) by adapting them to the video domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-switch-efficient-clip-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
