<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:19:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ViPlan: A Benchmark for Visual Planning with Symbolic Predicates and Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/viplan-a-benchmark-for-visual-planning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ViPlan features a series of increasingly challenging tasks in two domains: a visual variant of the classic Blocksworld planning problem and a simulated household robotics environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/viplan-a-benchmark-for-visual-planning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Explanations for Continuous Action Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanations-for-continuous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning (RL) has shown great promise in domains like healthcare and robotics but often struggles with adoption due to its lack of interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanations-for-continuous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ineq-Comp: Benchmarking Human-Intuitive Compositional Reasoning in Automated Theorem Proving on Inequalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ineq-comp-benchmarking-human-intuitive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLM-based formal proof assistants (e. g., in Lean) hold great promise for automating mathematical discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ineq-comp-benchmarking-human-intuitive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Iterative Formalization and Planning in Partially Observable Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-iterative-formalization-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In planning, using LLMs not to predict plans but to formalize an environment into the Planning Domain Definition Language (PDDL) has been shown to greatly improve performance and control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-iterative-formalization-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIE: Controlling Language Model Text Generations Using Continuous Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cie-controlling-language-model-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This calls for designing methods that can allow users to control the properties of the language that LMs generate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cie-controlling-language-model-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JNLP at SemEval-2025 Task 11: Cross-Lingual Multi-Label Emotion Detection Using Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jnlp-at-semeval-2025-task-11-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our paper focuses on two sub-tracks of this task: (1) Track A: Multi-label emotion detection, and (2) Track B: Emotion intensity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jnlp-at-semeval-2025-task-11-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GuRE:Generative Query REwriter for Legal Passage Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gure-generative-query-rewriter-for-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One primary reason is the significant vocabulary mismatch between the query and the target passage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gure-generative-query-rewriter-for-legal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards A Generalist Code Embedding Model Based On Massive Data Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-generalist-code-embedding-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Code embedding models attract increasing attention due to the widespread popularity of retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) in software development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-generalist-code-embedding-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Low-Latency Event Stream-based Visual Object Tracking: A Slow-Fast Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-low-latency-event-stream-based-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing tracking algorithms typically rely on low-frame-rate RGB cameras coupled with computationally intensive deep neural network architectures to achieve effective tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-low-latency-event-stream-based-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Graph Induced Contour-aware Heat Conduction Network for Event-based Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-graph-induced-contour-aware-heat</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, this paper proposes a novel dynamic graph induced contour-aware heat conduction network for event stream based object detection, termed CvHeat-DET.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-graph-induced-contour-aware-heat</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Transformer via Unrolling of Mixed Graph Algorithms for Traffic Forecast</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-transformer-via-unrolling-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To forecast traffic with both spatial and temporal dimensions, we unroll a mixed-graph-based optimization algorithm into a lightweight and interpretable transformer-like neural net.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-transformer-via-unrolling-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Low Rank Adaptation Lead to Lower Robustness against Training-Time Attacks?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-low-rank-adaptation-lead-to-lower</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we theoretically investigate the security implications of LoRA's low-rank structure during fine-tuning, in the context of its robustness against data poisoning and backdoor attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-low-rank-adaptation-lead-to-lower</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MA-COIR: Leveraging Semantic Search Index and Generative Models for Ontology-Driven Biomedical Concept Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ma-coir-leveraging-semantic-search-index-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizing biomedical concepts in the text is vital for ontology refinement, knowledge graph construction, and concept relationship discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ma-coir-leveraging-semantic-search-index-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Speech Language Modeling via Energy Distance in Continuous Latent Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-speech-language-modeling-via-energy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce SLED, an alternative approach to speech language modeling by encoding speech waveforms into sequences of continuous latent representations and modeling them autoregressively using an energy distance objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-speech-language-modeling-via-energy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow-FT: Tuning Instruct via Base</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadow-ft-tuning-instruct-via-base</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key insight is to fine-tune the BASE model, and then directly graft the learned weight updates to the INSTRUCT model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadow-ft-tuning-instruct-via-base</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Turn-Taking and Backchannel in Human-Machine Conversations Using Linguistic, Acoustic, and Visual Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-turn-taking-and-backchannel-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From this, we construct a Multi-Modal Face-to-Face (MM-F2F) human conversation dataset, including over 1. 5M words and corresponding turn-taking and backchannel annotations from approximately 20M frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-turn-taking-and-backchannel-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardware-Adaptive and Superlinear-Capacity Memristor-based Associative Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardware-adaptive-and-superlinear-capacity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we introduce and experimentally demonstrate on integrated memristor hardware a new hardware-adaptive learning algorithm for associative memories that significantly improves defect tolerance and capacity, and naturally extends to scalable multilayer architectures capable of handling both binary and continuous patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardware-adaptive-and-superlinear-capacity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALM-PDE: Continuous and Adaptive Convolutions for Latent Space Modeling of Time-dependent PDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calm-pde-continuous-and-adaptive-convolutions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While these approaches reduce computational complexity, they often use Transformer-based attention mechanisms to handle irregularly sampled domains, resulting in increased memory consumption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calm-pde-continuous-and-adaptive-convolutions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Degradation-Aware Feature Perturbation for All-in-One Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/degradation-aware-feature-perturbation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, motivated by the routing strategy, we propose DFPIR, a novel all-in-one image restorer that introduces Degradation-aware Feature Perturbations(DFP) to adjust the feature space to align with the unified parameter space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/degradation-aware-feature-perturbation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoMat: Enabling Automated Crystal Structure Reconstruction from Microscopy via Agentic Tool Use</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automat-enabling-automated-crystal-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning-based interatomic potentials and force fields depend critically on accurate atomic structures, yet such data are scarce due to the limited availability of experimentally resolved crystals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automat-enabling-automated-crystal-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Reward Model Evaluation Through the Lens of Reward Overoptimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-reward-model-evaluation-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reward models (RMs) play a crucial role in reinforcement learning from human feedback (RLHF), aligning model behavior with human preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-reward-model-evaluation-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$μ$PC: Scaling Predictive Coding to 100+ Layer Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-pc-scaling-predictive-coding-to-100-layer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The biological implausibility of backpropagation (BP) has motivated many alternative, brain-inspired algorithms that attempt to rely only on local information, such as predictive coding (PC) and equilibrium propagation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-pc-scaling-predictive-coding-to-100-layer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiBOG: Lifelong Learning for Black-Box Optimizer Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/libog-lifelong-learning-for-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore a novel paradigm of lifelong learning in MetaBBO and introduce LiBOG, a novel approach designed to learn from sequentially encountered problems and generate high-performance optimizers for Black-Box Optimization (BBO).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/libog-lifelong-learning-for-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-KG-Bench 3.0: A Compass for SemanticTechnology Capabilities in the Ocean of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-kg-bench-3-0-a-compass-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper the LLM-KG-Bench framework is presented in Version 3 along with a dataset of prompts, answers and evaluations generated with it and several state-of-the-art LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-kg-bench-3-0-a-compass-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MatPredict: a dataset and benchmark for learning material properties of diverse indoor objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matpredict-a-dataset-and-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To support this, we introduce MatPredict, a dataset that combines the high-quality synthetic objects from Replica dataset with MatSynth dataset's material properties classes - to create objects with diverse material properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matpredict-a-dataset-and-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picturized and Recited with Dialects: A Multimodal Chinese Representation Framework for Sentiment Analysis of Classical Chinese Poetry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/picturized-and-recited-with-dialects-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a dialect-enhanced multimodal framework for classical Chinese poetry sentiment analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/picturized-and-recited-with-dialects-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R3: Robust Rubric-Agnostic Reward Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r3-robust-rubric-agnostic-reward-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reward models are essential for aligning language model outputs with human preferences, yet existing approaches often lack both controllability and interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r3-robust-rubric-agnostic-reward-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Anytime Reasoning via Budget Relative Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-anytime-reasoning-via-budget</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, such methods optimize only the final performance under a large and fixed token budget, which hinders efficiency in both training and deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-anytime-reasoning-via-budget</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGI-1: Autoregressive Video Generation at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magi-1-autoregressive-video-generation-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present MAGI-1, a world model that generates videos by autoregressively predicting a sequence of video chunks, defined as fixed-length segments of consecutive frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magi-1-autoregressive-video-generation-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-PRM: Enhancing Multimodal Mathematical Reasoning with Scalable Step-Level Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-prm-enhancing-multimodal-mathematical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) have achieved impressive progress in vision-language understanding, they still struggle with complex multi-step reasoning, often producing logically inconsistent or partially correct solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-prm-enhancing-multimodal-mathematical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Sequential Numerical Prediction in Autoregressive Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-sequential-numerical-prediction-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoregressive models have become the de facto choice for sequence generation tasks, but standard approaches treat digits as independent tokens and apply cross-entropy loss, overlooking the coherent structure of numerical sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-sequential-numerical-prediction-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StarFT: Robust Fine-tuning of Zero-shot Models via Spuriosity Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/starft-robust-fine-tuning-of-zero-shot-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a regularization that aligns the output distribution for spuriosity-injected labels with the original zero-shot model, ensuring that the model is not induced to extract irrelevant features further from these descriptions. We leverage recent language models to get such spuriosity-injected labels by generating alternative textual descriptions that highlight potentially confounding features. Extensive experiments validate the robust generalization of StarFT and its emerging properties: zero-shot group robustness and improved zero-shot classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/starft-robust-fine-tuning-of-zero-shot-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising Diffusion Probabilistic Model for Point Cloud Compression at Low Bit-Rates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-probabilistic-model-for-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficient compression of low-bit-rate point clouds is critical for bandwidth-constrained applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-probabilistic-model-for-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimeSeriesGym: A Scalable Benchmark for (Time Series) Machine Learning Engineering Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timeseriesgym-a-scalable-benchmark-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we implement evaluation mechanisms for multiple research artifacts, including submission files, code, and models, using both precise numeric measures and more flexible LLM-based evaluation approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timeseriesgym-a-scalable-benchmark-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlowPure: Continuous Normalizing Flows for Adversarial Purification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowpure-continuous-normalizing-flows-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant advancements in the area, adversarial robustness remains a critical challenge in systems employing machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowpure-continuous-normalizing-flows-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinkless: LLM Learns When to Think</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thinkless-llm-learns-when-to-think</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reasoning Language Models, capable of extended chain-of-thought reasoning, have demonstrated remarkable performance on tasks requiring complex logical inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thinkless-llm-learns-when-to-think</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBF++: Quantifying and Optimizing Reasoning Boundaries across Measurable and Unmeasurable Capabilities for Chain-of-Thought Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rbf-quantifying-and-optimizing-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, two primary challenges remain for real-world applications: (1) the lack of quantitative metrics and actionable guidelines for evaluating and optimizing measurable boundaries of CoT capability, and (2) the absence of methods to assess boundaries of unmeasurable CoT capability, such as multimodal perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rbf-quantifying-and-optimizing-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaptThink: Reasoning Models Can Learn When to Think</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptthink-reasoning-models-can-learn-when-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, large reasoning models have achieved impressive performance on various tasks by employing human-like deep thinking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptthink-reasoning-models-can-learn-when-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Step Offline Distillation of Diffusion-based Models via Koopman Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-step-offline-distillation-of-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide theoretical justification for our approach: (1) under mild assumptions, the learned diffusion dynamics admit a finite-dimensional Koopman representation; and (2) proximity in the Koopman latent space correlates with semantic similarity in the generated outputs, allowing for effective trajectory alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-step-offline-distillation-of-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VTBench: Evaluating Visual Tokenizers for Autoregressive Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vtbench-evaluating-visual-tokenizers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we introduce VTBench, a comprehensive benchmark that systematically evaluates VTs across three core tasks: Image Reconstruction, Detail Preservation, and Text Preservation, and covers a diverse range of evaluation scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vtbench-evaluating-visual-tokenizers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uniformity First: Uniformity-aware Test-time Adaptation of Vision-language Models against Image Corruption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniformity-first-uniformity-aware-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We found that this is because image embeddings are "corrupted" in terms of uniformity, a measure related to the amount of information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniformity-first-uniformity-aware-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G1: Bootstrapping Perception and Reasoning Abilities of Vision-Language Model via Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g1-bootstrapping-perception-and-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-Language Models (VLMs) excel in many direct multimodal tasks but struggle to translate this prowess into effective decision-making within interactive, visually rich environments like games.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g1-bootstrapping-perception-and-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEALLM: Advancing Facial Emotion Analysis in Multimodal Large Language Models with Emotional Synergy and Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feallm-advancing-facial-emotion-analysis-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial Emotion Analysis (FEA) plays a crucial role in visual affective computing, aiming to infer a person's emotional state based on facial data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feallm-advancing-facial-emotion-analysis-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DD-Ranking: Rethinking the Evaluation of Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dd-ranking-rethinking-the-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, dataset distillation has provided a reliable solution for data compression, where models trained on the resulting smaller synthetic datasets achieve performance comparable to those trained on the original datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dd-ranking-rethinking-the-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recollection from Pensieve: Novel View Synthesis via Learning from Uncalibrated Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recollection-from-pensieve-novel-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first stage, we learn to reconstruct the scene implicitly in a latent space without relying on any explicit 3D representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recollection-from-pensieve-novel-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Automation to Autonomy: A Survey on Large Language Models in Scientific Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-automation-to-autonomy-a-survey-on-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are catalyzing a paradigm shift in scientific discovery, evolving from task-specific automation tools into increasingly autonomous agents and fundamentally redefining research processes and human-AI collaboration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-automation-to-autonomy-a-survey-on-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Functional: Learning Function to Scalar Maps for Neural PDE Surrogates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-functional-learning-function-to-scalar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many architectures for neural PDE surrogates have been proposed in recent years, largely based on neural networks or operator learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-functional-learning-function-to-scalar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRAbench and GenEval: Scaling Fine-Grained Aspect Evaluation across Tasks, Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frabench-and-geneval-scaling-fine-grained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating the open-ended outputs of large language models (LLMs) has become a bottleneck as model capabilities, task diversity, and modality coverage rapidly expand.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frabench-and-geneval-scaling-fine-grained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The role of data partitioning on the performance of EEG-based deep learning models in supervised cross-subject analysis: a preliminary study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-role-of-data-partitioning-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To assist researchers in identifying optimal experimental strategies, this paper thoroughly investigates the role of data partitioning and cross-validation in evaluating EEG deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-role-of-data-partitioning-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEM: Gaussian Embedding Modeling for Out-of-Distribution Detection in GUI Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gem-gaussian-embedding-modeling-for-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional OOD detection methods perform suboptimally in this domain due to the complex embedding space and evolving GUI environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gem-gaussian-embedding-modeling-for-out-of</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
