<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 21:08:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>An Incremental Phase Mapping Approach for X-ray Diffraction Patterns using Binary Peak Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-incremental-phase-mapping-approach-for-x</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the huge advancement in knowledge discovery and data mining techniques, the X-ray diffraction (XRD) analysis process has mostly remained untouched and still involves manual investigation, comparison, and verification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-incremental-phase-mapping-approach-for-x</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new BART prior for flexible modeling with categorical predictors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-bart-prior-for-flexible-modeling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Regression trees built with these indicators partition the levels using a ``remove one a time strategy.'']]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-bart-prior-for-flexible-modeling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Graph Neural Networks at Scale: Combining Approximate PageRank and CoreRank</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-graph-neural-networks-at-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have achieved great successes in many learning tasks performed on graph structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-graph-neural-networks-at-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Determining Accessible Sidewalk Width by Extracting Obstacle Information from Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/determining-accessible-sidewalk-width-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Obstacles on the sidewalk often block the path, limiting passage and resulting in frustration and wasted time, especially for citizens and visitors who use assistive devices (wheelchairs, walkers, strollers, canes, etc).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/determining-accessible-sidewalk-width-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Individualized and Global Feature Attributions for Gradient Boosted Trees in the Presence of $\ell_2$ Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individualized-and-global-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Prediction Decomposition Attribution (PreDecomp), a novel individualized feature attribution for gradient boosted trees when they are trained with $\ell_2$ regularization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individualized-and-global-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reduced Order Probabilistic Emulation for Physics-Based Thermosphere Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduced-order-probabilistic-emulation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The geospace environment is volatile and highly driven.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduced-order-probabilistic-emulation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third-Party Aligner for Neural Word Alignments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/third-party-aligner-for-neural-word</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Word alignment is to find translationally equivalent words between source and target sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/third-party-aligner-for-neural-word</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When &amp; How to Transfer with Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-how-to-transfer-with-transfer-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In deep learning, transfer learning (TL) has become the de facto approach when dealing with image related tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-how-to-transfer-with-transfer-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dynamic Graph Interactive Framework with Label-Semantic Injection for Spoken Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamic-graph-interactive-framework-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-intent detection and slot filling joint models are gaining increasing traction since they are closer to complicated real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamic-graph-interactive-framework-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Summarization via Node Grouping: A Spectral Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-summarization-via-node-grouping-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By initially allowing relaxed (fractional) solutions for integer maximization, we analytically expose the underlying connections to the spectral properties of the adjacency matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-summarization-via-node-grouping-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Shortcuts in Medical Images - A Case Study in Chest X-rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-shortcuts-in-medical-images-a-case</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The availability of large public datasets and the increased amount of computing power have shifted the interest of the medical community to high-performance algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-shortcuts-in-medical-images-a-case</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preserving Semantics in Textual Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-semantics-in-textual-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of this kind of adversarial attack is to modify the input text to fool a classifier while maintaining the original meaning of the text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-semantics-in-textual-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning advisor networks for noisy image classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-advisor-networks-for-noisy-image-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduced the novel concept of advisor network to address the problem of noisy labels in image classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-advisor-networks-for-noisy-image-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleviating Sparsity of Open Knowledge Graphs with Ternary Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alleviating-sparsity-of-open-knowledge-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparsity of formal knowledge and roughness of non-ontological construction make sparsity problem particularly prominent in Open Knowledge Graphs (OpenKGs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alleviating-sparsity-of-open-knowledge-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOD-D: On Unsupervised Graph Out-Of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/good-d-on-unsupervised-graph-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a pioneering work in unsupervised graph-level OOD detection, we build a comprehensive benchmark to compare our proposed approach with different state-of-the-art methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/good-d-on-unsupervised-graph-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLATE: A Sequence Labeling Approach for Task Extraction from Free-form Inked Content</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slate-a-sequence-labeling-approach-for-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SLATE, a sequence labeling approach for extracting tasks from free-form content such as digitally handwritten (or "inked") notes on a virtual whiteboard.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slate-a-sequence-labeling-approach-for-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubly Inhomogeneous Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doubly-inhomogeneous-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, by borrowing information over time and population, it allows us to detect weaker signals and has better convergence properties when compared to applying the clustering algorithm per time or the change point detection algorithm per subject.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doubly-inhomogeneous-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Discovery in Linear Latent Variable Models Subject to Measurement Error</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-in-linear-latent-variable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate a somewhat surprising connection between this problem and causal discovery in the presence of unobserved parentless causes, in the sense that there is a mapping, given by the mixing matrix, between the underlying models to be inferred in these problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-in-linear-latent-variable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Data Depth via Multi-Armed Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-data-depth-via-multi-armed-bandits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, we may want to find the most central point in a data set (a generalized median), or to identify and remove all outliers (points on the fringe of the data set with low depth).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-data-depth-via-multi-armed-bandits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPEN: Probing Conceptual Knowledge in Pre-trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copen-probing-conceptual-knowledge-in-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe this is a critical bottleneck for realizing human-like cognition in PLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copen-probing-conceptual-knowledge-in-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReLoc: A Restoration-Assisted Framework for Robust Image Tampering Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reloc-a-restoration-assisted-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ReLoc framework mainly consists of an image restoration module and a tampering localization module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reloc-a-restoration-assisted-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective compression learning of latent representations for variable-rate image compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-compression-learning-of-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this, we first generate a 3D importance map as the nature of input content to represent the underlying importance of the representation elements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-compression-learning-of-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Unstructured Knowledge Access in Conversational Dialogue with ASR Errors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-unstructured-knowledge-access-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge cluster classification is boosted from 0. 7924 to 0. 9333 in Recall@1.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-unstructured-knowledge-access-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Significance-Based Categorical Data Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/significance-based-categorical-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a by-product, we can further calculate an empirical $p$-value to assess the statistical significance of a set of clusters and develop an improved gap statistic for estimating the cluster number.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/significance-based-categorical-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELLS: A Parallel Corpus for Biomedical Lay Language Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cells-a-parallel-corpus-for-biomedical-lay</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent lay language generation systems have used Transformer models trained on a parallel corpus to increase health information accessibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cells-a-parallel-corpus-for-biomedical-lay</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AX-MABSA: A Framework for Extremely Weakly Supervised Multi-label Aspect Based Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ax-mabsa-a-framework-for-extremely-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aspect Based Sentiment Analysis is a dominant research area with potential applications in social media analytics, business, finance, and health.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ax-mabsa-a-framework-for-extremely-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-Machine Collaboration Approaches to Build a Dialogue Dataset for Hate Speech Countering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-machine-collaboration-approaches-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fighting online hate speech is a challenge that is usually addressed using Natural Language Processing via automatic detection and removal of hate content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-machine-collaboration-approaches-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black-Box Attack against GAN-Generated Image Detector with Contrastive Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/black-box-attack-against-gan-generated-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is significant to assess the vulnerability of such forensic detectors against adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/black-box-attack-against-gan-generated-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Change-Point Detection in Time Series via Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-change-point-detection-in-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show how to automatically generate new detection methods based on training a neural network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-change-point-detection-in-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERNIE-SAT: Speech and Text Joint Pretraining for Cross-Lingual Multi-Speaker Text-to-Speech</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ernie-sat-speech-and-text-joint-pretraining-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we extend the pretraining method for cross-lingual multi-speaker speech synthesis tasks, including cross-lingual multi-speaker voice cloning and cross-lingual multi-speaker speech editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ernie-sat-speech-and-text-joint-pretraining-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Word Embedding Model Is Perfect: Evaluating the Representation Accuracy for Social Bias in the Media</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-word-embedding-model-is-perfect-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To cover the whole spectrum of political bias in the US, we collect 500k articles and review psychology literature with respect to expected social bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-word-embedding-model-is-perfect-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Max-Min Off-Policy Actor-Critic Method Focusing on Worst-Case Robustness to Model Misspecification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/max-min-off-policy-actor-critic-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we focus on scenarios involving a simulation environment with uncertainty parameters and the set of their possible values, called the uncertainty parameter set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/max-min-off-policy-actor-critic-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pyGSL: A Graph Structure Learning Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pygsl-a-graph-structure-learning-toolkit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implementations of differentiable graph structure learning models are written in PyTorch, allowing us to leverage the rich software ecosystem that exists e. g., around logging, hyperparameter search, and GPU-communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pygsl-a-graph-structure-learning-toolkit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Denoising Diffusions to Denoising Markov Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-denoising-diffusions-to-denoising-markov</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Denoising diffusions are state-of-the-art generative models which exhibit remarkable empirical performance and come with theoretical guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-denoising-diffusions-to-denoising-markov</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Horseshoe Estimation via Expectation-Maximisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-horseshoe-estimation-via-expectation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A particular strength of our approach is that the M-step depends only on the form of the prior and it is independent of the form of the likelihood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-horseshoe-estimation-via-expectation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Much Does Attention Actually Attend? Questioning the Importance of Attention in Pretrained Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-much-does-attention-actually-attend</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results motivate research on simpler alternatives to input-dependent attention, as well as on methods for better utilization of this mechanism in the Transformer architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-much-does-attention-actually-attend</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving Frame Net: SE(3)-Equivariant Network for Volumes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moving-frame-net-se-3-equivariant-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Equivariance of neural networks to transformations helps to improve their performance and reduce generalization error in computer vision tasks, as they apply to datasets presenting symmetries (e. g. scalings, rotations, translations).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moving-frame-net-se-3-equivariant-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Set Covering to Generate Databases for Holistic Steganalysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-set-covering-to-generate-databases-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within an operational framework, covers used by a steganographer are likely to come from different sensors and different processing pipelines than the ones used by researchers for training their steganalysis models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-set-covering-to-generate-databases-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private Set Generation with Discriminative Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/private-set-generation-with-discriminative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Differentially private data generation techniques have become a promising solution to the data privacy challenge -- it enables sharing of data while complying with rigorous privacy guarantees, which is essential for scientific progress in sensitive domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/private-set-generation-with-discriminative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reranking Overgenerated Responses for End-to-End Task-Oriented Dialogue Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reranking-overgenerated-responses-for-end-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At training, the high-scoring partition comprises all generated responses whose similarity to the gold response is higher than the similarity of the greedy response to the gold response.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reranking-overgenerated-responses-for-end-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debiasing Graph Transfer Learning via Item Semantic Clustering for Cross-Domain Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-graph-transfer-learning-via-item</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this data sparsity problem, cross-domain recommender systems (CDRSs) exploit the data from an auxiliary source domain to facilitate the recommendation on the sparse target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-graph-transfer-learning-via-item</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SC-DepthV3: Robust Self-supervised Monocular Depth Estimation for Dynamic Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sc-depthv3-robust-self-supervised-monocular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised monocular depth estimation has shown impressive results in static scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sc-depthv3-robust-self-supervised-monocular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum-based Asymmetric Multi-task Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-based-asymmetric-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the negative influence of customizing the one-off training order in curriculum-based AMTL, CAMRL switches its training mode between parallel single-task RL and asymmetric multi-task RL (MTRL), according to an indicator regarding the training time, the overall performance, and the performance gap among tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-based-asymmetric-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HFedMS: Heterogeneous Federated Learning with Memorable Data Semantics in Industrial Metaverse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hfedms-heterogeneous-federated-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL), as a rapidly evolving privacy-preserving collaborative machine learning paradigm, is a promising approach to enable edge intelligence in the emerging Industrial Metaverse.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hfedms-heterogeneous-federated-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeSOTIF: a Challenging Visual Dataset for Perception SOTIF Problems in Long-tail Traffic Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pesotif-a-challenging-visual-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Perception algorithms in autonomous driving systems confront great challenges in long-tail traffic scenarios, where the problems of Safety of the Intended Functionality (SOTIF) could be triggered by the algorithm performance insufficiencies and dynamic operational environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pesotif-a-challenging-visual-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlphaPose: Whole-Body Regional Multi-Person Pose Estimation and Tracking in Real-Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alphapose-whole-body-regional-multi-person</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate whole-body multi-person pose estimation and tracking is an important yet challenging topic in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alphapose-whole-body-regional-multi-person</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLOPT: Bandit Optimization Framework for Mutation-Based Fuzzing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slopt-bandit-optimization-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fuzzing can be optimized when targeting specific programs, and given that, some studies have employed online optimization methods to do it automatically, i. e., tuning fuzzers for any given program in a program-agnostic manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slopt-bandit-optimization-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accented Text-to-Speech Synthesis with a Conditional Variational Autoencoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accented-text-to-speech-synthesis-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accent plays a significant role in speech communication, influencing understanding capabilities and also conveying a person's identity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accented-text-to-speech-synthesis-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TLP: A Deep Learning-based Cost Model for Tensor Program Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tlp-a-deep-learning-based-cost-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of extracting features from the tensor program itself, TLP extracts features from the schedule primitives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tlp-a-deep-learning-based-cost-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fixing Model Bugs with Natural Language Patches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fixing-model-bugs-with-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current approaches for fixing systematic problems in NLP models (e. g. regex patches, finetuning on more data) are either brittle, or labor-intensive and liable to shortcuts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fixing-model-bugs-with-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
