<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 09:15:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Deep learning for predicting the occurrence of tipping points</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-predicting-the-occurrence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to predict the occurrence of tipping points from time series data remains an outstanding challenge and a major interest in a broad range of research fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-predicting-the-occurrence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Agent Trajectory Prediction with Difficulty-Guided Feature Enhancement Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-trajectory-prediction-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional methods usually perform holistic inference on the trajectories of agents, neglecting the differences in prediction difficulty among agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-trajectory-prediction-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do We Really Need Graph Convolution During Training? Light Post-Training Graph-ODE for Efficient Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-we-really-need-graph-convolution-during</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The efficiency and scalability of graph convolution networks (GCNs) in training recommender systems (RecSys) have been persistent concerns, hindering their deployment in real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-we-really-need-graph-convolution-during</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Robustification via Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-robustification-via-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial robustness has been conventionally believed as a challenging property to encode for neural networks, requiring plenty of training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-robustification-via-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AppWorld: A Controllable World of Apps and People for Benchmarking Interactive Coding Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/appworld-a-controllable-world-of-apps-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To remedy this gap, we built $\textbf{AppWorld Engine}$, a high-quality execution environment (60K lines of code) of 9 day-to-day apps operable via 457 APIs and populated with realistic digital activities simulating the lives of ~100 fictitious users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/appworld-a-controllable-world-of-apps-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Dysarthric Speech Recognition for Unseen Speakers via Prototype-Based Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-dysarthric-speech-recognition-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we introduce a prototype-based approach that markedly improves DSR performance for unseen dysarthric speakers without additional fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-dysarthric-speech-recognition-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReALFRED: An Embodied Instruction Following Benchmark in Photo-Realistic Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realfred-an-embodied-instruction-following</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge the gap between these learning environments and deploying (i. e., real) environments, we propose the ReALFRED benchmark that employs real-world scenes, objects, and room layouts to learn agents to complete household tasks by understanding free-form language instructions and interacting with objects in large, multi-room and 3D-captured scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realfred-an-embodied-instruction-following</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Graph Structure as Prompt: Improving Small Language Models Capabilities for Knowledge-based Causal Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graph-structure-as-prompt-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the capabilities of Small Language Models (SLMs, defined as LLMs with fewer than 1 billion parameters) with prompt-based learning for knowledge-based causal discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graph-structure-as-prompt-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VSSD: Vision Mamba with Non-Casual State Space Duality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vssd-vision-mamba-with-non-casual-state-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, State Space Duality (SSD), an improved variant of SSMs, was introduced in Mamba2 to enhance model performance and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vssd-vision-mamba-with-non-casual-state-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Dependence Measures to Prevent Shortcut Learning in Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-dependence-measures-to-prevent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical imaging cohorts are often confounded by factors such as acquisition devices, hospital sites, patient backgrounds, and many more.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-dependence-measures-to-prevent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMPISD-MTPNet: Scene Semantic Prior-Assisted Infrared Ship Detection Using Multi-Task Perception Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smpisd-mtpnet-scene-semantic-prior-assisted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose the Scene Semantic Prior-Assisted Multi-Task Perception Network (SMPISD-MTPNet), which includes three stages: scene semantic extraction, deep feature extraction, and prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smpisd-mtpnet-scene-semantic-prior-assisted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness Definitions in Language Models Explained</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-definitions-in-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we begin with a brief introduction to LMs and fairness in LMs, followed by a comprehensive, up-to-date overview of existing fairness notions in LMs and the introduction of a novel taxonomy that categorizes these concepts based on their foundational principles and operational distinctions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-definitions-in-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is larger always better? Evaluating and prompting large language models for non-generative medical tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-larger-always-better-evaluating-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The use of Large Language Models (LLMs) in medicine is growing, but their ability to handle both structured Electronic Health Record (EHR) data and unstructured clinical notes is not well-studied.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-larger-always-better-evaluating-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Cross-Domain Point Classification via Distilling Relational Priors from 2D Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-cross-domain-point-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic pattern of an object point cloud is determined by its topological configuration of local geometries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-cross-domain-point-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Role-specific Guided Large Language Model for Ophthalmic Consultation Based on Stylistic Differentiation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-role-specific-guided-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ophthalmology consultations are crucial for diagnosing, treating, and preventing eye diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-role-specific-guided-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Universal Prompting Strategy for Extracting Process Model Information from Natural Language Text using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-universal-prompting-strategy-for-extracting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the past decade, extensive research efforts have been dedicated to the extraction of information from textual process descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-universal-prompting-strategy-for-extracting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Flexible and Scalable Approach for Collecting Wildlife Advertisements on the Web</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-flexible-and-scalable-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, given that the volume of data is staggering, we need scalable mechanisms to acquire, filter, and store the ads, as well as to make them available for analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-flexible-and-scalable-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOoSE: Multi-Orientation Sharing Experts for Open-set Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moose-multi-orientation-sharing-experts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we first propose a Multi-Oriented Open-Set Text Recognition task (MOOSTR) to model the challenges of both novel characters and writing direction variety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moose-multi-orientation-sharing-experts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Molecule Optimization with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/small-molecule-optimization-with-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models have opened new possibilities for generative molecular drug design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/small-molecule-optimization-with-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HybridDepth: Robust Depth Fusion for Mobile AR by Leveraging Depth from Focus and Single-Image Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybriddepth-robust-depth-fusion-for-mobile-ar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through comprehensive quantitative and qualitative analyses, we demonstrate that HYBRIDDEPTH not only outperforms state-of-the-art (SOTA) models in common datasets (DDFF12, NYU Depth v2) and a real-world AR dataset ARKitScenes but also demonstrates strong zero-shot generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybriddepth-robust-depth-fusion-for-mobile-ar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Decoupling Learning and Metric-Adaptive Thresholding for Semi-Supervised Multi-Label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-decoupling-learning-and-metric-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a dual-perspective method to generate high-quality pseudo-labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-decoupling-learning-and-metric-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reshape Dimensions Network for Speaker Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reshape-dimensions-network-for-speaker-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present Reshape Dimensions Network (ReDimNet), a novel neural network architecture for extracting utterance-level speaker representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reshape-dimensions-network-for-speaker-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detection of manatee vocalisations using the Audio Spectrogram Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-of-manatee-vocalisations-using-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel end-to-end approach to detect manatee vocalisations building on the Audio Spectrogram Transformer (AST).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-of-manatee-vocalisations-using-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse vs Contiguous Adversarial Pixel Perturbations in Multimodal Models: An Empirical Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-vs-contiguous-adversarial-pixel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our attacks target less than 0. 04% of perturbed image area and integrate different spatial positioning of perturbed pixels: sparse positioning and pixels arranged in different contiguous shapes (row, column, diagonal, and patch).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-vs-contiguous-adversarial-pixel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmentation by registration-enabled SAM prompt engineering using five reference images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-by-registration-enabled-sam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach utilises established image registration algorithms to align the new image (to-be-segmented) and a small number of reference images, without requiring segmentation labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-by-registration-enabled-sam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating learning-independent abstract reasoning in artificial neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-learning-independent-abstract</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, assuming a similarity between the cognitive processing of Artificial Neural Networks (ANNs) and humans, the extent to which training is required for ANNs' abstract reasoning is informative about this question in humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-learning-independent-abstract</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move and Act: Enhanced Object Manipulation and Background Integrity for Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/move-and-act-enhanced-object-manipulation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these methods lack control over the generation position of the edited object and have issues with background preservation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/move-and-act-enhanced-object-manipulation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RefMask3D: Language-Guided Transformer for 3D Referring Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refmask3d-language-guided-transformer-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D referring segmentation is an emerging and challenging vision-language task that aims to segment the object described by a natural language expression in a point cloud scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refmask3d-language-guided-transformer-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FADAS: Towards Federated Adaptive Asynchronous Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fadas-towards-federated-adaptive-asynchronous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) has emerged as a widely adopted training paradigm for privacy-preserving machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fadas-towards-federated-adaptive-asynchronous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KiVA: Kid-inspired Visual Analogies for Testing Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kiva-kid-inspired-visual-analogies-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates visual analogical reasoning in large multimodal models (LMMs) compared to human adults and children.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kiva-kid-inspired-visual-analogies-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AsEP: Benchmarking Deep Learning Methods for Antibody-specific Epitope Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asep-benchmarking-deep-learning-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AsEP comes with an easy-to-use interface in Python and pre-built graph representations of each antibody-antigen complex while also supporting customizable embedding methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asep-benchmarking-deep-learning-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Side of Function Calling: Pathways to Jailbreaking Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dark-side-of-function-calling-pathways-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable capabilities, but their power comes with significant security considerations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dark-side-of-function-calling-pathways-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Resolution Histopathology Patch Graphs for Ovarian Cancer Subtyping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-resolution-histopathology-patch-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this only exceeded the performance of attention-based multiple instance learning in external validation, with a 93% balanced accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-resolution-histopathology-patch-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LION: Linear Group RNN for 3D Object Detection in Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lion-linear-group-rnn-for-3d-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, we simply introduce a 3D spatial feature descriptor and integrate it into the linear group RNN operators to enhance their spatial features rather than blindly increasing the number of scanning orders for voxel features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lion-linear-group-rnn-for-3d-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervision Improves Diffusion Models for Tabular Data Imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervision-improves-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, the sparsity inherent in tabular data poses challenges for diffusion models in accurately modeling the data manifold, impacting the robustness of these models for data imputation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervision-improves-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation of Neural Responses to Classical Music Using Organoid Intelligence Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-of-neural-responses-to-classical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Organoid intelligence and deep learning models show promise for simulating and analyzing these neural responses to classical music, an area significantly unexplored in computational neuroscience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-of-neural-responses-to-classical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-informed nonlinear vector autoregressive models for the prediction of dynamical systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-nonlinear-vector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning techniques have recently been of great interest for solving differential equations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-nonlinear-vector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Training Data with Lossy Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-training-data-with-lossy-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to capture this trade-off and optimize storage of training data, we propose a `storage scaling law' that describes the joint evolution of test error with sample size and number of bits per image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-training-data-with-lossy-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Numerical Literals in Link Prediction: A Critical Examination of Models and Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/numerical-literals-in-link-prediction-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a methodology to evaluate LP models that incorporate numerical literals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/numerical-literals-in-link-prediction-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEFT-U: Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning for User Personalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peft-u-parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using PEFT-U, we explore the challenge of efficiently personalizing LLMs to accommodate user-specific preferences in the context of diverse user-centered tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peft-u-parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Temporal Causality for Advanced Temporal Action Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-temporal-causality-for-advanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a fundamental task in long-form video understanding, temporal action detection (TAD) aims to capture inherent temporal relations in untrimmed videos and identify candidate actions with precise boundaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-temporal-causality-for-advanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Training of Neural Cellular Automata on Edge Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-training-of-neural-cellular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The disparity in access to machine learning tools for medical imaging across different regions significantly limits the potential for universal healthcare innovation, particularly in remote areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-training-of-neural-cellular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invariance of deep image quality metrics to affine transformations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariance-of-deep-image-quality-metrics-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This methodology involves transforming the distance measured by an arbitrary metric to a common distance representation based on available subjectively rated databases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariance-of-deep-image-quality-metrics-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Driven Neural Collaborative Filtering Model for Paper Source Tracing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-driven-neural-collaborative-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identifying significant references within the complex interrelations of a citation knowledge graph is challenging, which encompasses connections through citations, authorship, keywords, and other relational attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-driven-neural-collaborative-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint RGB-Spectral Decomposition Model Guided Image Enhancement in Mobile Photography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-rgb-spectral-decomposition-model-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The integration of miniaturized spectrometers into mobile devices offers new avenues for image quality enhancement and facilitates novel downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-rgb-spectral-decomposition-model-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MapTune: Advancing ASIC Technology Mapping via Reinforcement Learning Guided Library Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maptune-advancing-asic-technology-mapping-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The effectiveness of MapTune is evaluated on a wide range of benchmarks, different technology libraries and technology mappers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maptune-advancing-asic-technology-mapping-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoRA-Pro: Are Low-Rank Adapters Properly Optimized?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lora-pro-are-low-rank-adapters-properly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method constrains the optimization process, shrinking the performance gap between LoRA and full fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lora-pro-are-low-rank-adapters-properly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Stage Face-Voice Association Learning with Keynote Speaker Diarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stage-face-voice-association-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a ``Multi-stage Face-voice Association Learning with Keynote Speaker Diarization''~(MFV-KSD) framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stage-face-voice-association-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weighted Risk Invariance: Domain Generalization under Invariant Feature Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-risk-invariance-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Invariant models are also supposed to generalize to shifts in the marginal distribution $p(X_{\text{inv}})$ of the extracted features $X_{\text{inv}}$, a type of shift we call an $\textit{invariant covariate shift}$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-risk-invariance-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Data Labeling for Software Vulnerability Prediction Models: How Far Are We?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-data-labeling-for-software</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Background: Software Vulnerability (SV) prediction needs large-sized and high-quality data to perform well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-data-labeling-for-software</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
