<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 09:12:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>AMS-DRL: Learning Multi-Pursuit Evasion for Safe Targeted Navigation of Drones</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ams-drl-learning-multi-pursuit-evasion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safe navigation of drones in the presence of adversarial physical attacks from multiple pursuers is a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ams-drl-learning-multi-pursuit-evasion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BenCoref: A Multi-Domain Dataset of Nominal Phrases and Pronominal Reference Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bencoref-a-multi-domain-dataset-of-nominal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While widely studied for English and other resource-rich languages, research on coreference resolution in Bengali largely remains unexplored due to the absence of relevant datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bencoref-a-multi-domain-dataset-of-nominal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Unified Language Checking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-unified-language-checking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent concerns about undesirable behaviors generated by large language models (LLMs), including non-factual, biased, and hateful language, we find LLMs are inherent multi-task language checkers based on their latent representations of natural and social knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-unified-language-checking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asynchronous Federated Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asynchronous-federated-continual-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel federated learning setting (AFCL) where the continual learning of multiple tasks happens at each client with different orderings and in asynchronous time slots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asynchronous-federated-continual-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness through Aleatoric Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-through-aleatoric-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a unique solution to tackle the often-competing goals of fairness and utility in machine learning classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-through-aleatoric-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A2J-Transformer: Anchor-to-Joint Transformer Network for 3D Interacting Hand Pose Estimation from a Single RGB Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a2j-transformer-anchor-to-joint-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D interacting hand pose estimation from a single RGB image is a challenging task, due to serious self-occlusion and inter-occlusion towards hands, confusing similar appearance patterns between 2 hands, ill-posed joint position mapping from 2D to 3D, etc.. To address these, we propose to extend A2J-the state-of-the-art depth-based 3D single hand pose estimation method-to RGB domain under interacting hand condition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a2j-transformer-anchor-to-joint-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adjustable Privacy using Autoencoder-based Learning Structure</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjustable-privacy-using-autoencoder-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inference centers need more data to have a more comprehensive and beneficial learning model, and for this purpose, they need to collect data from data providers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjustable-privacy-using-autoencoder-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Recommendation: Towards Next-generation Recommender Paradigm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-recommendation-towards-next</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, such a retrieval-based recommender paradigm faces two limitations: 1) the human-generated items in the corpus might fail to satisfy the users' diverse information needs, and 2) users usually adjust the recommendations via passive and inefficient feedback such as clicks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-recommendation-towards-next</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DualRefine: Self-Supervised Depth and Pose Estimation Through Iterative Epipolar Sampling and Refinement Toward Equilibrium</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dualrefine-self-supervised-depth-and-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our novel update pipeline uses a deep equilibrium model framework to iteratively refine depth estimates and a hidden state of feature maps by computing local matching costs based on epipolar geometry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dualrefine-self-supervised-depth-and-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Unsupervised 3D Point Cloud Anomaly Detection using Variational Autoencoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-unsupervised-3d-point-cloud-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a deep variational autoencoder-based unsupervised anomaly detection network adapted to the 3D point cloud and an anomaly score specifically for 3D point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-unsupervised-3d-point-cloud-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T2Ranking: A large-scale Chinese Benchmark for Passage Ranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t2ranking-a-large-scale-chinese-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[T2Ranking comprises more than 300K queries and over 2M unique passages from real-world search engines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t2ranking-a-large-scale-chinese-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Generalization In Robust Invariant Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalization-in-robust-invariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised approaches for learning representations invariant to common transformations are used quite often for object recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalization-in-robust-invariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Unbounded External Archive and Population Size in Preference-based Evolutionary Multi-objective Optimization Using a Reference Point</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-unbounded-external-archive-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we investigate the influence of the UA and population size on the performance of PBEMO algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-unbounded-external-archive-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniSeg: A Prompt-driven Universal Segmentation Model as well as A Strong Representation Learner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniseg-a-prompt-driven-universal-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, UniSeg also beats other pre-trained models on two downstream datasets, providing the community with a high-quality pre-trained model for 3D medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniseg-a-prompt-driven-universal-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inductive Graph Unlearning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inductive-graph-unlearning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To extend machine unlearning to graph data, \textit{GraphEraser} has been proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inductive-graph-unlearning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-Resolving Face Image by Facial Parsing Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolving-face-image-by-facial-parsing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we build a novel parsing map guided face super-resolution network which extracts the face prior (i. e., parsing map) directly from low-resolution face image for the following utilization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolving-face-image-by-facial-parsing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffMimic: Efficient Motion Mimicking with Differentiable Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffmimic-efficient-motion-mimicking-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motion mimicking is a foundational task in physics-based character animation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffmimic-efficient-motion-mimicking-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointCAT: Cross-Attention Transformer for point cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointcat-cross-attention-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based models have significantly advanced natural language processing and computer vision in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointcat-cross-attention-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face Animation with an Attribute-Guided Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-animation-with-an-attribute-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Face animation has achieved much progress in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-animation-with-an-attribute-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making AI Less "Thirsty": Uncovering and Addressing the Secret Water Footprint of AI Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-ai-less-thirsty-uncovering-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The growing carbon footprint of artificial intelligence (AI) models, especially large ones such as GPT-3 and GPT-4, has been undergoing public scrutiny.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-ai-less-thirsty-uncovering-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geometric-aware Pretraining for Vision-centric 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-aware-pretraining-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also conduct experiments on various image backbones and view transformations to validate the efficacy of our approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-aware-pretraining-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT detectors are biased against non-native English writers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-detectors-are-biased-against-non-native</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we evaluate the performance of several widely-used GPT detectors using writing samples from native and non-native English writers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-detectors-are-biased-against-non-native</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micron-BERT: BERT-based Facial Micro-Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/micron-bert-bert-based-facial-micro</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating these components into an end-to-end deep network, the proposed $\mu$-BERT significantly outperforms all previous work in various micro-expression tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/micron-bert-bert-based-facial-micro</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTK-SAP: Improving neural network pruning by aligning training dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntk-sap-improving-neural-network-pruning-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in neural tangent kernel (NTK) theory suggest that the training dynamics of large enough neural networks is closely related to the spectrum of the NTK.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntk-sap-improving-neural-network-pruning-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InterFormer: Real-time Interactive Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interformer-real-time-interactive-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, the model has to repeatedly process the image, the annotator's current click, and the model's feedback of the annotator's former clicks at each step of interaction, resulting in redundant computations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interformer-real-time-interactive-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLPD: Context-Aware Pedestrian Detection via Vision-Language Semantic Self-Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlpd-context-aware-pedestrian-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we propose a self-supervised Vision-Language Semantic (VLS) segmentation method, which learns both fully-supervised pedestrian detection and contextual segmentation via self-generated explicit labels of semantic classes by vision-language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlpd-context-aware-pedestrian-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthesizing Anyone, Anywhere, in Any Pose</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesizing-anyone-anywhere-in-any-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our main contribution is TriA-GAN, a keypoint-guided GAN that can synthesize Anyone, Anywhere, in Any given pose.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesizing-anyone-anywhere-in-any-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask Detection and Classification in Thermal Face Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-detection-and-classification-in-thermal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Face masks are recommended to reduce the transmission of many viruses, especially SARS-CoV-2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-detection-and-classification-in-thermal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instruction Tuning with GPT-4</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-tuning-with-gpt-4</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior work has shown that finetuning large language models (LLMs) using machine-generated instruction-following data enables such models to achieve remarkable zero-shot capabilities on new tasks, and no human-written instructions are needed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-tuning-with-gpt-4</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient SAGE Estimation via Causal Structure Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-sage-estimation-via-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose $d$-SAGE, a method that accelerates SAGE approximation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-sage-estimation-via-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALUDA: Surface-based Automotive Lidar Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saluda-surface-based-automotive-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning models on one labeled dataset that generalize well on another domain is a difficult task, as several shifts might happen between the data domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saluda-surface-based-automotive-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Dependency Transformers: Dependency Tree Emerges from Reversed Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-dependency-transformers-dependency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When looking at an image, we can decompose the scene into entities and their parts as well as obtain the dependencies between them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-dependency-transformers-dependency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SegGPT: Segmenting Everything In Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seggpt-segmenting-everything-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We unify various segmentation tasks into a generalist in-context learning framework that accommodates different kinds of segmentation data by transforming them into the same format of images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seggpt-segmenting-everything-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETPNav: Evolving Topological Planning for Vision-Language Navigation in Continuous Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/etpnav-evolving-topological-planning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To develop a robust VLN-CE agent, we propose a new navigation framework, ETPNav, which focuses on two critical skills: 1) the capability to abstract environments and generate long-range navigation plans, and 2) the ability of obstacle-avoiding control in continuous environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/etpnav-evolving-topological-planning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFAConv: Innovating Spatital Attention and Standard Convolutional Operation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rfaconv-innovating-spatital-attention-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explain the effectiveness of spatial attention from a new perspective, it is that the spatial attention mechanism essentially solves the problem of convolutional kernel parameter sharing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rfaconv-innovating-spatital-attention-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Pareto Front of Multilingual Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-pareto-front-of-multilingual-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our observations, we propose the Double Power Law to predict the unique performance trade-off front in MNMT, which is robust across various languages, data adequacy, and the number of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-pareto-front-of-multilingual-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-task learning for tissue segmentation and tumor detection in colorectal cancer histology slides</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-tissue-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automating tissue segmentation and tumor detection in histopathology images of colorectal cancer (CRC) is an enabler for faster diagnostic pathology workflows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-tissue-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Concept of Forward-Forward Learning Applied to a Multi Output Perceptron</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-concept-of-forward-forward-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The concept of a recently proposed Forward-Forward learning algorithm for fully connected artificial neural networks is applied to a single multi output perceptron for classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-concept-of-forward-forward-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting the Complementarity of 2D and 3D Networks to Address Domain-Shift in 3D Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-the-complementarity-of-2d-and-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D semantic segmentation is a critical task in many real-world applications, such as autonomous driving, robotics, and mixed reality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-the-complementarity-of-2d-and-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PopulAtion Parameter Averaging (PAPA)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/population-parameter-averaging-papa</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ensemble methods combine the predictions of multiple models to improve performance, but they require significantly higher computation costs at inference time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/population-parameter-averaging-papa</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A review of ensemble learning and data augmentation models for class imbalanced problems: combination, implementation and evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-ensemble-learning-and-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a computational review to evaluate data augmentation and ensemble learning methods used to address prominent benchmark CI problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-ensemble-learning-and-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Content-Based Neural News Recommendation: On User Modeling and Training Objectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-content-based-neural-news</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most neural news recommenders rely on user click behavior and typically introduce dedicated user encoders that aggregate the content of clicked news into user embeddings (early fusion).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-content-based-neural-news</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoUnseen: Zero-Shot Object Detection for Robotic Grasping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dounseen-zero-shot-object-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we are interested in open sets where the number of classes is unknown, varying, and without pre-knowledge about the objects' types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dounseen-zero-shot-object-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cerebras-GPT: Open Compute-Optimal Language Models Trained on the Cerebras Wafer-Scale Cluster</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cerebras-gpt-open-compute-optimal-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study recent research advances that improve large language models through efficient pre-training and scaling, and open datasets and tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cerebras-gpt-open-compute-optimal-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-shot Generative Model Adaptation via Image-specific Prompt Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-generative-model-adaptation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, CLIP-guided image synthesis has shown appealing performance on adapting a pre-trained source-domain generator to an unseen target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-generative-model-adaptation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Conformal Prediction for Reliable Uncertainty Quantification in Quantum Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-conformal-prediction-for-reliable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantum machine learning is a promising programming paradigm for the optimization of quantum algorithms in the current era of noisy intermediate scale quantum (NISQ) computers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-conformal-prediction-for-reliable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Coherent Image Inpainting Using Denoising Diffusion Implicit Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-coherent-image-inpainting-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[COPAINT also uses the Bayesian framework to jointly modify both revealed and unrevealed regions, but approximates the posterior distribution in a way that allows the errors to gradually drop to zero throughout the denoising steps, thus strongly penalizing any mismatches with the reference image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-coherent-image-inpainting-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Next-Item Recommendation using Large Pretrained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-next-item-recommendation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have achieved impressive zero-shot performance in various natural language processing (NLP) tasks, demonstrating their capabilities for inference without training examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-next-item-recommendation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TagGPT: Large Language Models are Zero-shot Multimodal Taggers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taggpt-large-language-models-are-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a new entity that needs tagging for distribution, TagGPT introduces two alternative options for zero-shot tagging, i. e., a generative method with late semantic matching with the tag set, and another selective method with early matching in prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taggpt-large-language-models-are-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViralVectors: Compact and Scalable Alignment-free Virome Feature Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/viralvectors-compact-and-scalable-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose \emph{ViralVectors}, a compact feature vector generation from virome sequencing data that allows effective downstream analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/viralvectors-compact-and-scalable-alignment</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
