<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 21:08:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Target Semantics Clustering via Text Representations for Robust Universal Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-semantics-clustering-via-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Universal Domain Adaptation (UniDA) focuses on transferring source domain knowledge to the target domain under both domain shift and unknown category shift.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-semantics-clustering-via-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Makes a Good Diffusion Planner for Decision Making?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-makes-a-good-diffusion-planner-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have recently shown significant potential in solving decision-making problems, particularly in generating behavior plans -- also known as diffusion planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-makes-a-good-diffusion-planner-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BodyGen: Advancing Towards Efficient Embodiment Co-Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bodygen-advancing-towards-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Embodiment co-design aims to optimize a robot's morphology and control policy simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bodygen-advancing-towards-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating convolutional layers and biformer network with forward-forward and backpropagation training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-convolutional-layers-and-biformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate molecular property prediction is crucial for drug discovery and computational chemistry, facilitating the identification of promising compounds and accelerating therapeutic development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-convolutional-layers-and-biformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenTAD: A Unified Framework and Comprehensive Study of Temporal Action Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opentad-a-unified-framework-and-comprehensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal action detection (TAD) is a fundamental video understanding task that aims to identify human actions and localize their temporal boundaries in videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opentad-a-unified-framework-and-comprehensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HVI: A New color space for Low-light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hvi-a-new-color-space-for-low-light-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-Light Image Enhancement (LLIE) is a crucial computer vision task that aims to restore detailed visual information from corrupted low-light images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hvi-a-new-color-space-for-low-light-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReCon: Enhancing True Correspondence Discrimination through Relation Consistency for Robust Noisy Correspondence Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recon-enhancing-true-correspondence-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we propose a general Relation Consistency learning framework, namely ReCon, to accurately discriminate the true correspondences among the multimodal data and thus effectively mitigate the adverse impact caused by mismatches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recon-enhancing-true-correspondence-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SegLocNet: Multimodal Localization Network for Autonomous Driving via Bird's-Eye-View Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seglocnet-multimodal-localization-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on the nuScenes and Argoverse datasets demonstrate that our method outperforms the current state-of-the-art methods, and that our method can accurately estimate the ego pose in urban environments without relying on GNSS, while maintaining strong generalization ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seglocnet-multimodal-localization-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WalnutData: A UAV Remote Sensing Dataset of Green Walnuts and Model Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/walnutdata-a-uav-remote-sensing-dataset-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Currently, there is no dataset related to green walnuts in the field of agricultural computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/walnutdata-a-uav-remote-sensing-dataset-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention Distillation: A Unified Approach to Visual Characteristics Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-distillation-a-unified-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in generative diffusion models have shown a notable inherent understanding of image style and semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-distillation-a-unified-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AsymLoRA: Harmonizing Data Conflicts and Commonalities in MLLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymlora-harmonizing-data-conflicts-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Effective instruction fine-tuning on diverse image-text datasets is crucial for developing a versatile Multimodal Large Language Model (MLLM), where dataset composition dictates the model's adaptability across multimodal tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymlora-harmonizing-data-conflicts-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongRoPE2: Near-Lossless LLM Context Window Scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longrope2-near-lossless-llm-context-window</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LongRoPE2 is a novel approach that extends the effective context window of pre-trained large language models (LLMs) to the target length, while preserving the performance on the original shorter context window.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longrope2-near-lossless-llm-context-window</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playing Pokémon Red via Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/playing-pokemon-red-via-deep-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pok\'emon Red, a classic Game Boy JRPG, presents significant challenges as a testbed for agents, including multi-tasking, long horizons of tens of thousands of steps, hard exploration, and a vast array of potential policies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/playing-pokemon-red-via-deep-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeisMoLLM: Advancing Seismic Monitoring via Cross-modal Transfer with Pre-trained Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seismollm-advancing-seismic-monitoring-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in deep learning have revolutionized seismic monitoring, yet developing a foundation model that performs well across multiple complex tasks remains challenging, particularly when dealing with degraded signals or data scarcity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seismollm-advancing-seismic-monitoring-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniDepthV2: Universal Monocular Metric Depth Estimation Made Simpler</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidepthv2-universal-monocular-metric-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the remarkable accuracy of recent MMDE methods is confined to their training domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidepthv2-universal-monocular-metric-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMKE-Bench: A Multimodal Editing Benchmark for Diverse Visual Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmke-bench-a-multimodal-editing-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge editing techniques have emerged as essential tools for updating the factual knowledge of large language models (LLMs) and multimodal models (LMMs), allowing them to correct outdated or inaccurate information without retraining from scratch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmke-bench-a-multimodal-editing-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoPulse: Short-Term Cryptocurrency Forecasting with Dual-Prediction and Cross-Correlated Market Indicators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cryptopulse-short-term-cryptocurrency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies fluctuate in markets with high price volatility, posing significant challenges for investors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cryptopulse-short-term-cryptocurrency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Language Models Falsify? Evaluating Algorithmic Reasoning with Counterexample Creation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-language-models-falsify-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is growing excitement about the potential of Language Models (LMs) to accelerate scientific discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-language-models-falsify-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AKDT: Adaptive Kernel Dilation Transformer for Effective Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/akdt-adaptive-kernel-dilation-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the core of AKDT, the NE is seamlessly integrated within standard Transformer components to form the Noise-Guided Feed-Forward Network (NG-FFN) and Noise-Guided Multi-Headed Self-Attention (NG-MSA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/akdt-adaptive-kernel-dilation-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reward Shaping to Mitigate Reward Hacking in RLHF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reward-shaping-to-mitigate-reward-hacking-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning from Human Feedback (RLHF) is essential for aligning large language models (LLMs) with human values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reward-shaping-to-mitigate-reward-hacking-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Graph Tasks with Pure LLMs: A Comprehensive Benchmark and Investigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-graph-tasks-with-pure-llms-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, large language models (LLMs) have emerged as promising candidates for graph tasks, yet most studies focus primarily on performance benchmarks and fail to address their broader potential, including their ability to handle limited data, their transferability across tasks, and their robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-graph-tasks-with-pure-llms-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Know You First and Be You Better: Modeling Human-Like User Simulators via Implicit Profiles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/know-you-first-and-be-you-better-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we adopt a diverse profile sampler to capture the distribution of real-world user profiles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/know-you-first-and-be-you-better-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nexus: A Lightweight and Scalable Multi-Agent Framework for Complex Tasks Automation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nexus-a-lightweight-and-scalable-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In coding tasks, Nexus-driven MASs achieve a 99% pass rate on HumanEval and a flawless 100% on VerilogEval-Human, outperforming cutting-edge reasoning language models such as o3-mini and DeepSeek-R1.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nexus-a-lightweight-and-scalable-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distill Any Depth: Distillation Creates a Stronger Monocular Depth Estimator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distill-any-depth-distillation-creates-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we systematically analyze the impact of different depth normalization strategies on pseudo-label distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distill-any-depth-distillation-creates-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poster: Long PHP webshell files detection based on sliding window attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poster-long-php-webshell-files-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a webshell detection method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poster-long-php-webshell-files-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BatteryLife: A Comprehensive Dataset and Benchmark for Battery Life Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batterylife-a-comprehensive-dataset-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, BatteryLife is the first to release battery life datasets of zinc-ion batteries, sodium-ion batteries, and industry-tested large-capacity lithium-ion batteries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batterylife-a-comprehensive-dataset-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM Knows Geometry Better than Algebra: Numerical Understanding of LLM-Based Agents in A Trading Arena</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-knows-geometry-better-than-algebra</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) have significantly improved performance in natural language processing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-knows-geometry-better-than-algebra</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tip of the Tongue Query Elicitation for Simulated Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tip-of-the-tongue-query-elicitation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For human-elicited queries, we developed an interface that uses visual stimuli to place participants in a TOT state, enabling the collection of natural queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tip-of-the-tongue-query-elicitation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FFT Strikes Back: An Efficient Alternative to Self-Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-fft-strikes-back-an-efficient-alternative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional self-attention mechanisms incur quadratic complexity, limiting their scalability on long sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-fft-strikes-back-an-efficient-alternative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escaping The Big Data Paradigm in Self-Supervised Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/escaping-the-big-data-paradigm-in-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce SCOTT (Sparse Convolutional Tokenizer for Transformers), a shallow tokenization architecture that is compatible with Masked Image Modeling (MIM) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/escaping-the-big-data-paradigm-in-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient Trajectory Prediction: Integrating Clinical Notes with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patient-trajectory-prediction-integrating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current models, primarily based on structured data, struggle to capture the complete medical context of patients, resulting in a loss of valuable information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patient-trajectory-prediction-integrating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViDoRAG: Visual Document Retrieval-Augmented Generation via Dynamic Iterative Reasoning Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vidorag-visual-document-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce ViDoSeek, a novel dataset designed to evaluate RAG performance on visually rich documents requiring complex reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vidorag-visual-document-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Offensive Memes with Social Biases in Singapore Context Using Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-offensive-memes-with-social-biases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional online content moderation systems struggle to classify modern multimodal means of communication, such as memes, a highly nuanced and information-dense medium.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-offensive-memes-with-social-biases</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoeni6: a Systematic Approach for Evaluating the Energy Consumption of Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phoeni6-a-systematic-approach-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents Phoeni6, a systematic approach for assessing the energy consumption of neural networks while upholding the principles of fair comparison and reproducibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phoeni6-a-systematic-approach-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WiCkeD: A Simple Method to Make Multiple Choice Benchmarks More Challenging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wicked-a-simple-method-to-make-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of the models drops 12. 1 points on average with respect to the original versions of the datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wicked-a-simple-method-to-make-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S-Graphs 2.0 -- A Hierarchical-Semantic Optimization and Loop Closure for SLAM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-graphs-2-0-a-hierarchical-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Works based on localization and mapping do not exploit the inherent semantic-relational information from the environment for faster and efficient management and optimization of the robot poses and its map elements, often leading to pose and map inaccuracies and computational inefficiencies in large scale environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-graphs-2-0-a-hierarchical-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Vision to Sound: Advancing Audio Anomaly Detection with Vision-Based Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-vision-to-sound-advancing-audio-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in Visual Anomaly Detection (VAD) have introduced sophisticated algorithms leveraging embeddings generated by pre-trained feature extractors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-vision-to-sound-advancing-audio-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RankCoT: Refining Knowledge for Retrieval-Augmented Generation through Ranking Chain-of-Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankcot-refining-knowledge-for-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) enhances the performance of Large Language Models (LLMs) by incorporating external knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankcot-refining-knowledge-for-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Key Factors for Distilling Chain-of-Thought Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-key-factors-for-distilling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) excel in reasoning tasks through Chain-of-Thought (CoT) prompting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-key-factors-for-distilling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling dynamics of stochastic systems with deep reinforcement learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-dynamics-of-stochastic-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A properly designed controller can help improve the quality of experimental measurements or force a dynamical system to follow a completely new time-evolution path.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-dynamics-of-stochastic-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpargeAttn: Accurate Sparse Attention Accelerating Any Model Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spargeattn-accurate-sparse-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A universal sparse attention that guarantees both the speedup and end-to-end performance of diverse models remains elusive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spargeattn-accurate-sparse-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AirCast: Improving Air Pollution Forecasting Through Multi-Variable Data Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aircast-improving-air-pollution-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce AirCast, a novel multi-variable air pollution forecasting model, by combining weather and air quality variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aircast-improving-air-pollution-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Neural Activity with Conditionally Linear Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-neural-activity-with-conditionally</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural population activity exhibits complex, nonlinear dynamics, varying in time, over trials, and across experimental conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-neural-activity-with-conditionally</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIR: Complex Instruction Generation via Automatic Iterative Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/air-complex-instruction-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the development of large language models, their ability to follow simple instructions has significantly improved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/air-complex-instruction-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Multimodal LLMs Perform Time Series Anomaly Detection?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-multimodal-llms-perform-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Starting with the univariate case (point- and range-wise anomalies), we extend our evaluation to more practical scenarios, including multivariate and irregular time series scenarios, and variate-wise anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-multimodal-llms-perform-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recurrent Neural Networks for Dynamic VWAP Execution: Adaptive Trading Strategies with Temporal Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrent-neural-networks-for-dynamic-vwap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The execution of Volume Weighted Average Price (VWAP) orders remains a critical challenge in modern financial markets, particularly as trading volumes and market complexity continue to increase.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrent-neural-networks-for-dynamic-vwap</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaseGen: A Benchmark for Multi-Stage Legal Case Documents Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/casegen-a-benchmark-for-multi-stage-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, CaseGen is the first benchmark designed to evaluate LLMs in the context of legal case document generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/casegen-a-benchmark-for-multi-stage-legal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Structure-Supporting Dependencies via Keypoint Interactive Transformer for General Mammal Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-structure-supporting-dependencies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a Keypoint Interactive Transformer (KIT) to learn instance-level structure-supporting dependencies for general mammal pose estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-structure-supporting-dependencies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A General Framework to Enhance Fine-tuning-based LLM Unlearning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-framework-to-enhance-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlearning has been proposed to remove copyrighted and privacy-sensitive data from Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-framework-to-enhance-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MRBTP: Efficient Multi-Robot Behavior Tree Planning and Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mrbtp-efficient-multi-robot-behavior-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These relevant actions can be pre-planned to form long-horizon subtrees, significantly enhancing the planning speed and collaboration efficiency of MRBTP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mrbtp-efficient-multi-robot-behavior-tree</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
