<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 09:12:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Discriminative Sample-Guided and Parameter-Efficient Feature Space Adaptation for Cross-Domain Few-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discriminative-sample-guided-and-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we look at cross-domain few-shot classification which presents the challenging task of learning new classes in unseen domains with few labelled examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discriminative-sample-guided-and-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphInstruct: Empowering Large Language Models with Graph Understanding and Reasoning Capability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphinstruct-empowering-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate and enhance the graph understanding abilities of LLMs, in this paper, we propose a benchmark named GraphInstruct, which comprehensively includes 21 classical graph reasoning tasks, providing diverse graph generation pipelines and detailed reasoning steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphinstruct-empowering-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster Neighborhood Attention: Reducing the O(n^2) Cost of Self Attention at the Threadblock Level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-neighborhood-attention-reducing-the-o</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that our fused kernels successfully circumvent some of the unavoidable inefficiencies in unfused implementations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-neighborhood-attention-reducing-the-o</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Court View Generation with Knowledge Injection and Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-court-view-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Court View Generation (CVG) is a challenging task in the field of Legal Artificial Intelligence (LegalAI), which aims to generate court views based on the plaintiff claims and the fact descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-court-view-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Recommendation via Hybrid Retrieval Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-recommendation-via-hybrid-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose GPT-FedRec, a federated recommendation framework leveraging ChatGPT and a novel hybrid Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-recommendation-via-hybrid-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAWA: Gradient-based Weighted Averaging for Distributed Training of Deep Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grawa-gradient-based-weighted-averaging-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study distributed training of deep learning models in time-constrained environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grawa-gradient-based-weighted-averaging-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUFormer: Vision Transformers are Parameter-Efficient Facial Action Unit Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auformer-vision-transformers-are-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial Action Units (AU) is a vital concept in the realm of affective computing, and AU detection has always been a hot research topic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auformer-vision-transformers-are-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Large Language Model Understand Multi-Intent Spoken Language ?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-large-language-model-understand-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study marks a significant advancement by harnessing Large Language Models (LLMs) for multi-intent spoken language understanding (SLU), proposing a unique methodology that capitalizes on the generative power of LLMs within an SLU context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-large-language-model-understand-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-PD: How Far Can SAM Take Us in Tracking and Segmenting Anything in Videos by Prompt Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-pd-how-far-can-sam-take-us-in-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, promptable segmentation models, such as the Segment Anything Model (SAM), have demonstrated robust zero-shot generalization capabilities on static images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-pd-how-far-can-sam-take-us-in-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking of Encoder-based Warm-start Methods in Hyperparameter Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-of-encoder-based-warm-start</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our package is based on an established model for heterogeneous tabular data proposed in [Iwata and Kumagai, 2020].]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-of-encoder-based-warm-start</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Graph to Word Bag: Introducing Domain Knowledge to Confusing Charge Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-graph-to-word-bag-introducing-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel From Graph to Word Bag (FWGB) approach, which introduces domain knowledge regarding constituent elements to guide the model in making judgments on confusing charges, much like a judge's reasoning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-graph-to-word-bag-introducing-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Adaptation of Language Models with a Memory of Amortized Contexts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-adaptation-of-language-models-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an amortized feature extraction and memory-augmentation approach to compress and extract information from new documents into compact modulations stored in a memory bank.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-adaptation-of-language-models-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Influence of Dimensionality Reduction on Anomaly Detection Performance in Multivariate Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-influence-of-dimensionality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an extensive empirical study on the integration of dimensionality reduction techniques with advanced unsupervised time series anomaly detection models, focusing on the MUTANT and Anomaly-Transformer models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-influence-of-dimensionality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Learning of Harmonic Analysis Based on Neural HSMM with Code Quality Templates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-of-harmonic-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a method of unsupervised learning of harmonic analysis based on a hidden semi-Markov model (HSMM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-of-harmonic-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAX-SPH: A Differentiable Smoothed Particle Hydrodynamics Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jax-sph-a-differentiable-smoothed-particle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particle-based fluid simulations have emerged as a powerful tool for solving the Navier-Stokes equations, especially in cases that include intricate physics and free surfaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jax-sph-a-differentiable-smoothed-particle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single-Image HDR Reconstruction Assisted Ghost Suppression and Detail Preservation Network for Multi-Exposure HDR Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-image-hdr-reconstruction-assisted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This network, comprising single-frame HDR reconstruction with enhanced stop image (SHDR-ESI) and SHDR-ESI-assisted multi-exposure HDR reconstruction (SHDRA-MHDR), effectively leverages the ghost-free characteristic of single-frame HDR reconstruction and the detail-enhancing capability of ESI in oversaturated areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-image-hdr-reconstruction-assisted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Membership Inference Attacks and Privacy in Topic Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membership-inference-attacks-and-privacy-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research shows that large language models are susceptible to privacy attacks that infer aspects of the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membership-inference-attacks-and-privacy-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the Visual Sim-to-Real Gap with Object-Composable NeRFs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-visual-sim-to-real-gap-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning methods for perception are the cornerstone of many robotic systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-visual-sim-to-real-gap-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ducho 2.0: Towards a More Up-to-Date Feature Extraction and Processing Framework for Multimodal Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ducho-2-0-towards-a-more-up-to-date-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Ducho 2. 0, the latest stable version of our framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ducho-2-0-towards-a-more-up-to-date-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delving into the Trajectory Long-tail Distribution for Muti-object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delving-into-the-trajectory-long-tail</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we pioneer an exploration into the distribution patterns of tracking data and identify a pronounced long-tail distribution issue within existing MOT datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delving-into-the-trajectory-long-tail</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifelong Intelligence Beyond the Edge using Hyperdimensional Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelong-intelligence-beyond-the-edge-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On-device learning has emerged as a prevailing trend that avoids the slow response time and costly communication of cloud-based learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelong-intelligence-beyond-the-edge-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs in the Imaginarium: Tool Learning through Simulated Trial and Error</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-in-the-imaginarium-tool-learning-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that existing LLMs, including GPT-4 and open-source LLMs specifically fine-tuned for tool use, only reach a correctness rate in the range of 30% to 60%, far from reliable use in practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-in-the-imaginarium-tool-learning-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAT: Enhancing Multimodal Large Language Model to Answer Questions in Dynamic Audio-Visual Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-enhancing-multimodal-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper focuses on the challenge of answering questions in scenarios that are composed of rich and complex dynamic audio-visual components.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-enhancing-multimodal-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable Generation with Text-to-Image Diffusion Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-generation-with-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the rapidly advancing realm of visual generation, diffusion models have revolutionized the landscape, marking a significant shift in capabilities with their impressive text-guided generative functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-generation-with-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UltraWiki: Ultra-fine-grained Entity Set Expansion with Negative Seed Entities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultrawiki-ultra-fine-grained-entity-set</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve this issue, we first introduce negative seed entities in the inputs, which belong to the same fine-grained semantic class as the positive seed entities but differ in certain attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultrawiki-ultra-fine-grained-entity-set</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AO-DETR: Anti-Overlapping DETR for X-Ray Prohibited Items Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ao-detr-anti-overlapping-detr-for-x-ray</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering the significant overlapping phenomenon in X-ray prohibited item images, we propose an Anti-Overlapping DETR (AO-DETR) based on one of the state-of-the-art general object detectors, DINO.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ao-detr-anti-overlapping-detr-for-x-ray</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSDRec: Self-Augmented Sequence Denoising for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssdrec-self-augmented-sequence-denoising-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the second stage, we devise a self-augmentation module to augment sequences to alleviate OUPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssdrec-self-augmented-sequence-denoising-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiative Gaussian Splatting for Efficient X-ray Novel View Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radiative-gaussian-splatting-for-efficient-x</link>
      <description><![CDATA[X-ray is widely applied for transmission imaging due to its stronger penetration than natural light.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radiative-gaussian-splatting-for-efficient-x</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Can't Believe It's Not Scene Flow!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-can-t-believe-it-s-not-scene-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current scene flow methods broadly fail to describe motion on small objects, and current scene flow evaluation protocols hide this failure by averaging over many points, with most drawn larger objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-can-t-believe-it-s-not-scene-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computational Modelling of Plurality and Definiteness in Chinese Noun Phrases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-modelling-of-plurality-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on the omission of the plurality and definiteness markers in Chinese noun phrases (NPs) to investigate the predictability of their intended meaning given the contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-modelling-of-plurality-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperparameter Tuning MLPs for Probabilistic Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameter-tuning-mlps-for-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series forecasting attempts to predict future events by analyzing past trends and patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameter-tuning-mlps-for-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextMonkey: An OCR-Free Large Multimodal Model for Understanding Document</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textmonkey-an-ocr-free-large-multimodal-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present TextMonkey, a large multimodal model (LMM) tailored for text-centric tasks, including document question answering (DocVQA) and scene text analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textmonkey-an-ocr-free-large-multimodal-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YYDS: Visible-Infrared Person Re-Identification with Coarse Descriptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yyds-visible-infrared-person-re</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we present the Refer-VI-ReID settings, which aims to match target visible images from both infrared images and coarse language descriptions (e. g., "a man with red top and black pants") to complement the missing color information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yyds-visible-infrared-person-re</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Study of Dropout-Induced Modality Bias on Robustness to Missing Video Frames for Audio-Visual Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-study-of-dropout-induced-modality-bias-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate this contrasting phenomenon from the perspective of modality bias and reveal that an excessive modality bias on the audio caused by dropout is the underlying reason.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-study-of-dropout-induced-modality-bias-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP: MAsk-Pruning for Source-Free Model Intellectual Property Protection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-mask-pruning-for-source-free-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we target a practical setting where only a well-trained source model is available and investigate how we can realize IP protection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-mask-pruning-for-source-free-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Retrieval in Theme-specific Applications using a Corpus Topical Taxonomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-retrieval-in-theme-specific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Document retrieval has greatly benefited from the advancements of large-scale pre-trained language models (PLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-retrieval-in-theme-specific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Far Are We from Intelligent Visual Deductive Reasoning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-are-we-from-intelligent-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-Language Models (VLMs) such as GPT-4V have recently demonstrated incredible strides on diverse vision language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-are-we-from-intelligent-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Source Matters: Source Dataset Impact on Model Robustness in Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/source-matters-source-dataset-impact-on-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the domain shift from natural to medical images has prompted alternatives such as RadImageNet, often demonstrating comparable classification performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/source-matters-source-dataset-impact-on-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QAQ: Quality Adaptive Quantization for LLM KV Cache</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qaq-quality-adaptive-quantization-for-llm-kv</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emergence of LLMs has ignited a fresh surge of breakthroughs in NLP applications, particularly in domains such as question-answering systems and text generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qaq-quality-adaptive-quantization-for-llm-kv</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Generalized Category Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-generalized-category-discovery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalized Category Discovery (GCD) is a pragmatic and challenging open-world task, which endeavors to cluster unlabeled samples from both novel and old classes, leveraging some labeled data of old classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-generalized-category-discovery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Remove Wrinkled Transparent Film with Polarized Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-remove-wrinkled-transparent-film</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim to remove interference from the film (specular highlights and other degradations) with an end-to-end framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-remove-wrinkled-transparent-film</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PPTC-R benchmark: Towards Evaluating the Robustness of Large Language Models for PowerPoint Task Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pptc-r-benchmark-towards-evaluating-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The growing dependence on Large Language Models (LLMs) for finishing user instructions necessitates a comprehensive understanding of their robustness to complex task completion in real-world situations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pptc-r-benchmark-towards-evaluating-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Geolocated Realtime Data of Interfleet Urban Transit Bus Idling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-geolocated-realtime-data-of-interfleet-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Urban transit bus idling is a contributor to ecological stress, economic inefficiency, and medically hazardous health outcomes due to emissions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-geolocated-realtime-data-of-interfleet-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Efficient and Effective Unlearning of Large Language Models for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-and-effective-unlearning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in order to protect user privacy and optimize utility, it is also crucial for LLMRec to intentionally forget specific user data, which is generally referred to as recommendation unlearning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-and-effective-unlearning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Diffusion Policy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-diffusion-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Imitation learning provides an efficient way to teach robots dexterous skills; however, learning complex skills robustly and generalizablely usually consumes large amounts of human demonstrations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-diffusion-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance Evaluation of Semi-supervised Learning Frameworks for Multi-Class Weed Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-evaluation-of-semi-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we assess the effectiveness of a semi-supervised learning framework for multi-class weed detection, employing two well-known object detection frameworks, namely FCOS and Faster-RCNN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-evaluation-of-semi-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Heuristic Core: Understanding Subnetwork Generalization in Pretrained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-heuristic-core-understanding-subnetwork</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of finding competing subnetworks, we find that all subnetworks -- whether they generalize or not -- share a set of attention heads, which we refer to as the heuristic core.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-heuristic-core-understanding-subnetwork</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A&amp;B BNN: Add&amp;Bit-Operation-Only Hardware-Friendly Binary Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-b-bnn-add-bit-operation-only-hardware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A&B BNN is proposed to directly remove part of the multiplication operations in a traditional BNN and replace the rest with an equal number of bit operations, introducing the mask layer and the quantized RPReLU structure based on the normalizer-free network architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-b-bnn-add-bit-operation-only-hardware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GaLore: Memory-Efficient LLM Training by Gradient Low-Rank Projection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galore-memory-efficient-llm-training-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach reduces memory usage by up to 65. 5% in optimizer states while maintaining both efficiency and performance for pre-training on LLaMA 1B and 7B architectures with C4 dataset with up to 19. 7B tokens, and on fine-tuning RoBERTa on GLUE tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galore-memory-efficient-llm-training-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Hallucination in Large Language Models based on Unanswerable Math Word Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-hallucination-in-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new method for evaluating LLM hallucination in Question Answering (QA) based on the unanswerable math word problem (MWP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-hallucination-in-large-language</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
