<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 09:16:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Representation Consistency Model via Contrastive Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-representation-consistency-model-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, our method outperforms the certified accuracy of diffusion-based methods on ImageNet across all perturbation radii by 5. 3% on average, with up to 11. 6% at larger radii, while reducing inference costs by 85$\times$ on average.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-representation-consistency-model-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlanEC: Exploring Flan-T5 for Post-ASR Error Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flanec-exploring-flan-t5-for-post-asr-error</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an encoder-decoder model leveraging Flan-T5 for post-Automatic Speech Recognition (ASR) Generative Speech Error Correction (GenSEC), and we refer to it as FlanEC.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flanec-exploring-flan-t5-for-post-asr-error</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAMED-Snake: Gradient-aware Adaptive Momentum Evolution Deep Snake Model for Multi-organ Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gamed-snake-gradient-aware-adaptive-momentum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-organ segmentation is a critical yet challenging task due to complex anatomical backgrounds, blurred boundaries, and diverse morphologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gamed-snake-gradient-aware-adaptive-momentum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Preference Alignment for Language Models via Count-based Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-preference-alignment-for-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we reformulate our objective to direct preference optimization with an exploration term, where the UCB-term can be converted to a count-based exploration bonus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-preference-alignment-for-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OnionEval: An Unified Evaluation of Fact-conflicting Hallucination for Small-Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onioneval-an-unified-evaluation-of-fact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are highly capable but require significant computational resources for both training and inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onioneval-an-unified-evaluation-of-fact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patent Figure Classification using Large Vision-language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patent-figure-classification-using-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Patent figure classification facilitates faceted search in patent retrieval systems, enabling efficient prior art search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patent-figure-classification-using-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoLLaMA 3: Frontier Multimodal Foundation Models for Image and Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videollama-3-frontier-multimodal-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key insight of our vision-centric training paradigm is that high-quality image-text data is crucial for both image and video understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videollama-3-frontier-multimodal-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViDDAR: Vision Language Model-Based Task-Detrimental Content Detection for Augmented Reality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/viddar-vision-language-model-based-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Augmented Reality (AR), virtual content enhances user experience by providing additional information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/viddar-vision-language-model-based-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STMDNet: A Lightweight Directional Framework for Motion Pattern Recognition of Tiny Targets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stmdnet-a-lightweight-directional-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizing motions of tiny targets - only few dozen pixels - in cluttered backgrounds remains a fundamental challenge when standard feature-based or deep learning methods fail under scarce visual cues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stmdnet-a-lightweight-directional-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimeFilter: Patch-Specific Spatial-Temporal Graph Filtration for Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timefilter-patch-specific-spatial-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current time series forecasting methods can be broadly classified into two categories: Channel Independent (CI) and Channel Dependent (CD) strategies, both aiming to capture the complex dependencies within time series data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timefilter-patch-specific-spatial-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Objective Hyperparameter Selection via Hypothesis Testing on Reliability Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-hyperparameter-selection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed approach, RG-based PT (RG-PT), leverages the RG to enable the efficient, parallel testing of multiple hyperparameters at the same reliability level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-hyperparameter-selection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDG-Diff: Frequency-Domain-Guided Diffusion Framework for Compressed Hazy Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fdg-diff-frequency-domain-guided-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we reveal that the interaction between haze degradation and JPEG compression introduces complex joint loss effects, which significantly complicate image restoration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fdg-diff-frequency-domain-guided-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeD-Loc: Text Distillation for Weakly Supervised Object Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ted-loc-text-distillation-for-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly supervised object localization (WSOL) using classification models trained with only image-class labels remains an important challenge in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ted-loc-text-distillation-for-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Losses for Hierarchical Embedding Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-losses-for-hierarchical-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In traditional supervised learning, the cross-entropy loss treats all incorrect predictions equally, ignoring the relevance or proximity of wrong labels to the correct answer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-losses-for-hierarchical-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test-Time Preference Optimization: On-the-Fly Alignment via Iterative Textual Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-preference-optimization-on-the-fly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Test-time Preference Optimization (TPO), a framework that aligns LLM outputs with human preferences during inference, removing the need to update model parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-preference-optimization-on-the-fly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX: Causal Discovery based on Machine Learning and Explainability techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rex-causal-discovery-based-on-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Explainability techniques hold significant potential for enhancing the causal discovery process, which is crucial for understanding complex systems in areas like healthcare, economics, and artificial intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rex-causal-discovery-based-on-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PPO-Based Vehicle Control for Ramp Merging Scheme Assisted by Enhanced C-V2X</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppo-based-vehicle-control-for-ramp-merging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On-ramp merging presents a critical challenge in autonomous driving, as vehicles from merging lanes need to dynamically adjust their positions and speeds while monitoring traffic on the main road to prevent collisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppo-based-vehicle-control-for-ramp-merging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Invariant Learning Framework for Graph Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-invariant-learning-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It provides a unified perspective on invariant graph learning, emphasizing both structural and semantic invariance principles to identify more robust stable features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-invariant-learning-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating the Conformal Prediction Threshold from Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-the-conformal-prediction-threshold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conformal Prediction (CP) is a method to control prediction uncertainty by producing a small prediction set, ensuring a predetermined probability that the true class lies within this set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-the-conformal-prediction-threshold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Modeling for Multi-order Human Visual Motion Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-modeling-for-multi-order</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While recent advances in computer vision (CV) have enabled DNN-based models to accurately estimate optical flow in naturalistic images, a significant disparity remains between CV models and the biological visual system in both architecture and behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-modeling-for-multi-order</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Table Source Matter? Benchmarking and Improving Multimodal Scientific Table Understanding and Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-table-source-matter-benchmarking-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While multimodal large language models (MLLMs) enable direct visual processing, they face limitations in handling scientific tables due to fixed input image resolutions and insufficient numerical reasoning capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-table-source-matter-benchmarking-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pairwise RM: Perform Best-of-N Sampling with Knockout Tournament</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pairwise-rm-perform-best-of-n-sampling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose a Pairwise Reward Model (Pairwise RM) combined with a knockout tournament for BoN sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pairwise-rm-perform-best-of-n-sampling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularization, Semi-supervision, and Supervision for a Plausible Attention-Based Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularization-semi-supervision-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We thus propose 3 additional constraints to the learning objective function to improve the plausibility of the attention map: regularization to increase the attention weight sparsity, semi-supervision to supervise the map by a heuristic and supervision by human annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularization-semi-supervision-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O1-Pruner: Length-Harmonizing Fine-Tuning for O1-Like Reasoning Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/o1-pruner-length-harmonizing-fine-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on various mathematical reasoning benchmarks show that O1-Pruner not only significantly reduces inference overhead but also achieves higher accuracy, providing a novel and promising solution to this challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/o1-pruner-length-harmonizing-fine-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distillation Quantification for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-quantification-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model distillation is a technique for transferring knowledge from large language models (LLMs) to smaller ones, aiming to create resource-efficient yet high-performing models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-quantification-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Accelerating Deep Neural Network Mutation Analysis by Neuron and Mutant Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-accelerating-deep-neural-network-mutation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When compared to exhaustive, or vanilla, mutation analysis, the results provide empirical evidence that neuron clustering approach, on average, accelerates mutation analysis by 69. 77%, with an average -26. 84% error in mutation score.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-accelerating-deep-neural-network-mutation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Marginal Importance of Distortions and Alignment in CASSI systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-marginal-importance-of-distortions-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a differentiable ray-tracing based model that incorporates aberrations and distortions to render realistic coded hyperspectral acquisitions using Coded-Aperture Spectral Snapshot Imagers (CASSI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-marginal-importance-of-distortions-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Versatile Optimizers on a Compute Diet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-versatile-optimizers-on-a-compute</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learned optimization has emerged as a promising alternative to hand-crafted optimizers, with the potential to discover stronger learned update rules that enable faster, hyperparameter-free training of neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-versatile-optimizers-on-a-compute</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Instance Partial-Label Learning with Margin Adjustment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-instance-partial-label-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-instance partial-label learning (MIPL) is an emerging learning framework where each training sample is represented as a multi-instance bag associated with a candidate label set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-instance-partial-label-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-image Object Detection for Fine-grained Recognition of Punches Patterns in Medieval Panel Painting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-image-object-detection-for-fine-grained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The attribution of the author of an art piece is typically a laborious manual process, usually relying on subjective evaluations of expert figures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-image-object-detection-for-fine-grained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunyuan3D 2.0: Scaling Diffusion Models for High Resolution Textured 3D Assets Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunyuan3d-2-0-scaling-diffusion-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This system includes two foundation components: a large-scale shape generation model -- Hunyuan3D-DiT, and a large-scale texture synthesis model -- Hunyuan3D-Paint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunyuan3d-2-0-scaling-diffusion-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabularARGN: A Flexible and Efficient Auto-Regressive Framework for Generating High-Fidelity Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabularargn-a-flexible-and-efficient-auto</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthetic data generation for tabular datasets must balance fidelity, efficiency, and versatility to meet the demands of real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabularargn-a-flexible-and-efficient-auto</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modality Collaborative Learning for Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modality-collaborative-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, by introducing a Multi-Modality Collaborative Learning (MMCL) framework, we facilitate cross-modal interactions and capture enhanced and complementary features from modality-common and modality-specific representations, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modality-collaborative-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utilising Deep Learning to Elicit Expert Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilising-deep-learning-to-elicit-expert</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work [ 14 ] has introduced a method for prior elicitation that utilizes records of expert decisions to infer a prior distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilising-deep-learning-to-elicit-expert</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget-constrained Collaborative Renewable Energy Forecasting Market</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/budget-constrained-collaborative-renewable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate power forecasting from renewable energy sources (RES) is crucial for integrating additional RES capacity into the power system and realizing sustainability goals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/budget-constrained-collaborative-renewable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HERITAGE: An End-to-End Web Platform for Processing Korean Historical Documents in Hanja</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heritage-an-end-to-end-web-platform-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, anyone interested in these documents can get a general understanding from the model predictions and the interactive glossary, especially MT outputs in Korean and English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heritage-an-end-to-end-web-platform-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MirrorCBO: A consensus-based optimization method in the spirit of mirror descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mirrorcbo-a-consensus-based-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we propose MirrorCBO, a consensus-based optimization (CBO) method which generalizes standard CBO in the same way that mirror descent generalizes gradient descent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mirrorcbo-a-consensus-based-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedS$^3$: Towards Medical Small Language Models with Self-Evolved Slow Thinking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meds-3-towards-medical-small-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a deployable, small-scale medical language model, \mone, designed for long-chain reasoning in clinical tasks using a self-evolution paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meds-3-towards-medical-small-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating High Quality RT Planning at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-high-quality-rt-planning-at-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Radiotherapy (RT) planning is complex, subjective, and time-intensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-high-quality-rt-planning-at-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoGERNN: An Inductive Traffic Predictor for Unobserved Locations in Dynamic Sensing Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mogernn-an-inductive-traffic-predictor-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a partially observed road network, how can we predict the traffic state of unobserved locations?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mogernn-an-inductive-traffic-predictor-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALoFTRAG: Automatic Local Fine Tuning for Retrieval Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aloftrag-automatic-local-fine-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) systems have been shown to improve the accuracy of Large Language Model (LLM) outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aloftrag-automatic-local-fine-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Discrete Denoising Diffusion Model for Molecular Generation with OpenFL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-discrete-denoising-diffusion-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The federated model achieves comparable performance with a model trained on centralized data when evaluating the uniqueness and validity of the generated molecules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-discrete-denoising-diffusion-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabularARGN: A Flexible and Efficient Auto-Regressive Framework for Generating High-Fidelity Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabularargn-a-flexible-and-efficient-auto-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthetic data generation for tabular datasets must balance fidelity, efficiency, and versatility to meet the demands of real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabularargn-a-flexible-and-efficient-auto-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAC++: Towards 100X Compression of 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hac-towards-100x-compression-of-3d-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) has emerged as a promising framework for novel view synthesis, boasting rapid rendering speed with high fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hac-towards-100x-compression-of-3d-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VARGPT: Unified Understanding and Generation in a Visual Autoregressive Multimodal Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vargpt-unified-understanding-and-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present VARGPT, a novel multimodal large language model (MLLM) that unifies visual understanding and generation within a single autoregressive framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vargpt-unified-understanding-and-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise-Resilient Point-wise Anomaly Detection in Time Series Using Weak Segment Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-resilient-point-wise-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting anomalies in temporal data has gained significant attention across various real-world applications, aiming to identify unusual events and mitigate potential hazards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-resilient-point-wise-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EDoRA: Efficient Weight-Decomposed Low-Rank Adaptation via Singular Value Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edora-efficient-weight-decomposed-low-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parameter-efficient fine-tuning methods, such as LoRA, reduces the number of trainable parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edora-efficient-weight-decomposed-low-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternLM-XComposer2.5-Reward: A Simple Yet Effective Multi-Modal Reward Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internlm-xcomposer2-5-reward-a-simple-yet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the promising performance of Large Vision Language Models (LVLMs) in visual understanding, they occasionally generate incorrect outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internlm-xcomposer2-5-reward-a-simple-yet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics of Skill Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-of-skill-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim to understand physics of skill learning, i. e., how skills are learned in neural networks during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-of-skill-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expertise elevates AI usage: experimental evidence comparing laypeople and professional artists</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expertise-elevates-ai-usage-experimental</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Novel capacities of generative AI to analyze and generate cultural artifacts raise inevitable questions about the nature and value of artistic education and human expertise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expertise-elevates-ai-usage-experimental</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
