<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 09:15:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Staircase Cascaded Fusion of Lightweight Local Pattern Recognition and Long-Range Dependencies for Structural Crack Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/staircase-cascaded-fusion-of-lightweight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The F1 and mIoU scores on the TUT dataset are 0. 8382 and 0. 8473, respectively, achieving state-of-the-art (SOTA) performance while requiring the least computational resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/staircase-cascaded-fusion-of-lightweight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-Efficient LLM Training with Online Subspace Descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-efficient-llm-training-with-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, a wide range of memory-efficient LLM training algorithms have gained substantial popularity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-efficient-llm-training-with-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O-Mamba: O-shape State-Space Model for Underwater Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/o-mamba-o-shape-state-space-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This branch includes MS-MoE for fusing multi-scale information within branches, Mutual Promotion module for interaction between spatial and channel information across branches, and Cyclic Multi-scale optimization strategy to maximize the use of multi-scale information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/o-mamba-o-shape-state-space-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VFM-Det: Towards High-Performance Vehicle Detection via Large Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vfm-det-towards-high-performance-vehicle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new vehicle detection paradigm based on a pre-trained foundation vehicle model (VehicleMAE) and a large language model (T5), termed VFM-Det.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vfm-det-towards-high-performance-vehicle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing the Potential of SAM2 for Biomedical Images and Videos: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-potential-of-sam2-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The unprecedented developments in segmentation foundational models have become a dominant force in the field of computer vision, introducing a multitude of previously unexplored capabilities in a wide range of natural images and videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-potential-of-sam2-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal dimensions of visual representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-dimensions-of-visual-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Do neural network models of vision learn brain-aligned representations because they share architectural constraints and task objectives with biological vision or because they learn universal features of natural image processing?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-dimensions-of-visual-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reproduction of scan B-statistic for kernel change-point detection algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproduction-of-scan-b-statistic-for-kernel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Change-point detection has garnered significant attention due to its broad range of applications, including epidemic disease outbreaks, social network evolution, image analysis, and wireless communications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproduction-of-scan-b-statistic-for-kernel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Centric Approach to Constrained Machine Learning: A Case Study on Conway's Game of Life</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-centric-approach-to-constrained-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper focuses on a data-centric approach to machine learning applications in the context of Conway's Game of Life.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-centric-approach-to-constrained-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoostTrack++: using tracklet information to detect more objects in multiple object tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosttrack-using-tracklet-information-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we identify the limitations of the confidence boost used in BoostTrack and propose a method to improve its performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosttrack-using-tracklet-information-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedDec: A Dataset for Extracting Medical Decisions from Discharge Summaries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meddec-a-dataset-for-extracting-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical decisions directly impact individuals' health and well-being.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meddec-a-dataset-for-extracting-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ml_edm package: a Python toolkit for Machine Learning based Early Decision Making</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ml-edm-package-a-python-toolkit-for-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[\texttt{ml\_edm} is a Python 3 library, designed for early decision making of any learning tasks involving temporal/sequential data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ml-edm-package-a-python-toolkit-for-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIMP: Large Language Model Enhanced Intent-aware Mobility Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/limp-large-language-model-enhanced-intent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we propose a transformer-based intention-aware mobility prediction model to effectively harness the intention inference ability of LLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/limp-large-language-model-enhanced-intent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T3M: Text Guided 3D Human Motion Synthesis from Speech</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t3m-text-guided-3d-human-motion-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speech-driven 3D motion synthesis seeks to create lifelike animations based on human speech, with potential uses in virtual reality, gaming, and the film production.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t3m-text-guided-3d-human-motion-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Knowledge Tracing with Concept Map and Response Disentanglement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-knowledge-tracing-with-concept-map</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CRKT benefits KT by directly leveraging answer choices--beyond merely identifying correct or incorrect answers--to distinguish responses with different incorrect choices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-knowledge-tracing-with-concept-map</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multivariate Time-Series Anomaly Detection based on Enhancing Graph Attention Networks with Topological Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multivariate-time-series-anomaly-detection-5</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we present an augmented GAT to manage complex inter-feature dependencies, which incorporates graph topology into node features across multiple scales, a versatile, plug-and-play enhancement that significantly boosts the performance of GAT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multivariate-time-series-anomaly-detection-5</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EvalYaks: Instruction Tuning Datasets and LoRA Fine-tuned Models for Automated Scoring of CEFR B2 Speaking Assessment Transcripts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evalyaks-instruction-tuning-datasets-and-lora</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, new instruction-tuned datasets are developed from the English Vocabulary Profile (up to CEFR B2 level) and the CEFR-SP WikiAuto datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evalyaks-instruction-tuning-datasets-and-lora</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Video Generation with Pyramid Attention Broadcast</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-video-generation-with-pyramid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Pyramid Attention Broadcast (PAB), a real-time, high quality and training-free approach for DiT-based video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-video-generation-with-pyramid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Data Heterogeneity in Federated Learning via Loss Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-data-heterogeneity-in-federated-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the impact of data heterogeneity on FL performance, we start with analyzing how FL training influence FL performance by decomposing the global loss into three terms: local loss, distribution shift loss and aggregation loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-data-heterogeneity-in-federated-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized SAM: Efficient Fine-Tuning of SAM for Variable Input Image Sizes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-sam-efficient-fine-tuning-of-sam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The input image size of SAM is fixed at 1024 x 1024, resulting in substantial computational demands during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-sam-efficient-fine-tuning-of-sam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssProp: Energy-Efficient Training for Convolutional Neural Networks with Scheduled Sparse Back Propagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssprop-energy-efficient-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Back-propagation (BP) is a major source of computational expense during training deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssprop-energy-efficient-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning (Medical) LLMs for (Counterfactual) Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-medical-llms-for-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have emerged as promising solutions for a variety of medical and clinical decision support applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-medical-llms-for-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPARK: Multi-Vision Sensor Perception and Reasoning Benchmark for Large-scale Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spark-multi-vision-sensor-perception-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we observe that current LVLMs view images taken from multi-vision sensors as if they were in the same RGB domain without considering the physical characteristics of multi-vision sensors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spark-multi-vision-sensor-perception-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GSFusion: Online RGB-D Mapping Where Gaussian Splatting Meets TSDF Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gsfusion-online-rgb-d-mapping-where-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this way, we simultaneously generate a compact 3D Gaussian map with fewer artifacts and a volumetric map on the fly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gsfusion-online-rgb-d-mapping-where-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Realistic X-ray Scattering Images Using Stable Diffusion and Human-in-the-loop Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-realistic-x-ray-scattering-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We fine-tuned a foundational stable diffusion model using X-ray scattering images and their corresponding descriptions to generate new scientific images from given prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-realistic-x-ray-scattering-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantization-free Lossy Image Compression Using Integer Matrix Factorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantization-free-lossy-image-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remarkably, our method improved top-1 accuracy by over 5 percentage points compared to JPEG at bit rates under 0. 25 bpp.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantization-free-lossy-image-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Fine-Tuning of Lightweight Domain-Specific Q&amp;A Model Based on Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multivariate-time-series-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) excel at general question-answering (Q&A) but often fall short in specialized domains due to a lack of domain-specific knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multivariate-time-series-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Evaluating and Building Versatile Large Language Models for Medicine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-evaluating-and-building-versatile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To promote further advancements in the application of LLMs to clinical challenges, we have made the MedS-Ins dataset fully accessible and invite the research community to contribute to its expansion. Additionally, we have launched a dynamic leaderboard for MedS-Bench, which we plan to regularly update the test set to track progress and enhance the adaptation of general LLMs to the medical domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-evaluating-and-building-versatile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CODE: Confident Ordinary Differential Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/code-confident-ordinary-differential-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, conditioning on noisy or Out-of-Distribution (OoD) images poses significant challenges, particularly in balancing fidelity to the input and realism of the output.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/code-confident-ordinary-differential-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrolled Decomposed Unpaired Learning for Controllable Low-Light Video Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unrolled-decomposed-unpaired-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above challenge, we propose the Unrolled Decomposed Unpaired Network (UDU-Net) for enhancing low-light videos by unrolling the optimization functions into a deep network to decompose the signal into spatial and temporal-related factors, which are updated iteratively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unrolled-decomposed-unpaired-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Percolation Model of Emergence: Analyzing Transformers Trained on a Formal Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-percolation-model-of-emergence-analyzing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Increase in data, size, or compute can lead to sudden learning of specific capabilities by a neural network -- a phenomenon often called "emergence".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-percolation-model-of-emergence-analyzing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UMAD: University of Macau Anomaly Detection Benchmark Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/umad-university-of-macau-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our best knowledge, this is the first benchmark dataset designed specifically for anomaly detection with reference in robotic patrolling scenarios, e. g., where an autonomous robot is employed to detect anomalous objects by comparing a reference and a query video sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/umad-university-of-macau-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLM Meets LLM: Balancing Latency, Interpretability and Consistency in Hallucination Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slm-meets-llm-balancing-latency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are highly capable but face latency challenges in real-time applications, such as conducting online hallucination detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slm-meets-llm-balancing-latency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UMERegRobust -- Universal Manifold Embedding Compatible Features for Robust Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/umeregrobust-universal-manifold-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we adopt the Universal Manifold Embedding (UME) framework for the estimation of rigid transformations and extend it, so that it can accommodate scenarios involving partial overlap and differently sampled point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/umeregrobust-universal-manifold-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Domain Foundation Model Adaptation: Pioneering Computer Vision Models for Geophysical Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-foundation-model-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore adapting foundation models (FMs) from the computer vision domain to geoscience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-foundation-model-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show-o: One Single Transformer to Unify Multimodal Understanding and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-o-one-single-transformer-to-unify</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a unified transformer, i. e., Show-o, that unifies multimodal understanding and generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-o-one-single-transformer-to-unify</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRExplainer: Quantifiable Interpretability in Drug Response Prediction with Directed Graph Convolutional Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drexplainer-quantifiable-interpretability-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DRExplainer constructs a directed bipartite network integrating multi-omics profiles of cell lines, the chemical structure of drugs and known drug response to achieve directed prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drexplainer-quantifiable-interpretability-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behavior Pattern Mining-based Multi-Behavior Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behavior-pattern-mining-based-multi-behavior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-behavior recommendation systems enhance effectiveness by leveraging auxiliary behaviors (such as page views and favorites) to address the limitations of traditional models that depend solely on sparse target behaviors like purchases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behavior-pattern-mining-based-multi-behavior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Spiking Neural Networks with Hybrid Coding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-spiking-neural-networks-with-hybrid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Spiking Neural Network (SNN), due to its unique spiking-driven nature, is a more energy-efficient and effective neural network compared to Artificial Neural Networks (ANNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-spiking-neural-networks-with-hybrid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive DualChecker for Mitigating Hallucinations in Distilling Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-dualchecker-for-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, current methods for knowledge distillation using LLMs often struggle to enhance the effectiveness of both teacher and student models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-dualchecker-for-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Information Consistency in Frequency and Spatial Domain for Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-information-consistency-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate the effectiveness of frequency domain-based attacks, aligning with similar findings in the spatial domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-information-consistency-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenderCARE: A Comprehensive Framework for Assessing and Reducing Gender Bias in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gendercare-a-comprehensive-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By offering a realistic assessment and tailored reduction of gender biases, we hope that our GenderCARE can represent a significant step towards achieving fairness and equity in LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gendercare-a-comprehensive-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning Factual Knowledge in Structured Data with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-factual-knowledge-in-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This benchmark allows us to investigate the capability of LLMs across five factual tasks derived from the unique characteristics of structural facts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-factual-knowledge-in-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WCEbleedGen: A wireless capsule endoscopy dataset and its benchmarking for automatic bleeding classification, detection, and segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wcebleedgen-a-wireless-capsule-endoscopy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, a medically annotated WCE dataset for training and evaluation of automatic classification, detection, and segmentation of bleeding and non-bleeding frames is currently lacking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wcebleedgen-a-wireless-capsule-endoscopy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable Text Generation for Large Language Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-text-generation-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper systematically reviews the latest advancements in CTG for LLMs, offering a comprehensive definition of its core concepts and clarifying the requirements for control conditions and text quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-text-generation-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISETHDR: A Physics-based Synthetic Radiance Dataset for High Dynamic Range Driving Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isethdr-a-physics-based-synthetic-radiance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes a physics-based end-to-end software simulation for image systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isethdr-a-physics-based-synthetic-radiance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlexEdit: Marrying Free-Shape Masks to VLLM for Flexible Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexedit-marrying-free-shape-masks-to-vllm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach employs a VLLM in comprehending the image content, mask, and user instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexedit-marrying-free-shape-masks-to-vllm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDD-5k: A New Diagnostic Conversation Dataset for Mental Disorders Synthesized via Neuro-Symbolic LLM Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdd-5k-a-new-diagnostic-conversation-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By applying the proposed framework, we develop the largest Chinese mental disorders diagnosis dataset MDD-5k, which is built upon 1000 cleaned real patient cases by cooperating with a pioneering psychiatric hospital, and contains 5000 high-quality long conversations with diagnosis results as labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdd-5k-a-new-diagnostic-conversation-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair Augmentation for Graph Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-augmentation-for-graph-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite emerging regulations addressing fairness of automated systems, unfairness issues in graph collaborative filtering remain underexplored, especially from the consumer's perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-augmentation-for-graph-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Riemannian Approach for Spatiotemporal Analysis and Generation of 4D Tree-shaped Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-riemannian-approach-for-spatiotemporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel mathematical representation of the shape space of such trajectories, a Riemannian metric on that space, and computational tools for fast and accurate spatiotemporal registration and geodesics computation between 4D tree-shaped structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-riemannian-approach-for-spatiotemporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple testing for signal-agnostic searches of new physics with machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-testing-for-signal-agnostic-searches</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address the question of how to enhance signal-agnostic searches by leveraging multiple testing strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-testing-for-signal-agnostic-searches</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
