<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 21:07:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Scientific Concepts Understanding: Can Analogy from Teacher Models Empower Student Models?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-scientific-concepts-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analogical reasoning plays a critical role in human cognition, enabling us to understand new concepts by associating them with familiar ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-scientific-concepts-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Data Mixing Maximizes Instruction Tuning for Mixture-of-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-data-mixing-maximizes-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) models have shown remarkable capability in instruction tuning, especially when the number of tasks scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-data-mixing-maximizes-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Model Pre-training via Language Guided Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-model-pre-training-via-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, for the first time, we introduce language guidance to the distillation process and propose a new method named Language-Guided Distillation (LGD) system, which uses category names of the target downstream task to help refine the knowledge transferred between the teacher and student.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-model-pre-training-via-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARE: HumAn pRiors, a key to small language model Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hare-human-priors-a-key-to-small-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human priors play a crucial role in efficiently utilizing data in deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hare-human-priors-a-key-to-small-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Copilot: the perfect Code compLeeter?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/github-copilot-the-perfect-code-compleeter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim to evaluate Copilot's reliability in the code generation stage, the correctness of the generated code and its dependency on the programming language, problem's difficulty level and problem's topic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/github-copilot-the-perfect-code-compleeter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistency^2: Consistent and Fast 3D Painting with Latent Consistency Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-2-consistent-and-fast-3d-painting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative 3D Painting is among the top productivity boosters in high-resolution 3D asset management and recycling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-2-consistent-and-fast-3d-painting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AvaTaR: Optimizing LLM Agents for Tool-Assisted Knowledge Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avatar-optimizing-llm-agents-for-tool</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, developing the prompting techniques that make LLM agents able to effectively use external tools and knowledge is a heuristic and laborious task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avatar-optimizing-llm-agents-for-tool</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling the Codebook Size of VQGAN to 100,000 with a Utilization Rate of 99%</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-the-codebook-size-of-vqgan-to-100000</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the superior performance of our model over its counterparts across a variety of tasks, including image reconstruction, image classification, auto-regressive image generation using GPT, and image creation with diffusion- and flow-based generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-the-codebook-size-of-vqgan-to-100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMDU: A Multi-Turn Multi-Image Dialog Understanding Benchmark and Instruction-Tuning Dataset for LVLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmdu-a-multi-turn-multi-image-dialog</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating natural and meaningful responses to communicate with multi-modal human inputs is a fundamental capability of Large Vision-Language Models(LVLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmdu-a-multi-turn-multi-image-dialog</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhyBench: A Physical Commonsense Benchmark for Evaluating Text-to-Image Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phybench-a-physical-commonsense-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings reveal that: (1) even advanced models frequently err in various physical scenarios, except for optics; (2) GPT-4o, with item-specific scoring instructions, effectively evaluates the models' understanding of physical commonsense, closely aligning with human assessments; and (3) current T2I models are primarily focused on text-to-image translation, lacking profound reasoning regarding physical commonsense.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phybench-a-physical-commonsense-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Instructions and Demonstrations for Multi-Stage Language Model Programs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-instructions-and-demonstrations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language Model Programs, i. e. sophisticated pipelines of modular language model (LM) calls, are increasingly advancing NLP tasks, but they require crafting prompts that are jointly effective for all modules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-instructions-and-demonstrations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Denoising Diffusion GAN: Faster sampling, Higher image quality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-denoising-diffusion-gan-faster</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to its predecessors, DiffusionGAN and Wavelet Diffusion, our model shows remarkable improvements in all evaluation metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-denoising-diffusion-gan-faster</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch Every Step! LLM Agent Learning via Iterative Step-Level Process Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watch-every-step-llm-agent-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language model agents have exhibited exceptional performance across a range of complex interactive tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watch-every-step-llm-agent-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Needle in a Haystack: Benchmarking Long-Context Capability of Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-needle-in-a-haystack-benchmarking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, a comprehensive evaluation of their long-context capabilities remains underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-needle-in-a-haystack-benchmarking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Generalization during Instruction Tuning: Insights from Similarity and Granularity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-generalization-during-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the first time, we show that zero-shot generalization during instruction tuning is a form of similarity-based generalization between training and test data at the instance level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-generalization-during-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GECOBench: A Gender-Controlled Text Dataset and Benchmark for Quantifying Biases in Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gecobench-a-gender-controlled-text-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This gives rise to ground-truth 'world explanations' for gender classification tasks, enabling the objective evaluation of the correctness of XAI methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gecobench-a-gender-controlled-text-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep-Reinforcement-Learning-Based AoI-Aware Resource Allocation for RIS-Aided IoV Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-reinforcement-learning-based-aoi-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconfigurable Intelligent Surface (RIS) is a pivotal technology in communication, offering an alternative path that significantly enhances the link quality in wireless communication environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-reinforcement-learning-based-aoi-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRACE the Evidence: Constructing Knowledge-Grounded Reasoning Chains for Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trace-the-evidence-constructing-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) offers an effective approach for addressing question answering (QA) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trace-the-evidence-constructing-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intrinsic Evaluation of Unlearning Using Parametric Knowledge Traces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsic-evaluation-of-unlearning-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a general methodology for eliciting directions in the parameter space (termed "concept vectors") that encode concrete concepts, and construct ConceptVectors, a benchmark dataset containing hundreds of common concepts and their parametric knowledge traces within two open-source LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsic-evaluation-of-unlearning-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairer Preferences Elicit Improved Human-Aligned Large Language Model Judgments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairer-preferences-elicit-improved-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this phenomenon, we propose an automatic Zero-shot Evaluation-oriented Prompt Optimization framework, ZEPO, which aims to produce fairer preference decisions and improve the alignment of LLM evaluators with human judgments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairer-preferences-elicit-improved-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super(ficial)-alignment: Strong Models May Deceive Weak Models in Weak-to-Strong Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-ficial-alignment-strong-models-may</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we are concerned that behind such a promising phenomenon, whether there exists an issue of weak-to-strong deception, where strong models may deceive weak models by exhibiting well-aligned in areas known to weak models but producing misaligned behaviors in cases weak models do not know.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-ficial-alignment-strong-models-may</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling Encoder-Free Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-encoder-free-vision-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training pure VLMs that accept the seamless vision and language inputs, i. e., without vision encoders, remains challenging and rarely explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-encoder-free-vision-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Structured Generation: CVPR's 2nd MMFM Challenge Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-structured-generation-cvpr-s-2nd</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide a detailed account of our approach, including the technical details, theoretical discussions, and final evaluation results in the 2nd Multimodal Foundation Models Challenge hosted by the Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR) conference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-structured-generation-cvpr-s-2nd</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Annotator Bias in Large Language Models for Hate Speech Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-annotator-bias-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce our custom hate speech detection dataset, HateSpeechCorpus, to conduct this research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-annotator-bias-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLO9tr: A Lightweight Model for Pavement Damage Detection Utilizing a Generalized Efficient Layer Aggregation Network and Attention Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo9tr-a-lightweight-model-for-pavement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Maintaining road pavement integrity is crucial for ensuring safe and efficient transportation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo9tr-a-lightweight-model-for-pavement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELLA-Merging: Reducing Interference in Model Merging through Magnitude-Based Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/della-merging-reducing-interference-in-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the proliferation of domain-specific models, model merging has emerged as a set of techniques that combine the capabilities of multiple models into one that can multitask without the cost of additional training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/della-merging-reducing-interference-in-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OoDIS: Anomaly Instance Segmentation Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oodis-anomaly-instance-segmentation-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous vehicles require a precise understanding of their environment to navigate safely.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oodis-anomaly-instance-segmentation-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graspness Discovery in Clutters for Fast and Accurate Grasp Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graspness-discovery-in-clutters-for-fast-and-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on a large-scale benchmark, GraspNet-1Billion, show that our method outperforms previous arts by a large margin (30+ AP) and achieves a high inference speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graspness-discovery-in-clutters-for-fast-and-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MINT-1T: Scaling Open-Source Multimodal Data by 10x: A Multimodal Dataset with One Trillion Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mint-1t-scaling-open-source-multimodal-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal interleaved datasets featuring free-form interleaved sequences of images and text are crucial for training frontier large multimodal models (LMMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mint-1t-scaling-open-source-multimodal-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconfigurable Intelligent Surface Assisted VEC Based on Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconfigurable-intelligent-surface-assisted-28</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vehicular edge computing (VEC) is an emerging technology that enables vehicles to perform high-intensity tasks by executing tasks locally or offloading them to nearby edge devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconfigurable-intelligent-surface-assisted-28</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WPO: Enhancing RLHF with Weighted Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wpo-enhancing-rlhf-with-weighted-preference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method not only addresses the distributional gap problem but also enhances the optimization process without incurring additional costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wpo-enhancing-rlhf-with-weighted-preference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feasibility of Federated Learning from Client Databases with Different Brain Diseases and MRI Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feasibility-of-federated-learning-from-client</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These results demonstrate, for the first time, feasibility and effectiveness of using FL to train a single segmentation model on decentralised data with diverse brain diseases and MRI modalities, a necessary step towards leveraging heterogeneous real-world databases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feasibility-of-federated-learning-from-client</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correspondence Free Multivector Cloud Registration using Conformal Geometric Algebra</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correspondence-free-multivector-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present, for the first time, a novel theoretical approach to address the problem of correspondence free multivector cloud registration in conformal geometric algebra.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correspondence-free-multivector-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Efficacy of Open-Source LLMs in Enterprise-Specific RAG Systems: A Comparative Study of Performance and Scalability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-efficacy-of-open-source-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an analysis of open-source large language models (LLMs) and their application in Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) tasks, specific for enterprise-specific data sets scraped from their websites.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-efficacy-of-open-source-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Input Conditioned Graph Generation for Language Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/input-conditioned-graph-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within this graph framework, we aim to learn a model that can generate edges for every given input to the language agent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/input-conditioned-graph-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUICourse: From General Vision Language Models to Versatile GUI Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guicourse-from-general-vision-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Utilizing Graphic User Interface (GUI) for human-computer interaction is essential for accessing a wide range of digital tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guicourse-from-general-vision-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Modeling with Editable External Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-modeling-with-editable-external</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces ERASE, which instead improves model behavior when new documents are acquired, by incrementally deleting or rewriting other entries in the knowledge base each time a document is added.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-modeling-with-editable-external</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Efficient Language and Vision Assistants for Visually-Situated Natural Language Understanding: What Matters in Reading and Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-efficient-language-and-vision-assistants</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in language and vision assistants have showcased impressive capabilities but suffer from a lack of transparency, limiting broader research and reproducibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-efficient-language-and-vision-assistants</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incentivizing Quality Text Generation via Statistical Contracts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incentivizing-quality-text-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the success of large language models (LLMs) increases demand for machine-generated text, current pay-per-token pricing schemes create a misalignment of incentives known in economics as moral hazard: Text-generating agents have strong incentive to cut costs by preferring a cheaper model over the cutting-edge one, and this can be done "behind the scenes" since the agent performs inference internally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incentivizing-quality-text-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can LLM be a Personalized Judge?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llm-be-a-personalized-judge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ensuring that large language models (LLMs) reflect diverse user values and preferences is crucial as their user bases expand globally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llm-be-a-personalized-judge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-to-Jailbreak: One Knowledge Point Worth One Attack</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-to-jailbreak-one-knowledge-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we propose a new task, knowledge-to-jailbreak, which aims to generate jailbreaks from domain knowledge to evaluate the safety of LLMs when applied to those domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-to-jailbreak-one-knowledge-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Boundaries: Learning a Universal Entity Taxonomy across Datasets and Languages for Open Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-boundaries-learning-a-universal-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open Named Entity Recognition (NER), which involves identifying arbitrary types of entities from arbitrary domains, remains challenging for Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-boundaries-learning-a-universal-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExCP: Extreme LLM Checkpoint Compression via Weight-Momentum Joint Shrinking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/excp-extreme-llm-checkpoint-compression-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For instance, we achieve approximately $70\times$ compression for the Pythia-410M model, with the final performance being as accurate as the original model on various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/excp-extreme-llm-checkpoint-compression-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards an End-to-End Framework for Invasive Brain Signal Decoding with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-end-to-end-framework-for-invasive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a groundbreaking end-to-end (E2E) framework for decoding invasive brain signals, marking a significant advancement in the field of speech neuroprosthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-end-to-end-framework-for-invasive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task Me Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-me-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, when a developer wants to identify which models to use for their application, they are overwhelmed by the number of benchmarks and remain uncertain about which benchmark's results are most reflective of their specific use case.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-me-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OGNI-DC: Robust Depth Completion with Optimization-Guided Neural Iterations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ogni-dc-robust-depth-completion-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Depth completion is the task of generating a dense depth map given an image and a sparse depth map as inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ogni-dc-robust-depth-completion-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysing the Behaviour of Tree-Based Neural Networks in Regression Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysing-the-behaviour-of-tree-based-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extend the application of established models--tree-based Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs), Code2Vec, and Transformer-based methods--to predict the execution time of source code by parsing it to an AST.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysing-the-behaviour-of-tree-based-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Pixels to Progress: Generating Road Network from Satellite Imagery for Socioeconomic Insights in Impoverished Areas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-pixels-to-progress-generating-road</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs) aim to resolve societal challenges, such as eradicating poverty and improving the lives of vulnerable populations in impoverished areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-pixels-to-progress-generating-road</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Supervised Domain Adaptation Using Target-Oriented Domain Augmentation for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-domain-adaptation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TODA efficiently utilizes all available data, including labeled data in the source domain, and both labeled data and unlabeled data in the target domain to enhance domain adaptation performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-domain-adaptation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety Arithmetic: A Framework for Test-time Safety Alignment of Language Models by Steering Parameters and Activations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-arithmetic-a-framework-for-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ensuring the safe alignment of large language models (LLMs) with human values is critical as they become integral to applications like translation and question answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-arithmetic-a-framework-for-test-time</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
