<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 09:18:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Robustness of Adversarial Defenses in Malware Detection Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-robustness-of-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarially trained defenses, including AT-rFGSM-k, AT-MaxMA, improves robustness under small budgets but remains vulnerable to unrestricted perturbations, with attack success rates of 99. 45% and 96. 62%, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-robustness-of-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAD Neural Networks: Divergent Gradient Flows and Asymptotic Optimality via o-minimal Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sad-neural-networks-divergent-gradient-flows</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that the gradient flow either converges to a critical point or diverges to infinity while the loss converges to an asymptotic critical value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sad-neural-networks-divergent-gradient-flows</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Learning with Augmented Class via Forests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-learning-with-augmented-class-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we focus on learning with augmented class via forests, where an augmented class may appear in testing data yet not in training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-learning-with-augmented-class-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Isolation Forest</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-isolation-forest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The anomaly detection literature is abundant with offline methods, which require repeated access to data in memory, and impose impractical assumptions when applied to a streaming context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-isolation-forest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Mixed Precision Quantization in Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-mixed-precision-quantization-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mixed precision quantization emerges as a promising solution to enhance the efficiency of GNN architectures without compromising prediction performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-mixed-precision-quantization-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contactless Cardiac Pulse Monitoring Using Event Cameras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contactless-cardiac-pulse-monitoring-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An end-to-end model is trained to extract the cardiac signal from a two-dimensional representation of the event stream, with model performance evaluated based on the accuracy of the calculated heart rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contactless-cardiac-pulse-monitoring-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable and Convexified Information Bottleneck Optimization via Symbolic Continuation and Entropy-Regularized Trajectories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-and-convexified-information-bottleneck</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Information Bottleneck (IB) method frequently suffers from unstable optimization, characterized by abrupt representation shifts near critical points of the IB trade-off parameter, beta.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-and-convexified-information-bottleneck</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Train a Multi-Task Diffusion Policy on RLBench-18 in One Day with One GPU</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/train-a-multi-task-diffusion-policy-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a method for training multi-task vision-language robotic diffusion policies that reduces training time and memory usage by an order of magnitude.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/train-a-multi-task-diffusion-policy-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Computations for Generalized Mixed Effects Models with Crossed Random Effects Using Krylov Subspace Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-computations-for-generalized-mixed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mixed effects models are widely used for modeling data with hierarchically grouped structures and high-cardinality categorical predictor variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-computations-for-generalized-mixed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformal Bounds on Full-Reference Image Quality for Imaging Inverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-bounds-on-full-reference-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In imaging inverse problems, we would like to know how close the recovered image is to the true image in terms of full-reference image quality (FRIQ) metrics like PSNR, SSIM, LPIPS, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-bounds-on-full-reference-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRRNet: Macro-Micro Feature Fusion and Dual Reverse Refinement for Camouflaged Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drrnet-macro-micro-feature-fusion-and-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the decoder, we also introduce a reverse refinement module that leverages spatial edge priors and frequency-domain noise suppression to perform a two-stage inverse refinement of the output.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drrnet-macro-micro-feature-fusion-and-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Shot Anomaly-Driven Generation for Anomaly Classification and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-anomaly-driven-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experiments demonstrate that our generated anomalies effectively improve the model performance of both anomaly classification and segmentation tasks simultaneously, \eg, DRAEM and DseTSeg achieved a 5. 8\% and 1. 5\% improvement in AU-PR metric on segmentation task, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-anomaly-driven-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenLKA: An Open Dataset of Lane Keeping Assist from Recent Car Models under Real-world Driving Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openlka-an-open-dataset-of-lane-keeping-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lane Keeping Assist (LKA) is widely adopted in modern vehicles, yet its real-world performance remains underexplored due to proprietary systems and limited data access.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openlka-an-open-dataset-of-lane-keeping-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focus, Merge, Rank: Improved Question Answering Based on Semi-structured Knowledge Bases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focus-merge-rank-improved-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many real-world settings, machine learning models and interactive systems have access to both structured knowledge, e. g., knowledge graphs or tables, and unstructured content, e. g., natural language documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focus-merge-rank-improved-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLIP3-o: A Family of Fully Open Unified Multimodal Models-Architecture, Training and Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blip3-o-a-family-of-fully-open-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on our innovative model design, training recipe, and datasets, we develop BLIP3-o, a suite of state-of-the-art unified multimodal models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blip3-o-a-family-of-fully-open-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaFortiTran: An Adaptive Transformer Model for Robust OFDM Channel Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adafortitran-an-adaptive-transformer-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning models for channel estimation in Orthogonal Frequency Division Multiplexing (OFDM) systems often suffer from performance degradation under fast-fading channels and low-SNR scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adafortitran-an-adaptive-transformer-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACTors: A New Dataset for Studying the Fact-checking Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factors-a-new-dataset-for-studying-the-fact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It contains 118, 112 claims from 117, 993 fact-checking reports in English (co-)authored by 1, 953 individuals and published during the period of 1995-2025 by 39 fact-checking organisations that are active signatories of the IFCN (International Fact-Checking Network) and/or EFCSN (European Fact-Checking Standards Network).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factors-a-new-dataset-for-studying-the-fact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaUAS: Universal Anomaly Segmentation with One-Prompt Meta-Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metauas-universal-anomaly-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paradigm enables us to leverage large-scale synthetic image pairs, featuring object-level and local region changes, derived from existing image datasets, which are independent of target anomaly datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metauas-universal-anomaly-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atomic Consistency Preference Optimization for Long-Form Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomic-consistency-preference-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) frequently produce factoid hallucinations - plausible yet incorrect answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomic-consistency-preference-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UMotion: Uncertainty-driven Human Motion Estimation from Inertial and Ultra-wideband Units</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/umotion-uncertainty-driven-human-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse wearable inertial measurement units (IMUs) have gained popularity for estimating 3D human motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/umotion-uncertainty-driven-human-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WavReward: Spoken Dialogue Models With Generalist Reward Evaluators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavreward-spoken-dialogue-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we propose WavReward, a reward feedback model based on audio language models that can evaluate both the IQ and EQ of spoken dialogue systems with speech input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavreward-spoken-dialogue-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Prefix Tuning for Diverse and Accurate Code Summarization Using Pre-trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-prefix-tuning-for-diverse-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in source code summarization have leveraged transformer-based pre-trained models, including Large Language Models of Code (LLMCs), to automate and improve the generation of code summaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-prefix-tuning-for-diverse-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ranking-Based At-Risk Student Prediction Using Federated Learning and Differential Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ranking-based-at-risk-student-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such textbooks yield learning log data that have been used in numerous educational data mining (EDM) studies for student behavior analysis and performance prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ranking-based-at-risk-student-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EDBench: Large-Scale Electron Density Data for Molecular Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edbench-large-scale-electron-density-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing molecular machine learning force fields (MLFFs) generally focus on the learning of atoms, molecules, and simple quantum chemical properties (such as energy and force), but ignore the importance of electron density (ED) $\rho(r)$ in accurately understanding molecular force fields (MFFs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edbench-large-scale-electron-density-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Detect Multi-class Anomalies with Just One Normal Image Prompt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-detect-multi-class-anomalies-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these self-attention reconstruction models primarily operate on target features, which may result in perfect reconstruction for both normal and anomaly features due to high consistency with context, leading to failure in detecting anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-detect-multi-class-anomalies-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spec2VolCAMU-Net: A Spectrogram-to-Volume Model for EEG-to-fMRI Reconstruction based on Multi-directional Time-Frequency Convolutional Attention Encoder and Vision-Mamba U-Net</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spec2volcamu-net-a-spectrogram-to-volume</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-resolution functional magnetic resonance imaging (fMRI) is essential for mapping human brain activity; however, it remains costly and logistically challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spec2volcamu-net-a-spectrogram-to-volume</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Point Cloud Patches Rendering via Splitting 2D Gaussians</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-point-cloud-patches-rendering-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, we introduce a novel point cloud rendering method by predicting 2D Gaussians from point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-point-cloud-patches-rendering-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAKE: Multi-Aspect Knowledge-Enhanced Vision-Language Pretraining for Zero-shot Dermatological Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-multi-aspect-knowledge-enhanced-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dermatological diagnosis represents a complex multimodal challenge that requires integrating visual features with specialized clinical knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-multi-aspect-knowledge-enhanced-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APR-Transformer: Initial Pose Estimation for Localization in Complex Environments through Absolute Pose Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apr-transformer-initial-pose-estimation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Precise initialization plays a critical role in the performance of localization algorithms, especially in the context of robotics, autonomous driving, and computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apr-transformer-initial-pose-estimation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TopoDiT-3D: Topology-Aware Diffusion Transformer with Bottleneck Structure for 3D Point Cloud Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topodit-3d-topology-aware-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose TopoDiT-3D, a Topology-Aware Diffusion Transformer with a bottleneck structure for 3D point cloud generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topodit-3d-topology-aware-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensitivity-Constrained Fourier Neural Operators for Forward and Inverse Problems in Parametric Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensitivity-constrained-fourier-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These gains are achieved with a modest increase in training time (30% to 130% per epoch) and generalize across various types of differential equations and neural operators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensitivity-constrained-fourier-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implet: A Post-hoc Subsequence Explainer for Time Series Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implet-a-post-hoc-subsequence-explainer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Explainability in time series models is crucial for fostering trust, facilitating debugging, and ensuring interpretability in real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implet-a-post-hoc-subsequence-explainer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIM-Shapley: A Stable and Computationally Efficient Approach to Shapley Value Approximation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim-shapley-a-stable-and-computationally</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Stochastic Iterative Momentum for Shapley Value Approximation (SIM-Shapley), a stable and efficient SV approximation method inspired by stochastic optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim-shapley-a-stable-and-computationally</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models for Computer-Aided Design: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-computer-aided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have seen rapid advancements in recent years, with models like ChatGPT and DeepSeek, showcasing their remarkable capabilities across diverse domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-computer-aided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HMPNet: A Feature Aggregation Architecture for Maritime Object Detection from a Shipborne Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hmpnet-a-feature-aggregation-architecture-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based upon this dataset, we propose HMPNet, a lightweight architecture tailored for shipborne object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hmpnet-a-feature-aggregation-architecture-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADC-GS: Anchor-Driven Deformable and Compressed Gaussian Splatting for Dynamic Scene Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adc-gs-anchor-driven-deformable-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing 4D Gaussian Splatting methods rely on per-Gaussian deformation from a canonical space to target frames, which overlooks redundancy among adjacent Gaussian primitives and results in suboptimal performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adc-gs-anchor-driven-deformable-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimized Couplings for Watermarking Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimized-couplings-for-watermarking-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that a key component in watermark design is generating a coupling between the side information shared with the watermark detector and a random partition of the LLM vocabulary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimized-couplings-for-watermarking-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foundation Models Knowledge Distillation For Battery Capacity Degradation Forecast</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-models-knowledge-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate estimation of lithium-ion battery capacity degradation is critical for enhancing the reliability and safety of battery operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-models-knowledge-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prioritizing Image-Related Tokens Enhances Vision-Language Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prioritizing-image-related-tokens-enhances</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PRIOR introduces a reference model-a text-only large language model (LLM) trained on the captions without image inputs, to weight each token based on its probability for LVLMs training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prioritizing-image-related-tokens-enhances</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skeleton-Guided Diffusion Model for Accurate Foot X-ray Synthesis in Hallux Valgus Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-guided-diffusion-model-for-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image synthesis plays a crucial role in providing anatomically accurate images for diagnosis and treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-guided-diffusion-model-for-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IrrMap: A Large-Scale Comprehensive Dataset for Irrigation Method Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irrmap-a-large-scale-comprehensive-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce IrrMap, the first large-scale dataset (1. 1 million patches) for irrigation method mapping across regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irrmap-a-large-scale-comprehensive-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judging the Judges: Can Large Vision-Language Models Fairly Evaluate Chart Comprehension and Reasoning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/judging-the-judges-can-large-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While using LVLMs as judges to assess the chart comprehension capabilities of other LVLMs could streamline evaluation processes, challenges like proprietary datasets, restricted access to powerful models, and evaluation costs hinder their adoption in industrial settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/judging-the-judges-can-large-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Segment Anything Model for Source-Free Domain Adaptation via Dual Feature Guided Auto-Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-segment-anything-model-for-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Source-free domain adaptation (SFDA) for segmentation aims at adapting a model trained in the source domain to perform well in the target domain with only the source model and unlabeled target data. Inspired by the recent success of Segment Anything Model (SAM) which exhibits the generality of segmenting images of various modalities and in different domains given human-annotated prompts like bounding boxes or points, we for the first time explore the potentials of Segment Anything Model for SFDA via automatedly finding an accurate bounding box prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-segment-anything-model-for-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thermal Detection of People with Mobility Restrictions for Barrier Reduction at Traffic Lights Controlled Intersections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermal-detection-of-people-with-mobility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we build the thermal dataset for people with mobility restrictions (TD4PWMR), designed to capture diverse pedestrian scenarios, particularly focusing on individuals with mobility aids or mobility burden under varying environmental conditions, such as different lighting, weather, and crowded urban settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermal-detection-of-people-with-mobility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSurgSAM2: Referring Segment Anything in Surgical Video via Credible Long-term Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resurgsam2-referring-segment-anything-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce ReSurgSAM2, a two-stage surgical referring segmentation framework that leverages Segment Anything Model 2 to perform text-referred target detection, followed by tracking with reliable initial frame identification and diversity-driven long-term memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resurgsam2-referring-segment-anything-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rejoining fragmented ancient bamboo slips with physics-driven deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rejoining-fragmented-ancient-bamboo-slips</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach enables the training of a matching network without requiring manually paired samples, providing ranked suggestions to facilitate the rejoining process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rejoining-fragmented-ancient-bamboo-slips</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Out-of-Distribution Detection in Medical Imaging Using Multi-Exit Class Activation Maps and Feature Masking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-out-of-distribution-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings emphasize the potential of multi-exit networks and feature masking for advancing unsupervised OOD detection in medical imaging, paving the way for more reliable and interpretable models in clinical practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-out-of-distribution-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Foundation Models for Experimental Readout Systems Combining Discrete and Continuous Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-foundation-models-for-experimental</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a (proto) Foundation Model for Nuclear Physics, capable of operating on low-level detector inputs from Imaging Cherenkov Detectors at the future Electron Ion Collider.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-foundation-models-for-experimental</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large-Scale Empirical Analysis of Custom GPTs' Vulnerabilities in the OpenAI Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-empirical-analysis-of-custom</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we analyze 14, 904 custom GPTs to assess their susceptibility to seven exploitable threats, such as roleplay-based attacks, system prompt leakage, phishing content generation, and malicious code synthesis, across various categories and popularity tiers within the OpenAI marketplace.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-empirical-analysis-of-custom</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Removing Watermarks with Partial Regeneration using Semantic Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/removing-watermarks-with-partial-regeneration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As AI-generated imagery becomes ubiquitous, invisible watermarks have emerged as a primary line of defense for copyright and provenance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/removing-watermarks-with-partial-regeneration</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
