<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 09:11:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Inductive Graph Unlearning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inductive-graph-unlearning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To extend machine unlearning to graph data, \textit{GraphEraser} has been proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inductive-graph-unlearning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unconstrained Parametrization of Dissipative and Contracting Neural Ordinary Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unconstrained-parametrization-of-dissipative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We validate the properties of NodeRENs, including the possibility of handling irregularly sampled data, in a case study in nonlinear system identification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unconstrained-parametrization-of-dissipative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Mixture of Experts: Learning on Large-Scale Graphs with Explicit Diversity Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-mixture-of-experts-learning-on-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, GMoE includes information aggregation experts with varying aggregation hop sizes, where the experts with larger hop sizes are specialized in capturing information over longer ranges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-mixture-of-experts-learning-on-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTK-SAP: Improving neural network pruning by aligning training dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntk-sap-improving-neural-network-pruning-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in neural tangent kernel (NTK) theory suggest that the training dynamics of large enough neural networks is closely related to the spectrum of the NTK.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntk-sap-improving-neural-network-pruning-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Fast and Lightweight Network for Low-Light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fast-and-lightweight-network-for-low-light</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve efficient low-light image enhancement, we recognize the challenges of the lack of an absolute reference and the need for a large receptive field to obtain global contrast.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fast-and-lightweight-network-for-low-light</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Content-Based Neural News Recommendation: On User Modeling and Training Objectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-content-based-neural-news</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most neural news recommenders rely on user click behavior and typically introduce dedicated user encoders that aggregate the content of clicked news into user embeddings (early fusion).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-content-based-neural-news</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient SAGE Estimation via Causal Structure Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-sage-estimation-via-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose $d$-SAGE, a method that accelerates SAGE approximation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-sage-estimation-via-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Concept of Forward-Forward Learning Applied to a Multi Output Perceptron</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-concept-of-forward-forward-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The concept of a recently proposed Forward-Forward learning algorithm for fully connected artificial neural networks is applied to a single multi output perceptron for classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-concept-of-forward-forward-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MemeFier: Dual-stage Modality Fusion for Image Meme Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memefier-dual-stage-modality-fusion-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hate speech is a societal problem that has significantly grown through the Internet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memefier-dual-stage-modality-fusion-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards an Effective and Efficient Transformer for Rain-by-snow Weather Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-effective-and-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rain-by-snow weather removal is a specialized task in weather-degraded image restoration aiming to eliminate coexisting rain streaks and snow particles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-effective-and-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-Resolving Face Image by Facial Parsing Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolving-face-image-by-facial-parsing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we build a novel parsing map guided face super-resolution network which extracts the face prior (i. e., parsing map) directly from low-resolution face image for the following utilization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolving-face-image-by-facial-parsing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIF: A General Graph Unlearning Strategy via Influence Function</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gif-a-general-graph-unlearning-strategy-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we recognize the crux to the inability of traditional influence function for graph unlearning, and devise Graph Influence Function (GIF), a model-agnostic unlearning method that can efficiently and accurately estimate parameter changes in response to a $\epsilon$-mass perturbation in deleted data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gif-a-general-graph-unlearning-strategy-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Dependency Transformers: Dependency Tree Emerges from Reversed Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-dependency-transformers-dependency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When looking at an image, we can decompose the scene into entities and their parts as well as obtain the dependencies between them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-dependency-transformers-dependency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLPD: Context-Aware Pedestrian Detection via Vision-Language Semantic Self-Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlpd-context-aware-pedestrian-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we propose a self-supervised Vision-Language Semantic (VLS) segmentation method, which learns both fully-supervised pedestrian detection and contextual segmentation via self-generated explicit labels of semantic classes by vision-language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlpd-context-aware-pedestrian-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making AI Less "Thirsty": Uncovering and Addressing the Secret Water Footprint of AI Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-ai-less-thirsty-uncovering-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The growing carbon footprint of artificial intelligence (AI) models, especially large ones such as GPT-3 and GPT-4, has been undergoing public scrutiny.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-ai-less-thirsty-uncovering-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffMimic: Efficient Motion Mimicking with Differentiable Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffmimic-efficient-motion-mimicking-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motion mimicking is a foundational task in physics-based character animation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffmimic-efficient-motion-mimicking-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Pareto Front of Multilingual Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-pareto-front-of-multilingual-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our observations, we propose the Double Power Law to predict the unique performance trade-off front in MNMT, which is robust across various languages, data adequacy and number of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-pareto-front-of-multilingual-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask Detection and Classification in Thermal Face Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-detection-and-classification-in-thermal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Face masks are recommended to reduce the transmission of many viruses, especially SARS-CoV-2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-detection-and-classification-in-thermal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InterFormer: Real-time Interactive Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interformer-real-time-interactive-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, the model has to repeatedly process the image, the annotator's current click, and the model's feedback of the annotator's former clicks at each step of interaction, resulting in redundant computations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interformer-real-time-interactive-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncurated Image-Text Datasets: Shedding Light on Demographic Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncurated-image-text-datasets-shedding-light</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing tendency to collect large and uncurated datasets to train vision-and-language models has raised concerns about fair representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncurated-image-text-datasets-shedding-light</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting the Complementarity of 2D and 3D Networks to Address Domain-Shift in 3D Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-the-complementarity-of-2d-and-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D semantic segmentation is a critical task in many real-world applications, such as autonomous driving, robotics, and mixed reality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-the-complementarity-of-2d-and-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geometric-aware Pretraining for Vision-centric 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-aware-pretraining-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also conduct experiments on various image backbones and view transformations to validate the efficacy of our approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-aware-pretraining-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-task learning for tissue segmentation and tumor detection in colorectal cancer histology slides</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-tissue-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automating tissue segmentation and tumor detection in histopathology images of colorectal cancer (CRC) is an enabler for faster diagnostic pathology workflows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-tissue-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micron-BERT: BERT-based Facial Micro-Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/micron-bert-bert-based-facial-micro</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating these components into an end-to-end deep network, the proposed $\mu$-BERT significantly outperforms all previous work in various micro-expression tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/micron-bert-bert-based-facial-micro</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFAConv: Innovating Spatital Attention and Standard Convolutional Operation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rfaconv-innovating-spatital-attention-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explain the effectiveness of spatial attention from a new perspective, it is that the spatial attention mechanism essentially solves the problem of convolutional kernel parameter sharing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rfaconv-innovating-spatital-attention-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SegGPT: Segmenting Everything In Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seggpt-segmenting-everything-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We unify various segmentation tasks into a generalist in-context learning framework that accommodates different kinds of segmentation data by transforming them into the same format of images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seggpt-segmenting-everything-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNICORN: A Unified Backdoor Trigger Inversion Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unicorn-a-unified-backdoor-trigger-inversion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, it proposes a unified framework to invert backdoor triggers based on the formalization of triggers and the identified inner behaviors of backdoor models from our analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unicorn-a-unified-backdoor-trigger-inversion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structured prompt interrogation and recursive extraction of semantics (SPIRES): A method for populating knowledge bases using zero-shot learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-prompt-interrogation-and-recursive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Creating knowledge bases and ontologies is a time consuming task that relies on a manual curation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-prompt-interrogation-and-recursive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Saudi Privacy Policy Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-saudi-privacy-policy-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the Saudi Privacy Policy Dataset, a diverse compilation of Arabic privacy policies from various sectors in Saudi Arabia, annotated according to the 10 principles of the Personal Data Protection Law (PDPL); the PDPL was established to be compatible with General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR); one of the most comprehensive data regulations worldwide.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-saudi-privacy-policy-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Deduplication and Leakage Detection in Large Scale Image Datasets with a focus on the CrowdAI Mapping Challenge Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-deduplication-and-leakage-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The CrowdAI Mapping Challenge Dataset is one of these datasets that has been used extensively in recent years to train deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-deduplication-and-leakage-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Knowledge-Rich Sequential Model for Planar Homography Estimation in Aerial Video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-knowledge-rich-sequential-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this concern, we develop a sequential estimator that directly processes a sequence of video frames and estimates their pairwise planar homographic transformations in batches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-knowledge-rich-sequential-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of ChatGPT Family of Models for Biomedical Reasoning and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-chatgpt-family-of-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first task is classifying whether statements of clinical and policy recommendations in scientific literature constitute health advice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-chatgpt-family-of-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-Shot Learning for Fictional Claim Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-shot-learning-for-fictional-claim</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the problem of claim verification in the context of claims about fictional stories in a low-shot learning setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-shot-learning-for-fictional-claim</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EigenFold: Generative Protein Structure Prediction with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigenfold-generative-protein-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Protein structure prediction has reached revolutionary levels of accuracy on single structures, yet distributional modeling paradigms are needed to capture the conformational ensembles and flexibility that underlie biological function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigenfold-generative-protein-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiFormer: Learning Bilateral Motion Estimation via Bilateral Transformer for 4K Video Frame Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biformer-learning-bilateral-motion-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, in global motion estimation, we predict symmetric bilateral motion fields at a coarse scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biformer-learning-bilateral-motion-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Validation in Structure from Motion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-validation-in-structure-from-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, semantic labels on input images are used for the removal of objects associated with motion in the output SfM models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-validation-in-structure-from-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Impact of Voice Anonymization on Speech-Based COVID-19 Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-impact-of-voice-anonymization-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With advances seen in deep learning, voice-based applications are burgeoning, ranging from personal assistants, affective computing, to remote disease diagnostics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-impact-of-voice-anonymization-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ParroT: Translating During Chat Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parrot-translating-during-chat-using-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose the $\mathbf{ParroT}$ framework to enhance and regulate the translation abilities during chat based on open-sourced LLMs (i. e., LLaMA-7b) and human written translation and evaluation data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parrot-translating-during-chat-using-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoStGAN-V: Video Generation with Temporal Motion Styles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mostgan-v-video-generation-with-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video generation remains a challenging task due to spatiotemporal complexity and the requirement of synthesizing diverse motions with temporal consistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mostgan-v-video-generation-with-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selecting Features by their Resilience to the Curse of Dimensionality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-features-by-their-resilience-to-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-world datasets are often of high dimension and effected by the curse of dimensionality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-features-by-their-resilience-to-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape complexity estimation using VAE</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-complexity-estimation-using-vae</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we compare methods for estimating the complexity of two-dimensional shapes and introduce a method that exploits reconstruction loss of Variational Autoencoders with different sizes of latent vectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-complexity-estimation-using-vae</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MS3D: Leveraging Multiple Detectors for Unsupervised Domain Adaptation in 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ms3d-leveraging-multiple-detectors-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed Kernel-Density Estimation (KDE) Box Fusion method fuses box proposals from multiple domains to obtain pseudo-labels that surpass the performance of the best source domain detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ms3d-leveraging-multiple-detectors-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A dynamic Bayesian optimized active recommender system for curiosity-driven Human-in-the-loop automated experiments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamic-bayesian-optimized-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimization of experimental materials synthesis and characterization through active learning methods has been growing over the last decade, with examples ranging from measurements of diffraction on combinatorial alloys at synchrotrons, to searches through chemical space with automated synthesis robots for perovskites.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamic-bayesian-optimized-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-annotator Deep Learning: A Probabilistic Framework for Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-annotator-deep-learning-a-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training standard deep neural networks leads to subpar performances in such multi-annotator supervised learning settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-annotator-deep-learning-a-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Distillation for Gaussian Process Regression and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-distillation-for-gaussian-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose two approaches to extend the notion of knowledge distillation to Gaussian Process Regression (GPR) and Gaussian Process Classification (GPC); data-centric and distribution-centric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-distillation-for-gaussian-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Anomaly Detection with Domain Shift: A Real-world Dataset and Masked Multi-scale Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/industrial-anomaly-detection-with-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, to bridge this gap, we propose the Aero-engine Blade Anomaly Detection (AeBAD) dataset, consisting of two sub-datasets: the single-blade dataset and the video anomaly detection dataset of blades.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/industrial-anomaly-detection-with-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoocRadar: A Fine-grained and Multi-aspect Knowledge Repository for Improving Cognitive Student Modeling in MOOCs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moocradar-a-fine-grained-and-multi-aspect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Student modeling, the task of inferring a student's learning characteristics through their interactions with coursework, is a fundamental issue in intelligent education.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moocradar-a-fine-grained-and-multi-aspect</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HNeRV: A Hybrid Neural Representation for Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hnerv-a-hybrid-neural-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such embedding largely limits the regression capacity and internal generalization for video interpolation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hnerv-a-hybrid-neural-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to choose your best allies for a transferable attack?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-choose-your-best-allies-for-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The transferability of adversarial examples is a key issue in the security of deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-choose-your-best-allies-for-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Certified Radius-Guided Attack Framework to Image Segmentation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-certified-radius-guided-attack-framework-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We are the first, from the attacker perspective, to leverage the properties of certified radius and propose a certified radius guided attack framework against image segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-certified-radius-guided-attack-framework-to</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
