<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:07:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable Human Gaussians from Single-View Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-human-gaussians-from-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose single-view generalizable Human Gaussian model (HGM), a diffusion-guided framework for 3D human modeling from a single image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-human-gaussians-from-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARES: A Comprehensive Benchmark of Trustworthiness in Medical Vision Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cares-a-comprehensive-benchmark-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence has significantly impacted medical applications, particularly with the advent of Medical Large Vision Language Models (Med-LVLMs), sparking optimism for the future of automated and personalized healthcare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cares-a-comprehensive-benchmark-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing to Unseen Domains in Diabetic Retinopathy with Disentangled Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-to-unseen-domains-in-diabetic-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, to improve the robustness of the decoupled representations, class and domain prototypes are employed to interpolate the disentangled representations while data-aware weights are designed to focus on rare classes and domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-to-unseen-domains-in-diabetic-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthesizing Efficient Data with Diffusion Models for Person Re-Identification Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesizing-efficient-data-with-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel paradigm Diffusion-ReID to efficiently augment and generate diverse images based on known identities without requiring any cost of data collection and annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesizing-efficient-data-with-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compute Better Spent: Replacing Dense Layers with Structured Matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compute-better-spent-replacing-dense-layers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that different structures often require drastically different initialization scales and learning rates, which are crucial to performance, especially as models scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compute-better-spent-replacing-dense-layers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaskLID: Code-Switching Language Identification through Iterative Masking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masklid-code-switching-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method uses the LID itself to identify the features that require masking and does not rely on any external resource.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masklid-code-switching-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UEMM-Air: A Synthetic Multi-modal Dataset for Unmanned Aerial Vehicle Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uemm-air-a-synthetic-multi-modal-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a synthetic multi-modal UAV-based object detection dataset, UEMM-Air.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uemm-air-a-synthetic-multi-modal-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Far Can Transformers Reason? The Locality Barrier and Inductive Scratchpad</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-can-transformers-reason-the-locality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Can Transformers predict new syllogisms by composing established ones?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-can-transformers-reason-the-locality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOSA: Music Motion with Semantic Annotation Dataset for Cross-Modal Music Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mosa-music-motion-with-semantic-annotation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In cross-modal music processing, translation between visual, auditory, and semantic content opens up new possibilities as well as challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mosa-music-motion-with-semantic-annotation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM Dataset Inference: Did you train on my dataset?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-dataset-inference-did-you-train-on-my</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead, we propose a new dataset inference method to accurately identify the datasets used to train large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-dataset-inference-did-you-train-on-my</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EpiLearn: A Python Library for Machine Learning in Epidemic Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epilearn-a-python-library-for-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[EpiLearn is a Python toolkit developed for modeling, simulating, and analyzing epidemic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epilearn-a-python-library-for-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Husky: A Unified, Open-Source Language Agent for Multi-Step Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/husky-a-unified-open-source-language-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite using 7B models, Husky matches or even exceeds frontier LMs such as GPT-4 on these tasks, showcasing the efficacy of our holistic approach in addressing complex reasoning problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/husky-a-unified-open-source-language-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dual-View Approach to Classifying Radiology Reports by Co-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dual-view-approach-to-classifying-radiology</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Radiology report analysis provides valuable information that can aid with public health initiatives, and has been attracting increasing attention from the research community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dual-view-approach-to-classifying-radiology</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Real-World Efficiency: Domain Randomization in Reinforcement Learning for Pre-Capture of Free-Floating Moving Targets by Autonomous Robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-efficiency-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this research, we introduce a deep reinforcement learning-based control approach to address the intricate challenge of the robotic pre-grasping phase under microgravity conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-efficiency-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINGOLY: A Benchmark of Olympiad-Level Linguistic Reasoning Puzzles in Low-Resource and Extinct Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lingoly-a-benchmark-of-olympiad-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present the LingOly benchmark, a novel benchmark for advanced reasoning abilities in large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lingoly-a-benchmark-of-olympiad-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ThaiCoref: Thai Coreference Resolution Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thaicoref-thai-coreference-resolution-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce ThaiCoref, a dataset for Thai coreference resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thaicoref-thai-coreference-resolution-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLEUR: An Explainable Reference-Free Evaluation Metric for Image Captioning Using a Large Multimodal Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fleur-an-explainable-reference-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By leveraging a large multimodal model, FLEUR can evaluate the caption against the image without the need for reference captions, and provide the explanation for the assigned score.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fleur-an-explainable-reference-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphStorm: all-in-one graph machine learning framework for industry applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphstorm-all-in-one-graph-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GraphStorm has the following desirable properties: (a) Easy to use: it can perform graph construction and model training and inference with just a single command; (b) Expert-friendly: GraphStorm contains many advanced GML modeling techniques to handle complex graph data and improve model performance; (c) Scalable: every component in GraphStorm can operate on graphs with billions of nodes and can scale model training and inference to different hardware without changing any code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphstorm-all-in-one-graph-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey See, Monkey Do: Harnessing Self-attention in Motion Diffusion for Zero-shot Motion Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monkey-see-monkey-do-harnessing-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the remarkable results of motion synthesis with diffusion models, a natural question arises: how can we effectively leverage these models for motion editing?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monkey-see-monkey-do-harnessing-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UMBRELA: UMbrela is the (Open-Source Reproduction of the) Bing RELevance Assessor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/umbrela-umbrela-is-the-open-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Copious amounts of relevance judgments are necessary for the effective training and accurate evaluation of retrieval systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/umbrela-umbrela-is-the-open-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vript: A Video Is Worth Thousands of Words</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vript-a-video-is-worth-thousands-of-words</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vriptor is also a powerful model capable of end-to-end generation of dense and detailed captions for long videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vript-a-video-is-worth-thousands-of-words</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety Alignment Should Be Made More Than Just a Few Tokens Deep</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-alignment-should-be-made-more-than</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We refer to this issue as shallow safety alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-alignment-should-be-made-more-than</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Bridges: A Dataset for Evaluating Gender-Fair Machine Translation into German</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-bridges-a-dataset-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The translation of gender-neutral person-referring terms (e. g., the students) is often non-trivial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-bridges-a-dataset-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Useful is Intermittent, Asynchronous Expert Feedback for Bayesian Optimization?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-useful-is-intermittent-asynchronous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The gathered feedback is used to learn a Bayesian preference model that can readily be incorporated into the BO thread, to steer its exploration-exploitation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-useful-is-intermittent-asynchronous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoregressive Model Beats Diffusion: Llama for Scalable Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-model-beats-diffusion-llama</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(3) A text-conditional image generation model with 775M parameters, from two-stage training on LAION-COCO and high aesthetics quality images, demonstrating competitive performance of visual quality and text alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-model-beats-diffusion-llama</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>fSEAD: a Composable FPGA-based Streaming Ensemble Anomaly Detection Library</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fsead-a-composable-fpga-based-streaming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning ensembles combine multiple base models to produce a more accurate output.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fsead-a-composable-fpga-based-streaming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Value Functions Estimation with Classification Plug-and-play for Offline Reinforcement Learning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-value-functions-estimation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In deep Reinforcement Learning (RL), value functions are typically approximated using deep neural networks and trained via mean squared error regression objectives to fit the true value functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-value-functions-estimation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Safety of GPT-4o: An Empirical Study using Jailbreak Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-safety-of-gpt-4o-an-empirical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent release of GPT-4o has garnered widespread attention due to its powerful general capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-safety-of-gpt-4o-an-empirical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MATES: Model-Aware Data Selection for Efficient Pretraining with Data Influence Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mates-model-aware-data-selection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce model-aware data selection with data influence models (MATES), where a data influence model continuously adapts to the evolving data preferences of the pretraining model and then selects the data most effective for the current pretraining progress.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mates-model-aware-data-selection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recurrent Context Compression: Efficiently Expanding the Context Window of LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrent-context-compression-efficiently</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To extend the context length of Transformer-based large language models (LLMs) and improve comprehension capabilities, we often face limitations due to computational resources and bounded memory storage capacity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrent-context-compression-efficiently</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural-g: A Deep Learning Framework for Mixing Density Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-g-a-deep-learning-framework-for-mixing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mixing (or prior) density estimation is an important problem in machine learning and statistics, especially in empirical Bayes $g$-modeling where accurately estimating the prior is necessary for making good posterior inferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-g-a-deep-learning-framework-for-mixing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multicam-SLAM: Non-overlapping Multi-camera SLAM for Indirect Visual Localization and Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multicam-slam-non-overlapping-multi-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed Muticam-SLAM includes a unique multi-camera model, a multi-keyframes structure, and several parallel SLAM threads.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multicam-slam-non-overlapping-multi-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diving into Underwater: Segment Anything Model Guided Underwater Salient Instance Segmentation and A Large-scale Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diving-into-underwater-segment-anything-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Underwater salient instance segmentation is a foundational and vital step for various underwater vision tasks, which often suffer from low segmentation accuracy due to the complex underwater circumstances and the adaptive ability of models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diving-into-underwater-segment-anything-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models are Alignable Decision-Makers: Dataset and Application to the Medical Triage Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-are-alignable-decision-makers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such decisions may be guided by different attributes that can be used to characterize an individual's decision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-are-alignable-decision-makers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synth-SBDH: A Synthetic Dataset of Social and Behavioral Determinants of Health for Clinical Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synth-sbdh-a-synthetic-dataset-of-social-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Social and behavioral determinants of health (SBDH) play a crucial role in health outcomes and are frequently documented in clinical text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synth-sbdh-a-synthetic-dataset-of-social-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-RPO: Aligning Diffusion Models through Relative Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-rpo-aligning-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aligning large language models with human preferences has emerged as a critical focus in language modeling research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-rpo-aligning-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VillagerAgent: A Graph-Based Multi-Agent Framework for Coordinating Complex Task Dependencies in Minecraft</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/villageragent-a-graph-based-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to evaluate multi-agent systems against complex dependencies, including spatial, causal, and temporal constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/villageragent-a-graph-based-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binarized Diffusion Model for Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binarized-diffusion-model-for-image-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nonetheless, due to the model structure and the multi-step iterative attribute of DMs, existing binarization methods result in significant performance degradation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binarized-diffusion-model-for-image-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The BiGGen Bench: A Principled Benchmark for Fine-grained Evaluation of Language Models with Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-biggen-bench-a-principled-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, we introduce the BiGGen Bench, a principled generation benchmark designed to thoroughly evaluate nine distinct capabilities of LMs across 77 diverse tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-biggen-bench-a-principled-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Graph Convolutions for Mobile Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-graph-convolutions-for-mobile-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To compete with existing mobile architectures, MobileViG introduces Sparse Vision Graph Attention (SVGA), a fast token-mixing operator based on the principles of GNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-graph-convolutions-for-mobile-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peer Review as A Multi-Turn and Long-Context Dialogue with Role-Based Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peer-review-as-a-multi-turn-and-long-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated wide-ranging applications across various fields and have shown significant potential in the academic peer-review process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peer-review-as-a-multi-turn-and-long-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoPS: Modular Story Premise Synthesis for Open-Ended Automatic Story Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mops-modular-story-premise-synthesis-for-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In supplementary materials, we provide the MoPS code suite, along with 7. 6k generated premises and 1k extended stories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mops-modular-story-premise-synthesis-for-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARLING: Self-supervised Training of Text-based Reinforcement Learning Agent with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/starling-self-supervised-training-of-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce an interactive environment for self-supervised RL, STARLING, for text-based games that bootstraps the text-based RL agents with automatically generated games (based on the seed set of game ideas) to boost the performance and generalization capabilities to reach a goal of the target environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/starling-self-supervised-training-of-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QGEval: A Benchmark for Question Generation Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qgeval-a-benchmark-for-question-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, there is a lack of unified evaluation criteria, which hampers the development of both QG technologies and automatic evaluation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qgeval-a-benchmark-for-question-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A DeNoising FPN With Transformer R-CNN for Tiny Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-denoising-fpn-with-transformer-r-cnn-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, based on the two-stage framework, we replace the obsolete R-CNN detector with a novel Trans R-CNN detector to focus on the representation of tiny objects with self-attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-denoising-fpn-with-transformer-r-cnn-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSC: A toolbox for aerial imagery mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bosc-a-toolbox-for-aerial-imagery-mapping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate and efficient label of aerial images is essential for informed decision-making and resource allocation, whether in identifying crop types or delineating land-use patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bosc-a-toolbox-for-aerial-imagery-mapping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention as a Hypernetwork</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-as-a-hypernetwork</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using the framework of attention as a hypernetwork we further propose a simple modification of multi-head linear attention that strengthens the ability for compositional generalization on a range of abstract reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-as-a-hypernetwork</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SinkLoRA: Enhanced Efficiency and Chat Capabilities for Long-Context Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sinklora-enhanced-efficiency-and-chat</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, LongLoRA is still not as efficient as vanilla attention, reaching only 39\% of the perplexity improvement compared to full attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sinklora-enhanced-efficiency-and-chat</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly Multi-classification in Industrial Scenarios: Transferring Few-shot Learning to a New Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomaly-multi-classification-in-industrial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In industrial scenarios, it is crucial not only to identify anomalous items but also to classify the type of anomaly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomaly-multi-classification-in-industrial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flow of Reasoning: Efficient Training of LLM Policy with Divergent Thinking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-of-reasoning-efficient-training-of-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FoR formulates multi-step LLM reasoning as a Markovian flow from an initial state to terminal states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-of-reasoning-efficient-training-of-llm</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
