<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 21:07:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jury: A Comprehensive Evaluation Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jury-a-comprehensive-evaluation-toolkit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the vast number of Natural Language Processing (NLP) tasks and the development of various metrics have led to challenges in evaluating different systems with different metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jury-a-comprehensive-evaluation-toolkit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Editing Personality for LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editing-personality-for-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This task seeks to adjust the models' responses to opinion-related questions on specified topics since an individual's personality often manifests in the form of their expressed opinions, thereby showcasing different personality traits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editing-personality-for-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards End-to-End Embodied Decision Making via Multi-modal Large Language Model: Explorations with GPT4-Vision and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-end-to-end-embodied-decision-making</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we explore the potential of Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) in improving embodied decision-making processes for agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-end-to-end-embodied-decision-making</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance Needs More Care: Rewriting Prompts for Instances Yields Better Zero-Shot Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-needs-more-care-rewriting-prompts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose PRoMPTd, an approach that rewrites the task prompt for each individual test input to be more specific, unambiguous, and complete, so as to provide better guidance to the task LLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-needs-more-care-rewriting-prompts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiniGPT-5: Interleaved Vision-and-Language Generation via Generative Vokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minigpt-5-interleaved-vision-and-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have garnered significant attention for their advancements in natural language processing, demonstrating unparalleled prowess in text comprehension and generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minigpt-5-interleaved-vision-and-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Autoencoding of Dropout Patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-autoencoding-of-dropout-patterns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a generative model termed Deciphering Autoencoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-autoencoding-of-dropout-patterns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models as Knowledge Bases for Visual Word Sense Disambiguation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-as-knowledge-bases-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Word Sense Disambiguation (VWSD) is a novel challenging task that lies between linguistic sense disambiguation and fine-grained multimodal retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-as-knowledge-bases-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Reach-Avoid for Bayesian Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-reach-avoid-for-bayesian-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such computed lower bounds provide safety certification for the given policy and BNN model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-reach-avoid-for-bayesian-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Stable Backdoor Purification through Feature Shift Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-stable-backdoor-purification-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, it is necessary to disentangle the backdoor and clean features in order to improve backdoor purification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-stable-backdoor-purification-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Encoded Observation Spaces for Perceptive Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-encoded-observation-spaces-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our approach with three state-of-the-art DRL algorithms and find that differential image encoding reduces the memory footprint by as much as 14. 2x and 16. 7x across tasks from the Atari 2600 benchmark and the DeepMind Control Suite (DMC) respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-encoded-observation-spaces-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mini-BEHAVIOR: A Procedurally Generated Benchmark for Long-horizon Decision-Making in Embodied AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-behavior-a-procedurally-generated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Mini-BEHAVIOR, a novel benchmark for embodied AI that challenges agents to use reasoning and decision-making skills to solve complex activities that resemble everyday human challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-behavior-a-procedurally-generated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensemble Distillation for Unsupervised Constituency Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-distillation-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the unsupervised constituency parsing task, which organizes words and phrases of a sentence into a hierarchical structure without using linguistically annotated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-distillation-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Pitfalls of Knowledge Editing for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-pitfalls-of-knowledge-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper pioneers the investigation into the potential pitfalls associated with knowledge editing for LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-pitfalls-of-knowledge-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models Represent Space and Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-represent-space-and-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The capabilities of large language models (LLMs) have sparked debate over whether such systems just learn an enormous collection of superficial statistics or a coherent model of the data generating process -- a world model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-represent-space-and-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LanguageBind: Extending Video-Language Pretraining to N-modality by Language-based Semantic Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/languagebind-extending-video-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While LanguageBind ensures that we can extend VL modalities to N modalities, we also need a high-quality dataset with alignment data pairs centered on language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/languagebind-extending-video-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OceanGPT: A Large Language Model for Ocean Science Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oceangpt-a-large-language-model-for-ocean</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ocean science, which delves into the oceans that are reservoirs of life and biodiversity, is of great significance given that oceans cover over 70% of our planet's surface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oceangpt-a-large-language-model-for-ocean</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Transformers under Occlusion: How Physics and Background Attributes Impact Large Models for Robotic Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-transformers-under-occlusion-how</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As transformer architectures and dataset sizes continue to scale, the need to understand the specific dataset factors affecting model performance becomes increasingly urgent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-transformers-under-occlusion-how</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust deformable image registration using cycle-consistent implicit representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-deformable-image-registration-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve robustness, we propose a deformable registration method using pairs of cycle-consistent Implicit Neural Representations: each implicit representation is linked to a second implicit representation that estimates the opposite transformation, causing each network to act as a regularizer for its paired opposite.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-deformable-image-registration-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Collaboration Mechanisms for LLM Agents: A Social Psychology View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-collaboration-mechanisms-for-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper probes the collaboration mechanisms among contemporary NLP systems by melding practical experiments with theoretical insights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-collaboration-mechanisms-for-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning and reusing primitive behaviours to improve Hindsight Experience Replay sample efficiency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-and-reusing-primitive-behaviours-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hindsight Experience Replay (HER) is a technique used in reinforcement learning (RL) that has proven to be very efficient for training off-policy RL-based agents to solve goal-based robotic manipulation tasks using sparse rewards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-and-reusing-primitive-behaviours-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stack Attention: Improving the Ability of Transformers to Model Hierarchical Patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stack-attention-improving-the-ability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Attention, specifically scaled dot-product attention, has proven effective for natural language, but it does not have a mechanism for handling hierarchical patterns of arbitrary nesting depth, which limits its ability to recognize certain syntactic structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stack-attention-improving-the-ability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VENOM: A Vectorized N:M Format for Unleashing the Power of Sparse Tensor Cores</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/venom-a-vectorized-n-m-format-for-unleashing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the V:N:M format, which enables the execution of arbitrary N:M ratios on SPTCs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/venom-a-vectorized-n-m-format-for-unleashing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMRD: SURE-based Robust MRI Reconstruction with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smrd-sure-based-robust-mri-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, diffusion models require careful tuning of inference hyperparameters on a validation set and are still sensitive to distribution shifts during testing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smrd-sure-based-robust-mri-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised High Dynamic Range Imaging with Multi-Exposure Images in Dynamic Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-high-dynamic-range-imaging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The color component is estimated from aligned multi-exposure images, while the structure one is generated through a structure-focused network that is supervised by the color component and an input reference (\eg, medium-exposure) image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-high-dynamic-range-imaging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shifting More Attention to Breast Lesion Segmentation in Ultrasound Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shifting-more-attention-to-breast-lesion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also devise a localization-based contrastive loss to reduce the lesion location distance between neighboring video frames within the same video and enlarge the location distances between frames from different ultrasound videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shifting-more-attention-to-breast-lesion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Quantum Processes with Quantum Statistical Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-quantum-processes-with-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning complex quantum processes is a central challenge in many areas of quantum computing and quantum machine learning, with applications in quantum benchmarking, cryptanalysis, and variational quantum algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-quantum-processes-with-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Feasible Counterfactual Explanations: A Taxonomy Guided Template-based NLG Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-feasible-counterfactual-explanations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterfactual Explanations (cf-XAI) describe the smallest changes in feature values necessary to change an outcome from one class to another.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-feasible-counterfactual-explanations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving with LLMs: Fusing Object-Level Vector Modality for Explainable Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/driving-with-llms-fusing-object-level-vector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have shown promise in the autonomous driving sector, particularly in generalization and interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/driving-with-llms-fusing-object-level-vector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMBERSim: A Large-Scale Databank for Boosting Similarity Search in Malware Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embersim-a-large-scale-databank-for-boosting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years there has been a shift from heuristics-based malware detection towards machine learning, which proves to be more robust in the current heavily adversarial threat landscape.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embersim-a-large-scale-databank-for-boosting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FiGURe: Simple and Efficient Unsupervised Node Representations with Filter Augmentations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/figure-simple-and-efficient-unsupervised-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a simple filter-based augmentation method to capture different parts of the eigen-spectrum.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/figure-simple-and-efficient-unsupervised-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransRadar: Adaptive-Directional Transformer for Real-Time Multi-View Radar Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transradar-adaptive-directional-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scene understanding plays an essential role in enabling autonomous driving and maintaining high standards of performance and safety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transradar-adaptive-directional-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Classic Deconvolution and Feature Extraction in Zero-Shot Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-classic-deconvolution-and-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach combines a pre-trained network to extract deep features from the input image with iterative Richardson-Lucy deconvolution steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-classic-deconvolution-and-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Generalization of Training-based ChatGPT Detection Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-generalization-of-training-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ChatGPT is one of the most popular language models which achieve amazing performance on various natural language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-generalization-of-training-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Cardiac Segmentation using Graph Convolutional Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-cardiac-segmentation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a graph architecture that uses two convolutional rings based on cardiac anatomy and show that this eliminates anatomical incorrect multi-structure segmentations on the publicly available CAMUS dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-cardiac-segmentation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning on Graphs: Faithful and Interpretable Large Language Model Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-on-graphs-faithful-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel method called reasoning on graphs (RoG) that synergizes LLMs with KGs to enable faithful and interpretable reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-on-graphs-faithful-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diagnosis and Prognosis of Faults in High-Speed Aeronautical Bearings with a Collaborative Selection Incremental Deep Transfer Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnosis-and-prognosis-of-faults-in-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The diagnosis and prognosis of aeronautical-bearing health conditions are essential to proactively ensuring efficient power transmission, safety, and reduced downtime.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnosis-and-prognosis-of-faults-in-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing the Power of Choices in Decision Tree Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-the-power-of-choices-in-decision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a simple generalization of standard and empirically successful decision tree learning algorithms such as ID3, C4. 5, and CART.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-the-power-of-choices-in-decision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM Lies: Hallucinations are not Bugs, but Features as Adversarial Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-lies-hallucinations-are-not-bugs-but</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This phenomenon forces us to revisit that hallucination may be another view of adversarial examples, and it shares similar features with conventional adversarial examples as the basic feature of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-lies-hallucinations-are-not-bugs-but</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Retrieval-Augmented Language Models Robust to Irrelevant Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-retrieval-augmented-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An important desideratum of RALMs, is that retrieved information helps model performance when it is relevant, and does not harm performance when it is not.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-retrieval-augmented-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Training Derivative-Constrained Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-training-derivative-constrained-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We refer to the setting where the (partial) derivatives of a neural network's (NN's) predictions with respect to its inputs are used as additional training signal as a derivative-constrained (DC) NN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-training-derivative-constrained-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Continuous Prompt Transfer: Generalizing Task Semantics Across Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-continuous-prompt-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompt tuning in natural language processing (NLP) has become an increasingly popular method for adapting large language models to specific tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-continuous-prompt-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAT-LM: Training Language Models on Aligned Code And Tests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-lm-training-language-models-on-aligned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also drastically increase the maximum sequence length of inputs to 8, 192 tokens, 4x more than typical code generation models, to ensure that the code context is available to the model when generating test code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-lm-training-language-models-on-aligned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Learning on Neural Networks through Interactive Generation of Digit Patterns and Visual Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-on-neural-networks-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, to improve users' learning and understanding of NNs, an interactive learning system is designed to create digit patterns and recognize them in real time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-on-neural-networks-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Gap between Structural and Semantic Similarity in Diverse Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-structural-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose two new domain-independent metrics which are able to capture relevant information on the difference between two given plans from a domain-dependent viewpoint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-structural-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Investigation of Representation and Allocation Harms in Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-investigation-of-representation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we demonstrate that contrastive learning (CL), a popular variant of SSL, tends to collapse representations of minority groups with certain majority groups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-investigation-of-representation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensor Ring Optimized Quantum-Enhanced Tensor Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensor-ring-optimized-quantum-enhanced-tensor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantum machine learning researchers often rely on incorporating Tensor Networks (TN) into Deep Neural Networks (DNN) and variational optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensor-ring-optimized-quantum-enhanced-tensor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting Tropical Cyclones with Cascaded Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-tropical-cyclones-with-cascaded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As cyclones become more intense due to climate change, the rise of AI-based modelling provides a more affordable and accessible approach compared to traditional methods based on mathematical models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-tropical-cyclones-with-cascaded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling Vision-Language Models for Universal Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-vision-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a degradation-aware vision-language model (DA-CLIP) to better transfer pretrained vision-language models to low-level vision tasks as a universal framework for image restoration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-vision-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PC-NeRF: Parent-Child Neural Radiance Fields under Partial Sensor Data Loss in Autonomous Driving Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pc-nerf-parent-child-neural-radiance-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstructing large-scale 3D scenes is essential for autonomous vehicles, especially when partial sensor data is lost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pc-nerf-parent-child-neural-radiance-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Direct Inversion: Boosting Diffusion-based Editing with 3 Lines of Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/direct-inversion-boosting-diffusion-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, in the context of diffusion-based editing, where a source image is edited according to a target prompt, the process commences by acquiring a noisy latent vector corresponding to the source image via the diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/direct-inversion-boosting-diffusion-based</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
