<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 21:08:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MF-MOS: A Motion-Focused Model for Moving Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mf-mos-a-motion-focused-model-for-moving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moving object segmentation (MOS) provides a reliable solution for detecting traffic participants and thus is of great interest in the autonomous driving field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mf-mos-a-motion-focused-model-for-moving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking Free Transformer Models: Task-specific Context Attribution Promises Improved Generalizability Without Fine-tuning Pre-trained LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-free-transformer-models-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that a linear transformation of the text representation from any transformer model using the task-specific concept operator results in a projection onto the latent concept space, referred to as context attribution in this paper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-free-transformer-models-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Step Forward and Backtrack: Overcoming Zig-Zagging in Loss-Aware Quantization Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-step-forward-and-backtrack-overcoming-zig</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During the gradient descent learning, a one-step forward search is designed to find the trial gradient of the next-step, which is adopted to adjust the gradient of current step towards the direction of fast convergence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-step-forward-and-backtrack-overcoming-zig</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Value Generation with Prompt Learning and Self-Training for Low-Resource Dialogue State Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/state-value-generation-with-prompt-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results on the MultiWOZ 2. 1 dataset show that our method which has only less than 1 billion parameters achieves state-of-the-art performance under the data ratio settings of 5%, 10%, and 25% when limited to models under 100 billion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/state-value-generation-with-prompt-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model Evaluation via Matrix Entropy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-evaluation-via-matrix</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have revolutionized the field of natural language processing, extending their strong capabilities into multi-modal domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-evaluation-via-matrix</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Scaled layouts from non-central panoramas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atlanta-scaled-layouts-from-non-central</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our new pipeline aims to extract the boundaries of the structural lines of an indoor environment with a neural network and exploit the properties of non-central projection systems in a new geometrical processing to recover an scaled 3D layout.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atlanta-scaled-layouts-from-non-central</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weak-to-Strong Jailbreaking on Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weak-to-strong-jailbreaking-on-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Upon examining the jailbreaking vulnerability of aligned LLMs, we observe that the decoding distributions of jailbroken and aligned models differ only in the initial generations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weak-to-strong-jailbreaking-on-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Reinforcement Learning via Function Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-reinforcement-learning-via-function</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although reinforcement learning (RL) can solve many challenging sequential decision making problems, achieving zero-shot transfer across related tasks remains a challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-reinforcement-learning-via-function</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLIC: A Learned Image Codec Using Structure and Color</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slic-a-learned-image-codec-using-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the structure and color based learned image codec (SLIC) in which the task of compression is split into that of luminance and chrominance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slic-a-learned-image-codec-using-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRUD-RAG: A Comprehensive Chinese Benchmark for Retrieval-Augmented Generation of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crud-rag-a-comprehensive-chinese-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For each of these CRUD categories, we have developed comprehensive datasets to evaluate the performance of RAG systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crud-rag-a-comprehensive-chinese-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-granularity Correspondence Learning from Long-term Noisy Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-correspondence-learning-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing video-language studies mainly focus on learning short video clips, leaving long-term temporal dependencies rarely explored due to over-high computational cost of modeling long videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-correspondence-learning-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Assessing the Synthetic-to-Measured Adversarial Vulnerability of SAR ATR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-assessing-the-synthetic-to-measured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, there has been increasing concern about the vulnerability of deep neural network (DNN)-based synthetic aperture radar (SAR) automatic target recognition (ATR) to adversarial attacks, where a DNN could be easily deceived by clean input with imperceptible but aggressive perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-assessing-the-synthetic-to-measured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distinguishing Fictional Voices: a Study of Authorship Verification Models for Quotation Attribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinguishing-fictional-voices-a-study-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent approaches to automatically detect the speaker of an utterance of direct speech often disregard general information about characters in favor of local information found in the context, such as surrounding mentions of entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinguishing-fictional-voices-a-study-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taking Action Towards Graceful Interaction: The Effects of Performing Actions on Modelling Policies for Instruction Clarification Requests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taking-action-towards-graceful-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clarification requests are a mechanism to help solve communication problems, e. g. due to ambiguity or underspecification, in instruction-following interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taking-action-towards-graceful-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLO-World: Real-Time Open-Vocabulary Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo-world-real-time-open-vocabulary-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The You Only Look Once (YOLO) series of detectors have established themselves as efficient and practical tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo-world-real-time-open-vocabulary-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Parametric Anomaly Detection on Tabular Data Non-Parametric Again</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-parametric-anomaly-detection-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning for tabular data has garnered increasing attention in recent years, yet employing deep models for structured data remains challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-parametric-anomaly-detection-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Checkmating One, by Using Many: Combining Mixture of Experts with MCTS to Improve in Chess</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/checkmating-one-by-using-many-combining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new approach that integrates deep learning with computational chess, using both the Mixture of Experts (MoE) method and Monte-Carlo Tree Search (MCTS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/checkmating-one-by-using-many-combining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taxonomy of Mathematical Plagiarism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taxonomy-of-mathematical-plagiarism</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we analyze the best-performing approaches to detect plagiarism and mathematical content similarity on the newly established taxonomy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taxonomy-of-mathematical-plagiarism</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H-SynEx: Using synthetic images and ultra-high resolution ex vivo MRI for hypothalamus subregion segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h-synex-using-synthetic-images-and-ultra-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Materials and Methods: We trained our deep learning method, H-synEx, with synthetic images derived from label maps built from ultra-high resolution ex vivo MRI scans, which enables finer-grained manual segmentation when compared with 1mm isometric in vivo images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h-synex-using-synthetic-images-and-ultra-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MuSc: Zero-Shot Industrial Anomaly Classification and Segmentation with Mutual Scoring of the Unlabeled Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musc-zero-shot-industrial-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We reveal that the abundant normal and abnormal cues implicit in unlabeled test images can be exploited for anomaly determination, which is ignored by prior methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musc-zero-shot-industrial-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gazetteer-Enhanced Bangla Named Entity Recognition with BanglaBERT Semantic Embeddings K-Means-Infused CRF Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gazetteer-enhanced-bangla-named-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this research, we explored the existing state of research in Bangla Named Entity Recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gazetteer-enhanced-bangla-named-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MT-Ranker: Reference-free machine translation evaluation by inter-system ranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mt-ranker-reference-free-machine-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditionally, Machine Translation (MT) Evaluation has been treated as a regression problem -- producing an absolute translation-quality score.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mt-ranker-reference-free-machine-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-central panorama indoor dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-central-panorama-indoor-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Omnidirectional images are one of the main sources of information for learning based scene understanding algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-central-panorama-indoor-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traffic estimation in unobserved network locations using data-driven macroscopic models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-estimation-in-unobserved-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper leverages macroscopic models and multi-source spatiotemporal data collected from automatic traffic counters and probe vehicles to accurately estimate traffic flow and travel time in links where these measurements are unavailable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-estimation-in-unobserved-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPR++: Object Localization via Single Coarse Point Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cpr-object-localization-via-single-coarse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CPR reduces the semantic variance by selecting a semantic centre point in a neighbourhood region to replace the initial annotated point.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cpr-object-localization-via-single-coarse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NormEnsembleXAI: Unveiling the Strengths and Weaknesses of XAI Ensemble Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normensemblexai-unveiling-the-strengths-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a comprehensive comparative analysis of explainable artificial intelligence (XAI) ensembling methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normensemblexai-unveiling-the-strengths-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating ML-Based Anomaly Detection Across Datasets of Varied Integrity: A Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-ml-based-anomaly-detection-across</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we address the prevalent issue of data integrity in network traffic datasets, which are instrumental in developing machine learning (ML) models for anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-ml-based-anomaly-detection-across</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Prompt Optimization for Defending Language Models Against Jailbreaking Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-prompt-optimization-for-defending</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite advances in AI alignment, language models (LM) remain vulnerable to adversarial attacks or jailbreaking, in which adversaries modify input prompts to induce harmful behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-prompt-optimization-for-defending</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morality is Non-Binary: Building a Pluralist Moral Sentence Embedding Space using Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morality-is-non-binary-building-a-pluralist</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that a pluralist approach to morality can be captured in an embedding space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morality-is-non-binary-building-a-pluralist</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multivariate Beta Mixture Model: Probabilistic Clustering With Flexible Cluster Shapes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multivariate-beta-mixture-model-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the multivariate beta mixture model (MBMM), a new probabilistic model for soft clustering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multivariate-beta-mixture-model-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proactive Detection of Voice Cloning with Localized Watermarking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proactive-detection-of-voice-cloning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the rapidly evolving field of speech generative models, there is a pressing need to ensure audio authenticity against the risks of voice cloning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proactive-detection-of-voice-cloning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning, Creation, Usage: Benchmarking LLMs for Comprehensive Tool Utilization in Real-World Complex Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planning-creation-usage-benchmarking-llms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent trend of using Large Language Models (LLMs) as intelligent agents in real-world applications underscores the necessity for comprehensive evaluations of their capabilities, particularly in complex scenarios involving planning, creating, and using tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planning-creation-usage-benchmarking-llms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-ray Image Generation as a Method of Performance Prediction for Real-Time Inspection: a Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-ray-image-generation-as-a-method-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show how a calibrated image generation model can be used to quantitatively evaluate the effect of the X-ray exposure time on the performance of the inspection system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-ray-image-generation-as-a-method-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Channel Characterization of UAV-RIS-aided Systems with Adaptive Phase-shift Configuration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/channel-characterization-of-uav-ris-aided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This letter considers a UAV aiding communication between a ground transmitter and a ground receiver in the presence of co-channel interference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/channel-characterization-of-uav-ris-aided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Differential Privacy for Ridge Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-differential-privacy-for-ridge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DP requires to specify a uniform privacy level $\varepsilon$ that expresses the maximum privacy loss that each data point in the entire dataset is willing to tolerate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-differential-privacy-for-ridge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layered and Staged Monte Carlo Tree Search for SMT Strategy Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layered-and-staged-monte-carlo-tree-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method treats strategy synthesis as a sequential decision-making process, whose search tree corresponds to the strategy space, and employs MCTS to navigate this vast search space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layered-and-staged-monte-carlo-tree-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OptiState: State Estimation of Legged Robots using Gated Networks with Transformer-based Vision and Kalman Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optistate-state-estimation-of-legged-robots</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State estimation for legged robots is challenging due to their highly dynamic motion and limitations imposed by sensor accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optistate-state-estimation-of-legged-robots</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Category-wise Fine-Tuning: Resisting Incorrect Pseudo-Labels in Multi-Label Image Classification with Partial Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/category-wise-fine-tuning-resisting-incorrect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale image datasets are often partially labeled, where only a few categories' labels are known for each image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/category-wise-fine-tuning-resisting-incorrect</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Machine Learning for Cost-Effective Allocation of Development Aid</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-machine-learning-for-cost-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we demonstrate our framework using real-world HIV data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-machine-learning-for-cost-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prospects for inconsistency detection using large language models and sheaves</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prospects-for-inconsistency-detection-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that large language models can produce reasonable numerical ratings of the logical consistency of claims.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prospects-for-inconsistency-detection-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OmniSCV: An Omnidirectional Synthetic Image Generator for Computer Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omniscv-an-omnidirectional-synthetic-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a tool for generating datasets of omnidirectional images with semantic and depth information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omniscv-an-omnidirectional-synthetic-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A fully differentiable model for unsupervised singing voice separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fully-differentiable-model-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A novel model was recently proposed by Schulze-Forster et al. in [1] for unsupervised music source separation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fully-differentiable-model-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBSCSR: The Piano Bootleg Score Composer Style Recognition Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pbscsr-the-piano-bootleg-score-composer-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this goal, we sample fixed-length bootleg score fragments from piano sheet music images on IMSLP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pbscsr-the-piano-bootleg-score-composer-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>History-Aware Conversational Dense Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/history-aware-conversational-dense-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the aforementioned issues, we propose a History-Aware Conversational Dense Retrieval (HAConvDR) system, which incorporates two ideas: context-denoised query reformulation and automatic mining of supervision signals based on the actual impact of historical turns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/history-aware-conversational-dense-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPnet-SPK: full pipeline speaker embedding toolkit with reproducible recipes, self-supervised front-ends, and off-the-shelf models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/espnet-spk-full-pipeline-speaker-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we provide an open-source platform for researchers in the speaker recognition community to effortlessly build models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/espnet-spk-full-pipeline-speaker-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient-Based Language Model Red Teaming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-based-language-model-red-teaming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Red teaming is a common strategy for identifying weaknesses in generative language models (LMs), where adversarial prompts are produced that trigger an LM to generate unsafe responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-based-language-model-red-teaming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NNOSE: Nearest Neighbor Occupational Skill Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nnose-nearest-neighbor-occupational-skill</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The labor market is changing rapidly, prompting increased interest in the automatic extraction of occupational skills from text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nnose-nearest-neighbor-occupational-skill</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmenting Replay in World Models for Continual Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-replay-in-world-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In continual RL, the environment of a reinforcement learning (RL) agent undergoes change.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-replay-in-world-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reviving Undersampling for Long-Tailed Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reviving-undersampling-for-long-tailed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to enhance the accuracy of the worst-performing categories and utilize the harmonic mean and geometric mean to assess the model's performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reviving-undersampling-for-long-tailed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeenyTinyLlama: open-source tiny language models trained in Brazilian Portuguese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teenytinyllama-open-source-tiny-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have significantly advanced natural language processing, but their progress has yet to be equal across languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teenytinyllama-open-source-tiny-language</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
