<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 09:13:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>FeTrIL: Feature Translation for Exemplar-Free Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fetril-feature-translation-for-exemplar-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Actual features of new classes and pseudo-features of past classes are fed into a linear classifier which is trained incrementally to discriminate between all classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fetril-feature-translation-for-exemplar-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAH: Shifting-aware Asymmetric Hashing for Reverse $k$-Maximum Inner Product Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sah-shifting-aware-asymmetric-hashing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To speed up the Maximum Inner Product Search (MIPS) on item vectors, we design a shifting-invariant asymmetric transformation and develop a novel sublinear-time Shifting-Aware Asymmetric Locality Sensitive Hashing (SA-ALSH) scheme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sah-shifting-aware-asymmetric-hashing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subgroup Robustness Grows On Trees: An Empirical Baseline Investigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subgroup-robustness-grows-on-trees-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers have proposed many methods for fair and robust machine learning, but comprehensive empirical evaluation of their subgroup robustness is lacking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subgroup-robustness-grows-on-trees-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reliable Robustness Evaluation via Automatically Constructed Attack Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliable-robustness-evaluation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Attack Ensemble (AE), which combines multiple attacks together, provides a reliable way to evaluate adversarial robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliable-robustness-evaluation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SketchBoost: Fast Gradient Boosted Decision Tree for Multioutput Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sketchboost-fast-gradient-boosted-decision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We are interested in its application to multioutput problems when the output is highly multidimensional.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sketchboost-fast-gradient-boosted-decision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dynamic Weighted Federated Learning for Android Malware Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamic-weighted-federated-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In traditional FL, Federated Averaging (FedAvg) is utilized to construct the global model at each round by merging all of the local models obtained from all of the customers that participated in the FL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamic-weighted-federated-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Feature Attribution Methods for Electrocardiogram</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-feature-attribution-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of cardiac arrhythmia detection with electrocardiograms(ECGs) has been considerably improved since the introduction of deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-feature-attribution-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhostNetV2: Enhance Cheap Operation with Long-Range Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ghostnetv2-enhance-cheap-operation-with-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The convolutional operation can only capture local information in a window region, which prevents performance from being further improved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ghostnetv2-enhance-cheap-operation-with-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Unlearning of Concept Drift with Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-unlearning-of-concept-drift-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose an autoencoder-based method for "unlearning" the concept drift in an unsupervised manner, without having to retrain or adapt any of the learning models operating on the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-unlearning-of-concept-drift-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Identity-Aware Learning for Multi-Agent Value Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-identity-aware-learning-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Value Decomposition (VD) aims to deduce the contributions of agents for decentralized policies in the presence of only global rewards, and has recently emerged as a powerful credit assignment paradigm for tackling cooperative Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning (MARL) problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-identity-aware-learning-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DyRRen: A Dynamic Retriever-Reranker-Generator Model for Numerical Reasoning over Tabular and Textual Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dyrren-a-dynamic-retriever-reranker-generator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerical reasoning over hybrid data containing tables and long texts has recently received research attention from the AI community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dyrren-a-dynamic-retriever-reranker-generator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning on Non-IID Graphs via Structural Knowledge Sharing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-on-non-iid-graphs-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by this, we propose FedStar, an FGL framework that extracts and shares the common underlying structure information for inter-graph federated learning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-on-non-iid-graphs-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAS-LID: Efficient Neural Architecture Search with Local Intrinsic Dimension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nas-lid-efficient-neural-architecture-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One-shot neural architecture search (NAS) substantially improves the search efficiency by training one supernet to estimate the performance of every possible child architecture (i. e., subnet).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nas-lid-efficient-neural-architecture-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DGEKT: A Dual Graph Ensemble Learning Method for Knowledge Tracing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgekt-a-dual-graph-ensemble-learning-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge tracing aims to trace students' evolving knowledge states by predicting their future performance on concept-related exercises.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgekt-a-dual-graph-ensemble-learning-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Autoencoding for Scalable and Generalizable Decision Making</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoding-for-scalable-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We are interested in learning scalable agents for reinforcement learning that can learn from large-scale, diverse sequential data similar to current large vision and language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoding-for-scalable-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrally Pre-Trained Transformer Pyramid Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrally-pre-trained-transformer-pyramid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an integral pre-training framework based on masked image modeling (MIM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrally-pre-trained-transformer-pyramid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is the way: designing and compiling LEPISZCZE, a comprehensive NLP benchmark for Polish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/this-is-the-way-designing-and-compiling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce LEPISZCZE (the Polish word for glew, the Middle English predecessor of glue), a new, comprehensive benchmark for Polish NLP with a large variety of tasks and high-quality operationalization of the benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/this-is-the-way-designing-and-compiling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Video Diffusion Models for High-Fidelity Video Generation with Arbitrary Lengths</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-video-diffusion-models-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models (DMs) are another class of deep generative models and have recently achieved remarkable performance on various image synthesis tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-video-diffusion-models-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransVCL: Attention-enhanced Video Copy Localization Network with Flexible Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transvcl-attention-enhanced-video-copy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous methods typically start from frame-to-frame similarity matrix generated by cosine similarity between frame-level features of the input video pair, and then detect and refine the boundaries of copied segments on similarity matrix under temporal constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transvcl-attention-enhanced-video-copy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texts as Images in Prompt Tuning for Multi-Label Image Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texts-as-images-in-prompt-tuning-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nonetheless, visual data (e. g., images) is by default prerequisite for learning prompts in existing methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texts-as-images-in-prompt-tuning-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can lies be faked? Comparing low-stakes and high-stakes deception video datasets from a Machine Learning perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-lies-be-faked-comparing-low-stakes-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the great impact of lies in human societies and a meager 54% human accuracy for Deception Detection (DD), Machine Learning systems that perform automated DD are still not viable for proper application in real-life settings due to data scarcity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-lies-be-faked-comparing-low-stakes-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVFormer: Semi-supervised Video Transformer for Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svformer-semi-supervised-video-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the use of transformer models under the SSL setting for action recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svformer-semi-supervised-video-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Generation of Socratic Subquestions for Teaching Math Word Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-generation-of-socratic-subquestions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On both automatic and human quality evaluations, we find that LMs constrained with desirable question properties generate superior questions and improve the overall performance of a math word problem solver.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-generation-of-socratic-subquestions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EurNet: Efficient Multi-Range Relational Modeling of Spatial Multi-Relational Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eurnet-efficient-multi-range-relational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study EurNets in two important domains for image and protein structure modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eurnet-efficient-multi-range-relational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TorchScale: Transformers at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchscale-transformers-at-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Transformers have achieved state-of-the-art performance across many tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchscale-transformers-at-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paint by Example: Exemplar-based Image Editing with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paint-by-example-exemplar-based-image-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language-guided image editing has achieved great success recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paint-by-example-exemplar-based-image-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inversion-Based Creativity Transfer with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inversion-based-creativity-transfer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce the task of "Creativity Transfer".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inversion-based-creativity-transfer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Masked Face Classification Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-masked-face-classification-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results show that the richness of SF-MASK (real + synthetic images) leads all of the tested classifiers to perform better than exploiting comparative face mask datasets, on a fixed 1077 images testing set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-masked-face-classification-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Completing point cloud from few points by Wasserstein GAN and Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/completing-point-cloud-from-few-points-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the successful applications of GAN and Transformers in the image-based vision task, we introduce GAN and Transformer techniques to address the above problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/completing-point-cloud-from-few-points-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lite-Mono: A Lightweight CNN and Transformer Architecture for Self-Supervised Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lite-mono-a-lightweight-cnn-and-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we investigate the efficient combination of CNNs and Transformers, and design a hybrid architecture Lite-Mono.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lite-mono-a-lightweight-cnn-and-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MECCH: Metapath Context Convolution-based Heterogeneous Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mecch-metapath-context-convolution-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Heterogeneous graph neural networks (HGNNs) were proposed for representation learning on structural data with multiple types of nodes and edges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mecch-metapath-context-convolution-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Enhancing Optical Embeddings for Lensless Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-enhancing-optical-embeddings-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we enhance the privacy provided by lensless imaging by (1) downsampling at the sensor and (2) using a programmable mask with variable patterns as our optical encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-enhancing-optical-embeddings-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Representation Bottleneck of Chinese Characters: Neural Machine Translation with Stroke Sequence Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-representation-bottleneck-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing research generally treats Chinese character as a minimum unit for representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-representation-bottleneck-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accuracy Prediction for NAS Acceleration using Feature Selection and Extrapolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accuracy-prediction-for-nas-acceleration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When a candidate architecture has properties that are similar to other known architectures, the prediction task is rather straightforward using off-the-shelf regression algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accuracy-prediction-for-nas-acceleration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Cross-Residual Learning for Image Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cross-residual-learning-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ResNets and its variants play an important role in various fields of image recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cross-residual-learning-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SinDiffusion: Learning a Diffusion Model from a Single Natural Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sindiffusion-learning-a-diffusion-model-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SinDiffusion, leveraging denoising diffusion models to capture internal distribution of patches from a single natural image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sindiffusion-learning-a-diffusion-model-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HaRiM$^+$: Evaluating Summary Quality with Hallucination Risk</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harim-evaluating-summary-quality-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the challenges of developing a summarization model arises from the difficulty in measuring the factual inconsistency of the generated text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harim-evaluating-summary-quality-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U-Flow: A U-shaped Normalizing Flow for Anomaly Detection with Unsupervised Threshold</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-flow-a-u-shaped-normalizing-flow-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we propose a non-contrastive method for anomaly detection and segmentation in images, that benefits both from a modern machine learning approach and a more classic statistical detection theory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-flow-a-u-shaped-normalizing-flow-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepJoin: Learning a Joint Occupancy, Signed Distance, and Normal Field Function for Shape Repair</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepjoin-learning-a-joint-occupancy-signed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We generate a high-resolution restoration shape by inferring a corresponding complete shape and a break surface from an input fractured shape.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepjoin-learning-a-joint-occupancy-signed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIC-Score: Probabilistic Interpretable Comparison Score for Optimal Matching Confidence in Single- and Multi-Biometric (Face) Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pic-score-probabilistic-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of biometrics, matching confidence refers to the confidence that a given matching decision is correct.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pic-score-probabilistic-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anatomy-guided domain adaptation for 3D in-bed human pose estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomy-guided-domain-adaptation-for-3d-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a remedy, we present a novel domain adaptation method, adapting a model from a labeled source to a shifted unlabeled target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomy-guided-domain-adaptation-for-3d-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the Type and Target of Offensive Social Media Posts in Marathi</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-type-and-target-of-offensive-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Marathi Offensive Language Dataset v. 2. 0 or MOLD 2. 0 and present multiple experiments on this dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-type-and-target-of-offensive-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mapping City-Wide Perceptions of Neighbourhood Quality using Street View Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-city-wide-perceptions-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers demonstrated the efficacy of crowd-sourcing perception ratings of image pairs across 56 cities and training a model to predict perceptions from street-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-city-wide-perceptions-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Earth Data and Machine Learning for Sustainable and Resilient Agriculture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/big-earth-data-and-machine-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Big streams of Earth images from satellites or other platforms (e. g., drones and mobile phones) are becoming increasingly available at low or no cost and with enhanced spatial and temporal resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/big-earth-data-and-machine-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-task Learning for Camera Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-camera-calibration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As far as we are aware, our approach is the first one that uses an approach to multi-task learning that includes mathematical formulas in a framework for learning to estimate camera parameters to predict both the extrinsic and intrinsic parameters jointly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-camera-calibration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Transferability of Visual Features in Generalized Zero-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-transferability-of-visual-features-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalized Zero-Shot Learning (GZSL) aims to train a classifier that can generalize to unseen classes, using a set of attributes as auxiliary information, and the visual features extracted from a pre-trained convolutional neural network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-transferability-of-visual-features-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Center-based Deep Contrastive Metric Learning Method for the Detection of Polymicrogyria in Pediatric Brain MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-center-based-deep-contrastive-metric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an anomaly detection method based on a novel center-based deep contrastive metric learning loss function (cDCM) which enables the automatic detection of cases of potential PMG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-center-based-deep-contrastive-metric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Program of Thoughts Prompting: Disentangling Computation from Reasoning for Numerical Reasoning Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/program-of-thoughts-prompting-disentangling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By combining PoT with self-consistency decoding, we can achieve SoTA performance on all math problem datasets and near-SoTA performance on financial datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/program-of-thoughts-prompting-disentangling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ontology-aware Learning and Evaluation for Audio Tagging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontology-aware-learning-and-evaluation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed metric, ontology-aware mean average precision (OmAP) addresses the weaknesses of mAP by utilizing the AudioSet ontology information during the evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontology-aware-learning-and-evaluation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Person Image Synthesis via Denoising Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/person-image-synthesis-via-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show how denoising diffusion models can be applied for high-fidelity person image synthesis with strong sample diversity and enhanced mode coverage of the learnt data distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/person-image-synthesis-via-denoising</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
