<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 21:07:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>HoW-3D: Holistic 3D Wireframe Perception from a Single Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-3d-holistic-3d-wireframe-perception-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the problem of holistic 3D wireframe perception (HoW-3D), a new task of perceiving both the visible 3D wireframes and the invisible ones from single-view 2D images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-3d-holistic-3d-wireframe-perception-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Video Domain Adaptation: A Disentanglement Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-video-domain-adaptation-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we consider the generation of cross-domain videos from two sets of latent factors, one encoding the static domain-related information and another encoding the temporal and semantic-related information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-video-domain-adaptation-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Causal View of Domain Invariant Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-causal-view-of-domain-invariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning methods can be unreliable when deployed in domains that differ from the domains on which they were trained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-causal-view-of-domain-invariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Task-Oriented Dialogue Systems with Response Selection as an Auxiliary Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-task-oriented-dialogue-systems-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The adoption of pre-trained language models in task-oriented dialogue systems has resulted in significant enhancements of their text generation abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-task-oriented-dialogue-systems-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of impact of emotions on target speech extraction and speech separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-impact-of-emotions-on-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the factors causing such degradation may be intrinsic speaker variability, such as emotions, occurring commonly in realistic speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-impact-of-emotions-on-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Z-BERT-A: a zero-shot Pipeline for Unknown Intent detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/z-bert-a-a-zero-shot-pipeline-for-unknown</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main challenge resides in the need to identify from input utterances novel unseen in-tents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/z-bert-a-a-zero-shot-pipeline-for-unknown</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Does Data Freshness Affect Real-time Supervised Learning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-does-data-freshness-affect-real-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To minimize the inference error in real-time, we propose a new "selection-from-buffer" model for sending the features, which is more general than the "generate-at-will" model used in earlier studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-does-data-freshness-affect-real-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applying Regularized Schrödinger-Bridge-Based Stochastic Process in Generative Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applying-regularized-schrodinger-bridge-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, this study tried to reduce the number of timesteps and training time required and proposed regularization terms to the existing SB models to make the bidirectional stochastic processes consistent and stable with a reduced number of timesteps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applying-regularized-schrodinger-bridge-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pyramidal Predictive Network: A Model for Visual-frame Prediction Based on Predictive Coding Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyramidal-predictive-network-a-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main innovation of our model is that the update frequency of neural units on each of the layer decreases with the increasing of network levels, which results in the model appears like a pyramid from the perspective of time dimension, so we call it the Pyramid Predictive Network (PPNet).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyramidal-predictive-network-a-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Pole Segmentation on Range Images for Long-term LiDAR Localization in Urban Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-pole-segmentation-on-range-images-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further use the extracted poles as pseudo labels to train a deep neural network for online range image-based pole segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-pole-segmentation-on-range-images-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Deep Learning-based 3-lead ECG Classification with Heartbeat Counting and Demographic Data Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-deep-learning-based-3-lead-ecg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nowadays, an increasing number of people are being diagnosed with cardiovascular diseases (CVDs), the leading cause of death globally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-deep-learning-based-3-lead-ecg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InvisibiliTee: Angle-agnostic Cloaking from Person-Tracking Systems with a Tee</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invisibilitee-angle-agnostic-cloaking-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After a survey for person-tracking system-induced privacy concerns, we propose a black-box adversarial attack method on state-of-the-art human detection models called InvisibiliTee.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invisibilitee-angle-agnostic-cloaking-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLAND: Graph Learning Framework for Dynamic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roland-graph-learning-framework-for-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we propose a scalable and efficient training approach for dynamic GNNs via incremental training and meta-learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roland-graph-learning-framework-for-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DM-NeRF: 3D Scene Geometry Decomposition and Manipulation from 2D Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dm-nerf-3d-scene-geometry-decomposition-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the problem of 3D scene geometry decomposition and manipulation from 2D views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dm-nerf-3d-scene-geometry-decomposition-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Interpretable Sleep Stage Classification Using Cross-Modal Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-interpretable-sleep-stage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we propose Cross-Modal Transformers, which is a transformer-based method for sleep stage classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-interpretable-sleep-stage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SYN-MAD 2022: Competition on Face Morphing Attack Detection Based on Privacy-aware Synthetic Training Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syn-mad-2022-competition-on-face-morphing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The competition attracted a total of 12 participating teams, both from academia and industry and present in 11 different countries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syn-mad-2022-competition-on-face-morphing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Attention Network for Few-Shot Object Detection via Meta-Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-attention-network-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a hierarchical attention network with sequentially large receptive fields to fully exploit the query and support images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-attention-network-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computational Empathy Counteracts the Negative Effects of Anger on Creative Problem Solving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-empathy-counteracts-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an online experiment with 1, 006 participants randomly assigned to an emotion elicitation intervention (with a control elicitation condition and anger elicitation condition) and a computational empathy intervention (with a control virtual agent and an empathic virtual agent), we examine how anger and empathy influence participants' performance in solving a word game based on Wordle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-empathy-counteracts-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man-in-the-Middle Attack against Object Detection Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/man-in-the-middle-attack-against-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Is deep learning secure for robots?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/man-in-the-middle-attack-against-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Vision Transformers for Malware Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-vision-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Malware detection plays a crucial role in cyber-security with the increase in malware growth and advancements in cyber-attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-vision-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining Gradients and Probabilities for Heterogeneous Approximation of Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-gradients-and-probabilities-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further demonstrate that our error model can predict the parameters of an approximate multiplier in the context of the commonly used additive Gaussian noise (AGN) model with high accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-gradients-and-probabilities-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WiFi Based Distance Estimation Using Supervised Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wifi-based-distance-estimation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, measuring the spatial distance between given set of WiFi fingerprints is heavily affected by the selection of the signal distance function used to model signal space as geospatial distance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wifi-based-distance-estimation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELEVANT: A Fully Automatic Fine-Grained Entity Linking Evaluation and Analysis Tool</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elevant-a-fully-automatic-fine-grained-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Elevant, a tool for the fully automatic fine-grained evaluation of a set of entity linkers on a set of benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elevant-a-fully-automatic-fine-grained-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Attribute Open Set Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-attribute-open-set-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While conventional OSR approaches can detect Out-of-Distribution (OOD) samples, they cannot provide explanations indicating which underlying visual attribute(s) (e. g., shape, color or background) cause a specific sample to be unknown.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-attribute-open-set-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flow-Guided Transformer for Video Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-guided-transformer-for-video-inpainting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Especially in spatial transformer, we design a dual perspective spatial MHSA, which integrates the global tokens to the window-based attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-guided-transformer-for-video-inpainting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HighlightNet: Highlighting Low-Light Potential Features for Real-Time UAV Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/highlightnet-highlighting-low-light-potential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pixel-level range mask is introduced to make HighlightNet more focused on the enhancement of the tracking object and regions without light sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/highlightnet-highlighting-low-light-potential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyP$^2$ Loss: Beyond Hypersphere Metric Space for Multi-label Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyp-2-loss-beyond-hypersphere-metric-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image retrieval has become an increasingly appealing technique with broad multimedia application prospects, where deep hashing serves as the dominant branch towards low storage and efficient retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyp-2-loss-beyond-hypersphere-metric-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Learning Radiance Fields by Shooting Much Fewer Rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-learning-radiance-fields-by-shooting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results show that our method achieves comparable accuracy to the state-of-the-art with much faster training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-learning-radiance-fields-by-shooting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Link-Backdoor: Backdoor Attack on Link Prediction via Node Injection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-backdoor-backdoor-attack-on-link</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consequently, the link prediction model trained on the backdoored dataset will predict the link with trigger to the target state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-backdoor-backdoor-attack-on-link</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNPassGAN: Improved Generative Adversarial Networks For Trawling Offline Password Guessing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnpassgan-improved-generative-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach, however, needs domain-specific knowledge and expertise that are difficult to duplicate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnpassgan-improved-generative-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Localization via Few-Shot Scene Region Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-localization-via-few-shot-scene-region</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual (re)localization addresses the problem of estimating the 6-DoF (Degree of Freedom) camera pose of a query image captured in a known scene, which is a key building block of many computer vision and robotics applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-localization-via-few-shot-scene-region</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shuffle Instances-based Vision Transformer for Pancreatic Cancer ROSE Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shuffle-instances-based-vision-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid on-site evaluation (ROSE) technique can signifi-cantly accelerate the diagnosis of pancreatic cancer by im-mediately analyzing the fast-stained cytopathological images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shuffle-instances-based-vision-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TripJudge: A Relevance Judgement Test Collection for TripClick Health Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tripjudge-a-relevance-judgement-test</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust test collections are crucial for Information Retrieval research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tripjudge-a-relevance-judgement-test</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVisT: A Benchmark for Visual Object Tracking in Adverse Visibility</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avist-a-benchmark-for-visual-object-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While being greatly benefiting to the tracking research, existing benchmarks do not pose the same difficulty as before with recent trackers achieving higher performance mainly due to (i) the introduction of more sophisticated transformers-based methods and (ii) the lack of diverse scenarios with adverse visibility such as, severe weather conditions, camouflage and imaging effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avist-a-benchmark-for-visual-object-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTCSNN: Multi-task Clinical Siamese Neural Network for Diabetic Retinopathy Severity Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtcsnn-multi-task-clinical-siamese-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The novelty of this project is to utilize the ordinal information among labels and add a new regression task, which can help the model learn more discriminative feature embedding for fine-grained classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtcsnn-multi-task-clinical-siamese-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virgo: Scalable Unsupervised Classification of Cosmological Shock Waves</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virgo-scalable-unsupervised-classification-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cosmological shock waves are essential to understanding the formation of cosmological structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virgo-scalable-unsupervised-classification-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frouros: A Python library for drift detection in Machine Learning problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frouros-a-python-library-for-drift-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Frouros is a Python library capable of detecting drift in machine learning problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frouros-a-python-library-for-drift-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An approach to generalizing some impossibility theorems in social choice</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-approach-to-generalizing-some</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In social choice theory, voting methods can be classified by invariance properties: a voting method is said to be C1 if it selects the same winners for any two profiles of voter preferences that produce the same majority graph on the set of candidates; a voting method is said to be pairwise if it selects the same winners for any two preference profiles that produce the same weighted majority graph on the set of candidates; and other intermediate classifications are possible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-approach-to-generalizing-some</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoShNet: A Hybird Complex Valued Neural Network using Shearlets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coshnet-a-hybird-complex-valued-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a hybrid neural network, the expensive convolutional layers are replaced by a non-trainable fixed transform with a great reduction in parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coshnet-a-hybird-complex-valued-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imputation Strategies Under Clinical Presence: Impact on Algorithmic Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imputation-strategies-under-clinical-presence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we provide a structured view of the relationship between clinical presence mechanisms and group-specific missingness patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imputation-strategies-under-clinical-presence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BenchPress: A Deep Active Benchmark Genertor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchpress-a-deep-active-benchmark-genertor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop BenchPress, the first ML benchmark generator for compilers that is steerable within feature space representations of source code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchpress-a-deep-active-benchmark-genertor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpansionNet v2: Block Static Expansion in fast end to end training for Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expansionnet-v2-block-static-expansion-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Expansion methods explore the possibility of performance bottlenecks in the input length in Deep Learning methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expansionnet-v2-block-static-expansion-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Network-level Traffic Flow Transitions on Sparse Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-network-level-traffic-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DTIGNN models the traffic system as a dynamic graph influenced by traffic signals, learns the transition models grounded by fundamental transition equations from transportation, and predicts future traffic states with imputation in the process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-network-level-traffic-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Comparison of Explainable Artificial Intelligence Methods for Clinical Data: A Case Study on Traumatic Brain Injury</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-comparison-of-explainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The implemented methods were compared to one another in terms of several XAI characteristics such as understandability, fidelity, and stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-comparison-of-explainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Contained Entity Discovery from Captioned Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-contained-entity-discovery-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the task of visual named entity discovery in videos without the need for task-specific supervision or task-specific external knowledge sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-contained-entity-discovery-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Limitations of Continual Learning for Malware Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-limitations-of-continual-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our surprise, continual learning methods significantly underperformed naive Joint replay of the training data in nearly all settings -- in some cases reducing accuracy by more than 70 percentage points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-limitations-of-continual-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Contrastive Representation Learning for Semi-supervised Time-Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-contrastive-representation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose time-series specific weak and strong augmentations and use their views to learn robust temporal relations in the proposed temporal contrasting module, besides learning discriminative representations by our proposed contextual contrasting module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-contrastive-representation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Linear Non-Gaussian Polytree Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-linear-non-gaussian-polytree-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of graphical causal discovery, we adapt the versatile framework of linear non-Gaussian acyclic models (LiNGAMs) to propose new algorithms to efficiently learn graphs that are polytrees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-linear-non-gaussian-polytree-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locating disparities in machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locating-disparities-in-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, ALD helps practitioners and researchers of algorithmic fairness to detect disparities in machine learning algorithms, so that disparate -- or even unfair -- outcomes can be mitigated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locating-disparities-in-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Matting-specific Portrait Enhancement and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-matting-specific-portrait</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, we invert an input portrait into the latent code of StyleGAN, and our aim is to discover whether there is an enhanced version in the latent space which is more compatible with a reference matting model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-matting-specific-portrait</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
