<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 09:13:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Moûsai: Text-to-Music Generation with Long-Context Latent Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mousai-text-to-music-generation-with-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our work, we investigate the potential of diffusion models for text-conditional music generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mousai-text-to-music-generation-with-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimally-Weighted Estimators of the Maximum Mean Discrepancy for Likelihood-Free Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimally-weighted-estimators-of-the-maximum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Likelihood-free inference methods typically make use of a distance between simulated and real data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimally-weighted-estimators-of-the-maximum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-Scale Traffic Data Imputation with Spatiotemporal Semantic Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-traffic-data-imputation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the proposed model introduces semantic descriptions consisting of network-wide spatial and temporal information of traffic data to help the GT-TDI model capture spatiotemporal correlations at a network level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-traffic-data-imputation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harmonizing Flows: Unsupervised MR harmonization based on normalizing flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harmonizing-flows-unsupervised-mr</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an unsupervised framework based on normalizing flows that harmonizes MR images to mimic the distribution of the source domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harmonizing-flows-unsupervised-mr</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Effects of Physical Actions in a Multi-modal Environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-effects-of-physical-actions-in-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, predicting the effects of an action before it is executed is crucial in planning, where coherent sequences of actions are often needed to achieve a goal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-effects-of-physical-actions-in-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcome-directed Reinforcement Learning by Uncertainty &amp; Temporal Distance-Aware Curriculum Goal Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outcome-directed-reinforcement-learning-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current reinforcement learning (RL) often suffers when solving a challenging exploration problem where the desired outcomes or high rewards are rarely observed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outcome-directed-reinforcement-learning-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional neural networks for valid and efficient causal inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-for-valid-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an application where we want to estimate the effect of early retirement on a health outcome, we propose to use CNN to control for time-structured covariates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-for-valid-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Input Perturbation Reduces Exposure Bias in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/input-perturbation-reduces-exposure-bias-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we observe that a long sampling chain also leads to an error accumulation phenomenon, which is similar to the \textbf{exposure bias} problem in autoregressive text generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/input-perturbation-reduces-exposure-bias-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-tuning Neural-Operator architectures for training and generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-neural-operator-architectures-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present an analysis of the generalization of Neural Operators (NOs) and derived architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-neural-operator-architectures-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CellMix: A General Instance Relationship based Method for Data Augmentation Towards Pathology Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cellmix-a-general-instance-relationship-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further understand the pathology characteristics and make up effective pseudo samples, we propose the CellMix framework with a novel distribution-based in-place shuffle strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cellmix-a-general-instance-relationship-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Restoration with Mean-Reverting Stochastic Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-restoration-with-mean-reverting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a stochastic differential equation (SDE) approach for general-purpose image restoration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-restoration-with-mean-reverting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Deep Learning Method for Comparing Bayesian Hierarchical Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-method-for-comparing-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian model comparison (BMC) offers a principled approach for assessing the relative merits of competing computational models and propagating uncertainty into model selection decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-method-for-comparing-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Guided Diffusion Sampling with Splitting Numerical Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-guided-diffusion-sampling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Guided diffusion is a technique for conditioning the output of a diffusion model at sampling time without retraining the network for each specific task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-guided-diffusion-sampling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Abstractions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-abstractions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel method for the safety verification of nonlinear dynamical models that uses neural networks to represent abstractions of their dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-abstractions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust variance-regularized risk minimization with concomitant scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-variance-regularized-risk-minimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under losses which are potentially heavy-tailed, we consider the task of minimizing sums of the loss mean and standard deviation, without trying to accurately estimate the variance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-variance-regularized-risk-minimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed Attention Network for Hyperspectral Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-attention-network-for-hyperspectral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing methods show limitations in exploring the spectral correlations across different bands and feature interactions within each band.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-attention-network-for-hyperspectral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Study of Pretrained Language Models for Long Clinical Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-pretrained-language-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Objective: Clinical knowledge enriched transformer models (e. g., ClinicalBERT) have state-of-the-art results on clinical NLP (natural language processing) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-pretrained-language-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event Causality Extraction with Event Argument Correlations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-causality-extraction-with-event-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event Causality Identification (ECI), which aims to detect whether a causality relation exists between two given textual events, is an important task for event causality understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-causality-extraction-with-event-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task-Agnostic Graph Neural Network Evaluation via Adversarial Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-agnostic-graph-neural-network-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GraphAC succeeds in distinguishing GNNs of different expressiveness across various aspects, and has been proven to be a principled and reliable GNN evaluation method, eliminating the need for handcrafted augmentations for stable SSL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-agnostic-graph-neural-network-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nik Defense: An Artificial Intelligence Based Defense Mechanism against Selfish Mining in Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nik-defense-an-artificial-intelligence-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, literature has shown that Bitcoin mining's protocol is not incentive-compatible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nik-defense-an-artificial-intelligence-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which Experiences Are Influential for Your Agent? Policy Iteration with Turn-over Dropout</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/which-experiences-are-influential-for-your</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In reinforcement learning (RL) with experience replay, experiences stored in a replay buffer influence the RL agent's performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/which-experiences-are-influential-for-your</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boundary Aware U-Net for Glacier Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-aware-u-net-for-glacier-segmentation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale study of glaciers improves our understanding of global glacier change and is imperative for monitoring the ecological environment, preventing disasters, and studying the effects of global climate change.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-aware-u-net-for-glacier-segmentation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MG-GNN: Multigrid Graph Neural Networks for Learning Multilevel Domain Decomposition Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mg-gnn-multigrid-graph-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain decomposition methods (DDMs) are popular solvers for discretized systems of partial differential equations (PDEs), with one-level and multilevel variants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mg-gnn-multigrid-graph-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Robust Optimisation Perspective on Counterexample-Guided Repair of Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-robust-optimisation-perspective-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterexample-guided repair aims at creating neural networks with mathematical safety guarantees, facilitating the application of neural networks in safety-critical domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-robust-optimisation-perspective-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Domain Adaptation for Remote Sensing Image Scene Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-domain-adaptation-for-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirical results show that the proposed model is effective and practical for remote sensing image scene classification, regardless of whether the source data is available or not.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-domain-adaptation-for-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling Cognitive Backdoor Patterns within an Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-cognitive-backdoor-patterns-within</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct extensive experiments to show that CD can robustly detect a wide range of advanced backdoor attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-cognitive-backdoor-patterns-within</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Problems in Applied Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-problems-in-applied-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work formulates the machine learning mechanism as a bi-level optimization problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-problems-in-applied-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trajectory-Aware Eligibility Traces for Off-Policy Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajectory-aware-eligibility-traces-for-off</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Off-policy learning from multistep returns is crucial for sample-efficient reinforcement learning, but counteracting off-policy bias without exacerbating variance is challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajectory-aware-eligibility-traces-for-off</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Train Hard, Fight Easy: Robust Meta Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/train-hard-fight-easy-robust-meta</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that the former disappears in MRL, and address the latter via the novel Robust Meta RL algorithm (RoML).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/train-hard-fight-easy-robust-meta</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemSup-XC: Semantic Supervision for Zero and Few-shot Extreme Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semsup-xc-semantic-supervision-for-zero-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we develop SemSup-XC, a model that achieves state-of-the-art zero-shot and few-shot performance on three XC datasets derived from legal, e-commerce, and Wikipedia data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semsup-xc-semantic-supervision-for-zero-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Reasoning of Entities and Events in Procedural Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-reasoning-of-entities-and-events-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entities and events have long been regarded as the crux of machine reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-reasoning-of-entities-and-events-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Regions of Counterfactual Explanations via Robust Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-regions-of-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, our method provides a whole region of CEs allowing the user to choose a suitable recourse to obtain a desired outcome.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-regions-of-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoRaLay: A Multilingual and Multimodal Dataset for Long Range and Layout-Aware Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loralay-a-multilingual-and-multimodal-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text Summarization is a popular task and an active area of research for the Natural Language Processing community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loralay-a-multilingual-and-multimodal-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WL meet VC</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wl-meet-vc</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, when an upper bound on the graphs' order is known, we show a tight connection between the number of graphs distinguishable by the $1\text{-}\mathsf{WL}$ and GNNs' VC dimension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wl-meet-vc</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftMatch: Addressing the Quantity-Quality Trade-off in Semi-supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softmatch-addressing-the-quantity-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The critical challenge of Semi-Supervised Learning (SSL) is how to effectively leverage the limited labeled data and massive unlabeled data to improve the model's generalization performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softmatch-addressing-the-quantity-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A benchmark for toxic comment classification on Civil Comments dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-toxic-comment-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BiLSTM remains a good compromise between performance and inference time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-toxic-comment-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-based Recommendation for Sparse and Heterogeneous User Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-recommendation-for-sparse-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a graph-based recommender model which utilizes heterogeneous interactions between users and content of different types and is able to operate well on small-scale datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-recommendation-for-sparse-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affective Faces for Goal-Driven Dyadic Communication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affective-faces-for-goal-driven-dyadic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a video framework for modeling the association between verbal and non-verbal communication during dyadic conversation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affective-faces-for-goal-driven-dyadic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Systematic Review of Green AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-review-of-green-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a conclusion, the Green AI research field results to have reached a considerable level of maturity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-review-of-green-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Molecular Language Model as Multi-task Generator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-language-model-as-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further propose multi-task molecular prefix tuning across several molecular generation tasks and different molecular domains (synthetic & natural products) with a self-feedback mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-language-model-as-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-step interpretable modeling of Intensive Care Acquired Infections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-step-interpretable-modeling-of-intensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel methodology for integrating high resolution longitudinal data with the dynamic prediction capabilities of survival models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-step-interpretable-modeling-of-intensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Contrastive Learning for Skeleton-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-contrastive-learning-for-skeleton-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a graph contrastive learning framework for skeleton-based action recognition (\textit{SkeletonGCL}) to explore the \textit{global} context across all sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-contrastive-learning-for-skeleton-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Projection-Enhancement Network (PEN)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-projection-enhancement-network-pen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contemporary approaches to instance segmentation in cell science use 2D or 3D convolutional networks depending on the experiment and data structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-projection-enhancement-network-pen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Building Changes with Off-Nadir Aerial Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-building-changes-with-off-nadir</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The tilted viewing nature of the off-nadir aerial images brings severe challenges to the building change detection (BCD) problem: the mismatch of the nearby buildings and the semantic ambiguity of the building facades.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-building-changes-with-off-nadir</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Box$^2$EL: Concept and Role Box Embeddings for the Description Logic EL++</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/box-2-el-concept-and-role-box-embeddings-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representation learning in the form of semantic embeddings has been successfully applied to a variety of tasks in natural language processing and knowledge graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/box-2-el-concept-and-role-box-embeddings-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Multiple Independent Advisors in Multi-agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-multiple-independent-advisors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper considers the problem of simultaneously learning from multiple independent advisors in multi-agent reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-multiple-independent-advisors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cut and Learn for Unsupervised Object Detection and Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cut-and-learn-for-unsupervised-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Cut-and-LEaRn (CutLER), a simple approach for training unsupervised object detection and segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cut-and-learn-for-unsupervised-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compact Transformer Tracker with Correlative Masked Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-transformer-tracker-with-correlative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer framework has been showing superior performances in visual object tracking for its great strength in information aggregation across the template and search image with the well-known attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-transformer-tracker-with-correlative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Planning as Heuristic Search: A new planning search-space that leverages pointers over objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-planning-as-heuristic-search-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, the paper introduces a new pointer-based solution space for GP that is independent of the number of classical planning instances in a GP problem and the size of those instances (i. e. the number of objects, state variables and their domain sizes).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-planning-as-heuristic-search-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Temporal Modeling for CLIP-based Image-to-Video Knowledge Transferring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-temporal-modeling-for-clip-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, based on the CLIP model, we revisit temporal modeling in the context of image-to-video knowledge transferring, which is the key point for extending image-text pretrained models to the video domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-temporal-modeling-for-clip-based</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
