<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 21:07:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Context-Based Low-Light Image Enhancement via Neural Implicit Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-context-based-low-light-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current deep learning-based low-light image enhancement methods often struggle with high-resolution images, and fail to meet the practical demands of visual perception across diverse and unseen scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-context-based-low-light-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HGL: Hierarchical Geometry Learning for Test-time Adaptation in 3D Point Cloud Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgl-hierarchical-geometry-learning-for-test</link>
      <description><![CDATA[HGL comprises three complementary modules from local, global to temporal learning in a bottom-up manner. Technically, we first construct a local geometry learning module for pseudo-label generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgl-hierarchical-geometry-learning-for-test</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Better Angels of Machine Personality: How Personality Relates to LLM Safety</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-better-angels-of-machine-personality-how</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we discover that LLMs' personality traits are closely related to their safety abilities, i. e., toxicity, privacy, and fairness, based on the reliable MBTI-M scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-better-angels-of-machine-personality-how</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoSIGN: Few-Step Guidance of ConSIstency Model to Solve General INverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosign-few-step-guidance-of-consistency-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within comparable NFEs, our method achieves new state-of-the-art in diffusion-based inverse problem solving, showcasing the significant potential of employing prior-based inverse problem solvers for real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosign-few-step-guidance-of-consistency-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging the Mahalanobis Distance to enhance Unsupervised Brain MRI Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-the-mahalanobis-distance-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised Anomaly Detection (UAD) methods rely on healthy data distributions to identify anomalies as outliers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-the-mahalanobis-distance-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving Adaptive Re-Identification without Image Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-adaptive-re-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Re-Identification systems (Re-ID) are crucial for public safety but face the challenge of having to adapt to environments that differ from their training distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-adaptive-re-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NavGPT-2: Unleashing Navigational Reasoning Capability for Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navgpt-2-unleashing-navigational-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Capitalizing on the remarkable advancements in Large Language Models (LLMs), there is a burgeoning initiative to harness LLMs for instruction following robotic navigation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navgpt-2-unleashing-navigational-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProcTag: Process Tagging for Assessing the Efficacy of Document Instruction Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proctag-process-tagging-for-assessing-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An effective evaluation method for document instruction data is crucial in constructing instruction data with high efficacy, which, in turn, facilitates the training of LLMs and MLLMs for document VQA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proctag-process-tagging-for-assessing-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unifying Post-Processing Framework for Multi-Objective Learn-to-Defer Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unifying-post-processing-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although there are currently systems that follow this paradigm and are designed to optimize the accuracy of the final human-AI team, the general methodology for developing such systems under a set of constraints (e. g., algorithmic fairness, expert intervention budget, defer of anomaly, etc.)]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unifying-post-processing-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Calibration with Energy Based Instance-wise Scaling in the Wild Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-calibration-with-energy-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate robust post-hoc uncertainty calibration methods for DNNs within the context of multi-class classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-calibration-with-energy-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating 3D House Wireframes with Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-3d-house-wireframes-with-semantics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new approach for generating 3D house wireframes with semantic enrichment using an autoregressive model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-3d-house-wireframes-with-semantics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoME: Mixture of Multimodal Experts for Generalist Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mome-mixture-of-multimodal-experts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a mixture of multimodal experts (MoME) to mitigate task interference and obtain a generalist MLLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mome-mixture-of-multimodal-experts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Hybrid Attention Network for Specular Highlight Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-hybrid-attention-network-for-specular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specular highlight removal plays a pivotal role in multimedia applications, as it enhances the quality and interpretability of images and videos, ultimately improving the performance of downstream tasks such as content-based retrieval, object recognition, and scene understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-hybrid-attention-network-for-specular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy-Guided Diffusion Sampling for Offline-to-Online Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-guided-diffusion-sampling-for-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combining offline and online reinforcement learning (RL) techniques is indeed crucial for achieving efficient and safe learning where data acquisition is expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-guided-diffusion-sampling-for-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CerberusDet: Unified Multi-Task Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cerberusdet-unified-multi-task-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object detection is a core task in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cerberusdet-unified-multi-task-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EmoFace: Audio-driven Emotional 3D Face Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emoface-audio-driven-emotional-3d-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach can generate facial expressions with multiple emotions, and has the ability to generate random yet natural blinks and eye movements, while maintaining accurate lip synchronization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emoface-audio-driven-emotional-3d-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PersLLM: A Personified Training Approach for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persllm-a-personified-training-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models exhibit aspects of human-level intelligence that catalyze their application as human-like agents in domains such as social simulations, human-machine interactions, and collaborative multi-agent systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persllm-a-personified-training-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Robust Self-Supervised Learning Across Diverse Downstream Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-robust-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the purpose of a foundation model is to cater to multiple applications at once, our findings reveal the need to enhance encoder robustness more broadly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-robust-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstraction Alignment: Comparing Model and Human Conceptual Relationships</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstraction-alignment-comparing-model-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Abstraction -- the process of generalizing specific examples into broad reusable patterns -- is central to how people efficiently process and store information and apply their knowledge to new data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstraction-alignment-comparing-model-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphMuse: A Library for Symbolic Music Graph Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphmuse-a-library-for-symbolic-music-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing this gap, we present GraphMuse, a graph processing framework and library that facilitates efficient music graph processing and GNN training for symbolic music tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphmuse-a-library-for-symbolic-music-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LMMs-Eval: Reality Check on the Evaluation of Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmms-eval-reality-check-on-the-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To approach this evaluation trilemma, we further introduce LMMS-EVAL LITE, a pruned evaluation toolkit that emphasizes both coverage and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmms-eval-reality-check-on-the-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Frequency Matters: Uncertainty Guided Image Compression with Wavelet Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-frequency-matters-uncertainty-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a wavelet conditional diffusion model for high frequency prediction, followed by a residual codec that compresses and transmits prediction residuals to the decoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-frequency-matters-uncertainty-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reliable and Efficient Concept Erasure of Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliable-and-efficient-concept-erasure-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Reliable and Efficient Concept Erasure (RECE), a novel approach that modifies the model in 3 seconds without necessitating additional fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliable-and-efficient-concept-erasure-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of Length Text Recognition with Sub-String Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-length-text-recognition-with-sub</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we term this the Out of Length (OOL) text recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-length-text-recognition-with-sub</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Any Target Can be Offense: Adversarial Example Generation via Generalized Latent Infection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/any-target-can-be-offense-adversarial-example</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, compared with other generative methods, our method achieves an approximately $14. 13\%$ higher attack success rate for unknown classes and an approximately $4. 23\%$ higher success rate for known classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/any-target-can-be-offense-adversarial-example</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Wrist Abnormality Detection with YOLO: Analysis of State-of-the-art Single-stage Detection Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-wrist-abnormality-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diagnosing and treating abnormalities in the wrist, specifically distal radius, and ulna fractures, is a crucial concern among children, adolescents, and young adults, with a higher incidence rate during puberty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-wrist-abnormality-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLARE: Low Light Image Enhancement via Generative Latent Feature based Codebook Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glare-low-light-image-enhancement-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing Low-light Image Enhancement (LLIE) methods either directly map Low-Light (LL) to Normal-Light (NL) images or use semantic or illumination maps as guides.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glare-low-light-image-enhancement-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfoNorm: Mutual Information Shaping of Normals for Sparse-View Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infonorm-mutual-information-shaping-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D surface reconstruction from multi-view images is essential for scene understanding and interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infonorm-mutual-information-shaping-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Understanding Unsafe Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-understanding-unsafe-video-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the labeled information and the corresponding prompts, we created the first dataset of unsafe videos generated by VGMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-understanding-unsafe-video-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SG-NeRF: Neural Surface Reconstruction with Scene Graph Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sg-nerf-neural-surface-reconstruction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this challenge, we present a novel approach that optimizes radiance fields with scene graphs to mitigate the influence of outlier poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sg-nerf-neural-surface-reconstruction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch-Level Training for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-level-training-for-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As Large Language Models (LLMs) achieve remarkable progress in language understanding and generation, their training efficiency has become a critical concern.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-level-training-for-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMAGDressing-v1: Customizable Virtual Dressing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagdressing-v1-customizable-virtual-dressing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Latest advances have achieved realistic virtual try-on (VTON) through localized garment inpainting using latent diffusion models, significantly enhancing consumers' online shopping experience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagdressing-v1-customizable-virtual-dressing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E5-V: Universal Embeddings with Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e5-v-universal-embeddings-with-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a single modality training approach for E5-V, where the model is trained exclusively on text pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e5-v-universal-embeddings-with-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharif-STR at SemEval-2024 Task 1: Transformer as a Regression Model for Fine-Grained Scoring of Textual Semantic Relations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharif-str-at-semeval-2024-task-1-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study focuses on assessing the efficacy of this approach across different languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharif-str-at-semeval-2024-task-1-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Guided Generation of Minority Samples Using Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-guided-generation-of-minority-samples</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on benchmark real datasets demonstrate that our approach can greatly improve the capability of creating realistic low-likelihood minority instances over the existing techniques without the reliance on costly additional elements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-guided-generation-of-minority-samples</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Probably Looks Exactly Like That: An Invertible Prototypical Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/this-probably-looks-exactly-like-that-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We combine concept-based neural networks with generative, flow-based classifiers into a novel, intrinsically explainable, exactly invertible approach to supervised learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/this-probably-looks-exactly-like-that-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiteGPT: Large Vision-Language Model for Joint Chest X-ray Localization and Classification Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/litegpt-large-vision-language-model-for-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this is the first study to utilize vision-language models for the novel task of joint localization and classification in medical images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/litegpt-large-vision-language-model-for-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Calibration of Epistemic Uncertainty: Principles, Paradoxes and Conflictual Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-calibration-of-epistemic-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The calibration of predictive distributions has been widely studied in deep learning, but the same cannot be said about the more specific epistemic uncertainty as produced by Deep Ensembles, Bayesian Deep Networks, or Evidential Deep Networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-calibration-of-epistemic-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nowcasting R&amp;D Expenditures: A Machine Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nowcasting-r-d-expenditures-a-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we leverage the high frequency of our data to derive monthly estimates of R&D expenditures, which are currently unobserved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nowcasting-r-d-expenditures-a-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Pretext Task Learning for Human Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-pretext-task-learning-for-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the final stage, the model aims to address the entire future trajectory task by taking full advantage of the knowledge from previous stages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-pretext-task-learning-for-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNIT: Backdoor Mitigation via Automated Neural Distribution Tightening</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unit-backdoor-mitigation-via-automated-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While existing works have proposed various methods to mitigate backdoor effects in poisoned models, they tend to be less effective against recent advanced attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unit-backdoor-mitigation-via-automated-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask-Free Neuron Concept Annotation for Interpreting Neural Networks in Medical Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-free-neuron-concept-annotation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in deep neural networks have shown promise in aiding disease diagnosis and medical decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-free-neuron-concept-annotation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not Another Imputation Method: A Transformer-based Model for Missing Values in Tabular Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-another-imputation-method-a-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Handling missing values in tabular datasets presents a significant challenge in training and testing artificial intelligence models, an issue usually addressed using imputation techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-another-imputation-method-a-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Confidence Bounds for Classification with Imbalanced Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-confidence-bounds-for-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Class imbalance poses a significant challenge in classification tasks, where traditional approaches often lead to biased models and unreliable predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-confidence-bounds-for-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Split Computing and Early Exit Applications through Predefined Sparsity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-split-computing-and-early-exit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel approach to address this challenge by combining the concept of predefined sparsity with Split Computing (SC) and Early Exit (EE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-split-computing-and-early-exit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GV-Bench: Benchmarking Local Feature Matching for Geometric Verification of Long-term Loop Closure Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gv-bench-benchmarking-local-feature-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing feature matching methods focus on homography and pose estimation in long-term visual localization, lacking references for geometric verification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gv-bench-benchmarking-local-feature-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relation DETR: Exploring Explicit Position Relation Prior for Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relation-detr-exploring-explicit-position</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results on the dataset illustrate that the proposed explicit position relation achieves a clear improvement of 1. 3% AP, highlighting its potential towards universal object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relation-detr-exploring-explicit-position</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying the Theory on Over-Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-the-theory-on-over-smoothing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph convolutions have gained popularity due to their ability to efficiently operate on data with an irregular geometric structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-the-theory-on-over-smoothing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DreamCatalyst: Fast and High-Quality 3D Editing via Controlling Editability and Identity Preservation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamcatalyst-fast-and-high-quality-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing SDS-based 3D editing methods suffer from extensive training time and lead to low-quality results, primarily because these methods deviate from the sampling dynamics of diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamcatalyst-fast-and-high-quality-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDPT: Synchronous Dual Prompt Tuning for Fusion-based Visual-Language Pre-trained Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdpt-synchronous-dual-prompt-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing prompt tuning methods have not effectively addressed the modal mapping and aligning problem for tokens in different modalities, leading to poor transfer generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdpt-synchronous-dual-prompt-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
