<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 21:06:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Contextual Emotion Recognition Using Transformer Based Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-emotion-recognition-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to increase the precision of emotion identification in text, this research suggests a context-aware emotion recognition system employing transformer models, especially BERT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-emotion-recognition-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backdoor Defense with Non-Adversarial Backdoor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backdoor-defense-with-non-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNNs) are vulnerable to backdoor attack, which does not affect the network's performance on clean data but would manipulate the network behavior once a trigger pattern is added.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backdoor-defense-with-non-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is One Epoch All You Need For Multi-Fidelity Hyperparameter Optimization?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-one-epoch-all-you-need-for-multi-fidelity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperparameter optimization (HPO) is crucial for fine-tuning machine learning models but can be computationally expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-one-epoch-all-you-need-for-multi-fidelity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improvable Gap Balancing for Multi-Task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improvable-gap-balancing-for-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, following the loss balancing framework, we propose two novel improvable gap balancing (IGB) algorithms for MTL: one takes a simple heuristic, and the other (for the first time) deploys deep reinforcement learning for MTL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improvable-gap-balancing-for-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Practical Recipe for Federated Learning Under Statistical Heterogeneity Experimental Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-recipe-for-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many of the works use inconsistent experimental settings and there are no comprehensive studies on the effect of FL-specific experimental variables on the results and practical insights for a more comparable and consistent FL experimental setup.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-recipe-for-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum-noise-limited optical neural networks operating at a few quanta per activation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-noise-limited-optical-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We experimentally demonstrated MNIST classification with a test accuracy of 98% using an optical neural network with a hidden layer operating in the single-photon regime; the optical energy used to perform the classification corresponds to 0. 008 photons per multiply-accumulate (MAC) operation, which is equivalent to 0. 003 attojoules of optical energy per MAC.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-noise-limited-optical-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Instance Learning Framework with Masked Hard Instance Mining for Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-instance-learning-framework-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The whole slide image (WSI) classification is often formulated as a multiple instance learning (MIL) problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-instance-learning-framework-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From continuous-time formulations to discretization schemes: tensor trains and robust regression for BSDEs and parabolic PDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-continuous-time-formulations-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The numerical approximation of partial differential equations (PDEs) poses formidable challenges in high dimensions since classical grid-based methods suffer from the so-called curse of dimensionality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-continuous-time-formulations-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-attention Graph Pooling for Efficient Pairwise Graph Interaction Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-attention-graph-pooling-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have proven to be effective in processing and learning from graph-structured data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-attention-graph-pooling-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scale-aware Test-time Click Adaptation for Pulmonary Nodule and Mass Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-aware-test-time-click-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on both open-source and in-house datasets consistently demonstrate the effectiveness of the proposed method over some CNN and Transformer-based segmentation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-aware-test-time-click-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attentive Multimodal Fusion for Optical and Scene Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attentive-multimodal-fusion-for-optical-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an investigation into the estimation of optical and scene flow using RGBD information in scenarios where the RGB modality is affected by noise or captured in dark environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attentive-multimodal-fusion-for-optical-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OAFuser: Towards Omni-Aperture Fusion for Light Field Semantic Segmentation of Road Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oafuser-towards-omni-aperture-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To avoid feature loss during network propagation and simultaneously streamline the redundant information from the light field camera, we present a simple yet very effective Sub-Aperture Fusion Module (SAFM) to embed sub-aperture images into angular features without any additional memory cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oafuser-towards-omni-aperture-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Solution to Co-occurrence Bias: Attributes Disentanglement via Mutual Information Minimization for Pedestrian Attribute Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-solution-to-co-occurrence-bias-attributes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies on pedestrian attribute recognition progress with either explicit or implicit modeling of the co-occurrence among attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-solution-to-co-occurrence-bias-attributes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Offline Reinforcement Learning on Real-Robot Hardware</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-offline-reinforcement-learning-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To coordinate the efforts of the research community toward tackling this problem, we propose a benchmark including: i) a large collection of data for offline learning from a dexterous manipulation platform on two tasks, obtained with capable RL agents trained in simulation; ii) the option to execute learned policies on a real-world robotic system and a simulation for efficient debugging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-offline-reinforcement-learning-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUCID-GAN: Conditional Generative Models to Locate Unfairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lucid-gan-conditional-generative-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most group fairness notions detect unethical biases by computing statistical parity metrics on a model's output.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lucid-gan-conditional-generative-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ODTlearn: A Package for Learning Optimal Decision Trees for Prediction and Prescription</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odtlearn-a-package-for-learning-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ODTLearn is an open-source Python package that provides methods for learning optimal decision trees for high-stakes predictive and prescriptive tasks based on the mixed-integer optimization (MIO) framework proposed in Aghaei et al. (2019) and several of its extensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odtlearn-a-package-for-learning-optimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defocus Blur Synthesis and Deblurring via Interpolation and Extrapolation in Latent Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defocus-blur-synthesis-and-deblurring-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We train autoencoders with implicit and explicit regularization techniques to enforce linearity relations among the representations of different blur levels in the latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defocus-blur-synthesis-and-deblurring-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Distortion-free Watermarks for Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-distortion-free-watermarks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We generate watermarked text by mapping a sequence of random numbers -- which we compute using a randomized watermark key -- to a sample from the language model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-distortion-free-watermarks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recovering high-quality FODs from a reduced number of diffusion-weighted images using a model-driven deep learning architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recovering-high-quality-fods-from-a-reduced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a spherical deconvolution network, a model-driven deep learning FOD reconstruction architecture, that ensures intermediate and output FODs produced by the network are consistent with the input DWI signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recovering-high-quality-fods-from-a-reduced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shrink-Perturb Improves Architecture Mixing during Population Based Training for Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shrink-perturb-improves-architecture-mixing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show that simultaneously training and mixing neural networks is a promising way to conduct Neural Architecture Search (NAS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shrink-perturb-improves-architecture-mixing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaskExpert: Dynamically Assembling Multi-Task Representations with Memorial Mixture-of-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskexpert-dynamically-assembling-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, to establish long-range modeling of the task-specific representations from different layers of TaskExpert, we design a multi-task feature memory that updates at each layer and acts as an additional feature expert for dynamic task-specific feature decoding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskexpert-dynamically-assembling-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLIC++: Linear Complexity Multi-Reference Entropy Modeling for Learned Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlic-linear-complexity-multi-reference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, multi-reference entropy model has been proposed, which captures channel-wise, local spatial, and global spatial correlations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlic-linear-complexity-multi-reference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Road to Quality is Paved with Good Revisions: A Detailed Evaluation Methodology for Revision Policies in Incremental Sequence Labelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-road-to-quality-is-paved-with-good</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Incremental dialogue model components produce a sequence of output prefixes based on incoming input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-road-to-quality-is-paved-with-good</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is this model reliable for everyone? Testing for strong calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-this-model-reliable-for-everyone-testing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a well-calibrated risk prediction model, the average predicted probability is close to the true event rate for any given subgroup.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-this-model-reliable-for-everyone-testing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual Lexical Simplification via Paraphrase Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-lexical-simplification-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After feeding the input sentence into the encoder of paraphrase modeling, we generate the substitutes based on a novel decoding strategy that concentrates solely on the lexical variations of the complex word.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-lexical-simplification-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When to generate hedges in peer-tutoring interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-generate-hedges-in-peer-tutoring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the application of machine learning techniques to predict where hedging occurs in peer-tutoring interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-generate-hedges-in-peer-tutoring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Data Generation in Vision-and-Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-data-generation-in-vision-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research in language-guided visual navigation has demonstrated a significant demand for the diversity of traversable environments and the quantity of supervision for training generalizable agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-data-generation-in-vision-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Framework to Automatically Determine the Quality of Open Data Catalogs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/framework-to-automatically-determine-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data catalogs play a crucial role in modern data-driven organizations by facilitating the discovery, understanding, and utilization of diverse data assets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/framework-to-automatically-determine-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Nonlinear Projections for Reduced-Order Modeling of Dynamical Systems using Constrained Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-nonlinear-projections-for-reduced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To begin to address these issues, we introduce a parametric class of nonlinear projections described by constrained autoencoder neural networks in which both the manifold and the projection fibers are learned from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-nonlinear-projections-for-reduced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'What are you referring to?' Evaluating the Ability of Multi-Modal Dialogue Models to Process Clarificational Exchanges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-are-you-referring-to-evaluating-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Referential ambiguities arise in dialogue when a referring expression does not uniquely identify the intended referent for the addressee.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-are-you-referring-to-evaluating-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differential Evolution Algorithm based Hyper-Parameters Selection of Transformer Neural Network Model for Load Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-evolution-algorithm-based-hyper</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply several metaheuristics namely Differential Evolution to find the optimal hyperparameters of the Transformer-based Neural Network to produce accurate forecasts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-evolution-algorithm-based-hyper</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the Learning Behaviour of In-context Learning: A Comparison with Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-learning-behaviour-of-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown remarkable capacity for in-context learning (ICL), where learning a new task from just a few training examples is done without being explicitly pre-trained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-learning-behaviour-of-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speeding up Fourier Neural Operators via Mixed Precision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speeding-up-fourier-neural-operators-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we (i) profile memory and runtime for FNO with full and mixed-precision training, (ii) conduct a study on the numerical stability of mixed-precision training of FNO, and (iii) devise a training routine which substantially decreases training time and memory usage (up to 34%), with little or no reduction in accuracy, on the Navier-Stokes and Darcy flow equations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speeding-up-fourier-neural-operators-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widespread Flaws in Offline Evaluation of Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/widespread-flaws-in-offline-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even though offline evaluation is just an imperfect proxy of online performance -- due to the interactive nature of recommenders -- it will probably remain the primary way of evaluation in recommender systems research for the foreseeable future, since the proprietary nature of production recommenders prevents independent validation of A/B test setups and verification of online results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/widespread-flaws-in-offline-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal and Transferable Adversarial Attacks on Aligned Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-and-transferable-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our approach finds a suffix that, when attached to a wide range of queries for an LLM to produce objectionable content, aims to maximize the probability that the model produces an affirmative response (rather than refusing to answer).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-and-transferable-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Effect of Third Party Implementations on Reproducibility</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-third-party-implementations-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reproducibility of recommender systems research has come under scrutiny during recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-third-party-implementations-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiscale Dynamic Graph Representation for Biometric Recognition with Occlusions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiscale-dynamic-graph-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Occlusion is a common problem with biometric recognition in the wild.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiscale-dynamic-graph-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RCT Rejection Sampling for Causal Estimation Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rct-rejection-sampling-for-causal-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We contribute a new sampling algorithm, which we call RCT rejection sampling, and provide theoretical guarantees that causal identification holds in the observational data to allow for valid comparisons to the ground-truth RCT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rct-rejection-sampling-for-causal-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinker: Learning to Plan and Act</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thinker-learning-to-plan-and-act</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach eliminates the need for hand-crafted planning algorithms by enabling the agent to learn how to plan autonomously and allows for easy interpretation of the agent's plan with visualization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thinker-learning-to-plan-and-act</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BubbleML: A Multi-Physics Dataset and Benchmarks for Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bubbleml-a-multi-physics-dataset-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of phase change phenomena, the lack of accessible and diverse datasets suitable for machine learning (ML) training poses a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bubbleml-a-multi-physics-dataset-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clustering based Point Cloud Representation Learning for 3D Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clustering-based-point-cloud-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The mined patterns are, in turn, used to repaint the embedding space, so as to respect the underlying distribution of the entire training dataset and improve the robustness to the variations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clustering-based-point-cloud-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MESED: A Multi-modal Entity Set Expansion Dataset with Fine-grained Semantic Classes and Hard Negative Entities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesed-a-multi-modal-entity-set-expansion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Entity Set Expansion (ESE) task aims to expand a handful of seed entities with new entities belonging to the same semantic class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesed-a-multi-modal-entity-set-expansion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The RoboDepth Challenge: Methods and Advancements Towards Robust Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-robodepth-challenge-methods-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we summarize the winning solutions from the RoboDepth Challenge -- an academic competition designed to facilitate and advance robust OoD depth estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-robodepth-challenge-methods-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gzip versus bag-of-words for text classification with KNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gzip-versus-bag-of-words-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The effectiveness of compression distance in KNN-based text classification ('gzip') has recently garnered lots of attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gzip-versus-bag-of-words-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pCTFusion: Point Convolution-Transformer Fusion with Semantic Aware Loss for Outdoor LiDAR Point Cloud Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pctfusion-point-convolution-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The segmentation of point clouds is also essential for many applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pctfusion-point-convolution-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-based Polyphonic Multitrack Music Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-polyphonic-multitrack-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graphs can be leveraged to model polyphonic multitrack symbolic music, where notes, chords and entire sections may be linked at different levels of the musical hierarchy by tonal and rhythmic relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-polyphonic-multitrack-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Generative Models for Graph-to-Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-generative-models-for-graph-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have been widely employed for graph-to-text generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-generative-models-for-graph-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Explanations for Graph Classification Through the Lenses of Density</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanations-for-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterfactual examples have emerged as an effective approach to produce simple and understandable post-hoc explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanations-for-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Interaction Paradigm for Complex EDA Software Leveraging GPT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-interaction-paradigm-for-complex-eda</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the rapidly growing field of electronic design automation (EDA), professional software such as KiCad, Cadence , and Altium Designer provide increasingly extensive design functionalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-interaction-paradigm-for-complex-eda</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Adapt or Not to Adapt? Real-Time Adaptation for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-adapt-or-not-to-adapt-real-time-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of Online Domain Adaptation for semantic segmentation is to handle unforeseeable domain changes that occur during deployment, like sudden weather events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-adapt-or-not-to-adapt-real-time-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
