<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 21:09:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ZS-VCOS: Zero-Shot Outperforms Supervised Video Camouflaged Object Segmentation with Zero-Shot Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zs-vcos-zero-shot-outperforms-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method integrates optical flow, a vision-language model, and SAM 2 into a sequential pipeline, where the output of one component provides cues for the next.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zs-vcos-zero-shot-outperforms-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Models for Soil Parameter Prediction Based on Satellite, Weather, Clay and Yield Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-models-for-soil-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficient nutrient management and precise fertilization are essential for advancing modern agriculture, particularly in regions striving to optimize crop yields sustainably.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-models-for-soil-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixFunn: A Neural Network for Differential Equations with Improved Generalization and Interpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixfunn-a-neural-network-for-differential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce MixFunn, a novel neural network architecture designed to solve differential equations with enhanced precision, interpretability, and generalization capability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixfunn-a-neural-network-for-differential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STADE: Standard Deviation as a Pruning Metric</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stade-standard-deviation-as-a-pruning-metric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon Wanda's work, this study provides a theoretical explanation of why the method is effective and leverages these insights to enhance the pruning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stade-standard-deviation-as-a-pruning-metric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Low-Resource Retrieval Effectiveness using Zero-Shot Linguistic Similarity Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-low-resource-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that this approach improves the performance of the varieties upon which the models were directly trained, thereby regularising these models to generalise and perform better even on unseen language variety pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-low-resource-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preference-based Learning with Retrieval Augmented Generation for Conversational Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preference-based-learning-with-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational Question Answering (ConvQA) involves multiple subtasks, i) to understand incomplete questions in their context, ii) to retrieve relevant information, and iii) to generate answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preference-based-learning-with-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKDU at De-Factify 4.0: Natural Language Features for AI-Generated Text-Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skdu-at-de-factify-4-0-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of large language models (LLMs) has introduced new challenges in distinguishing human-written text from AI-generated content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skdu-at-de-factify-4-0-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPPO: Accelerating the Training of Group Relative Policy Optimization-Based Reasoning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cppo-accelerating-the-training-of-group</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces Completion Pruning Policy Optimization (CPPO) to accelerate the training of reasoning models based on Group Relative Policy Optimization (GRPO).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cppo-accelerating-the-training-of-group</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoSIL: Software Issue Localization via LLM-Driven Code Repository Graph Searching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosil-software-issue-localization-via-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CoSIL reduces the search space through module call graphs, iteratively searches the function call graph to obtain relevant contexts, and uses context pruning to control the search direction and manage contexts effectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosil-software-issue-localization-via-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaRank: Adaptive Rank Pruning for Enhanced Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adarank-adaptive-rank-pruning-for-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model merging has emerged as a promising approach for unifying independently fine-tuned models into an integrated framework, significantly enhancing computational efficiency in multi-task learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adarank-adaptive-rank-pruning-for-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historical Ink: Exploring Large Language Models for Irony Detection in 19th-Century Spanish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/historical-ink-exploring-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study explores the use of large language models (LLMs) to enhance datasets and improve irony detection in 19th-century Latin American newspapers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/historical-ink-exploring-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MO-CTranS: A unified multi-organ segmentation model learning from multiple heterogeneously labelled datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mo-ctrans-a-unified-multi-organ-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method was evaluated and compared to several baseline models and state-of-the-art (SOTA) solutions on abdominal MRI datasets that were acquired in different views (i. e. axial and coronal) and annotated for different organs (i. e. liver, kidney, spleen).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mo-ctrans-a-unified-multi-organ-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Q-Insight: Understanding Image Quality via Visual Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-insight-understanding-image-quality-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image quality assessment (IQA) focuses on the perceptual visual quality of images, playing a crucial role in downstream tasks such as image reconstruction, compression, and generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-insight-understanding-image-quality-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VITAL: More Understandable Feature Visualization through Distribution Alignment and Relevant Information Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vital-more-understandable-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Feature visualization (FV) is a powerful tool to decode what information neurons are responding to and hence to better understand the reasoning behind such networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vital-more-understandable-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Causal Framework to Measure and Mitigate Non-binary Treatment Discrimination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-causal-framework-to-measure-and-mitigate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fairness studies of algorithmic decision-making systems often simplify complex decision processes, such as bail or loan approvals, into binary classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-causal-framework-to-measure-and-mitigate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFiCS: Graph-Based Classification of Common Factors and Microcounseling Skills</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfics-graph-based-classification-of-common</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Common factors and microcounseling skills are critical to the effectiveness of psychotherapy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfics-graph-based-classification-of-common</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supposedly Equivalent Facts That Aren't? Entity Frequency in Pre-training Induces Asymmetry in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supposedly-equivalent-facts-that-aren-t</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we demonstrate that an asymmetry exists in the recognition of logically equivalent facts, which can be attributed to frequency discrepancies of entities appearing as subjects versus objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supposedly-equivalent-facts-that-aren-t</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spend Your Budget Wisely: Towards an Intelligent Distribution of the Privacy Budget in Differentially Private Text Rewriting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spend-your-budget-wisely-towards-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of $\textit{Differentially Private Text Rewriting}$ is a class of text privatization techniques in which (sensitive) input textual documents are $\textit{rewritten}$ under Differential Privacy (DP) guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spend-your-budget-wisely-towards-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Free Universal Attack by Exploiting the Intrinsic Vulnerability of Deep Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-free-universal-attack-by-exploiting-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this observation, we leverage the ill-conditioned nature of the linear components by aligning the UAP with the right singular vectors corresponding to the maximum singular value of each linear layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-free-universal-attack-by-exploiting-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Effectiveness of Multi-stage Fine-tuning for Cross-encoder Re-rankers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-effectiveness-of-multi-stage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art cross-encoders can be fine-tuned to be highly effective in passage re-ranking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-effectiveness-of-multi-stage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ActionStudio: A Lightweight Framework for Data and Training of Action Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actionstudio-a-lightweight-framework-for-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Action models are essential for enabling autonomous agents to perform complex tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actionstudio-a-lightweight-framework-for-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Stop at One Error? Benchmarking LLMs as Data Science Code Debuggers for Multi-Hop and Multi-Bug Errors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-stop-at-one-error-benchmarking-llms-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLMs are transforming software development, yet current code generation and code repair benchmarks mainly assess syntactic and functional correctness in simple, single-error cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-stop-at-one-error-benchmarking-llms-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EgoToM: Benchmarking Theory of Mind Reasoning from Egocentric Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egotom-benchmarking-theory-of-mind-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce EgoToM, a new video question-answering benchmark that extends Theory-of-Mind (ToM) evaluation to egocentric domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egotom-benchmarking-theory-of-mind-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using AI to Summarize US Presidential Campaign TV Advertisement Videos, 1952-2012</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-ai-to-summarize-us-presidential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the largest and most comprehensive dataset of US presidential campaign television advertisements, available in digital format.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-ai-to-summarize-us-presidential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landscape of Thoughts: Visualizing the Reasoning Process of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/landscape-of-thoughts-visualizing-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We showcase this advantage by adapting our tool to a lightweight verifier that evaluates the correctness of reasoning paths.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/landscape-of-thoughts-visualizing-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuzzy Cluster-Aware Contrastive Clustering for Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fuzzy-cluster-aware-contrastive-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose a fuzzy cluster-aware contrastive clustering framework (FCACC) that jointly optimizes representation learning and clustering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fuzzy-cluster-aware-contrastive-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unicorn: Text-Only Data Synthesis for Vision Language Model Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unicorn-text-only-data-synthesis-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By eliminating the dependency on real images while maintaining data quality and diversity, our framework offers a cost-effective and scalable solution for VLMs training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unicorn-text-only-data-synthesis-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIP: Towards Comprehensive and Reliable Evaluation of Federated Prompt Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flip-towards-comprehensive-and-reliable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing emphasis on privacy and data security has driven the adoption of federated learning, a decentralized approach to train machine learning models without sharing raw data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flip-towards-comprehensive-and-reliable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EndoLRMGS: Complete Endoscopic Scene Reconstruction combining Large Reconstruction Modelling and Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/endolrmgs-complete-endoscopic-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, EndoLRMGS improves the PSNR of the tools projection from 3. 82% to 11. 07%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/endolrmgs-complete-endoscopic-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Refined Analysis of Massive Activations in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-refined-analysis-of-massive-activations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated in part by their relevance for low-precision training and quantization, massive activations in large language models (LLMs) have recently emerged as a topic of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-refined-analysis-of-massive-activations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>consexpressionR: an R package for consensus differential gene expression analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consexpressionr-an-r-package-for-consensus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivation: Bulk RNA-Seq is a widely used method for studying gene expression across a variety of contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consexpressionr-an-r-package-for-consensus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGNA-VPR: A Novel Training Paradigm for Visual Place Recognition Based on Uncertainty-Guided NeRF Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ugna-vpr-a-novel-training-paradigm-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel training paradigm to improve the performance of existing VPR networks by enhancing multi-view diversity within current datasets through uncertainty estimation and NeRF-based data augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ugna-vpr-a-novel-training-paradigm-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaMHF: Adaptive Multimodal Hierarchical Fusion for Survival Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adamhf-adaptive-multimodal-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we introduce a survival prediction benchmark designed to resolve scenarios with missing modalities, mirroring real-world clinical conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adamhf-adaptive-multimodal-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Language Models versus Machine Learning Models Performance on Polyp Detection and Classification in Colonoscopy Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-language-models-versus-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Introduction: This study provides a comprehensive performance assessment of vision-language models (VLMs) against established convolutional neural networks (CNNs) and classic machine learning models (CMLs) for computer-aided detection (CADe) and computer-aided diagnosis (CADx) of colonoscopy polyp images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-language-models-versus-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOTPLACE: Bootstrapped Object Placement with Detection Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bootplace-bootstrapped-object-placement-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we tackle the copy-paste image-to-image composition problem with a focus on object placement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bootplace-bootstrapped-object-placement-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OntoAligner: A Comprehensive Modular and Robust Python Toolkit for Ontology Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontoaligner-a-comprehensive-modular-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ontology Alignment (OA) is fundamental for achieving semantic interoperability across diverse knowledge systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontoaligner-a-comprehensive-modular-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Agnostic Robotic Long-Horizon Manipulation with Vision-Language-Guided Closed-Loop Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-agnostic-robotic-long-horizon</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in language-conditioned robotic manipulation have leveraged imitation and reinforcement learning to enable robots to execute tasks from human commands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-agnostic-robotic-long-horizon</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pretrained Bayesian Non-parametric Knowledge Prior in Robotic Long-Horizon Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pretrained-bayesian-non-parametric-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement learning (RL) methods typically learn new tasks from scratch, often disregarding prior knowledge that could accelerate the learning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pretrained-bayesian-non-parametric-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embodied-Reasoner: Synergizing Visual Search, Reasoning, and Action for Embodied Interactive Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embodied-reasoner-synergizing-visual-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in deep thinking models have demonstrated remarkable reasoning capabilities on mathematical and coding tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embodied-reasoner-synergizing-visual-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RapidPoseTriangulation: Multi-view Multi-person Whole-body Human Pose Triangulation in a Millisecond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapidposetriangulation-multi-view-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The integration of multi-view imaging and pose estimation represents a significant advance in computer vision applications, offering new possibilities for understanding human movement and interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapidposetriangulation-multi-view-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VBench-2.0: Advancing Video Generation Benchmark Suite for Intrinsic Faithfulness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vbench-2-0-advancing-video-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce VBench-2. 0, a next-generation benchmark designed to automatically evaluate video generative models for their intrinsic faithfulness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vbench-2-0-advancing-video-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model Agent: A Survey on Methodology, Applications and Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-agent-a-survey-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The era of intelligent agents is upon us, driven by revolutionary advancements in large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-agent-a-survey-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Large Multimodal Models as Open-World Image Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-large-multimodal-models-as-open-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite this remarkable capability, most existing studies on LMM classification performance are surprisingly limited in scope, often assuming a closed-world setting with a predefined set of categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-large-multimodal-models-as-open-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tune It Up: Music Genre Transfer and Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tune-it-up-music-genre-transfer-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we adapt and improve CycleGAN model to perform music style transfer on Jazz and Classic genres.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tune-it-up-music-genre-transfer-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenHuEval: Evaluating Large Language Model on Hungarian Specifics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openhueval-evaluating-large-language-model-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce OpenHuEval, the first benchmark for LLMs focusing on the Hungarian language and specifics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openhueval-evaluating-large-language-model-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reward Design for Reinforcement Learning Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reward-design-for-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we build on this teacher-driven approach by introducing a novel method for adaptive interpretable reward design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reward-design-for-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barrier-Free Microhabitats: Self-Organized Seclusion in Microbial Communities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/barrier-free-microhabitats-self-organized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bacteria frequently colonize natural microcavities such as gut crypts, plant apoplasts, and soil pores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/barrier-free-microhabitats-self-organized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Task Learning for Dead Tree Detection and Segmentation with Hybrid Self-Attention U-Nets in Aerial Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-task-learning-for-dead-tree-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mapping standing dead trees is critical for assessing forest health, monitoring biodiversity, and mitigating wildfire risks, for which aerial imagery has proven useful.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-task-learning-for-dead-tree-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As easy as PIE: understanding when pruning causes language models to disagree</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/as-easy-as-pie-understanding-when-pruning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, when looking at how individual data points are affected by pruning, it turns out that a particular subset of data points always bears most of the brunt (in terms of reduced accuracy) when pruning, but this effect goes unnoticed when reporting the mean accuracy of all data points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/as-easy-as-pie-understanding-when-pruning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyUAT: Open-source Python framework for efficient and scalable cell tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyuat-open-source-python-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tracking individual cells in live-cell imaging provides fundamental insights, inevitable for studying causes and consequences of phenotypic heterogeneity, responses to changing environmental conditions or stressors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyuat-open-source-python-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
