<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 09:16:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MLGWSC-1: The first Machine Learning Gravitational-Wave Search Mock Data Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlgwsc-1-the-first-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The final of the 4 provided datasets contained real noise from the O3a observing run and signals up to a duration of 20 seconds with the inclusion of precession effects and higher order modes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlgwsc-1-the-first-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homophone Reveals the Truth: A Reality Check for Speech2Vec</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/homophone-reveals-the-truth-a-reality-check</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is no indication that these embeddings are generated by the Speech2Vec model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/homophone-reveals-the-truth-a-reality-check</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NamedMask: Distilling Segmenters from Complementary Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/namedmask-distilling-segmenters-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method, termed NamedMask, begins by using CLIP to construct category-specific archives of images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/namedmask-distilling-segmenters-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMGAN: Conformer-Based Metric-GAN for Monaural Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmgan-conformer-based-metric-gan-for-monaural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convolution-augmented transformers (Conformers) are recently proposed in various speech-domain applications, such as automatic speech recognition (ASR) and speech separation, as they can capture both local and global dependencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmgan-conformer-based-metric-gan-for-monaural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Lake: a Lakehouse for Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-lake-a-lakehouse-for-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional data lakes provide critical data infrastructure for analytical workloads by enabling time travel, running SQL queries, ingesting data with ACID transactions, and visualizing petabyte-scale datasets on cloud storage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-lake-a-lakehouse-for-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIG: Draping Implicit Garment over the Human Body</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dig-draping-implicit-garment-over-the-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing data-driven methods for draping garments over posed human bodies, despite being effective, cannot handle garments of arbitrary topology and are typically not end-to-end differentiable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dig-draping-implicit-garment-over-the-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EventNet: Detecting Events in EEG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eventnet-detecting-events-in-eeg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an end-to-end event detection approach (EventNet), based on deep learning, that directly works with events as learning targets, stepping away from ad-hoc postprocessing schemes to turn model outputs into events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eventnet-detecting-events-in-eeg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCALES: From Fairness Principles to Constrained Decision-Making</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scales-from-fairness-principles-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes SCALES, a general framework that translates well-established fairness principles into a common representation based on the Constraint Markov Decision Process (CMDP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scales-from-fairness-principles-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poisson Flow Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poisson-flow-generative-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We interpret the data points as electrical charges on the $z=0$ hyperplane in a space augmented with an additional dimension $z$, generating a high-dimensional electric field (the gradient of the solution to Poisson equation).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poisson-flow-generative-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Transduction through Invariant Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-transduction-through-invariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to generalize compositionally is key to understanding the potentially infinite number of sentences that can be constructed in a human language from only a finite number of words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-transduction-through-invariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look at Learned Optimization: Stability, Robustness, and Inductive Biases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-learned-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply the resulting learned optimizer to a variety of neural network training tasks, where it outperforms the current state of the art learned optimizer -- at matched optimizer computational overhead -- with regard to optimization performance and meta-training speed, and is capable of generalization to tasks far different from those it was meta-trained on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-learned-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation-based inference of Bayesian hierarchical models while checking for model misspecification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-based-inference-of-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents recent methodological advances to perform simulation-based inference (SBI) of a general class of Bayesian hierarchical models (BHMs), while checking for model misspecification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-based-inference-of-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Bibliographic View on Constrained Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bibliographic-view-on-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A keyword search on constrained clustering on Web-of-Science returned just under 3, 000 documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bibliographic-view-on-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Challenges in Visual Anomaly Detection for Mobile Robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenges-in-visual-anomaly-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the task of detecting anomalies for autonomous mobile robots based on vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenges-in-visual-anomaly-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Differential Privacy, There is Truth: On Vote Leakage in Ensemble Private Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-differential-privacy-there-is-truth-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When learning from sensitive data, care must be taken to ensure that training algorithms address privacy concerns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-differential-privacy-there-is-truth-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Few-Shot Learning Without Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-few-shot-learning-without-prompts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This simple framework requires no prompts or verbalizers, and achieves high accuracy with orders of magnitude less parameters than existing techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-few-shot-learning-without-prompts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity-Aware Hand Mesh Estimation and Personalization from RGB Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identity-aware-hand-mesh-estimation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an identity-aware hand mesh estimation model, which can incorporate the identity information represented by the intrinsic shape parameters of the subject.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identity-aware-hand-mesh-estimation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MnTTS: An Open-Source Mongolian Text-to-Speech Synthesis Dataset and Accompanied Baseline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mntts-an-open-source-mongolian-text-to-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a high-quality open-source text-to-speech (TTS) synthesis dataset for Mongolian, a low-resource language spoken by over 10 million people worldwide.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mntts-an-open-source-mongolian-text-to-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMRI Loss: Improving Recall of a Specific Class without Sacrificing Accuracy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camri-loss-improving-recall-of-a-specific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose a loss function that can improve the separation of the important class by setting the margin only for the important class, called Class-sensitive Additive Angular Margin Loss (CAMRI Loss).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camri-loss-improving-recall-of-a-specific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concept Activation Regions: A Generalized Framework For Concept-Based Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-activation-regions-a-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further demonstrate empirically that CARs offer (1) more accurate descriptions of how concepts are scattered in the DNN's latent space; (2) global explanations that are closer to human concept annotations and (3) concept-based feature importance that meaningfully relate concepts with each other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-activation-regions-a-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layer Freezing &amp; Data Sieving: Missing Pieces of a Generic Framework for Sparse Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layer-freezing-data-sieving-missing-pieces-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we analyze the feasibility and potentiality of using the layer freezing technique in sparse training and find it has the potential to save considerable training costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layer-freezing-data-sieving-missing-pieces-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pretraining the Vision Transformer using self-supervised methods for vision based Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pretraining-the-vision-transformer-using-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Vision Transformer architecture has shown to be competitive in the computer vision (CV) space where it has dethroned convolution-based networks in several benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pretraining-the-vision-transformer-using-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AcroFOD: An Adaptive Method for Cross-domain Few-shot Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acrofod-an-adaptive-method-for-cross-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under the domain shift, cross-domain few-shot object detection aims to adapt object detectors in the target domain with a few annotated target data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acrofod-an-adaptive-method-for-cross-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting pairwise preferences between TTS audio stimuli using parallel ratings data and anti-symmetric twin neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-pairwise-preferences-between-tts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While previous work has focused on predicting listeners' ratings (mean opinion scores) of individual stimuli, we focus on the simpler task of predicting subjective preference given two speech stimuli for the same text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-pairwise-preferences-between-tts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VToonify: Controllable High-Resolution Portrait Video Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vtoonify-controllable-high-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although a series of successful portrait image toonification models built upon the powerful StyleGAN have been proposed, these image-oriented methods have obvious limitations when applied to videos, such as the fixed frame size, the requirement of face alignment, missing non-facial details and temporal inconsistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vtoonify-controllable-high-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Explanations Using Optimization With Constraint Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanations-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterfactual explanations embody one of the many interpretability techniques that receive increasing attention from the machine learning community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanations-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated head and neck tumor segmentation from 3D PET/CT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-head-and-neck-tumor-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Head and neck tumor segmentation challenge (HECKTOR) 2022 offers a platform for researchers to compare their solutions to segmentation of tumors and lymph nodes from 3D CT and PET images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-head-and-neck-tumor-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptation of domain-specific transformer models with text oversampling for sentiment analysis of social media posts on Covid-19 vaccines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptation-of-domain-specific-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Covid-19 has spread across the world and several vaccines have been developed to counter its surge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptation-of-domain-specific-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entropic Descent Archetypal Analysis for Blind Hyperspectral Unmixing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropic-descent-archetypal-analysis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a new algorithm based on archetypal analysis for blind hyperspectral unmixing, assuming linear mixing of endmembers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropic-descent-archetypal-analysis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGTR: End-to-End Mutual Gaze Detection with Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgtr-end-to-end-mutual-gaze-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[People's looking at each other or mutual gaze is ubiquitous in our daily interactions, and detecting mutual gaze is of great significance for understanding human social scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgtr-end-to-end-mutual-gaze-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantically Consistent Data Augmentation for Neural Machine Translation via Conditional Masked Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantically-consistent-data-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, to enhance diversity, we incorporate the idea of soft word substitution for data augmentation which replaces a word with a probabilistic distribution over the vocabulary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantically-consistent-data-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MonoByte: A Pool of Monolingual Byte-level Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monobyte-a-pool-of-monolingual-byte-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The zero-shot cross-lingual ability of models pretrained on multilingual and even monolingual corpora has spurred many hypotheses to explain this intriguing empirical result.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monobyte-a-pool-of-monolingual-byte-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Information Minimization Based Contrastive Learning Model for Unsupervised Sentence Embeddings Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-information-minimization-based-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we present an information minimization based contrastive learning (InforMin-CL) model to retain the useful information and discard the redundant information by maximizing the mutual information and minimizing the information entropy between positive instances meanwhile for unsupervised sentence representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-information-minimization-based-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifiability and generalizability from multiple experts in Inverse Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifiability-and-generalizability-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Reinforcement Learning (RL) aims to train an agent from a reward function in a given environment, Inverse Reinforcement Learning (IRL) seeks to recover the reward function from observing an expert's behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifiability-and-generalizability-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Response Recovery Using Ambient Synchrophasor Data: A Synthetic Texas Interconnection Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-response-recovery-using-ambient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wide-area dynamic studies are of paramount importance to ensure the stability and reliability of power grids.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-response-recovery-using-ambient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proximal Point Imitation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proximal-point-imitation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to PPM, we avoid nested policy evaluation and cost updates for online IL appearing in the prior literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proximal-point-imitation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing and Experimenting with Diffusion Models for Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implementing-and-experimenting-with-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this thesis, we aim to contribute by firstly reviewing the different approaches and techniques used by these models, and then by proposing our own implementation of a text-to-image model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implementing-and-experimenting-with-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DLUNet: Semi-supervised Learning based Dual-Light UNet for Multi-organ Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dlunet-semi-supervised-learning-based-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the training phase, it consists of two light UNets, which make full use of label and unlabeled data simultaneously by using consistent-based learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dlunet-semi-supervised-learning-based-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Inference for Infinitely Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-inference-for-infinitely-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the unbounded depth neural network (UDN), an infinitely deep probabilistic model that adapts its complexity to the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-inference-for-infinitely-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LCRL: Certified Policy Synthesis via Logically-Constrained Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lcrl-certified-policy-synthesis-via-logically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LCRL is a software tool that implements model-free Reinforcement Learning (RL) algorithms over unknown Markov Decision Processes (MDPs), synthesising policies that satisfy a given linear temporal specification with maximal probability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lcrl-certified-policy-synthesis-via-logically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tree Methods for Hierarchical Classification in Parallel</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-methods-for-hierarchical-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose methods that enable efficient hierarchical classification in parallel.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-methods-for-hierarchical-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEVStereo: Enhancing Depth Estimation in Multi-view 3D Object Detection with Dynamic Temporal Stereo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bevstereo-enhancing-depth-estimation-in-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce an effective temporal stereo method to dynamically select the scale of matching candidates, enable to significantly reduce computation overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bevstereo-enhancing-depth-estimation-in-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaotic Hedging with Iterated Integrals and Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chaotic-hedging-with-iterated-integrals-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we extend the Wiener-Ito chaos decomposition to the class of diffusion processes, whose drift and diffusion coefficient are of linear growth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chaotic-hedging-with-iterated-integrals-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Speech Recognition via Large-Scale Weak Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-speech-recognition-via-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the capabilities of speech processing systems trained simply to predict large amounts of transcripts of audio on the internet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-speech-recognition-via-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Periodic Extrapolative Generalisation in Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/periodic-extrapolative-generalisation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The learning of the simplest possible computational pattern -- periodicity -- is an open problem in the research of strong generalisation in neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/periodic-extrapolative-generalisation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incremental Updates of Generalized Hypertree Decompositions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incremental-updates-of-generalized-hypertree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As decompositions can be reused to solve CSPs with the same constraint scopes, investing resources in computing good decompositions is beneficial, even though the computation itself is hard.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incremental-updates-of-generalized-hypertree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimation of circular statistics in the presence of measurement bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimation-of-circular-statistics-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The objective of this paper is to present a method to estimate circular statistics and their statistical significance even in this circumstance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimation-of-circular-statistics-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepVARwT: Deep Learning for a VAR Model with Trend</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepvarwt-deep-learning-for-a-var-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is a model for stationary time series which can be extended to allow the presence of a deterministic trend in each series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepvarwt-deep-learning-for-a-var-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Image Processing approach to identify solar plages observed at 393.37 nm by Kodaikanal Solar Observatory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-image-processing-approach-to-identify</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Solar Plages are bright chromospheric features observed in Ca II K photographic observations of the sun.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-image-processing-approach-to-identify</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Bayesian Kernel Inference for 3D Semantic Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-bayesian-kernel-inference-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robotic perception is currently at a cross-roads between modern methods which operate in an efficient latent space, and classical methods which are mathematically founded and provide interpretable, trustworthy results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-bayesian-kernel-inference-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
