<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 09:15:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ReactEmbed: A Cross-Domain Framework for Protein-Molecule Representation Learning via Biochemical Reaction Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reactembed-a-cross-domain-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The challenge in computational biology and drug discovery lies in creating comprehensive representations of proteins and molecules that capture their intrinsic properties and interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reactembed-a-cross-domain-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panacea: Mitigating Harmful Fine-tuning for Large Language Models via Post-fine-tuning Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panacea-mitigating-harmful-fine-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mainstream defenses aim to vaccinate the model such that the later harmful fine-tuning attack is less effective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panacea-mitigating-harmful-fine-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Private Steering for Large Language Model Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-steering-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also develop the first Membership Inference Attack (MIA) for evaluating and auditing the empirical privacy for the problem of LLM steering via activation editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-steering-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs can see and hear without any training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-can-see-and-hear-without-any-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present MILS: Multimodal Iterative LLM Solver, a surprisingly simple, training-free approach, to imbue multimodal capabilities into your favorite LLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-can-see-and-hear-without-any-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Neural Theorem Proving via Fine-grained Proof Structure Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-neural-theorem-proving-via-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The superiority of our method is validated on the miniF2F-test benchmark using the open-source deepseek-math-7b-base model and the Isabelle proof assistant.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-neural-theorem-proving-via-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDformer: Going Beyond Subsequence Isolation for Multivariate Time Series Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gdformer-going-beyond-subsequence-isolation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised anomaly detection of multivariate time series is a challenging task, given the requirements of deriving a compact detection criterion without accessing the anomaly points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gdformer-going-beyond-subsequence-isolation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Transformer for High Resolution Image Motion Deblurring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-transformer-for-high-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also provide detailed ablation studies analyzing the impact of our modifications on model behavior and performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-transformer-for-high-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free-T2M: Frequency Enhanced Text-to-Motion Diffusion Model With Consistency Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-t2m-frequency-enhanced-text-to-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rapid progress in text-to-motion generation has been largely driven by diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-t2m-frequency-enhanced-text-to-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepFRC: An End-to-End Deep Learning Model for Functional Registration and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepfrc-an-end-to-end-deep-learning-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Functional data analysis (FDA) is essential for analyzing continuous, high-dimensional data, yet existing methods often decouple functional registration and classification, limiting their efficiency and performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepfrc-an-end-to-end-deep-learning-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmark and Evaluation for Real-World Out-of-Distribution Detection Using Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-and-evaluation-for-real-world-out</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments reveal that recent CLIP-based OOD detection methods struggle to varying degrees across the three proposed benchmarks, and none of them consistently outperforms the others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-and-evaluation-for-real-world-out</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILDCHAT-50M: A Deep Dive Into the Role of Synthetic Data in Post-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wildchat-50m-a-deep-dive-into-the-role-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language model (LLM) post-training, from DPO to distillation, can refine behaviors and unlock new skills, but the open science supporting these post-training techniques is still in its infancy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wildchat-50m-a-deep-dive-into-the-role-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advances in Multimodal Adaptation and Generalization: From Traditional Approaches to Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-multimodal-adaptation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, the recent advent of large-scale pre-trained multimodal foundation models, such as CLIP, has inspired works leveraging these models to enhance adaptation and generalization performances or adapting them to downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-multimodal-adaptation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the Gap Between Synthetic and Ground Truth Time Series Distributions via Neural Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-gap-between-synthetic-and-ground</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Neural Mapper for Vector Quantized Time Series Generator (NM-VQTSG), a novel method aimed at addressing fidelity challenges in vector quantized (VQ) time series generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-gap-between-synthetic-and-ground</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Code Generation to Solve Open Instances of Combinatorial Design Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-code-generation-to-solve-open-instances</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Handbook of Combinatorial Designs catalogs many types of combinatorial designs, together with lists of open instances for which existence has not yet been determined.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-code-generation-to-solve-open-instances</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>acoupi: An Open-Source Python Framework for Deploying Bioacoustic AI Models on Edge Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acoupi-an-open-source-python-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By modularising key elements of the bioacoustic monitoring workflow, acoupi allows users to easily customise, extend, or select specific components to fit their unique monitoring needs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acoupi-an-open-source-python-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Beyond the Surface: How Far Can Continual Pre-Training with LoRA Enhance LLMs' Domain-Specific Insight Learning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-beyond-the-surface-how-far-can</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable performance on various tasks, yet their ability to extract and internalize deeper insights from domain-specific datasets remains underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-beyond-the-surface-how-far-can</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMP in the Odyssey: Provably Robust Reinforcement Learning with Certified Radius Maximization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camp-in-the-odyssey-provably-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the results, \texttt{CAMP} can achieve up to twice the certified expected return compared to that of baselines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camp-in-the-odyssey-provably-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiChallenge: A Realistic Multi-Turn Conversation Evaluation Benchmark Challenging to Frontier LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multichallenge-a-realistic-multi-turn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present MultiChallenge, a pioneering benchmark evaluating large language models (LLMs) on conducting multi-turn conversations with human users, a crucial yet underexamined capability for their applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multichallenge-a-realistic-multi-turn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Scene Adaptation for Vision-and-Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-scene-adaptation-for-vision-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the proposed task, one has to address two challenges in existing VLN datasets: the lack of OOD data, and the limited number and style diversity of instructions for each scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-scene-adaptation-for-vision-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reqo: A Robust and Explainable Query Optimization Cost Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reqo-a-robust-and-explainable-query</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating these innovations, we propose a cost model for a Robust and Explainable Query Optimizer, Reqo, that improves the accuracy, robustness, and explainability of cost estimation, outperforming state-of-the-art approaches in all three dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reqo-a-robust-and-explainable-query</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICoTA: Red-teaming of In-the-wild Conversation with Test Attempts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ricota-red-teaming-of-in-the-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With these prompts, we aim to evaluate LLMs' ability to identify the type of conversation and users' testing purposes to derive chatbot design implications for mitigating jailbreaking risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ricota-red-teaming-of-in-the-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Invariance Self-training for Reliable Semi-supervised Surgical Phase Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-invariance-self-training-for-reliable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate surgical phase recognition is crucial for advancing computer-assisted interventions, yet the scarcity of labeled data hinders training reliable deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-invariance-self-training-for-reliable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus: Harmful Fine-tuning Attack for Large Language Models Bypassing Guardrail Moderation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virus-harmful-fine-tuning-attack-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By designing a new red-teaming method, we in this paper show that purely relying on the moderation guardrail for data filtration is not reliable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virus-harmful-fine-tuning-attack-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Geometric Perspective for High-Dimensional Multiplex Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-geometric-perspective-for-high-dimensional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the node representations reside on highly curved manifolds, thus rendering their exploitation more challenging for downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-geometric-perspective-for-high-dimensional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Optimal Stopping for Early Classification within Finite Horizons via Sequential Probability Ratio Test</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-optimal-stopping-for-early</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We thus introduce FIRMBOUND, an SPRT-based framework that efficiently estimates the solution to backward induction from training data, bridging the gap between optimal stopping theory and real-world deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-optimal-stopping-for-early</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransRAD: Retentive Vision Transformer for Enhanced Radar Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transrad-retentive-vision-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant advancements in environment perception capabilities for autonomous driving and intelligent robotics, cameras and LiDARs remain notoriously unreliable in low-light conditions and adverse weather, which limits their effectiveness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transrad-retentive-vision-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yin-Yang: Developing Motifs With Long-Term Structure And Controllability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yin-yang-developing-motifs-with-long-term</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose Yin-Yang, a framework consisting of a phrase generator, phrase refiner, and phrase selector models for the development of motifs into melodies with long-term structure and controllability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yin-yang-developing-motifs-with-long-term</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PulmoFusion: Advancing Pulmonary Health with Efficient Multi-Modal Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pulmofusion-advancing-pulmonary-health-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel, non-invasive approach using multimodal predictive models that integrate RGB or thermal video data with patient metadata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pulmofusion-advancing-pulmonary-health-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Janus-Pro: Unified Multimodal Understanding and Generation with Data and Model Scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/janus-pro-unified-multimodal-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Janus-Pro, an advanced version of the previous work Janus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/janus-pro-unified-multimodal-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Your Model Ranking on Chatbot Arena by Vote Rigging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-your-model-ranking-on-chatbot-arena</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first introduce a straightforward target-only rigging strategy that focuses on new battles involving $m_{t}$, identifying it via watermarking or a binary classifier, and exclusively voting for $m_{t}$ wins.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-your-model-ranking-on-chatbot-arena</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Multimodal LLM for Inspirational User Interface Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-multimodal-llm-for-inspirational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspirational search, the process of exploring designs to inform and inspire new creative work, is pivotal in mobile user interface (UI) design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-multimodal-llm-for-inspirational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Action Recognition Using Temporal Shift Module and Ensemble Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/action-recognition-using-temporal-shift</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The competition aimed to recognize human actions using a diverse dataset of 20 action classes, collected from multi-modal sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/action-recognition-using-temporal-shift</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning With Individualized Privacy Through Client Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-with-individualized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on this idea, we propose an adapted method for enabling Individualized Differential Privacy (IDP) in Federated Learning (FL) by handling clients according to their personal privacy preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-with-individualized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When less is more: evolving large neural networks from small ones</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-less-is-more-evolving-large-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to conventional artificial neural networks, which are large and structurally static, we study feed-forward neural networks that are small and dynamic, whose nodes can be added (or subtracted) during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-less-is-more-evolving-large-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFPE: A Diverse Fingerprint Ensemble for Enhancing LLM Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfpe-a-diverse-fingerprint-ensemble-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have shown remarkable capabilities across various natural language processing tasks but often struggle to excel uniformly in diverse or complex domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfpe-a-diverse-fingerprint-ensemble-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Making Flowchart Images Machine Interpretable</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-making-flowchart-images-machine-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computer programming textbooks and software documentations often contain flowcharts to illustrate the flow of an algorithm or procedure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-making-flowchart-images-machine-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Conversational XAI All You Need? Human-AI Decision Making With a Conversational XAI Assistant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-conversational-xai-all-you-need-human-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In comparison to an XAI dashboard, we found that the conversational XAI interface can bring about a better understanding of the AI system among users and higher user trust.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-conversational-xai-all-you-need-human-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Quantification and Decomposition for LLM-based Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-and-decomposition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the widespread adoption of large language models (LLMs) for recommendation, we demonstrate that LLMs often exhibit uncertainty in their recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-and-decomposition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting harassment and defamation in cyberbullying with emotion-adaptive training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-harassment-and-defamation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[EAT consistently improves the average macro F1, precision and recall by 20% in cyberbullying detection tasks across nine transformer-based models under low-resource settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-harassment-and-defamation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Natural Language to Extensive-Form Game Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-natural-language-to-extensive-form-game</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With this information, the second stage leverages in-context learning alongside a self-debugging module to produce a complete extensive-form game tree represented using pygambit, the Python API of a recognized game-theoretic analysis tool called Gambit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-natural-language-to-extensive-form-game</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scanning Trojaned Models Using Out-of-Distribution Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scanning-trojaned-models-using-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TRODO leverages the concept of "blind spots"--regions where trojaned classifiers erroneously identify out-of-distribution (OOD) samples as in-distribution (ID).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scanning-trojaned-models-using-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exponential Family Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exponential-family-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The self-attention mechanism is the backbone of the transformer neural network underlying most large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exponential-family-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A General Bayesian Framework for Informative Input Design in System Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-bayesian-framework-for-informative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We tackle the problem of informative input design for system identification, where we select inputs, observe the corresponding outputs from the true system, and optimize the parameters of our model to best fit the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-bayesian-framework-for-informative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Rollouts in Model-Based Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-rollouts-in-model-based-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model-based reinforcement learning (MBRL) seeks to enhance data efficiency by learning a model of the environment and generating synthetic rollouts from it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-rollouts-in-model-based-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Transformers Learn Full Bayesian Inference in Context?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-transformers-learn-full-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have emerged as the dominant architecture in the field of deep learning, with a broad range of applications and remarkable in-context learning (ICL) capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-transformers-learn-full-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Phenology Modeling for Predicting Temperature Effects on Tree Dormancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-phenology-modeling-for-predicting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Biophysical models offer valuable insights into climate-phenology relationships in both natural and agricultural settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-phenology-modeling-for-predicting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outlier Synthesis via Hamiltonian Monte Carlo for Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-synthesis-via-hamiltonian-monte-carlo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Hamiltonian Monte Carlo with sampling acceptance rate almost close to 1 also makes our framework enjoy great efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-synthesis-via-hamiltonian-monte-carlo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JRE-L: Journalist, Reader, and Editor LLMs in the Loop for Science Journalism for the General Audience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jre-l-journalist-reader-and-editor-llms-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Science journalism reports current scientific discoveries to non-specialists, aiming to enable public comprehension of the state of the art.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jre-l-journalist-reader-and-editor-llms-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DBSCAN in domains with periodic boundary conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dbscan-in-domains-with-periodic-boundary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many scientific problems involve data that is embedded in a space with periodic boundary conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dbscan-in-domains-with-periodic-boundary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HateBench: Benchmarking Hate Speech Detectors on LLM-Generated Content and Hate Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hatebench-benchmarking-hate-speech-detectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose HateBench, a framework for benchmarking hate speech detectors on LLM-generated hate speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hatebench-benchmarking-hate-speech-detectors</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
