<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 09:12:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>GreenEyes: An Air Quality Evaluating Model based on WaveNet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/greeneyes-an-air-quality-evaluating-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accompanying rapid industrialization, humans are suffering from serious air pollution problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/greeneyes-an-air-quality-evaluating-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executing your Commands via Motion Diffusion in Latent Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/executing-your-commands-via-motion-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study a challenging task, conditional human motion generation, which produces plausible human motion sequences according to various conditional inputs, such as action classes or textual descriptors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/executing-your-commands-via-motion-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Video Representations from Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-video-representations-from-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce LaViLa, a new approach to learning video-language representations by leveraging Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-video-representations-from-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Editing Models with Task Arithmetic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editing-models-with-task-arithmetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Changing how pre-trained models behave -- e. g., improving their performance on a downstream task or mitigating biases learned during pre-training -- is a common practice when developing machine learning systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editing-models-with-task-arithmetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating and Weighting Semantically Consistent Sample Pairs for Ultrasound Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-and-weighting-semantically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we pre-train DNNs on ultrasound (US) domains instead of ImageNet to reduce the domain gap in medical US applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-and-weighting-semantically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-view Geo-localization via Learning Disentangled Geometric Layout Correspondence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-view-geo-localization-via-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We attribute this deficiency to the lack of ability to extract the spatial configuration of visual feature layouts and models' overfitting on low-level details from the training set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-view-geo-localization-via-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Model Assembling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-model-assembling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, the additional overhead introduced by the meta model is minimalized.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-model-assembling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Graph Neural Networks for Social Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-graph-neural-networks-for-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this survey, we first identify 80 papers on GNN-based SocialRS after annotating 2151 papers by following the PRISMA framework (Preferred Reporting Items for Systematic Reviews and Meta-Analysis).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-graph-neural-networks-for-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OFASys: A Multi-Modal Multi-Task Learning System for Building Generalist Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ofasys-a-multi-modal-multi-task-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a starting point, we provide presets of 7 different modalities and 23 highly-diverse example tasks in OFASys, with which we also develop a first-in-kind, single model, OFA+, that can handle text, image, speech, video, and motion data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ofasys-a-multi-modal-multi-task-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Unlabeled Data to Track Memorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-unlabeled-data-to-track</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We empirically show the effectiveness of our metric in tracking memorization on various architectures and datasets and provide theoretical insights into the design of the susceptibility metric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-unlabeled-data-to-track</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow Removal by High-Quality Shadow Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadow-removal-by-high-quality-shadow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the encoder extracts the shadow feature of a region identity which is then paired with another region identity to serve as the generator input to synthesize a pseudo image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadow-removal-by-high-quality-shadow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vicious Classifiers: Data Reconstruction Attack at Inference Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vicious-classifiers-data-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Privacy-preserving inference via edge or encrypted computing paradigms encourages users of machine learning services to confidentially run a model on their personal data for a target task and only share the model's outputs with the service provider; e. g., to activate further services.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vicious-classifiers-data-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining Photogrammetric Computer Vision and Semantic Segmentation for Fine-grained Understanding of Coral Reef Growth under Climate Change</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-photogrammetric-computer-vision-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Corals are the primary habitat-building life-form on reefs that support a quarter of the species in the ocean.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-photogrammetric-computer-vision-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C-VTON: Context-Driven Image-Based Virtual Try-On Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c-vton-context-driven-image-based-virtual-try</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the core of the C-VTON pipeline are: (i) a geometric matching procedure that efficiently aligns the target clothing with the pose of the person in the input images, and (ii) a powerful image generator that utilizes various types of contextual information when synthesizing the final try-on result.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c-vton-context-driven-image-based-virtual-try</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Accurate Ground Plane Normal Estimation from Ego-Motion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-accurate-ground-plane-normal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel approach for ground plane normal estimation of wheeled vehicles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-accurate-ground-plane-normal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNETR++: Delving into Efficient and Accurate 3D Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unetr-delving-into-efficient-and-accurate-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Owing to the success of transformer models, recent works study their applicability in 3D medical segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unetr-delving-into-efficient-and-accurate-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>evosax: JAX-based Evolution Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evosax-jax-based-evolution-strategies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to better harness these resources and to enable the next generation of black-box optimization algorithms, we release evosax: A JAX-based library of evolution strategies which allows researchers to leverage powerful function transformations such as just-in-time compilation, automatic vectorization and hardware parallelization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evosax-jax-based-evolution-strategies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINE: SINgle Image Editing with Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sine-single-image-editing-with-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel model-based guidance built upon the classifier-free guidance so that the knowledge from the model trained on a single image can be distilled into the pre-trained diffusion model, enabling content creation even with one given image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sine-single-image-editing-with-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConsistTL: Modeling Consistency in Transfer Learning for Low-Resource Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consisttl-modeling-consistency-in-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel transfer learning method for NMT, namely ConsistTL, which can continuously transfer knowledge from the parent model during the training of the child model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consisttl-modeling-consistency-in-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeeProb-kit: a Python Library for Deep Probabilistic Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deeprob-kit-a-python-library-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DeeProb-kit is a unified library written in Python consisting of a collection of deep probabilistic models (DPMs) that are tractable and exact representations for the modelled probability distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deeprob-kit-a-python-library-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Discrete Genres: Mapping News Items onto a Multidimensional Framework of Genre Cues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-discrete-genres-mapping-news-items</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the contemporary media landscape, with the vast and diverse supply of news, it is increasingly challenging to study such an enormous amount of items without a standardized framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-discrete-genres-mapping-news-items</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Parallel Exact Inference on Bayesian Networks: Poster</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-parallel-exact-inference-on-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian networks (BNs) are attractive, because they are graphical and interpretable machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-parallel-exact-inference-on-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Parallel Bayesian Network Structure Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-parallel-bayesian-network-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The mainstream BN structure learning methods require performing a large number of conditional independence (CI) tests.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-parallel-bayesian-network-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer learning for chemically accurate interatomic neural network potentials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-chemically-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work studies the capability of transfer learning for efficiently generating chemically accurate interatomic neural network potentials on organic molecules from the MD17 and ANI data sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-chemically-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CODEBench: A Neural Architecture and Hardware Accelerator Co-Design Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codebench-a-neural-architecture-and-hardware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AccelBench performs cycle-accurate simulations for a diverse set of accelerator architectures in a vast design space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codebench-a-neural-architecture-and-hardware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Action-Effect Dynamics for Hypothetical Vision-Language Reasoning Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-action-effect-dynamics-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA['Actions' play a vital role in how humans interact with the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-action-effect-dynamics-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dock2D: Synthetic data for the molecular recognition problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dock2d-synthetic-data-for-the-molecular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting the physical interaction of proteins is a cornerstone problem in computational biology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dock2d-synthetic-data-for-the-molecular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Matters: Investigating the Role of Supervision in Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-matters-investigating-the-role-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare ViTs trained through different methods of supervision, and show that they learn a diverse range of behaviors in terms of their attention, representations, and downstream performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-matters-investigating-the-role-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyclically Disentangled Feature Translation for Face Anti-spoofing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cyclically-disentangled-feature-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further extend CDFTN for multi-target domain adaptation by leveraging data from more unlabeled target domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cyclically-disentangled-feature-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIDER &amp; CLOSER: Mixture of Short-channel Distillers for Zero-shot Cross-lingual Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wider-closer-mixture-of-short-channel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, a mixture of short-channel distillers (MSD) method is proposed to fully interact the rich hierarchical information in the teacher model and to transfer knowledge to the student model sufficiently and efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wider-closer-mixture-of-short-channel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phase2vec: Dynamical systems embedding with a physics-informed convolutional network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phase2vec-dynamical-systems-embedding-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an auxiliary training period, embeddings are optimized so that they robustly encode the equations of unseen data over and above the performance of a per-equation fitting method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phase2vec-dynamical-systems-embedding-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic Rising Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-rising-bandits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper is in the field of stochastic Multi-Armed Bandits (MABs), i. e., those sequential selection techniques able to learn online using only the feedback given by the chosen option (a. k. a.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-rising-bandits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimVTP: Simple Video Text Pre-training with Masked Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simvtp-simple-video-text-pre-training-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents SimVTP: a Simple Video-Text Pretraining framework via masked autoencoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simvtp-simple-video-text-pre-training-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RainUNet for Super-Resolution Rain Movie Prediction under Spatio-temporal Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rainunet-for-super-resolution-rain-movie</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a solution to the Weather4cast 2022 Challenge Stage 2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rainunet-for-super-resolution-rain-movie</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-constrained deep learning postprocessing of temperature and humidity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-constrained-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weather forecasting centers currently rely on statistical postprocessing methods to minimize forecast error.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-constrained-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FSID: Fully Synthetic Image Denoising via Procedural Scene Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fsid-fully-synthetic-image-denoising-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we have developed a procedural synthetic data generation pipeline and dataset tailored to low-level vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fsid-fully-synthetic-image-denoising-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness and Explainability: Bridging the Gap Towards Fair Model Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-and-explainability-bridging-the-gap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although research efforts have been devoted to measuring and mitigating bias, they mainly study bias from the result-oriented perspective while neglecting the bias encoded in the decision-making procedure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-and-explainability-bridging-the-gap</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Compression With Learned Lifting-Based DWT and Learned Tree-Based Entropy Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-compression-with-learned-lifting-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores learned image compression based on traditional and learned discrete wavelet transform (DWT) architectures and learned entropy models for coding DWT subband coefficients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-compression-with-learned-lifting-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViTPose+: Vision Transformer Foundation Model for Generic Body Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitpose-vision-transformer-foundation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show the surprisingly good properties of plain vision transformers for body pose estimation from various aspects, namely simplicity in model structure, scalability in model size, flexibility in training paradigm, and transferability of knowledge between models, through a simple baseline model dubbed ViTPose.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitpose-vision-transformer-foundation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Specifying Behavior Preference with Tiered Reward Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/specifying-behavior-preference-with-tiered</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, we propose an environment-independent tiered reward structure and show it is guaranteed to induce policies that are Pareto-optimal according to our preference relation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/specifying-behavior-preference-with-tiered</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slimmable Pruned Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slimmable-pruned-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Slimmable Neural Networks (S-Net) is a novel network which enabled to select one of the predefined proportions of channels (sub-network) dynamically depending on the current computational resource availability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slimmable-pruned-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iQuery: Instruments as Queries for Audio-Visual Sound Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iquery-instruments-as-queries-for-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To generalize to a new instrument or event class, drawing inspiration from the text-prompt design, we insert an additional query as an audio prompt while freezing the attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iquery-instruments-as-queries-for-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLeaD: Improving GANs with A Generator-Leading Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glead-improving-gans-with-a-generator-leading</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative adversarial network (GAN) is formulated as a two-player game between a generator (G) and a discriminator (D), where D is asked to differentiate whether an image comes from real data or is produced by G. Under such a formulation, D plays as the rule maker and hence tends to dominate the competition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glead-improving-gans-with-a-generator-leading</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-Temporal Self-Supervised Learning for Traffic Flow Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-self-supervised-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ii) These models fail to capture the temporal heterogeneity induced by time-varying traffic patterns, as they typically model temporal correlations with a shared parameterized space for all time periods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-self-supervised-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Structure for Improved Classification of Grouped Biased Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-structure-for-improved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To model the inherent structure in such data, we assume the partition-projected class-conditional invariance across groups, defined in terms of the group-agnostic feature space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-structure-for-improved</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconciling a Centroid-Hypothesis Conflict in Source-Free Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconciling-a-centroid-hypothesis-conflict-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose to reconcile this conflict by aligning the entropy minimization objective with that of the pseudo labels' cross entropy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconciling-a-centroid-hypothesis-conflict-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIAR: Harmony of Data-Centric and Model-Centric for Multi-Modality Microscopy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mediar-harmony-of-data-centric-and-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cell segmentation is a fundamental task for computational biology analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mediar-harmony-of-data-centric-and-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truthful Meta-Explanations for Local Interpretability of Machine Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truthful-meta-explanations-for-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, the demand for a selection tool, a meta-explanation technique based on a high-quality evaluation metric, is apparent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truthful-meta-explanations-for-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intervening With Confidence: Conformal Prescriptive Monitoring of Business Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intervening-with-confidence-conformal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prescriptive process monitoring methods seek to improve the performance of a process by selectively triggering interventions at runtime (e. g., offering a discount to a customer) to increase the probability of a desired case outcome (e. g., a customer making a purchase).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intervening-with-confidence-conformal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Explainable Motion Prediction using Heterogeneous Graph Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explainable-motion-prediction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we aim to improve the explainability of motion prediction systems by using different approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explainable-motion-prediction-using</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
