<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 09:17:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-Guided Detector for SAR Airplanes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-guided-detector-for-sar-airplanes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main contributions of PGD include the physics-guided self-supervised learning, feature enhancement, and instance perception, denoted as PGSSL, PGFE, and PGIP, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-guided-detector-for-sar-airplanes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contourlet Refinement Gate Framework for Thermal Spectrum Distribution Regularized Infrared Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contourlet-refinement-gate-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we emphasize the infrared spectral distribution fidelity and propose a Contourlet refinement gate framework to restore infrared modal-specific features while preserving spectral distribution fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contourlet-refinement-gate-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SG-LRA: Self-Generating Automatic Scoliosis Cobb Angle Measurement with Low-Rank Approximation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sg-lra-self-generating-automatic-scoliosis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic Cobb angle measurement from X-ray images is crucial for scoliosis screening and diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sg-lra-self-generating-automatic-scoliosis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invariant Shape Representation Learning For Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-shape-representation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel framework that for the first time develops invariant shape representation learning (ISRL) to further strengthen the robustness of image classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-shape-representation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>libcll: an Extendable Python Toolkit for Complementary-Label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/libcll-an-extendable-python-toolkit-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Complementary-label learning (CLL) is a weakly supervised learning paradigm for multiclass classification, where only complementary labels -- indicating classes an instance does not belong to -- are provided to the learning algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/libcll-an-extendable-python-toolkit-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Prompt Steerability of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-prompt-steerability-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Achieving this requires first being able to evaluate the degree to which a given model is capable of reflecting various personas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-prompt-steerability-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CV-Cities: Advancing Cross-View Geo-Localization in Global Cities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cv-cities-advancing-cross-view-geo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-view geo-localization (CVGL), which involves matching and retrieving satellite images to determine the geographic location of a ground image, is crucial in GNSS-constrained scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cv-cities-advancing-cross-view-geo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DLBacktrace: A Model Agnostic Explainability for any Deep Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dlbacktrace-a-model-agnostic-explainability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of artificial intelligence has led to increasingly sophisticated deep learning models, which frequently operate as opaque 'black boxes' with limited transparency in their decision-making processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dlbacktrace-a-model-agnostic-explainability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motif Channel Opened in a White-Box: Stereo Matching via Motif Correlation Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motif-channel-opened-in-a-white-box-stereo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, learning-based stereo matching methods inherently suffer from the loss of geometric structures in certain feature channels, creating a bottleneck in achieving precise detail matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motif-channel-opened-in-a-white-box-stereo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoM: Efficient Image and Video Generation with the Polynomial Mixer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pom-efficient-image-and-video-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate this problem, we propose a drop-in replacement for MHA called the Polynomial Mixer (PoM) that has the benefit of encoding the entire sequence into an explicit state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pom-efficient-image-and-video-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM Carries the Burden: A Semi-Supervised Approach Refining Pseudo Labels for Medical Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-carries-the-burden-a-semi-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our work, we leverage SAM's abstract object understanding for medical image segmentation to provide pseudo labels for semi-supervised learning, thereby mitigating the need for extensive annotated training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-carries-the-burden-a-semi-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSiRe-GS: 4D Street Gaussians for Static-Dynamic Decomposition and Surface Reconstruction for Urban Driving Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/desire-gs-4d-street-gaussians-for-static</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present DeSiRe-GS, a self-supervised gaussian splatting representation, enabling effective static-dynamic decomposition and high-fidelity surface reconstruction in complex driving scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/desire-gs-4d-street-gaussians-for-static</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edge-Enhanced Dilated Residual Attention Network for Multimodal Medical Image Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge-enhanced-dilated-residual-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal medical image fusion is a crucial task that combines complementary information from different imaging modalities into a unified representation, thereby enhancing diagnostic accuracy and treatment planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge-enhanced-dilated-residual-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Unlearning Truly Unlearn? A Black Box Evaluation of LLM Unlearning Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-unlearning-truly-unlearn-a-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language model unlearning aims to remove harmful information that LLMs have learnt to prevent their use for malicious purposes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-unlearning-truly-unlearn-a-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual-Semantic Graph Matching Net for Zero-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-semantic-graph-matching-net-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, methods trained under this paradigm often struggle to learn robust embedding space because they align the two modalities in an isolated manner among classes, which ignore the crucial class relationship during the alignment process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-semantic-graph-matching-net-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMURAI: Adapting Segment Anything Model for Zero-Shot Visual Tracking with Motion-Aware Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samurai-adapting-segment-anything-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Segment Anything Model 2 (SAM 2) has demonstrated strong performance in object segmentation tasks but faces challenges in visual object tracking, particularly when managing crowded scenes with fast-moving or self-occluding objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samurai-adapting-segment-anything-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant spatio-hemispherical networks for diffusion MRI deconvolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-spatio-hemispherical-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Each voxel in a diffusion MRI (dMRI) image contains a spherical signal corresponding to the direction and strength of water diffusion in the brain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-spatio-hemispherical-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Speculative Decoding for Autoregressive Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-speculative-decoding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results show that our continuous speculative decoding achieves a remarkable $2. 33\times$ speed-up on off-the-shelf models while maintaining the output distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-speculative-decoding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Few-Step Diffusion Models with Dense Reward Difference Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-few-step-diffusion-models-with-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results demonstrate that SDPO consistently outperforms prior methods in reward-based alignment across diverse step configurations, underscoring its robust step generalization capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-few-step-diffusion-models-with-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SADDE: Semi-supervised Anomaly Detection with Dependable Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sadde-semi-supervised-anomaly-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this research paper, we introduce SADDE, a general framework designed to accomplish two primary objectives: (1) to render the anomaly detection process interpretable and enhance the credibility of interpretation outcomes, and (2) to assign high-confidence pseudo labels to unlabeled samples, thereby boosting the performance of anomaly detection systems when supervised data is scarce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sadde-semi-supervised-anomaly-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Milabench: Benchmarking Accelerators for AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introducing-milabench-benchmarking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AI workloads, particularly those driven by deep learning, are introducing novel usage patterns to high-performance computing (HPC) systems that are not comprehensively captured by standard HPC benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introducing-milabench-benchmarking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Fitness Exercise Classification and Counting from Video Frames</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-fitness-exercise-classification-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model was trained and validated on these diverse datasets, achieving an accuracy of over 99% on the test set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-fitness-exercise-classification-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise Filtering Benchmark for Neuromorphic Satellites Observations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-filtering-benchmark-for-neuromorphic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we introduce a new high-resolution satellite dataset with ground truth from a real-world platform under various noise conditions, which we have made publicly available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-filtering-benchmark-for-neuromorphic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color-Oriented Redundancy Reduction in Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-oriented-redundancy-reduction-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the image level, we employ a palette network, a specialized neural network, to dynamically allocate colors from a reduced color space to each pixel.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-oriented-redundancy-reduction-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relational Contrastive Learning and Masked Image Modeling for Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-contrastive-learning-and-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this, we further conduct relational contrastive learning to model the intra- and inter-hierarchical relations for frames, sub-words and words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-contrastive-learning-and-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable Person Re-identification via Balancing Alignment and Uniformity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-person-re-identification-via-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel framework, Balancing Alignment and Uniformity (BAU), which effectively mitigates this effect by maintaining a balance between alignment and uniformity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-person-re-identification-via-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newclid: A User-Friendly Replacement for AlphaGeometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/newclid-a-user-friendly-replacement-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Newclid contains a symbolic solver called DDARN (derived from DDAR-Newclid), which is a significant refactoring and upgrade of AlphaGeometry's DDAR symbolic solver by being more user-friendly - both for the end user as well as for a programmer wishing to extend the codebase.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/newclid-a-user-friendly-replacement-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMURAI: Adapting Segment Anything Model for Zero-Shot Visual Tracking with Motion-Aware Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samurai-adapting-segment-anything-model-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Segment Anything Model 2 (SAM 2) has demonstrated strong performance in object segmentation tasks but faces challenges in visual object tracking, particularly when managing crowded scenes with fast-moving or self-occluding objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samurai-adapting-segment-anything-model-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Geometric-Physical-Driven Robot Manipulation Skill Transfer via Skill Library and Tactile Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-geometric-physical-driven-robot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The framework hierarchically organizes operational knowledge by constructing a "task graph" and a "scene graph" to represent task and scene semantic information, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-geometric-physical-driven-robot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cascaded Diffusion Models for 2D and 3D Microscopy Image Synthesis to Enhance Cell Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascaded-diffusion-models-for-2d-and-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this, we propose a novel framework for synthesizing densely annotated 2D and 3D cell microscopy images using cascaded diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascaded-diffusion-models-for-2d-and-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZeFaV: Boosting Large Language Models for Zero-shot Fact Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zefav-boosting-large-language-models-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose ZeFaV - a zero-shot based fact-checking verification framework to enhance the performance on fact verification task of large language models by leveraging the in-context learning ability of large language models to extract the relations among the entities within a claim, re-organized the information from the evidence in a relationally logical form, and combine the above information with the original evidence to generate the context from which our fact-checking model provide verdicts for the input claims.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zefav-boosting-large-language-models-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITACLIP: Boosting Training-Free Semantic Segmentation with Image, Text, and Architectural Enhancements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/itaclip-boosting-training-free-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in foundational Vision Language Models (VLMs) have reshaped the evaluation paradigm in computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/itaclip-boosting-training-free-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSPRank: Bridging Pairwise and Listwise Methods with a Bilinear Travelling Salesman Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsprank-bridging-pairwise-and-listwise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TSPRank reframes the ranking problem as a Travelling Salesman Problem (TSP), a well-known combinatorial optimisation challenge that has been extensively studied for its numerous solution algorithms and applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsprank-bridging-pairwise-and-listwise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCExpert: Advancing MLLM Capability in Remote Sensing Change Captioning with Difference-Aware Integration and a Foundational Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccexpert-advancing-mllm-capability-in-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel model, CCExpert, based on a new, advanced multimodal large model framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccexpert-advancing-mllm-capability-in-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AtomThink: A Slow Thinking Framework for Multimodal Mathematical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomthink-a-slow-thinking-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we address the challenging task of multimodal mathematical reasoning by incorporating the ability of ``slow thinking" into multimodal large language models (MLLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomthink-a-slow-thinking-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ST-Tree with Interpretability for Multivariate Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/st-tree-with-interpretability-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, deep neural network models such as Transformers exhibit high accuracy in multivariate time series classification but lack interpretability and fail to provide insights into the decision-making process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/st-tree-with-interpretability-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuvis.Ai: An Open-Source, Low-Code Software Ecosystem for Hyperspectral Processing and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuvis-ai-an-open-source-low-code-software</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning is an important tool for analyzing high-dimension hyperspectral data; however, existing software solutions are either closed-source or inextensible research products.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuvis-ai-an-open-source-low-code-software</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifted Model Construction without Normalisation: A Vectorised Approach to Exploit Symmetries in Factor Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifted-model-construction-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lifted probabilistic inference exploits symmetries in a probabilistic model to allow for tractable probabilistic inference with respect to domain sizes of logical variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifted-model-construction-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Artificial Intelligence for Quantifying Compatibility Mechanisms in Traditional Chinese Medicine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-artificial-intelligence-for-quantifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional Chinese Medicine (TCM) involves complex compatibility mechanisms characterized by multi-component and multi-target interactions, which are challenging to quantify.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-artificial-intelligence-for-quantifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Neural Joint Activity in Spiking Neural Networks for Fraud Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-neural-joint-activity-in-spiking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed SNN approach with neural joint activity enables the classification of fraudulent opening of bank accounts more accurately and fairly than standard SNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-neural-joint-activity-in-spiking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BianCang: A Traditional Chinese Medicine Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biancang-a-traditional-chinese-medicine-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise of large language models (LLMs) has driven significant progress in medical applications, including traditional Chinese medicine (TCM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biancang-a-traditional-chinese-medicine-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SageAttention2 Technical Report: Accurate 4 Bit Attention for Plug-and-play Inference Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sageattention2-technical-report-accurate-4</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we propose a method to smooth $Q$ and $V$, enhancing the accuracy of attention with INT4 $QK$ and FP8 $PV$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sageattention2-technical-report-accurate-4</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Step Generating: A Universal Synthesized Deepfake Image Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-step-generating-a-universal-synthesized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Currently, high-fidelity text-to-image models are developed in an accelerating pace.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-step-generating-a-universal-synthesized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Multimodal LLMs: the Mechanistic Interpretability of Llava in Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-multimodal-llms-the-mechanistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the mechanisms behind Large Language Models (LLMs) is crucial for designing improved models and strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-multimodal-llms-the-mechanistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Primes to Paths: Enabling Fast Multi-Relational Graph Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-primes-to-paths-enabling-fast-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This enables a compact representation of a complete multi-relational graph using a single adjacency matrix, which, in turn, facilitates quick computation of multi-hop adjacency matrices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-primes-to-paths-enabling-fast-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TS-LLaVA: Constructing Visual Tokens through Thumbnail-and-Sampling for Training-Free Video Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ts-llava-constructing-visual-tokens-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For video understanding tasks, training-based video LLMs are difficult to build due to the scarcity of high-quality, curated video-text paired data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ts-llava-constructing-visual-tokens-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VeGaS: Video Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vegas-video-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One potential solution is to use a 3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) based model, such as the Video Gaussian Representation (VGR), which is capable of encoding video as a multitude of 3D Gaussians and is applicable for numerous video processing operations, including editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vegas-video-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dialectal Toxicity Detection: Evaluating LLM-as-a-Judge Consistency Across Language Varieties</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialectal-toxicity-detection-evaluating-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, if we have to rank the consistency, the weakest area is LLM-human agreement, followed by dialectal consistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialectal-toxicity-detection-evaluating-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Bayesian Bow tie Neural Networks with Shrinkage</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-bayesian-bow-tie-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the dominant role of deep models in machine learning, limitations persist, including overconfident predictions, susceptibility to adversarial attacks, and underestimation of variability in predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-bayesian-bow-tie-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving User Experience in Preference-Based Optimization of Reward Functions for Assistive Robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-user-experience-in-preference-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assistive robots interact with humans and must adapt to different users' preferences to be effective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-user-experience-in-preference-based</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
