<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 21:06:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Thin-Plate Spline Motion and Seamless Composition for Parallax-Tolerant Unsupervised Deep Image Stitching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-thin-plate-spline-motion-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we propose a robust and flexible warp to model the image registration from global homography to local thin-plate spline motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-thin-plate-spline-motion-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Hidden Representations in Transfer Learning for Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-hidden-representations-in-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings challenge the notion that transfer learning is effective due to the reuse of general features in the early layers of a convolutional neural network and show that weight similarity before and after fine-tuning is negatively related to performance gains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-hidden-representations-in-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D-aware Conditional Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-aware-conditional-image-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose pix2pix3D, a 3D-aware conditional generative model for controllable photorealistic image synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-aware-conditional-image-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAPLoss: A Temporal Acoustic Parameter Loss for Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taploss-a-temporal-acoustic-parameter-loss</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an objective for perceptual quality based on temporal acoustic parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taploss-a-temporal-acoustic-parameter-loss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Positive-unlabeled learning for binary and multi-class cell detection in histopathology images with incomplete annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/positive-unlabeled-learning-for-binary-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Typically, to train CNN-based cell detection models, every positive instance in the training images needs to be annotated, and instances that are not labeled as positive are considered negative samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/positive-unlabeled-learning-for-binary-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marich: A Query-efficient Distributionally Equivalent Model Extraction Attack using Public Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marich-a-query-efficient-distributionally</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Marich is able to extract models that achieve $69-96\%$ of true model's accuracy and uses $1, 070 - 6, 950$ samples from the publicly available query datasets, which are different from the private training datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marich-a-query-efficient-distributionally</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Realized recurrent conditional heteroskedasticity model for volatility modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realized-recurrent-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new approach to volatility modelling by combining deep learning (LSTM) and realized volatility measures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realized-recurrent-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empirical Investigation of Neural Symbolic Reasoning Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-investigation-of-neural-symbolic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural reasoning accuracy improves when generating intermediate reasoning steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-investigation-of-neural-symbolic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HE-MAN -- Homomorphically Encrypted MAchine learning with oNnx models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/he-man-homomorphically-encrypted-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fully homomorphic encryption (FHE) is a promising technique to enable individuals using ML services without giving up privacy and protecting the ML model of service providers at the same time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/he-man-homomorphically-encrypted-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theory and Implementation of Complex-Valued Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theory-and-implementation-of-complex-valued</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work explains in detail the theory behind Complex-Valued Neural Network (CVNN), including Wirtinger calculus, complex backpropagation, and basic modules such as complex layers, complex activation functions, or complex weight initialization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theory-and-implementation-of-complex-valued</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T2I-Adapter: Learning Adapters to Dig out More Controllable Ability for Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t2i-adapter-learning-adapters-to-dig-out-more</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The incredible generative ability of large-scale text-to-image (T2I) models has demonstrated strong power of learning complex structures and meaningful semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t2i-adapter-learning-adapters-to-dig-out-more</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>URCDC-Depth: Uncertainty Rectified Cross-Distillation with CutFlip for Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/urcdc-depth-uncertainty-rectified-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work aims to estimate a high-quality depth map from a single RGB image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/urcdc-depth-uncertainty-rectified-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Efficient Visual Adaption via Structural Re-parameterization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-visual-adaption-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For instance, by updating only 0. 6% parameters, we can improve the performance of ViT from 38. 8 to 55. 1 on Sun397.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-visual-adaption-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Non-Local Spatial-Angular Correlation for Light Field Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-non-local-spatial-angular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Exploiting spatial-angular correlation is crucial to light field (LF) image super-resolution (SR), but is highly challenging due to its non-local property caused by the disparities among LF images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-non-local-spatial-angular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counting Carbon: A Survey of Factors Influencing the Emissions of Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counting-carbon-a-survey-of-factors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning (ML) requires using energy to carry out computations during the model training process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counting-carbon-a-survey-of-factors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Spoken Language Identification with Map-Mix</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-spoken-language-identification-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pre-trained multi-lingual XLSR model generalizes well for language identification after fine-tuning on unseen languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-spoken-language-identification-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIFUSCO: Graph-based Diffusion Solvers for Combinatorial Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difusco-graph-based-diffusion-solvers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the MIS problem, DIFUSCO outperforms the previous state-of-the-art neural solver on the challenging SATLIB benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difusco-graph-based-diffusion-solvers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Neural PDE Solver with Temporal Stencil Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-pde-solver-with-temporal-stencil</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerical simulation of non-linear partial differential equations plays a crucial role in modeling physical science and engineering phenomena, such as weather, climate, and aerodynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-pde-solver-with-temporal-stencil</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Remote Sensing Image Super-Resolution based on Context Interaction in Implicit Function Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-remote-sensing-image-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite its fruitful applications in remote sensing, image super-resolution is troublesome to train and deploy as it handles different resolution magnifications with separate models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-remote-sensing-image-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A cloud-based deep learning system for improving crowd safety at event entrances</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cloud-based-deep-learning-system-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a cloud-based deep learning system for early detection of pushing automatically in the live video stream of crowded event entrances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cloud-based-deep-learning-system-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Causal Discovery for Estimating Causal Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-causal-discovery-for-estimating-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even when the causal graph underlying our data is unknown, we can use observational data to narrow down the possible values that an average treatment effect (ATE) can take by (1) identifying the graph up to a Markov equivalence class; and (2) estimating that ATE for each graph in the class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-causal-discovery-for-estimating-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClaPIM: Scalable Sequence CLAssification using Processing-In-Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clapim-scalable-sequence-classification-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a custom filtering technique that drastically narrows the search space and a search approach that facilitates approximate string matching through a distance function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clapim-scalable-sequence-classification-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SyreaNet: A Physically Guided Underwater Image Enhancement Framework Integrating Synthetic and Real Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syreanet-a-physically-guided-underwater-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although learning-based UIE methods have made remarkable achievements in recent years, it's still challenging for them to consistently deal with various underwater conditions, which could be caused by: 1) the use of the simplified atmospheric image formation model in UIE may result in severe errors; 2) the network trained solely with synthetic images might have difficulty in generalizing well to real underwater images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syreanet-a-physically-guided-underwater-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CluCDD:Contrastive Dialogue Disentanglement via Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clucdd-contrastive-dialogue-disentanglement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A huge number of multi-participant dialogues happen online every day, which leads to difficulty in understanding the nature of dialogue dynamics for both humans and machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clucdd-contrastive-dialogue-disentanglement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ST-MFNet Mini: Knowledge Distillation-Driven Frame Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/st-mfnet-mini-knowledge-distillation-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Currently, one of the major challenges in deep learning-based video frame interpolation (VFI) is the large model sizes and high computational complexity associated with many high performance VFI approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/st-mfnet-mini-knowledge-distillation-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LightGCL: Simple Yet Effective Graph Contrastive Learning for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightgcl-simple-yet-effective-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a simple yet effective graph contrastive learning paradigm LightGCL that mitigates these issues impairing the generality and robustness of CL-based recommenders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightgcl-simple-yet-effective-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective Noise Suppression in Random SVPWM to Shape the Voltage and Current Spectrum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-noise-suppression-in-random-svpwm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed methods provide a reference to eliminate the electromagnetic noise at the modal frequencies in motors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-noise-suppression-in-random-svpwm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assisting Human Decisions in Document Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assisting-human-decisions-in-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many practical applications, ranging from paper-reviewer assignment in peer review to job-applicant matching for hiring, require human decision makers to identify relevant matches by combining their expertise with predictions from machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assisting-human-decisions-in-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Millimeter-Wave Software-Defined Radio for Wireless Experimentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-millimeter-wave-software-defined-radio-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a low-cost and portable millimeter-wave software-defined radio (SDR) for wireless experimentation in the 60 GHz band.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-millimeter-wave-software-defined-radio-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-augmented Graph Machine Learning for Drug Discovery: A Survey from Precision to Interpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-augmented-graph-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As of late, Graph Machine Learning (GML) has gained considerable attention for its exceptional ability to model graph-structured biomedical data and investigate their properties and functional relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-augmented-graph-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NUAA-QMUL-AIIT at Memotion 3: Multi-modal Fusion with Squeeze-and-Excitation for Internet Meme Emotion Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nuaa-qmul-aiit-at-memotion-3-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes the participation of our NUAA-QMUL-AIIT team in the Memotion 3 shared task on meme emotion analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nuaa-qmul-aiit-at-memotion-3-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-augmented Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-image-captioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The encoder in our model jointly processes the image and retrieved captions using a pretrained V&L BERT, while the decoder attends to the multimodal encoder representations, benefiting from the extra textual evidence from the retrieved captions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-image-captioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boundary Guided Mixing Trajectory for Semantic Control with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-guided-mixing-trajectory-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then propose to further explore the critical step in the denoising trajectory that characterizes the convergence of a pre-trained DDM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-guided-mixing-trajectory-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiDiffusion: Fusing Diffusion Paths for Controlled Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multidiffusion-fusing-diffusion-paths-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present MultiDiffusion, a unified framework that enables versatile and controllable image generation, using a pre-trained text-to-image diffusion model, without any further training or finetuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multidiffusion-fusing-diffusion-paths-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fossil Image Identification using Deep Learning Ensembles of Data Augmented Multiviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fossil-image-identification-using-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, OGS obtains the superior or comparable performance compared to the method under well-known bagging framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fossil-image-identification-using-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Insights on Relieving Task-Recency Bias for Online Class Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-insights-on-relieving-task-recency-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In all settings, the online class incremental learning (CIL), where incoming samples from data stream can be used only once, is more challenging and can be encountered more frequently in real world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-insights-on-relieving-task-recency-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Adversarial Immunization for Certifiable Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-adversarial-immunization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose and formulate graph adversarial immunization, i. e., vaccinating part of graph structure to improve certifiable robustness of graph against any admissible adversarial attack.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-adversarial-immunization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHC: Weighted Hybrid Criterion for Filter Pruning on Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whc-weighted-hybrid-criterion-for-filter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Filter pruning has attracted increasing attention in recent years for its capacity in compressing and accelerating convolutional neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whc-weighted-hybrid-criterion-for-filter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Mid-Pass Filtering Graph Convolutional Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-mid-pass-filtering-graph-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Theoretical analyses guarantee the robustness of signals through the mid-pass filter, and we also shed light on the properties of different frequency signals under adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-mid-pass-filtering-graph-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficiency 360: Efficient Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiency-360-efficient-vision-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers are widely used for solving tasks in natural language processing, computer vision, speech, and music domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiency-360-efficient-vision-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Graph Neural Networks for Irregular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-graph-neural-networks-for-irregular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our TGNN4I model is designed to handle both irregular time steps and partial observations of the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-graph-neural-networks-for-irregular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On marginal feature attributions of tree-based models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-marginal-feature-attributions-of-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An important observation, showcased by experiments with XGBoost, LightGBM and CatBoost libraries, is that only a portion of all features appears in a tree from the ensemble; thus the complexity of computing marginal Shapley (or Owen or Banzhaf) feature attributions may be reduced.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-marginal-feature-attributions-of-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trieste: Efficiently Exploring The Depths of Black-box Functions with TensorFlow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trieste-efficiently-exploring-the-depths-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Trieste, an open-source Python package for Bayesian optimization and active learning benefiting from the scalability and efficiency of TensorFlow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trieste-efficiently-exploring-the-depths-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoupled Model Schedule for Deep Learning Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-model-schedule-for-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the schedule works on a PyTorch model and uses a set of schedule primitives to convert the model for common model training optimizations such as high-performance kernels, effective 3D parallelism, and efficient activation checkpointing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-model-schedule-for-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-VTS: Fact Extraction and Verification on Short Video Platforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covid-vts-fact-extraction-and-verification-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new benchmark, COVID-VTS, for fact-checking multi-modal information involving short-duration videos with COVID19- focused information from both the real world and machine generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covid-vts-fact-extraction-and-verification-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Online Conformal Prediction via Strongly Adaptive Online Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-online-conformal-prediction-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that our methods achieve near-optimal strongly adaptive regret for all interval lengths simultaneously, and approximately valid coverage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-online-conformal-prediction-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIVOTrack: A Novel Dataset and Baseline Method for Cross-View Multi-Object Tracking in DIVerse Open Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divotrack-a-novel-dataset-and-baseline-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although cross-view multi-object tracking has received increased attention in recent years, existing datasets still have several issues, including 1) missing real-world scenarios, 2) lacking diverse scenes, 3) owning a limited number of tracks, 4) comprising only static cameras, and 5) lacking standard benchmarks, which hinder the investigation and comparison of cross-view tracking methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divotrack-a-novel-dataset-and-baseline-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Target Specific De Novo Design of Drug Candidate Molecules with Graph Transformer-based Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-specific-de-novo-design-of-drug</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DrugGEN can be used to design completely novel and effective target-specific drug candidate molecules for any druggable protein, given target features and a dataset of experimental bioactivities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-specific-de-novo-design-of-drug</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Envisioning the Next-Gen Document Reader</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/envisioning-the-next-gen-document-reader</link>
      <description><![CDATA[People read digital documents on a daily basis to share, exchange, and understand information in electronic settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/envisioning-the-next-gen-document-reader</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depth- and Semantics-aware Multi-modal Domain Translation: Generating 3D Panoramic Color Images from LiDAR Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-and-semantics-aware-multi-modal-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents a new depth- and semantics-aware conditional generative model, named TITAN-Next, for cross-domain image-to-image translation in a multi-modal setup between LiDAR and camera sensors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-and-semantics-aware-multi-modal-domain</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
