<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 09:15:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing MMDiT-Based Text-to-Image Models for Similar Subject Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-mmdit-based-text-to-image-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant improvements, we observe that semantic ambiguity persists when generating multiple similar subjects, as the guidance provided by overlap loss is not explicit enough.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-mmdit-based-text-to-image-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating and Improving the Robustness of Security Attack Detectors Generated by LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-and-improving-the-robustness-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are increasingly used in software development to generate functions, such as attack detectors, that implement security requirements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-and-improving-the-robustness-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Mamba Distillation for Low-resolution Fine-grained Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-mamba-distillation-for-low-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-resolution fine-grained image classification has recently made significant progress, largely thanks to the super-resolution techniques and knowledge distillation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-mamba-distillation-for-low-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Fourier-embedded Network for Bi-modal Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fourier-embedded-network-for-bi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of deep learning provides a significant improvement of salient object detection combining both RGB and thermal images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fourier-embedded-network-for-bi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Knowledge Concepts to Whole Slide Images for Precise Histopathology Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-knowledge-concepts-to-whole-slide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the large size and lack of fine-grained annotation, Whole Slide Images (WSIs) analysis is commonly approached as a Multiple Instance Learning (MIL) problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-knowledge-concepts-to-whole-slide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RITA: Automatic Framework for Designing of Resilient IoT Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rita-automatic-framework-for-designing-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing resilient Internet of Things (IoT) systems requires i) identification of IoT Critical Objects (ICOs) such as services, devices, and resources, ii) threat analysis, and iii) mitigation strategy selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rita-automatic-framework-for-designing-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatRex: Taming Multimodal LLM for Joint Perception and Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatrex-taming-multimodal-llm-for-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From the data perspective, we build a fully automated data engine and construct the Rexverse-2M dataset which possesses multiple granularities to support the joint training of perception and understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatrex-taming-multimodal-llm-for-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning with Fairness Guarantees using Lorenz Dominance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-multi-objective-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning (MORL) aims to learn a set of policies that optimize trade-offs between multiple, often conflicting objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-multi-objective-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Runtime-Adaptive Transformer Neural Network Accelerator on FPGAs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-runtime-adaptive-transformer-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, it achieves a speedup of 1. 7 to 2. 25$\times$ compared to some state-of-the-art FPGA-based accelerators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-runtime-adaptive-transformer-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Open Vocabulary to Open World: Teaching Vision Language Models to Detect Novel Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-open-vocabulary-to-open-world-teaching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address theses limitations, we propose a framework that enables OVD models to operate in open world settings, by identifying and incrementally learning novel objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-open-vocabulary-to-open-world-teaching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUPE: Heuristic Underwater Perceptual Enhancement with Semantic Collaborative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hupe-heuristic-underwater-perceptual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To strike a balance between visual quality and application, we propose a heuristic invertible network for underwater perception enhancement, dubbed HUPE, which enhances visual quality and demonstrates flexibility in handling other downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hupe-heuristic-underwater-perceptual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulating Tabular Datasets through LLMs to Rapidly Explore Hypotheses about Real-World Entities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-tabular-datasets-through-llms-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Do horror writers have worse childhoods than other writers?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-tabular-datasets-through-llms-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectral-Spatial Transformer with Active Transfer Learning for Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-spatial-transformer-with-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a novel multi-stage active transfer learning (ATL) framework that integrates a Spatial-Spectral Transformer (SST) with an active learning process for efficient HSI classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-spatial-transformer-with-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Path: Multi-modal, Multi-granularity Path Representation Learning -- Extended Version</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-path-multi-modal-multi-granularity-path</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel Multi-modal, Multi-granularity Path Representation Learning Framework (MM-Path), which can learn a generic path representation by integrating modalities from both road paths and image paths.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-path-multi-modal-multi-granularity-path</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Draft Model Knows When to Stop: A Self-Verification Length Policy for Speculative Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/draft-model-knows-when-to-stop-a-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speculative Decoding (SD) has become an important technique in accelerating the inference speed of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/draft-model-knows-when-to-stop-a-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helvipad: A Real-World Dataset for Omnidirectional Stereo Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helvipad-a-real-world-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite considerable progress in stereo depth estimation, omnidirectional imaging remains underexplored, mainly due to the lack of appropriate data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helvipad-a-real-world-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuaLLM-Health: An Adaptation of an LLM-Based Framework for Quantitative Data Extraction from Online Health Discussions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quallm-health-an-adaptation-of-an-llm-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present an adapted framework from QuaLLM into QuaLLM-Health for extracting clinically relevant quantitative data from Reddit discussions about glucagon-like peptide-1 (GLP-1) receptor agonists using large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quallm-health-an-adaptation-of-an-llm-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Noise Token Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-noise-token-pruning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the present work we present Training Noise Token (TNT) Pruning for vision transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-noise-token-pruning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training and Evaluating Language Models with Template-based Data Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-evaluating-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we introduce Template-based Data Generation (TDG), a novel approach that leverages LLMs (GPT-4) to automatically generate parameterized meta-templates, which are then used to synthesize a vast array of high-quality problems and solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-evaluating-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Blind All-in-One Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-blind-all-in-one-image-restoration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Blind all-in-one image restoration models aim to recover a high-quality image from an input degraded with unknown distortions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-blind-all-in-one-image-restoration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimeMarker: A Versatile Video-LLM for Long and Short Video Understanding with Superior Temporal Localization Ability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timemarker-a-versatile-video-llm-for-long-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rapid development of large language models (LLMs) has significantly advanced multimodal large language models (LMMs), particularly in vision-language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timemarker-a-versatile-video-llm-for-long-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLS: Geometry-aware 3D Language Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gls-geometry-aware-3d-language-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, 3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) has achieved significant performance on indoor surface reconstruction and open-vocabulary segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gls-geometry-aware-3d-language-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Multispectral Object Detection: A Bag of Tricks and Comprehensive Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-multispectral-object-detection-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multispectral object detection, utilizing RGB and TIR (thermal infrared) modalities, is widely recognized as a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-multispectral-object-detection-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveying the space of descriptions of a composite system with machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surveying-the-space-of-descriptions-of-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By integrating machine learning into a fine-grained information theoretic analysis of composite random variables, our framework opens a new avenues for probing the structure of real-world complex systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surveying-the-space-of-descriptions-of-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoLLM Knows When to Speak: Enhancing Time-Sensitive Video Comprehension with Video-Text Duet Interaction Format</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videollm-knows-when-to-speak-enhancing-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We construct MMDuetIT, a video-text training dataset designed to adapt VideoLLMs to video-text duet interaction format.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videollm-knows-when-to-speak-enhancing-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Surface Priors for Editable Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-surface-priors-for-editable-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike other methods, our pipeline allows modifications applied to the extracted mesh to be propagated to the proxy representation, from which we recover the updated parameters of the Gaussians.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-surface-priors-for-editable-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RL for Mitigating Cascading Failures: Targeted Exploration via Sensitivity Factors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-for-mitigating-cascading-failures-targeted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Electricity grid's resiliency and climate change strongly impact one another due to an array of technical and policy-related decisions that impact both.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-for-mitigating-cascading-failures-targeted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Neural Networks Do Work with Pre-Defined Filters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-do-work-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel class of Convolutional Neural Networks called Pre-defined Filter Convolutional Neural Networks (PFCNNs), where all nxn convolution kernels with n>1 are pre-defined and constant during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-do-work-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuMapper: Towards Automatic Verification of Large-Scale POIs with Street Views at Baidu Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dumapper-towards-automatic-verification-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increased popularity of mobile devices, Web mapping services have become an indispensable tool in our daily lives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dumapper-towards-automatic-verification-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergence of Self-Identity in AI: A Mathematical Framework and Empirical Study with Generative Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-self-identity-in-ai-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a mathematical framework for defining and quantifying self-identity in artificial intelligence (AI) systems, addressing a critical gap in the theoretical foundations of artificial consciousness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-self-identity-in-ai-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeneQuery: A General QA-based Framework for Spatial Gene Expression Predictions from Histology Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genequery-a-general-qa-based-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gene expression profiling provides profound insights into molecular mechanisms, but its time-consuming and costly nature often presents significant challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genequery-a-general-qa-based-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isometry pursuit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isometry-pursuit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Isometry pursuit is a convex algorithm for identifying orthonormal column-submatrices of wide matrices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isometry-pursuit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaVLN: Towards Visual Language Navigation in Continuous Indoor Environments with Moving Humans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adavln-towards-visual-language-navigation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Language Navigation is a task that challenges robots to navigate in realistic environments based on natural language instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adavln-towards-visual-language-navigation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Representation Interaction Driven Image Quality Assessment with Restoration Assistance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-representation-interaction-driven-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we first introduce the DRI method to obtain degradation vectors and quality vectors of images, which separately model the degradation and quality information of low-quality images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-representation-interaction-driven-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergenet: A Digital Twin of Sequence Evolution for Scalable Emergence Risk Assessment of Animal Influenza A Strains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergenet-a-digital-twin-of-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite having triggered devastating pandemics in the past, our ability to quantitatively assess the emergence potential of individual strains of animal influenza viruses remains limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergenet-a-digital-twin-of-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Large Language Models for Expert Prior Elicitation in Predictive Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-large-language-models-for-expert-prior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study proposes using LLMs to elicit expert prior distributions for predictive models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-large-language-models-for-expert-prior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distractor-free Generalizable 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distractor-free-generalizable-3d-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve these objectives, DGGS introduces a scene-agnostic reference-based mask prediction and refinement methodology during training phase, coupled with a training view selection strategy, effectively improving distractor prediction accuracy and training stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distractor-free-generalizable-3d-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cWDM: Conditional Wavelet Diffusion Models for Cross-Modality 3D Medical Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cwdm-conditional-wavelet-diffusion-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper contributes to the "BraTS 2024 Brain MR Image Synthesis Challenge" and presents a conditional Wavelet Diffusion Model (cWDM) for directly solving a paired image-to-image translation task on high-resolution volumes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cwdm-conditional-wavelet-diffusion-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabulaX: Leveraging Large Language Models for Multi-Class Table Transformations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabulax-leveraging-large-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The integration of tabular data from diverse sources is often hindered by inconsistencies in formatting and representation, posing significant challenges for data analysts and personal digital assistants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabulax-leveraging-large-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTS-UNMixers: Multivariate Time Series Forecasting via Channel-Time Dual Unmixing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mts-unmixers-multivariate-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, MTS-UNMixers represent sequences over time as a mixture of multiple trends and cycles, with the time-correlated representation coefficients shared across both historical and future time periods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mts-unmixers-multivariate-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Word Pair-based Gaussian Sentence Similarity Algorithm For Bengali Extractive Text Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-word-pair-based-gaussian-sentence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we propose a novel Word pair-based Gaussian Sentence Similarity (WGSS) algorithm for calculating the semantic relation between two sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-word-pair-based-gaussian-sentence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can LLMs be Good Graph Judger for Knowledge Graph Construction?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llms-be-good-graph-judger-for-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We seek to utilize the capacity of LLMs to function as a graph judger, a capability superior to their role only as a predictor for KG construction problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llms-be-good-graph-judger-for-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReC-TTT: Contrastive Feature Reconstruction for Test-Time Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rec-ttt-contrastive-feature-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Test-Time Training (TTT) was proposed as an effective solution to this issue, which increases the generalization ability of trained models by adding an auxiliary task at train time and then using its loss at test time to adapt the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rec-ttt-contrastive-feature-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAD: Open-World Autonomous Driving Benchmark for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openad-open-world-autonomous-driving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we propose a vision-centric 3D open-world object detection baseline and further introduce an ensemble method by fusing general and specialized models to address the issue of lower precision in existing open-world methods for the OpenAD benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openad-open-world-autonomous-driving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT: Architectural Planning and Text-to-Blueprint Construction Using Large Language Models for Open-World Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apt-architectural-planning-and-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present APT, an advanced Large Language Model (LLM)-driven framework that enables autonomous agents to construct complex and creative structures within the Minecraft environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apt-architectural-planning-and-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omegance: A Single Parameter for Various Granularities in Diffusion-Based Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omegance-a-single-parameter-for-various</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a single parameter $\omega$, to effectively control granularity in diffusion-based synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omegance-a-single-parameter-for-various</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Box for Mask and Mask for Box: weak losses for multi-task partially supervised learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/box-for-mask-and-mask-for-box-weak-losses-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Making use of one task's information to train the other would be beneficial for multi-task partially supervised learning where each training example is annotated only for a single task, having the potential to expand training sets with different-task datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/box-for-mask-and-mask-for-box-weak-losses-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-MeshGraphNet: Scalable Multi-Scale Graph Neural Networks for Physics Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-meshgraphnet-scalable-multi-scale-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce X-MeshGraphNet, a scalable, multi-scale extension of MeshGraphNet designed to address these challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-meshgraphnet-scalable-multi-scale-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled Interpretable Representation for Efficient Long-term Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-interpretable-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing deep learning and linear models often suffer from excessive parameter complexity and lack intuitive interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-interpretable-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Explainable Treatment Policies with Clinician-Informed Representations: A Practical Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-explainable-treatment-policies-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our main contribution is to reveal the importance of clinical domain knowledge in developing state and action representations for effective, efficient, and interpretable targeting policies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-explainable-treatment-policies-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
