<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 09:17:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Infinity: Scaling Bitwise AutoRegressive Modeling for High-Resolution Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infinity-scaling-bitwise-autoregressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Infinity, a Bitwise Visual AutoRegressive Modeling capable of generating high-resolution, photorealistic images following language instruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infinity-scaling-bitwise-autoregressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransAdapter: Vision Transformer for Feature-Centric Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transadapter-vision-transformer-for-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised Domain Adaptation (UDA) aims to utilize labeled data from a source domain to solve tasks in an unlabeled target domain, often hindered by significant domain gaps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transadapter-vision-transformer-for-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Framework for Open-World Compositional Zero-shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-framework-for-open-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-World Compositional Zero-Shot Learning (OW-CZSL) addresses the challenge of recognizing novel compositions of known primitives and entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-framework-for-open-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDG2Seq: Periodic Dynamic Graph to Sequence Model for Traffic Flow Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdg2seq-periodic-dynamic-graph-to-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these findings, this paper proposes a Periodic Dynamic Graph to Sequence Model (PDG2Seq) for traffic flow prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdg2seq-periodic-dynamic-graph-to-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASIGN: An Anatomy-aware Spatial Imputation Graphic Network for 3D Spatial Transcriptomics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asign-an-anatomy-aware-spatial-imputation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Expanding ST to three-dimensional (3D) volumes is challenging due to the prohibitive costs; a 2D ST acquisition already costs over 50 times more than whole slide imaging (WSI), and a full 3D volume with 10 sections can be an order of magnitude more expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asign-an-anatomy-aware-spatial-imputation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alignment at Pre-training! Towards Native Alignment for Arabic LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignment-at-pre-training-towards-native</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The alignment of large language models (LLMs) is critical for developing effective and safe language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignment-at-pre-training-towards-native</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIMCaP: BIM-based AI-supported LiDAR-Camera Pose Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bimcap-bim-based-ai-supported-lidar-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces BIMCaP, a novel method to integrate mobile 3D sparse LiDAR data and camera measurements with pre-existing building information models (BIMs), enhancing fast and accurate indoor mapping with affordable sensors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bimcap-bim-based-ai-supported-lidar-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolve: Optimizing AI Systems by Tracking Response Evolution in Textual Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revolve-optimizing-ai-systems-by-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, relying solely on such feedback can be limited when the adjustments made in response to this feedback are either too small or fluctuate irregularly, potentially slowing down or even stalling the optimization process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revolve-optimizing-ai-systems-by-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Level Correlation Network For Few-Shot Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-correlation-network-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we argue that measure at such a level may not be effective enough to generalize from base to novel classes when using only a few images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-correlation-network-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A surprisal oracle for when every layer counts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-surprisal-oracle-for-when-every-layer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Active Curriculum Language Modeling (ACLM; Hong et al., 2023) is a learner directed approach to training a language model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-surprisal-oracle-for-when-every-layer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIM: Adaptive Inference of Multi-Modal LLMs via Token Merging and Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aim-adaptive-inference-of-multi-modal-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a minimalist design, our method can be applied to both video and image LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aim-adaptive-inference-of-multi-modal-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sifting through the haystack -- efficiently finding rare animal behaviors in large-scale datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sifting-through-the-haystack-efficiently</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method consistently outperformed traditional random sampling, offering an average improvement of 70% in performance and creating datasets even when the behavior of interest was only 0. 02% of the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sifting-through-the-haystack-efficiently</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Stitch in Time Saves Nine: Small VLM is a Precise Guidance for Accelerating Large VLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stitch-in-time-saves-nine-small-vlm-is-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language models (VLMs) have shown remarkable success across various multi-modal tasks, yet large VLMs encounter significant efficiency challenges due to processing numerous visual tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stitch-in-time-saves-nine-small-vlm-is-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PrefixKV: Adaptive Prefix KV Cache is What Vision Instruction-Following Models Need for Efficient Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prefixkv-adaptive-prefix-kv-cache-is-what</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With an adaptive layer-wise KV retention recipe based on binary search, the maximum contextual information can thus be preserved in each layer, facilitating the generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prefixkv-adaptive-prefix-kv-cache-is-what</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intuitive Axial Augmentation Using Polar-Sine-Based Piecewise Distortion for Medical Slice-Wise Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intuitive-axial-augmentation-using-polar-sine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most data-driven models for medical image analysis rely on universal augmentations to improve performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intuitive-axial-augmentation-using-polar-sine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LuxEmbedder: A Cross-Lingual Approach to Enhanced Luxembourgish Sentence Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/luxembedder-a-cross-lingual-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sentence embedding models play a key role in various Natural Language Processing tasks, such as in Topic Modeling, Document Clustering and Recommendation Systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/luxembedder-a-cross-lingual-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PatchDPO: Patch-level DPO for Finetuning-free Personalized Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchdpo-patch-level-dpo-for-finetuning-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, this work proposes PatchDPO that estimates the quality of image patches within each generated image and accordingly trains the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchdpo-patch-level-dpo-for-finetuning-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency-Guided Diffusion Model with Perturbation Training for Skeleton-Based Video Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-guided-diffusion-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a novel frequency-guided diffusion model with perturbation training, which enhances the model robustness by perturbation training and emphasizes the principal motion components guided by motion frequencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-guided-diffusion-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBP: Post-training Backdoor Purification for Malware Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pbp-post-training-backdoor-purification-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the rise of machine learning (ML) in cybersecurity has brought new challenges, including the increasing threat of backdoor poisoning attacks on ML malware classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pbp-post-training-backdoor-purification-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Semantic Association Rules from Internet of Things Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-semantic-association-rules-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel ARM pipeline for IoT data that utilizes both dynamic sensor data and static IoT system metadata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-semantic-association-rules-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Linguistic Diversity of Large Language Models with Possibility Exploration Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-linguistic-diversity-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although several fine-tuning and prompting techniques have been suggested to tackle the issue, they are often tailored to specific tasks or come with a substantial increase in computational cost and latency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-linguistic-diversity-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Multi-bit Text Watermark with LLM-based Paraphrasers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-multi-bit-text-watermark-with-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To embed our multi-bit watermark, we use two paraphrasers alternatively to encode the pre-defined binary code at the sentence level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-multi-bit-text-watermark-with-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mapping using Transformers for Volumes -- Network for Super-Resolution with Long-Range Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-using-transformers-for-volumes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This advantage is especially pronounced for images that are larger than what is seen in popularly used 3D datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-using-transformers-for-volumes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freshness and Informativity Weighted Cognitive Extent and Its Correlation with Cumulative Citation Count</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freshness-and-informativity-weighted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we revisit cognitive extent, originally defined as the number of unique phrases in a quota.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freshness-and-informativity-weighted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-trained Multiple Latent Variable Generative Models are good defenders against Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-trained-multiple-latent-variable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Attackers can deliberately perturb classifiers' input with subtle noise, altering final predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-trained-multiple-latent-variable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Relationship of EV Charging Station on the Uptake of Electric Vehicles -- Implication of the NEVI Formula Program</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-relationship-of-ev-charging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve the federal goal to make half of all new vehicles sold in the U. S. in 2030 zero-emissions vehicles, the U. S. Department of Transportation's (DOT) Federal Highway Administration (FHWA) has employed the National Electric Vehicle Infrastructure (NEVI) Formula Program, which aims to promote an interconnected network of publicly accessible electric vehicle (EV) charging stations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-relationship-of-ev-charging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling Diffusion Models to Efficient 3D LiDAR Scene Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-diffusion-models-to-efficient-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve completion quality, we also introduce a novel $\textbf{Structural Loss}$, which encourages the distilled model to capture the geometric structure of the 3D LiDAR scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-diffusion-models-to-efficient-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stain-aware Domain Alignment for Imbalance Blood Cell Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stain-aware-domain-alignment-for-imbalance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In real-world scenarios, blood cell image datasets often present the issues of domain shift and data imbalance, posing challenges for accurate blood cell identification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stain-aware-domain-alignment-for-imbalance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weighted-Reward Preference Optimization for Implicit Model Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-reward-preference-optimization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address distributional deviations between the source and target LLMs, WRPO introduces a progressive adaptation strategy that gradually shifts reliance on preferred examples from the target LLM to the source LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-reward-preference-optimization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERD: Geometric event response data generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gerd-geometric-event-response-data-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event-based vision sensors are appealing because of their time resolution, higher dynamic range, and low-power consumption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gerd-geometric-event-response-data-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Composed Image Retrieval for Training-Free Domain Conversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composed-image-retrieval-for-training-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work addresses composed image retrieval in the context of domain conversion, where the content of a query image is retrieved in the domain specified by the query text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composed-image-retrieval-for-training-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tight PAC-Bayesian Risk Certificates for Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tight-pac-bayesian-risk-certificates-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The resulting bounds for contrastive loss and downstream prediction are much tighter than those of previous risk certificates, as demonstrated by experiments on CIFAR-10.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tight-pac-bayesian-risk-certificates-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaussian Processes for Probabilistic Estimates of Earthquake Ground Shaking: A 1-D Proof-of-Concept</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-processes-for-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This proof-of-concept illustrates the importance of probabilistic methods for physics-based seismic hazard analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-processes-for-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing Neural Network Verifiers: A Soundness Benchmark with Hidden Counterexamples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testing-neural-network-verifiers-a-soundness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, many neural network (NN) verifiers have been developed to formally verify certain properties of neural networks such as robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testing-neural-network-verifiers-a-soundness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Generative AI into Art Therapy: A Technical Showcase</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-generative-ai-into-art-therapy-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the integration of generative AI into the field of art therapy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-generative-ai-into-art-therapy-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TASR: Timestep-Aware Diffusion Model for Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tasr-timestep-aware-diffusion-model-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method enhances the transmission of LR information in the early stages of diffusion to guarantee image fidelity and stimulates the generation ability of the SD model itself more in the later stages to enhance the detail of generated images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tasr-timestep-aware-diffusion-model-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLAIR: VLM with Fine-grained Language-informed Image Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flair-vlm-with-fine-grained-language-informed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CLIP has shown impressive results in aligning images and texts at scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flair-vlm-with-fine-grained-language-informed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained Behavior Simulation with Role-Playing Large Language Model on Social Media</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-behavior-simulation-with-role</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce \textbf{FineRob}, a novel fine-grained behavior simulation dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-behavior-simulation-with-role</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFSR: Improving ISR Diffusion Models via Reward Feedback Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rfsr-improving-isr-diffusion-models-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We posit that introducing reward feedback learning to finetune the existing models can further improve the quality of the generated images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rfsr-improving-isr-diffusion-models-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pay Attention to the Robustness of Chinese Minority Language Models! Syllable-level Textual Adversarial Attack on Tibetan Script</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pay-attention-to-the-robustness-of-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method is also used to evaluate the robustness of NLP models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pay-attention-to-the-robustness-of-chinese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASANet: Asymmetric Semantic Aligning Network for RGB and SAR image land cover classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asanet-asymmetric-semantic-aligning-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing studies on cross-modal fusion assume that consistent feature information is necessary between the two modalities, and as a result, they construct networks without adequately addressing the unique characteristics of each modality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asanet-asymmetric-semantic-aligning-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Learning via Classifier Impact and Greedy Selection for Interactive Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-via-classifier-impact-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we assess our performance for the interactive content-based image retrieval task on several benchmarks and demonstrate its superiority over existing approaches and common baselines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-via-classifier-impact-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoCo: Low-Contrast-Enhanced Contrastive Learning for Semi-Supervised Endoscopic Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loco-low-contrast-enhanced-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The segmentation of endoscopic images plays a vital role in computer-aided diagnosis and treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loco-low-contrast-enhanced-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Weisfeiler-Lehman Kernels to Subgraphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-weisfeiler-lehman-kernels-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subgraph representation learning has been effective in solving various real-world problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-weisfeiler-lehman-kernels-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaussian Object Carver: Object-Compositional Gaussian Splatting with surfaces completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-object-carver-object-compositional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D scene reconstruction is a foundational problem in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-object-carver-object-compositional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Simplifying Large-Scale Spatial Vectors: Fast, Memory-Efficient, and Cost-Predictable k-means</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-simplifying-large-scale-spatial-vectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments show that when simplifying datasets with scale such as $10^6$, Dask-means uses less than $30$MB of memory, achieves over $168$ times speedup compared to the widely-used Lloyd's algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-simplifying-large-scale-spatial-vectors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trajectory-based Road Autolabeling with Lidar-Camera Fusion in Winter Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajectory-based-road-autolabeling-with-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust road segmentation in all road conditions is required for safe autonomous driving and advanced driver assistance systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajectory-based-road-autolabeling-with-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agri-LLaVA: Knowledge-Infused Large Multimodal Assistant on Agricultural Pests and Diseases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agri-llava-knowledge-infused-large-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By open-sourcing our dataset and model, we aim to promote research and development in LMMs within the agricultural domain and make significant contributions to tackle the challenges of agricultural pests and diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agri-llava-knowledge-infused-large-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimuScope: Realistic Endoscopic Synthetic Dataset Generation through Surgical Simulation and Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simuscope-realistic-endoscopic-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This simulator generates a wide set of annotations that surpass those available in public synthetic datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simuscope-realistic-endoscopic-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShadowHack: Hacking Shadows via Luminance-Color Divide and Conquer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadowhack-hacking-shadows-via-luminance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Shadows introduce challenges such as reduced brightness, texture deterioration, and color distortion in images, complicating a holistic solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadowhack-hacking-shadows-via-luminance</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
