<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 21:06:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>AdaNPC: Exploring Non-Parametric Classifier for Test-Time Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adanpc-exploring-non-parametric-classifier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, when the adaptation target is a series of domains, the adaptation accuracy of AdaNPC is 50% higher than advanced TTA methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adanpc-exploring-non-parametric-classifier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centralized control for multi-agent RL in a complex Real-Time-Strategy game</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centralized-control-for-multi-agent-rl-in-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-agent Reinforcement learning (MARL) studies the behaviour of multiple learning agents that coexist in a shared environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centralized-control-for-multi-agent-rl-in-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnable Pillar-based Re-ranking for Image-Text Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-pillar-based-re-ranking-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image-text retrieval aims to bridge the modality gap and retrieve cross-modal content based on semantic similarities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-pillar-based-re-ranking-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proximal Curriculum for Reinforcement Learning Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proximal-curriculum-for-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of curriculum design for reinforcement learning (RL) agents in contextual multi-task settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proximal-curriculum-for-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Strong and Reproducible Object Detector with Only Public Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-strong-and-reproducible-object-detector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents Focal-Stable-DINO, a strong and reproducible object detection model which achieves 64. 6 AP on COCO val2017 and 64. 8 AP on COCO test-dev using only 700M parameters without any test time augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-strong-and-reproducible-object-detector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Answering Questions by Meta-Reasoning over Multiple Chains of Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/answering-questions-by-meta-reasoning-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern systems for multi-hop question answering (QA) typically break questions into a sequence of reasoning steps, termed chain-of-thought (CoT), before arriving at a final answer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/answering-questions-by-meta-reasoning-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flickr-PAD: New Face High-Resolution Presentation Attack Detection Database</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flickr-pad-new-face-high-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This will help researchers to compare new approaches to existing algorithms on a wider database.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flickr-pad-new-face-high-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explain like I am BM25: Interpreting a Dense Model's Ranked-List with a Sparse Approximation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explain-like-i-am-bm25-interpreting-a-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural retrieval models (NRMs) have been shown to outperform their statistical counterparts owing to their ability to capture semantic meaning via dense document representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explain-like-i-am-bm25-interpreting-a-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differential Privacy via Distributionally Robust Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-privacy-via-distributionally</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the problem affords a strong dual, and we exploit this duality to develop converging hierarchies of finite-dimensional upper and lower bounding problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-privacy-via-distributionally</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CitePrompt: Using Prompts to Identify Citation Intent in Scientific Papers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citeprompt-using-prompts-to-identify-citation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the ACL-ARC dataset, we report a 53. 86% F1 score for the zero-shot setting, which improves to 63. 61% and 66. 99% for the 5-shot and 10-shot settings, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citeprompt-using-prompts-to-identify-citation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly-Supervised Temporal Action Localization with Bidirectional Semantic Consistency Constraint</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-temporal-action-7</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed Bi-SCC firstly adopts a temporal context augmentation to generate an augmented video that breaks the correlation between positive actions and their co-scene actions in the inter-video; Then, a semantic consistency constraint (SCC) is used to enforce the predictions of the original video and augmented video to be consistent, hence suppressing the co-scene actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-temporal-action-7</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DQS3D: Densely-matched Quantization-aware Semi-supervised 3D Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dqs3d-densely-matched-quantization-aware-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While this paradigm is natural for image-level or pixel-level prediction, adapting it to the detection problem is challenged by the issue of proposal matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dqs3d-densely-matched-quantization-aware-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intent Induction from Conversations for Task-Oriented Dialogue Track at DSTC 11</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intent-induction-from-conversations-for-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With increasing demand for and adoption of virtual assistants, recent work has investigated ways to accelerate bot schema design through the automatic induction of intents or the induction of slots and dialogue states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intent-induction-from-conversations-for-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MG-ShopDial: A Multi-Goal Conversational Dataset for e-Commerce</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mg-shopdial-a-multi-goal-conversational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce MG-ShopDial: a dataset of conversations mixing different goals in the domain of e-commerce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mg-shopdial-a-multi-goal-conversational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parallel Spiking Neurons with High Efficiency and Long-term Dependencies Learning Ability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-spiking-neurons-with-high-efficiency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vanilla spiking neurons in Spiking Neural Networks (SNNs) use charge-fire-reset neuronal dynamics, which can only be simulated in serial and can hardly learn long-time dependencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-spiking-neurons-with-high-efficiency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixNeRF: Memory Efficient NeRF with Feature Mixed-up Hash Table</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixnerf-memory-efficient-nerf-with-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural radiance field (NeRF) has shown remarkable performance in generating photo-realistic novel views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixnerf-memory-efficient-nerf-with-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDSC-UNet: Dual Skip Connection ViT-based U-shaped Model for Building Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdsc-unet-dual-skip-connection-vit-based-u</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, unlike the previous single-skip-connection structure of U-shaped methods, we build a novel dual skip connection structure inside the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdsc-unet-dual-skip-connection-vit-based-u</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Massive Multitask Chinese Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-massive-multitask-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This test encompasses four major domains, including medicine, law, psychology, and education, with 15 subtasks in medicine and 8 subtasks in education.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-massive-multitask-chinese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(Local) Differential Privacy has NO Disparate Impact on Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-differential-privacy-has-no-disparate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, as the collection of multiple sensitive information becomes more prevalent across various industries, collecting a single sensitive attribute under LDP may not be sufficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-differential-privacy-has-no-disparate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class Attention Transfer Based Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-attention-transfer-based-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous knowledge distillation methods have shown their impressive performance on model compression tasks, however, it is hard to explain how the knowledge they transferred helps to improve the performance of the student network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-attention-transfer-based-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morphological Classification of Extragalactic Radio Sources Using Gradient Boosting Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphological-classification-of-extragalactic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most recent contributions in the field of morphological classification of extragalactic radio sources have proposed classifiers based on convolutional neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphological-classification-of-extragalactic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CompletionFormer: Depth Completion with Convolutions and Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/completionformer-depth-completion-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This hybrid architecture naturally benefits both the local connectivity of convolutions and the global context of the Transformer in one single model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/completionformer-depth-completion-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoseVocab: Learning Joint-structured Pose Embeddings for Human Avatar Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posevocab-learning-joint-structured-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Creating pose-driven human avatars is about modeling the mapping from the low-frequency driving pose to high-frequency dynamic human appearances, so an effective pose encoding method that can encode high-fidelity human details is essential to human avatar modeling. To this end, we present PoseVocab, a novel pose encoding method that encourages the network to discover the optimal pose embeddings for learning the dynamic human appearance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posevocab-learning-joint-structured-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMUPoser: Full-Body Pose Estimation using IMUs in Phones, Watches, and Earbuds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imuposer-full-body-pose-estimation-using-imus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tracking body pose on-the-go could have powerful uses in fitness, mobile gaming, context-aware virtual assistants, and rehabilitation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imuposer-full-body-pose-estimation-using-imus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Traversals in Generative Models as Potential Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-traversals-in-generative-models-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we instead propose to model latent structures with a learned dynamic potential landscape, thereby performing latent traversals as the flow of samples down the landscape's gradient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-traversals-in-generative-models-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phylo2Vec: a vector representation for binary trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phylo2vec-a-vector-representation-for-binary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, these heuristics often lack a systematic means of uniformly sampling random trees or effectively exploring a tree space that grows factorially, which are crucial to optimisation problems such as machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phylo2vec-a-vector-representation-for-binary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuETT: Dual Event Time Transformer for Electronic Health Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/duett-dual-event-time-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Electronic health records (EHRs) recorded in hospital settings typically contain a wide range of numeric time series data that is characterized by high sparsity and irregular observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/duett-dual-event-time-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AudioGPT: Understanding and Generating Speech, Music, Sound, and Talking Head</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audiogpt-understanding-and-generating-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a multi-modal AI system named AudioGPT, which complements LLMs (i. e., ChatGPT) with 1) foundation models to process complex audio information and solve numerous understanding and generation tasks; and 2) the input/output interface (ASR, TTS) to support spoken dialogue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audiogpt-understanding-and-generating-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-Informed Representation Learning for Emergent Organization in Complex Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-representation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the local causal states capture vortices and their power-law decay behavior in two-dimensional turbulence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-representation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constructing Tree-based Index for Efficient and Effective Dense Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-tree-based-index-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, while ANN can improve the efficiency of DR models, it usually comes with a significant price on retrieval performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-tree-based-index-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Challenges of Using Black-Box APIs for Toxicity Evaluation in Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-challenges-of-using-black-box-apis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate the implications of these changes on the reproducibility of findings that compare the relative merits of models and methods that aim to curb toxicity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-challenges-of-using-black-box-apis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KInITVeraAI at SemEval-2023 Task 3: Simple yet Powerful Multilingual Fine-Tuning for Persuasion Techniques Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kinitveraai-at-semeval-2023-task-3-simple-yet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the best-performing solution to the SemEval 2023 Task 3 on the subtask 3 dedicated to persuasion techniques detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kinitveraai-at-semeval-2023-task-3-simple-yet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking ChatGPT-4 on ACR Radiation Oncology In-Training Exam (TXIT): Potentials and Challenges for AI-Assisted Medical Education and Decision Making in Radiation Oncology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-chatgpt-4-on-acr-radiation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While ChatGPT-4 is not yet suitable for clinical decision making in radiation oncology, it has the potential to assist in medical education for the general public and cancer patients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-chatgpt-4-on-acr-radiation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixPro: Data Augmentation with MaskMix and Progressive Attention Labeling for Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixpro-data-augmentation-with-maskmix-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TransMix uses unreliable attention maps to compute mixed attention labels that can affect the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixpro-data-augmentation-with-maskmix-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Track Anything: Segment Anything Meets Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/track-anything-segment-anything-meets-videos</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, in this report, we propose Track Anything Model (TAM), which achieves high-performance interactive tracking and segmentation in videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/track-anything-segment-anything-meets-videos</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glocal Energy-based Learning for Few-Shot Open-Set Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glocal-energy-based-learning-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few-shot open-set recognition (FSOR) is a challenging task of great practical value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glocal-energy-based-learning-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SocialDial: A Benchmark for Socially-Aware Dialogue Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/socialdial-a-benchmark-for-socially-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, SocialDial is the first socially-aware dialogue dataset that covers multiple social factors and has fine-grained labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/socialdial-a-benchmark-for-socially-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicit Correspondence Matching for Generalizable Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-correspondence-matching-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key to our approach lies in the explicitly modeled correspondence matching information, so as to provide the geometry prior to the prediction of NeRF color and density for volume rendering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-correspondence-matching-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renate: A Library for Real-World Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/renate-a-library-for-real-world-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discuss requirements for the use of continual learning algorithms in practice, from which we derive design principles for Renate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/renate-a-library-for-real-world-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Context Constraints of LLMs: Enhancing Context Efficiency of LLMs with Self-Information-Based Content Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-context-constraints-of-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have received significant attention by achieving remarkable performance across various tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-context-constraints-of-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact-Oriented Contextual Scholar Profiling using Self-Citation Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-oriented-contextual-scholar-profiling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiment outcomes show that the F1 score of best GF profile significantly outperforms alternative methods of impact indicators and bibliometric networks in all the 6 computer science fields considered.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-oriented-contextual-scholar-profiling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical State Abstraction Based on Structural Information Principles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-state-abstraction-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State abstraction optimizes decision-making by ignoring irrelevant environmental information in reinforcement learning with rich observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-state-abstraction-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segment Anything in Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything-in-medical-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comprehensive experiments on 21 3D segmentation tasks and 9 2D segmentation tasks demonstrate that MedSAM outperforms the default SAM model with an average Dice Similarity Coefficient (DSC) of 22. 5% and 17. 6% on 3D and 2D segmentation tasks, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything-in-medical-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grad-PU: Arbitrary-Scale Point Cloud Upsampling via Gradient Descent with Learned Distance Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grad-pu-arbitrary-scale-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing point cloud upsampling methods have roughly three steps: feature extraction, feature expansion and 3D coordinate prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grad-pu-arbitrary-scale-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive-saturated RNN: Remember more with less instability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-saturated-rnn-remember-more-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Orthogonal parameterization is a compelling solution to the vanishing gradient problem (VGP) in recurrent neural networks (RNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-saturated-rnn-remember-more-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-capacity and Flexible Video Steganography via Invertible Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-capacity-and-flexible-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For large-capacity, we present a reversible pipeline to perform multiple videos hiding and recovering through a single invertible neural network (INN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-capacity-and-flexible-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stubborn: An Environment for Evaluating Stubbornness between Agents with Aligned Incentives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stubborn-an-environment-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our preliminary results, the agents learn to use their partner's stubbornness as a signal for improving the choices that they make in the environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stubborn-an-environment-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Directed Acyclic Transformer Pre-training for High-quality Non-autoregressive Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/directed-acyclic-transformer-pre-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Non-AutoRegressive (NAR) text generation models have drawn much attention because of their significantly faster decoding speed and good generation quality in machine translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/directed-acyclic-transformer-pre-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rank Flow Embedding for Unsupervised and Semi-Supervised Manifold Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rank-flow-embedding-for-unsupervised-and-semi-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High effective results demonstrate the effectiveness of the proposed method on different tasks: unsupervised image retrieval, semi-supervised classification, and person Re-ID.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rank-flow-embedding-for-unsupervised-and-semi-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WizardLM: Empowering Large Language Models to Follow Complex Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wizardlm-empowering-large-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By analyzing the human evaluation results of the high complexity part, we demonstrate that outputs from our WizardLM model are preferred to outputs from OpenAI ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wizardlm-empowering-large-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
