<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 21:09:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Imitrob: Imitation Learning Dataset for Training and Evaluating 6D Object Pose Estimators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imitrob-imitation-learning-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a dataset for training and evaluating methods for 6D pose estimation of hand-held tools in task demonstrations captured by a standard RGB camera.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imitrob-imitation-learning-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serialized Interacting Mixed Membership Stochastic Block Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/serialized-interacting-mixed-membership</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show that these models are all special cases of a single global framework: the Serialized Interacting Mixed membership Stochastic Block Model (SIMSBM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/serialized-interacting-mixed-membership</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IoT Data Analytics in Dynamic Environments: From An Automated Machine Learning Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iot-data-analytics-in-dynamic-environments</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine Learning (ML) approaches have shown their capacity for IoT data analytics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iot-data-analytics-in-dynamic-environments</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ImDrug: A Benchmark for Deep Imbalanced Learning in AI-aided Drug Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imdrug-a-benchmark-for-deep-imbalanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The last decade has witnessed a prosperous development of computational methods and dataset curation for AI-aided drug discovery (AIDD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imdrug-a-benchmark-for-deep-imbalanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-turn Machine Reading Comprehension Framework with Rethink Mechanism for Emotion-Cause Pair Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-turn-machine-reading-comprehension</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our framework can model complicated relations between emotions and causes while avoiding generating the pairing matrix (the leading cause of the label sparsity problem).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-turn-machine-reading-comprehension</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M$^2$DQN: A Robust Method for Accelerating Deep Q-learning Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-2-dqn-a-robust-method-for-accelerating-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Q-learning Network (DQN) is a successful way which combines reinforcement learning with deep neural networks and leads to a widespread application of reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-2-dqn-a-robust-method-for-accelerating-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causes of Catastrophic Forgetting in Class-Incremental Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causes-of-catastrophic-forgetting-in-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, in a set of experiments and representational analyses, we demonstrate that the semantic shift of the background class and a bias towards new classes are the major causes of forgetting in CiSS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causes-of-catastrophic-forgetting-in-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhance the Visual Representation via Discrete Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhance-the-visual-representation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For borrowing the advantage from NLP-style AT, we propose Discrete Adversarial Training (DAT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhance-the-visual-representation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Tumor Segmentation via False Positive Reduction Network for Whole-Body Multi-Modal PET/CT Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-tumor-segmentation-via-false</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce a false positive reduction network to overcome this limitation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-tumor-segmentation-via-false</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PINEAPPLE: Personifying INanimate Entities by Acquiring Parallel Personification data for Learning Enhanced generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pineapple-personifying-inanimate-entities-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose PINEAPPLE: Personifying INanimate Entities by Acquiring Parallel Personification data for Learning Enhanced generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pineapple-personifying-inanimate-entities-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Deep Moving-camera Background Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-moving-camera-background-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, existing MCBMs usually model the background either on the domain of a typically-large panoramic image or in an online fashion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-moving-camera-background-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaMask: Revisiting Dimensional Confounder for Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metamask-revisiting-dimensional-confounder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a successful approach to self-supervised learning, contrastive learning aims to learn invariant information shared among distortions of the input sample.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metamask-revisiting-dimensional-confounder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D VSG: Long-term Semantic Scene Change Prediction through 3D Variable Scene Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-vsg-long-term-semantic-scene-change</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we formalize the task of semantic scene variability estimation and identify three main varieties of semantic scene change: changes in the position of an object, its semantic state, or the composition of a scene as a whole.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-vsg-long-term-semantic-scene-change</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Multiple Views via Implicitly Preserving Global Consistency and Local Complementarity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-multiple-views-via-implicitly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a methodology, specifically consistency and complementarity network (CoCoNet), which avails of strict global inter-view consistency and local cross-view complementarity preserving regularization to comprehensively learn representations from multiple views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-multiple-views-via-implicitly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATraj: A Graph- and Attention-based Multi-Agent Trajectory Prediction Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gatraj-a-graph-and-attention-based-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model achieves performance on par with the state-of-the-art models at a much higher prediction speed tested on multiple open datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gatraj-a-graph-and-attention-based-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimation of Optical Aberrations in 3D Microscopic Bioimages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimation-of-optical-aberrations-in-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, our method incorporates object-specific information into the simulated images used for training the network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimation-of-optical-aberrations-in-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whole-Body Lesion Segmentation in 18F-FDG PET/CT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whole-body-lesion-segmentation-in-18f-fdg-pet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There has been growing research interest in using deep learning based method to achieve fully automated segmentation of lesion in Positron emission tomography computed tomography(PET CT) scans for the prognosis of various cancers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whole-body-lesion-segmentation-in-18f-fdg-pet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiscale Adaptive Scheduling and Path-Planning for Power-Constrained UAV-Relays via SMDPs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiscale-adaptive-scheduling-and-path</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe the orchestration of a decentralized swarm of rotary-wing UAV-relays, augmenting the coverage and service capabilities of a terrestrial base station.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiscale-adaptive-scheduling-and-path</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Benchmark for COVID-19 Predictive Modeling Using Electronic Health Records in Intensive Care: Choosing the Best Model for COVID-19 Prognosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-covid-19</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many deep learning models have been proposed to conduct clinical predictive tasks such as mortality prediction for COVID-19 patients in intensive care units using Electronic Health Record (EHR) data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-covid-19</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FairGBM: Gradient Boosting with Fairness Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairgbm-gradient-boosting-with-fairness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine Learning (ML) algorithms based on gradient boosted decision trees (GBDT) are still favored on many tabular data tasks across various mission critical applications, from healthcare to finance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairgbm-gradient-boosting-with-fairness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation via Progressive Patch Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-semantic-segmentation-via-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA["Progressive Patch Learning" further extends the feature destruction and patch learning to multi-level granularities in a progressive manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-semantic-segmentation-via-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selecting Stickers in Open-Domain Dialogue through Multitask Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-stickers-in-open-domain-dialogue-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increasing popularity of online chatting, stickers are becoming important in our online communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-stickers-in-open-domain-dialogue-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Mosquito is Worth 16x16 Larvae: Evaluation of Deep Learning Architectures for Mosquito Larvae Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mosquito-is-worth-16x16-larvae-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research introduces the application of the Vision Transformer (ViT) in a comparative study to improve image classification on Aedes and Culex larvae.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mosquito-is-worth-16x16-larvae-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game-theoretic Objective Space Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/game-theoretic-objective-space-planning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous Racing awards agents that react to opponents' behaviors with agile maneuvers towards progressing along the track while penalizing both over-aggressive and over-conservative agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/game-theoretic-objective-space-planning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expansion and Shrinkage of Localization for Weakly-Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expansion-and-shrinkage-of-localization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle with this issue, this paper proposes an Expansion and Shrinkage scheme based on the offset learning in the deformable convolution, to sequentially improve the recall and precision of the located object in the two respective stages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expansion-and-shrinkage-of-localization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SRFeat: Learning Locally Accurate and Globally Consistent Non-Rigid Shape Correspondence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srfeat-learning-locally-accurate-and-globally</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a novel learning-based framework that combines the local accuracy of contrastive learning with the global consistency of geometric approaches, for robust non-rigid matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srfeat-learning-locally-accurate-and-globally</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Learning with an Information Maximization Criterion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-with-an-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, we argue that a straightforward application of information maximization among alternative latent representations of the same input naturally solves the collapse problem and achieves competitive empirical results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-with-an-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omni-Dimensional Dynamic Convolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omni-dimensional-dynamic-convolution-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning a single static convolutional kernel in each convolutional layer is the common training paradigm of modern Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omni-dimensional-dynamic-convolution-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing Variance in Temporal-Difference Value Estimation via Ensemble of Deep Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-variance-in-temporal-difference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On a set of 26 benchmark Atari environments, MeanQ outperforms all tested baselines, including the best available baseline, SUNRISE, at 100K interaction steps in 16/26 environments, and by 68% on average.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-variance-in-temporal-difference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less is Better: Recovering Intended-Feature Subspace to Robustify NLU Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-better-recovering-intended-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When delving into a lower manifold to remove redundancies, RISK reveals that an extremely low-dimensional subspace with intended features can robustly represent the highly biased dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-better-recovering-intended-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deliberated Domain Bridging for Domain Adaptive Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deliberated-domain-bridging-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we resort to data mixing to establish a deliberated domain bridging (DDB) for DASS, through which the joint distributions of source and target domains are aligned and interacted with each in the intermediate space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deliberated-domain-bridging-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Window Attention Based Transformer Architecture for Brain Tumor Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-window-attention-based-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As intensities of MRI volumes are inconsistent across institutes, it is essential to extract universal features of multi-modal MRIs to precisely segment brain tumors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-window-attention-based-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeqOT: A Spatial-Temporal Transformer Network for Place Recognition Using Sequential LiDAR Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seqot-a-spatial-temporal-transformer-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It uses multi-scale transformers to generate a global descriptor for each sequence of LiDAR range images in an end-to-end fashion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seqot-a-spatial-temporal-transformer-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Robustness of Graph Neural Diffusion to Topology Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-robustness-of-graph-neural-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore the robustness properties of graph neural PDEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-robustness-of-graph-neural-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skill Extraction from Job Postings using Weak Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skill-extraction-from-job-postings-using-weak</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aggregated data obtained from job postings provide powerful insights into labor market demands, and emerging skills, and aid job matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skill-extraction-from-job-postings-using-weak</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Pair Potentials using Differentiable Simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-pair-potentials-using-differentiable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that our methods can be used to simultaneously fit potentials for simulations at different compositions and temperatures to improve the transferability of the learned potentials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-pair-potentials-using-differentiable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Shot Synthesis of Images and Segmentation Masks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-synthesis-of-images-and-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, inspired by the recent architectural developments of single-image GANs, we introduce our OSMIS model which enables the synthesis of segmentation masks that are precisely aligned to the generated images in the one-shot regime.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-synthesis-of-images-and-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CommunityLM: Probing Partisan Worldviews from Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communitylm-probing-partisan-worldviews-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As political attitudes have diverged ideologically in the United States, political speech has diverged lingusitically.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communitylm-probing-partisan-worldviews-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Stochastic Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-stochastic-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These two stochastic controllers thus are complementary in applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-stochastic-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEQGAN: Learning the Loss Function for PINNs with Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deqgan-learning-the-loss-function-for-pinns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Solutions to differential equations are of significant scientific and engineering relevance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deqgan-learning-the-loss-function-for-pinns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIZZA: A Powerful Image-only Zero-Shot Zero-CAD Approach to 6 DoF Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pizza-a-powerful-image-only-zero-shot-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results on challenging datasets are on par with previous works that require much more information (training images of the target objects, 3D models, and/or depth data).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pizza-a-powerful-image-only-zero-shot-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4DenoiseNet: Adverse Weather Denoising from Adjacent Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4denoisenet-adverse-weather-denoising-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reliable point cloud data is essential for perception tasks \textit{e. g.} in robotics and autonomous driving applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4denoisenet-adverse-weather-denoising-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold-Start Data Selection for Few-shot Language Model Fine-tuning: A Prompt-Based Uncertainty Propagation Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cold-start-data-selection-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose PATRON, a new method that uses prompt-based uncertainty estimation for data selection for pre-trained language model fine-tuning under cold-start scenarios, i. e., no initial labeled data are available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cold-start-data-selection-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIPping Privacy: Identity Inference Attacks on Multi-Modal Machine Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clipping-privacy-identity-inference-attacks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As deep learning is now used in many real-world applications, research has focused increasingly on the privacy of deep learning models and how to prevent attackers from obtaining sensitive information about the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clipping-privacy-identity-inference-attacks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constrained Update Projection Approach to Safe Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-update-projection-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to previous safe RL methods, CUP enjoys the benefits of 1) CUP generalizes the surrogate functions to generalized advantage estimator (GAE), leading to strong empirical performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-update-projection-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Is Flat: A Seq2Seq Generative Framework for Various Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-is-flat-a-seq2seq-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To remedy the KG structure information loss from the "flat" text, we further improve the input representations of entities and relations, and the inference algorithm in KG-S2S.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-is-flat-a-seq2seq-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AssembleRL: Learning to Assemble Furniture from Their Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assemblerl-learning-to-assemble-furniture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise of simulation environments has enabled learning-based approaches for assembly planning, which is otherwise a labor-intensive and daunting task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assemblerl-learning-to-assemble-furniture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modal Masked Autoencoders for Medical Vision-and-Language Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-masked-autoencoders-for-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, we conduct further analysis to better verify the effectiveness of different components of our approach and various settings of pre-training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-masked-autoencoders-for-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iFlipper: Label Flipping for Individual Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iflipper-label-flipping-for-individual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then propose an approximate linear programming algorithm and provide theoretical guarantees on how close its result is to the optimal solution in terms of the number of label flips.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iflipper-label-flipping-for-individual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward an understanding of the properties of neural network approaches for supernovae light curve approximation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-an-understanding-of-the-properties-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The modern time-domain photometric surveys collect a lot of observations of various astronomical objects, and the coming era of large-scale surveys will provide even more information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-an-understanding-of-the-properties-of</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
