<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 21:08:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>JoyGen: Audio-Driven 3D Depth-Aware Talking-Face Video Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joygen-audio-driven-3d-depth-aware-talking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Significant progress has been made in talking-face video generation research; however, precise lip-audio synchronization and high visual quality remain challenging in editing lip shapes based on input audio.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joygen-audio-driven-3d-depth-aware-talking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VITA-1.5: Towards GPT-4o Level Real-Time Vision and Speech Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vita-1-5-towards-gpt-4o-level-real-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) have typically focused on integrating visual and textual modalities, with less emphasis placed on the role of speech in enhancing interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vita-1-5-towards-gpt-4o-level-real-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IAM: Enhancing RGB-D Instance Segmentation with New Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iam-enhancing-rgb-d-instance-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image segmentation is a vital task for providing human assistance and enhancing autonomy in our daily lives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iam-enhancing-rgb-d-instance-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDPO: Segment-Level Direct Preference Optimization for Social Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdpo-segment-level-direct-preference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these limitations, we propose Segment-Level Direct Preference Optimization (SDPO), which focuses on specific key segments within interactions to optimize multi-turn agent behavior while minimizing training noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdpo-segment-level-direct-preference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Specialized Visual Encoders for Video Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-specialized-visual-encoders-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method, MERV, Multi-Encoder Representation of Videos, instead leverages multiple frozen visual encoders to create a unified representation of a video, providing the VideoLLM with a comprehensive set of specialized visual knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-specialized-visual-encoders-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HybridTrack: A Hybrid Approach for Robust Multi-Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybridtrack-a-hybrid-approach-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The evolution of Advanced Driver Assistance Systems (ADAS) has increased the need for robust and generalizable algorithms for multi-object tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybridtrack-a-hybrid-approach-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KaLM-Embedding: Superior Training Data Brings A Stronger Embedding Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kalm-embedding-superior-training-data-brings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As retrieval-augmented generation prevails in large language models, embedding models are becoming increasingly crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kalm-embedding-superior-training-data-brings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrapped Reward Shaping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bootstrapped-reward-shaping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In reinforcement learning, especially in sparse-reward domains, many environment steps are required to observe reward information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bootstrapped-reward-shaping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hadamard Attention Recurrent Transformer: A Strong Baseline for Stereo Matching Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hadamard-attention-recurrent-transformer-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, constrained by the low-rank bottleneck and quadratic complexity of attention mechanisms, stereo transformers still fail to demonstrate sufficient nonlinear expressiveness within a reasonable inference time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hadamard-attention-recurrent-transformer-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MuQ: Self-Supervised Music Representation Learning with Mel Residual Vector Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/muq-self-supervised-music-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a self-supervised music representation learning model for music understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/muq-self-supervised-music-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVFR: A Unified Framework for Generalized Video Face Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svfr-a-unified-framework-for-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach for the Generalized Video Face Restoration (GVFR) task, which integrates video BFR, inpainting, and colorization tasks that we empirically show to benefit each other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svfr-a-unified-framework-for-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-range Brain Graph Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-range-brain-graph-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, by employing the transformer framework, ALERT adaptively integrates both short- and long-range dependencies between brain ROIs, enabling an integrated understanding of multi-level communication across the entire brain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-range-brain-graph-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BatStyler: Advancing Multi-category Style Generation for Source-free Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batstyler-advancing-multi-category-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Coarse Semantic Generation module extracts coarse-grained semantics to prevent the compression of space for style diversity learning in multi-category configuration, while the Uniform Style Generation module provides a template of styles that are uniformly distributed in space and implements parallel training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batstyler-advancing-multi-category-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asymmetric Reinforcing against Multi-modal Representation Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymmetric-reinforcing-against-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The strength of multimodal learning lies in its ability to integrate information from various sources, providing rich and comprehensive insights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymmetric-reinforcing-against-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Large Language Models for Faithful Integrity Against Opposing Argument</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-language-models-for-faithful</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel framework, named Alignment for Faithful Integrity with Confidence Estimation (AFICE), which aims to align the LLM responses with faithful integrity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-language-models-for-faithful</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconstruction vs. Generation: Taming Optimization Dilemma in Latent Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstruction-vs-generation-taming-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The integrated system achieves state-of-the-art (SOTA) performance on ImageNet 256x256 generation with an FID score of 1. 35 while demonstrating remarkable training efficiency by reaching an FID score of 2. 11 in just 64 epochs--representing an over 21 times convergence speedup compared to the original DiT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstruction-vs-generation-taming-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Multi-Task Model Merging as Adaptive Projective Gradient Descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-multi-task-model-merging-as-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our findings, we frame model merging as a constrained optimization problem ($\textit{i. e.}$, minimizing the gap between the merged model and individual models, subject to the constraint of retaining shared knowledge) and solve it via adaptive projective gradient descent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-multi-task-model-merging-as-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Hyperparameter Optimization Pipeline for Transformer-Based Time Series Forecasting Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-hyperparameter-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based models for time series forecasting (TSF) have attracted significant attention in recent years due to their effectiveness and versatility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-hyperparameter-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional Consistency Guided Image Translation and Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-consistency-guided-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consistency models have emerged as a promising alternative to diffusion models, offering high-quality generative capabilities through single-step sample generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-consistency-guided-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeFAR: Semi-supervised Fine-grained Action Recognition with Temporal Perturbation and Learning Stabilization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sefar-semi-supervised-fine-grained-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments show that SeFAR achieves state-of-the-art performance on two FAR datasets, FineGym and FineDiving, across various data scopes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sefar-semi-supervised-fine-grained-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Interactive Deepfake Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-interactive-deepfake-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing deepfake analysis methods are primarily based on discriminative models, which significantly limit their application scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-interactive-deepfake-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlashInfer: Efficient and Customizable Attention Engine for LLM Inference Serving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashinfer-efficient-and-customizable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present FlashInfer: a customizable and efficient attention engine for LLM serving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashinfer-efficient-and-customizable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detail Matters: Mamba-Inspired Joint Unfolding Network for Snapshot Spectral Compressive Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detail-matters-mamba-inspired-joint-unfolding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a Mamba-inspired Joint Unfolding Network (MiJUN), which integrates physics-embedded DUNs with learning-based HSI imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detail-matters-mamba-inspired-joint-unfolding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScarNet: A Novel Foundation Model for Automated Myocardial Scar Quantification from LGE in Cardiac MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scarnet-a-novel-foundation-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Monte Carlo simulations with noise perturbations, ScarNet achieved significantly higher scar Dice (0. 892 \pm 0. 053, CoV = 5. 9%) than MedSAM (0. 048 \pm 0. 112, CoV = 233. 3%) and nnU-Net (0. 615 \pm 0. 537, CoV = 28. 7%).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scarnet-a-novel-foundation-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Active Learning By Distribution Disagreement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-active-learning-by-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we propose BALSA, an adaptation of the BALD algorithm, tailored for regression with normalizing flows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-active-learning-by-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Self-Refinement and Self-Correction for LLM-based Product Attribute Value Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-self-refinement-and-self-correction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates applying two self-refinement techniques, error-based prompt rewriting and self-correction, to the product attribute value extraction task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-self-refinement-and-self-correction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EliGen: Entity-Level Controlled Image Generation with Regional Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eligen-entity-level-controlled-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in diffusion models have significantly advanced text-to-image generation, yet global text prompts alone remain insufficient for achieving fine-grained control over individual entities within an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eligen-entity-level-controlled-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProjectedEx: Enhancing Generation in Explainable AI for Prostate Cancer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/projectedex-enhancing-generation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we conduct comprehensive experiments on both the generator and classifier, demonstrating the clinical relevance and effectiveness of ProjectedEx in enhancing interpretability and supporting the adoption of AI in medical settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/projectedex-enhancing-generation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED: Fast and Efficient Dataset Deduplication Framework with GPU Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fed-fast-and-efficient-dataset-deduplication</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dataset deduplication plays a crucial role in enhancing data quality, ultimately improving training performance and efficiency of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fed-fast-and-efficient-dataset-deduplication</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-Augmented Dynamic Prompt Tuning for Incomplete Multimodal Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-dynamic-prompt-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal learning with incomplete modality is practical and challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-dynamic-prompt-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Augmentation Techniques for Chinese Disease Name Normalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-techniques-for-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Disease name normalization is an important task in the medical domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-techniques-for-chinese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-task Supervised Compression Model for Split Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-task-supervised-compression-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Split computing ($\neq$ split learning) is a promising approach to deep learning models for resource-constrained edge computing systems, where weak sensor (mobile) devices are wirelessly connected to stronger edge servers through channels with limited communication capacity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-task-supervised-compression-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CySecBench: Generative AI-based CyberSecurity-focused Prompt Dataset for Benchmarking Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cysecbench-generative-ai-based-cybersecurity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Typically, these methods are evaluated using datasets of malicious prompts designed to bypass security policies established by LLM providers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cysecbench-generative-ai-based-cybersecurity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BeliN: A Novel Corpus for Bengali Religious News Headline Generation using Contextual Feature Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/belin-a-novel-corpus-for-bengali-religious</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic text summarization, particularly headline generation, remains a critical yet underexplored area for Bengali religious news.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/belin-a-novel-corpus-for-bengali-religious</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk forecasting using Long Short-Term Memory Mixture Density Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-forecasting-using-long-short-term-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The LSTM mechanism allowed the neural network to capture volatility clustering similarly to GARCH models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-forecasting-using-long-short-term-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Simplicity and Sophistication using GLinear: A Novel Architecture for Enhanced Time Series Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-simplicity-and-sophistication-using-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A performance comparison with state-of-the-art linear architectures (such as NLinear, DLinear, and RLinear) and transformer-based time series predictor (Autoformer) shows that the GLinear, despite being parametrically efficient, significantly outperforms the existing architectures in most cases of multivariate TSF.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-simplicity-and-sophistication-using-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning 3D Garment Animation from Trajectories of A Piece of Cloth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-3d-garment-animation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Without the priors from analytical physics models and differentiable simulation engines, EUNet is able to directly capture the constitutive behaviors from the observed piece of cloth and uniformly describes the change of energy caused by deformations, such as stretching and bending.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-3d-garment-animation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Connectivity-Preserving Instance Segmentation with Supervoxel-Based Loss Function</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-connectivity-preserving-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstructing the intricate local morphology of neurons and their long-range projecting axons can address many connectivity related questions in neuroscience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-connectivity-preserving-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RingFormer: A Neural Vocoder with Ring Attention and Convolution-Augmented Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ringformer-a-neural-vocoder-with-ring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, the sequential nature of sample generation in neural vocoders poses difficulties for real-time processing, making the direct adoption of transformers impractical.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ringformer-a-neural-vocoder-with-ring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-informed Gaussian Processes for Safe Envelope Expansion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-gaussian-processes-for-safe</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Flight test analysis often requires predefined test points with arbitrarily tight tolerances, leading to extensive and resource-intensive experimental campaigns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-gaussian-processes-for-safe</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are LLMs effective psychological assessors? Leveraging adaptive RAG for interpretable mental health screening through psychometric practice</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-llms-effective-psychological-assessors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In psychological practice, standardized questionnaires serve as essential tools for assessing mental constructs (e. g., attitudes, traits, and emotions) through structured questions (aka items).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-llms-effective-psychological-assessors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise-Resilient Symbolic Regression with Dynamic Gating Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-resilient-symbolic-regression-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Symbolic regression (SR) has emerged as a pivotal technique for uncovering the intrinsic information within data and enhancing the interpretability of AI models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-resilient-symbolic-regression-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multivariate Human Activity Segmentation: Systematic Benchmark with ClaSP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multivariate-human-activity-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this review, we provide a systematic benchmark of dimensionality reduction, model aggregation, and change point selection applied to the ClaSP TSS algorithm for real-world, multidimensional mobile sensing data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multivariate-human-activity-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diversity Optimization for Travelling Salesman Problem via Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diversity-optimization-for-travelling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing neural methods for the Travelling Salesman Problem (TSP) mostly aim at finding a single optimal solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diversity-optimization-for-travelling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FGAseg: Fine-Grained Pixel-Text Alignment for Open-Vocabulary Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fgaseg-fine-grained-pixel-text-alignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core of FGAseg is a Pixel-Level Alignment module that employs a cross-modal attention mechanism and a text-pixel alignment loss to refine the coarse-grained alignment from CLIP, achieving finer-grained pixel-text semantic alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fgaseg-fine-grained-pixel-text-alignment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUSIFER: Language Universal Space Integration for Enhanced Multilingual Embeddings with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lusifer-language-universal-space-integration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experimental results demonstrate that LUSIFER significantly enhances the multilingual performance across various embedding tasks, particularly for medium and low-resource languages, without requiring explicit multilingual training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lusifer-language-universal-space-integration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RORem: Training a Robust Object Remover with Human-in-the-Loop</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rorem-training-a-robust-object-remover-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first collect 60K training pairs from open-source datasets to train an initial object removal model for generating removal samples, and then utilize human feedback to select a set of high-quality object removal pairs, with which we train a discriminator to automate the following training data generation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rorem-training-a-robust-object-remover-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Nuance: In Quest for Political Truth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-nuance-in-quest-for-political</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the several nuanced rationales for countering the rise of political bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-nuance-in-quest-for-political</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoPresent: Designing Structured Visuals from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopresent-designing-structured-visuals-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We benchmark end-to-end image generation and program generation methods with a variety of models, and find that programmatic methods produce higher-quality slides in user-interactable formats.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopresent-designing-structured-visuals-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cached Adaptive Token Merging: Dynamic Token Reduction and Redundant Computation Elimination in Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cached-adaptive-token-merging-dynamic-token</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have emerged as a promising approach for generating high-quality, high-dimensional images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cached-adaptive-token-merging-dynamic-token</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
