<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 09:13:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>PIAFusion: A progressive infrared and visible image fusion network based on illumination aware</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/piafusion-a-progressive-infrared-and-visible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we utilize the illumination probability to construct an illumination-aware loss to guide the training of the fusion network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/piafusion-a-progressive-infrared-and-visible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color-aware two-branch DCNN for efficient plant disease classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-aware-two-branch-dcnn-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep convolutional neural networks (DCNNs) have been successfully applied to plant disease detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-aware-two-branch-dcnn-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Learning and Learnablity of Quasimetrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-learning-and-learnablity-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, our proposed Poisson Quasimetric Embedding (PQE) is the first quasimetric learning formulation that both is learnable with gradient-based optimization and enjoys strong performance guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-learning-and-learnablity-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoised MDPs: Learning World Models Better Than the World Itself</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoised-mdps-learning-world-models-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to separate signal from noise, and reason with clean abstractions, is critical to intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoised-mdps-learning-world-models-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Functions on Multiple Sets using Multi-Set Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-functions-on-multiple-sets-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a general deep architecture for learning functions on multiple permutation-invariant sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-functions-on-multiple-sets-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Copilot AI pair programmer: Asset or Liability?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/github-copilot-ai-pair-programmer-asset-or</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the capabilities of Copilot in two different programming tasks: (1) generating (and reproducing) correct and efficient solutions for fundamental algorithmic problems, and (2) comparing Copilot's proposed solutions with those of human programmers on a set of programming tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/github-copilot-ai-pair-programmer-asset-or</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Instance-Level Impact of Fairness Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-instance-level-impact-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A variety of fairness constraints have been proposed in the literature to mitigate group-level statistical bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-instance-level-impact-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BigBIO: A Framework for Data-Centric Biomedical Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bigbio-a-framework-for-data-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training and evaluating language models increasingly requires the construction of meta-datasets --diverse collections of curated data with clear provenance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bigbio-a-framework-for-data-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Learning with Deep Tabular Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-with-deep-tabular-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we demonstrate that upstream data gives tabular neural networks a decisive advantage over widely used GBDT models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-with-deep-tabular-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Randomized K-FACs: Speeding up K-FAC with Randomized Numerical Linear Algebra</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randomized-k-facs-speeding-up-k-fac-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we theoretically show that, owing to the exponential-average construction paradigm of the Kronecker factors that is typically used, their eigen-spectrum must decay.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randomized-k-facs-speeding-up-k-fac-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laplacian Autoencoders for Learning Stochastic Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplacian-autoencoders-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representation learning has become a practical family of methods for building rich parametric codifications of massive high-dimensional data while succeeding in the reconstruction side.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplacian-autoencoders-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Ensemble Distillation With Weight Averaging and Diversifying Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-ensemble-distillation-with-weight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ensembles of deep neural networks have demonstrated superior performance, but their heavy computational cost hinders applying them for resource-limited environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-ensemble-distillation-with-weight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable K-FAC Training for Deep Neural Networks with Distributed Preconditioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-k-fac-training-for-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The second-order optimization methods, notably the D-KFAC (Distributed Kronecker Factored Approximate Curvature) algorithms, have gained traction on accelerating deep neural network (DNN) training on GPU clusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-k-fac-training-for-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnoShift: A Distribution Shift Benchmark for Unsupervised Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anoshift-a-distribution-shift-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We validate the performance degradation over time with diverse models (MLM to classical Isolation Forest).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anoshift-a-distribution-shift-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmark Dataset for Precipitation Forecasting by Post-Processing the Numerical Weather Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-dataset-for-precipitation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a hybrid NWP-DL workflow to fill the gap between standalone NWP and DL approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-dataset-for-precipitation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Part-Of-Speech Model: Does Modeling Long Context Help Unsupervised POS-tagging?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-part-of-speech-model-does-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MPoSM can model arbitrary tag dependency and perform POS induction through the objective of masked POS reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-part-of-speech-model-does-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZeroC: A Neuro-Symbolic Model for Zero-shot Concept Recognition and Acquisition at Inference Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zeroc-a-neuro-symbolic-model-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Zero-shot Concept Recognition and Acquisition (ZeroC), a neuro-symbolic architecture that can recognize and acquire novel concepts in a zero-shot way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zeroc-a-neuro-symbolic-model-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking the Robustness of Deep Neural Networks to Common Corruptions in Digital Pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-the-robustness-of-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluated on two resulting benchmark datasets, we find that (1) a variety of deep neural network models suffer from a significant accuracy decrease (double the error on clean images) and the unreliable confidence estimation on corrupted images; (2) A low correlation between the validation and test errors while replacing the validation set with our benchmark can increase the correlation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-the-robustness-of-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting Future World Events with Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-future-world-events-with-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We test language models on our forecasting task and find that performance is far below a human expert baseline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-future-world-events-with-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grouped Pointwise Convolutions Reduce Parameters in Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grouped-pointwise-convolutions-reduce</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Deep Convolutional Neural Networks (DCNNs), the parameter count in pointwise convolutions quickly grows due to the multiplication of the filters and input channels from the preceding layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grouped-pointwise-convolutions-reduce</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Rendering for Stereo 3D Reconstruction of Deformable Tissues in Robotic Surgery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-rendering-for-stereo-3d-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstruction of the soft tissues in robotic surgery from endoscopic stereo videos is important for many applications such as intra-operative navigation and image-guided robotic surgery automation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-rendering-for-stereo-3d-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing the efficiency of forward and backward contact tracing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-the-efficiency-of-forward-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, Kojaku and colleagues reported that backward contact tracing was ``profoundly more effective'' than forward contact tracing, that contact tracing effectiveness ``hinges on reaching the `source' of infection'', and that contact tracing outperformed case isolation in terms of cost efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-the-efficiency-of-forward-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exposing and addressing the fragility of neural networks in digital pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposing-and-addressing-the-fragility-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we develop a new method for evaluating neural network models' ability to generalise by generating a large number of distribution-shifted datasets, which can be used to thoroughly investigate their robustness to variability encountered in clinical practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposing-and-addressing-the-fragility-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified End-to-End Retriever-Reader Framework for Knowledge-based VQA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-end-to-end-retriever-reader</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, pertaining to the implicit knowledge, the multi-modal implicit knowledge for knowledge-based VQA still remains largely unexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-end-to-end-retriever-reader</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-Stage Classifier for COVID-19 Misinformation Detection Using BERT: a Study on Indonesian Tweets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stage-classifier-for-covid-19</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although there were already several studies related to the detection of misinformation in social media data, most studies focused on the English dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stage-classifier-for-covid-19</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFGC 2022: The Second DeepFake Game Competition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfgc-2022-the-second-deepfake-game</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a two-party game between DeepFake creators and defenders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfgc-2022-the-second-deepfake-game</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Anomaly Detection in Echocardiograms with Dynamic Variational Trajectory Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-anomaly-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel anomaly detection method for echocardiogram videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-anomaly-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HRFuser: A Multi-resolution Sensor Fusion Architecture for 2D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrfuser-a-multi-resolution-sensor-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides standard cameras, autonomous vehicles typically include multiple additional sensors, such as lidars and radars, which help acquire richer information for perceiving the content of the driving scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrfuser-a-multi-resolution-sensor-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEAD: A Multi-Armed Approach for Evaluation of Adversarial Examples Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mead-a-multi-armed-approach-for-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detection of adversarial examples has been a hot topic in the last years due to its importance for safely deploying machine learning algorithms in critical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mead-a-multi-armed-approach-for-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Granularity Regularized Re-Balancing for Class Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-regularized-re-balancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Re-balancing methods are used to alleviate the influence of data imbalance; however, we empirically discover that they would under-fit new classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-regularized-re-balancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skeleton-based Action Recognition via Adaptive Cross-Form Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-based-action-recognition-via-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, each GCN model in ACFL not only learns action representation from the single-form skeletons, but also adaptively mimics useful representations derived from other forms of skeletons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-based-action-recognition-via-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Localizing the Recurrent Laryngeal Nerve via Ultrasound with a Bayesian Shape Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localizing-the-recurrent-laryngeal-nerve-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tumor infiltration of the recurrent laryngeal nerve (RLN) is a contraindication for robotic thyroidectomy and can be difficult to detect via standard laryngoscopy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localizing-the-recurrent-laryngeal-nerve-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The (de)biasing effect of GAN-based augmentation methods on skin lesion images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-de-biasing-effect-of-gan-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we examined classification models trained on both real and synthetic data with counterfactual bias explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-de-biasing-effect-of-gan-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PolarFormer: Multi-camera 3D Object Detection with Polar Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polarformer-multi-camera-3d-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D object detection in autonomous driving aims to reason "what" and "where" the objects of interest present in a 3D world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polarformer-multi-camera-3d-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Entity Candidate Generation for Low-Resource Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-entity-candidate-generation-for-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose a light-weight and simple solution based on the construction of indexes whose design is motivated by more complex transfer learning based neural approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-entity-candidate-generation-for-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shifts 2.0: Extending The Dataset of Real Distributional Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shifts-2-0-extending-the-dataset-of-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This creates a need to be able to assess how robustly ML models generalize as well as the quality of their uncertainty estimates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shifts-2-0-extending-the-dataset-of-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asymmetry Disentanglement Network for Interpretable Acute Ischemic Stroke Infarct Segmentation in Non-Contrast CT Scans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymmetry-disentanglement-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel Asymmetry Disentanglement Network (ADN) to automatically separate pathological asymmetries and intrinsic anatomical asymmetries in NCCTs for more effective and interpretable AIS segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymmetry-disentanglement-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiclass-SGCN: Sparse Graph-based Trajectory Prediction with Agent Class Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiclass-sgcn-sparse-graph-based-trajectory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trajectory prediction of road users in real-world scenarios is challenging because their movement patterns are stochastic and complex.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiclass-sgcn-sparse-graph-based-trajectory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Online Voltage Control with an Unknown Grid Topology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-online-voltage-control-with-an-unknown</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Voltage control generally requires accurate information about the grid's topology in order to guarantee network stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-online-voltage-control-with-an-unknown</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Targeted Minority Class Prediction in Sentence-Level Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-targeted-minority-class-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sentence-level relation extraction (RE) has a highly imbalanced data distribution that about 80% of data are labeled as negative, i. e., no relation; and there exist minority classes (MC) among positive labels; furthermore, some of MC instances have an incorrect label.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-targeted-minority-class-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ComDensE : Combined Dense Embedding of Relation-aware and Common Features for Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comdense-combined-dense-embedding-of-relation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the common feature extraction, we apply the common encoding function to all input embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comdense-combined-dense-embedding-of-relation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LinearAlifold: Linear-Time Consensus Structure Prediction for RNA Alignments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linearalifold-linear-time-consensus-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present LinearAlifold, an efficient algorithm for folding aligned RNA homologs that scales linearly with both the sequence length and the number of sequences, based on our recent work LinearFold that folds a single RNA in linear time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linearalifold-linear-time-consensus-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TE2Rules: Extracting Rule Lists from Tree Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/te2rules-extracting-rule-lists-from-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tree Ensemble (TE) models (e. g. Gradient Boosted Trees and Random Forests) often provide higher prediction performance compared to single decision trees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/te2rules-extracting-rule-lists-from-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causality for Inherently Explainable Transformers: CAT-XPLAIN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-for-inherently-explainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There have been several post-hoc explanation approaches developed to explain pre-trained black-box neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-for-inherently-explainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDKtor: Automatic Diadochokinetic Speech Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddktor-automatic-diadochokinetic-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These segmentations predicted by the models are used to obtain measures of speech rate and sound duration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddktor-automatic-diadochokinetic-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditionally Elicitable Dynamic Risk Measures for Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditionally-elicitable-dynamic-risk</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel framework to solve risk-sensitive reinforcement learning (RL) problems where the agent optimises time-consistent dynamic spectral risk measures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditionally-elicitable-dynamic-risk</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Data-Driven Requirements Engineering Approach: Automatic Analysis of User Reviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-data-driven-requirements</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We are concerned by Data Driven Requirements Engineering, and in particular the consideration of user's reviews.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-data-driven-requirements</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Score Matching for Truncated Density Estimation on a Manifold</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-matching-for-truncated-density</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When observations are truncated, we are limited to an incomplete picture of our dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-matching-for-truncated-density</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>vMFNet: Compositionality Meets Domain-generalised Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vmfnet-compositionality-meets-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, with a reconstruction module, unlabeled data can also be used to learn the vMF kernels and likelihoods by recombining them to reconstruct the input image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vmfnet-compositionality-meets-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoT-SORT: Robust Associations Multi-Pedestrian Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bot-sort-robust-associations-multi-pedestrian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of multi-object tracking (MOT) is detecting and tracking all the objects in a scene, while keeping a unique identifier for each object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bot-sort-robust-associations-multi-pedestrian</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
