<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 21:07:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Shot Continual Learning via Flat-to-Wide Approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-continual-learning-via-flat-to-wide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a few-shot continual learning approach, termed FLat-tO-WidE AppRoach (FLOWER), where a flat-to-wide learning process finding the flat-wide minima is proposed to address the catastrophic forgetting problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-continual-learning-via-flat-to-wide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ontology Enrichment from Texts: A Biomedical Dataset for Concept Discovery and Placement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontology-enrichment-from-texts-a-biomedical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mentions of new concepts appear regularly in texts and require automated approaches to harvest and place them into Knowledge Bases (KB), e. g., ontologies and taxonomies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontology-enrichment-from-texts-a-biomedical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video object detection for privacy-preserving patient monitoring in intensive care</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-object-detection-for-privacy-preserving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new method for exploiting information in the temporal succession of video frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-object-detection-for-privacy-preserving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn over Past, Evolve for Future: Forecasting Temporal Trends for Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-over-past-evolve-for-future-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we observe that the appearances of news events on the same topic may display discernible patterns over time, and posit that such patterns can assist in selecting training instances that could make the model adapt better to future data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-over-past-evolve-for-future-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Federated Model with Mixture of Personalized and Sharing Components</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-federated-model-with-mixture-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comparing with 13 existing related methods, the proposed method successfully achieves the best model performance, and meanwhile up to 60% improvement of communication efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-federated-model-with-mixture-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How About Kind of Generating Hedges using End-to-End Neural Models?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-about-kind-of-generating-hedges-using-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hedging is a strategy for softening the impact of a statement in conversation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-about-kind-of-generating-hedges-using-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FunQA: Towards Surprising Video Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/funqa-towards-surprising-video-comprehension</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Surprising videos, e. g., funny clips, creative performances, or visual illusions, attract significant attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/funqa-towards-surprising-video-comprehension</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Singing Voice Conversion Challenge 2023</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-singing-voice-conversion-challenge-2023</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A new database was constructed for two tasks, namely in-domain and cross-domain SVC.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-singing-voice-conversion-challenge-2023</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuzzy-Conditioned Diffusion and Diffusion Projection Attention Applied to Facial Image Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fuzzy-conditioned-diffusion-and-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we propose an application to facial image correction, where we combine our fuzzy-conditioned diffusion with diffusion-derived attention maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fuzzy-conditioned-diffusion-and-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A denoised Mean Teacher for domain adaptive point cloud registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-denoised-mean-teacher-for-domain-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-training with the Mean Teacher is an established approach to this problem but is impaired by the inherent noise of the pseudo labels from the teacher.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-denoised-mean-teacher-for-domain-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restart Sampling for Improving Generative Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/restart-sampling-for-improving-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Restart not only outperforms the previous best SDE results, but also accelerates the sampling speed by 10-fold / 2-fold on CIFAR-10 / ImageNet $64 \times 64$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/restart-sampling-for-improving-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MotionGPT: Human Motion as a Foreign Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motiongpt-human-motion-as-a-foreign-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon this "motion vocabulary", we perform language modeling on both motion and text in a unified manner, treating human motion as a specific language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motiongpt-human-motion-as-a-foreign-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Modulate pre-trained Models in RL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-modulate-pre-trained-models-in-rl</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, fine-tuning a pre-trained model often suffers from catastrophic forgetting, that is, the performance on the pre-training tasks deteriorates when fine-tuning on new tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-modulate-pre-trained-models-in-rl</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Sparsification of Brain Graphs: Better Practices and Effective Designs for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-sparsification-of-brain-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on these insights, we propose a new model, Interpretable Graph Sparsification (IGS), which enhances graph classification performance by up to 5. 1% with 55. 0% fewer edges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-sparsification-of-brain-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauno: The Italian Large Language Model that will leave you senza parole!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fauno-the-italian-large-language-model-that</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents Fauno, the first and largest open-source Italian conversational Large Language Model (LLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fauno-the-italian-large-language-model-that</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faithful Synthesis of Low-dose Contrast-enhanced Brain MRI Scans using Noise-preserving Conditional GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithful-synthesis-of-low-dose-contrast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our numerical experiments show that conditional GANs are suitable for generating images at different GBCA dose levels and can be used to augment datasets for virtual contrast models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithful-synthesis-of-low-dose-contrast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Solution to CVPR'2023 AQTC Challenge: Video Alignment for Multi-Step Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-solution-to-cvpr-2023-aqtc-challenge-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a solution for enhancing video alignment to improve multi-step inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-solution-to-cvpr-2023-aqtc-challenge-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Composing Parameter-Efficient Modules with Arithmetic Operations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composing-parameter-efficient-modules-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to compose these parameter-efficient modules through linear arithmetic operations in the weight space, thereby integrating different module capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composing-parameter-efficient-modules-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PTVD: A Large-Scale Plot-Oriented Multimodal Dataset Based on Television Dramas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptvd-a-large-scale-plot-oriented-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Art forms such as movies and television (TV) dramas are reflections of the real world, which have attracted much attention from the multimodal learning community recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptvd-a-large-scale-plot-oriented-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransERR: Translation-based Knowledge Graph Completion via Efficient Relation Rotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transerr-translation-based-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents translation-based knowledge graph completion method via efficient relation rotation (TransERR), a straightforward yet effective alternative to traditional translation-based knowledge graph completion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transerr-translation-based-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Preference-aware Meta-optimization Framework for Personalized Vehicle Energy Consumption Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-preference-aware-meta-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, this paper proposes a preference-aware meta-optimization framework Meta-Pec for personalized vehicle energy consumption estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-preference-aware-meta-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedLSAM: Localize and Segment Anything Model for 3D Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medlsam-localize-and-segment-anything-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nevertheless, both the original SAM and its medical adaptations necessitate slice-by-slice annotations, which directly increase the annotation workload with the size of the dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medlsam-localize-and-segment-anything-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>logLTN: Differentiable Fuzzy Logic in the Logarithm Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logltn-differentiable-fuzzy-logic-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A significant trend in the literature involves integrating axioms and facts in loss functions by grounding logical symbols with neural networks and operators with fuzzy semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logltn-differentiable-fuzzy-logic-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Scalable Unpaired Image Translation via Latent Space Anchoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-scalable-unpaired-image-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, given a UNIT model trained on certain domains, it is difficult for current methods to incorporate new domains because they often need to train the full model on both existing and new domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-scalable-unpaired-image-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond AUROC &amp; co. for evaluating out-of-distribution detection performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-auroc-co-for-evaluating-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While there has been a growing research interest in developing out-of-distribution (OOD) detection methods, there has been comparably little discussion around how these methods should be evaluated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-auroc-co-for-evaluating-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label-Aware Hyperbolic Embeddings for Fine-grained Emotion Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-aware-hyperbolic-embeddings-for-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-grained emotion classification (FEC) is a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-aware-hyperbolic-embeddings-for-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reciprocal Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reciprocal-sequential-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing RRS models mainly capture static user preferences, which have neglected the evolving user tastes and the dynamic matching relation between the two parties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reciprocal-sequential-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AME-CAM: Attentive Multiple-Exit CAM for Weakly Supervised Segmentation on MRI Brain Tumor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ame-cam-attentive-multiple-exit-cam-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) is commonly used for brain tumor segmentation, which is critical for patient evaluation and treatment planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ame-cam-attentive-multiple-exit-cam-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutual Query Network for Multi-Modal Product Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-query-network-for-multi-modal-product</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Product image segmentation is vital in e-commerce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-query-network-for-multi-modal-product</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CST-YOLO: A Novel Method for Blood Cell Detection Based on Improved YOLOv7 and CNN-Swin Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cst-yolo-a-novel-method-for-blood-cell</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Blood cell detection is a typical small-scale object detection problem in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cst-yolo-a-novel-method-for-blood-cell</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SugarCrepe: Fixing Hackable Benchmarks for Vision-Language Compositionality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sugarcrepe-fixing-hackable-benchmarks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the last year alone, a surge of new benchmarks to measure compositional understanding of vision-language models have permeated the machine learning ecosystem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sugarcrepe-fixing-hackable-benchmarks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering Political Hate Speech During Indian Election Campaign: A New Low-Resource Dataset and Baselines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-political-hate-speech-during</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The detection of hate speech in political discourse is a critical issue, and this becomes even more challenging in low-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-political-hate-speech-during</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On-Device Evaluation Toolkit for Machine Learning on Heterogeneous Low-Power System-on-Chip</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-device-evaluation-toolkit-for-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide an open source implementation of U-TOE and we demonstrate its use to experimentally evaluate the performance of a wide variety of models, on a wide variety of low-power boards, based on popular microcontroller architectures (ARM Cortex-M and RISC-V).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-device-evaluation-toolkit-for-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple and Effective Baseline for Attentional Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-and-effective-baseline-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthesising a text-to-image model of high-quality images by guiding the generative model through the Text description is an innovative and challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-and-effective-baseline-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-output Ensembles for Multi-step Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-output-ensembles-for-multi-step</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, the literature regarding the application of dynamic ensembles for multi-step ahead forecasting is scarce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-output-ensembles-for-multi-step</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-task Item-attribute Graph Pre-training for Strict Cold-start Item Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-item-attribute-graph-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore the role of the fine-grained item attributes in bridging the gaps between the existing and the SCS items and pre-train a knowledgeable item-attribute graph for SCS item recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-item-attribute-graph-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Large Multi-Modal Model with Robust Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-multi-modal-model-with-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our dataset consists of 120k visual instructions generated by GPT4, covering 16 vision-and-language tasks with open-ended instructions and answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-multi-modal-model-with-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PWSHAP: A Path-Wise Explanation Model for Targeted Variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pwshap-a-path-wise-explanation-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Path-Wise Shapley effects (PWSHAP), a framework for assessing the targeted effect of a binary (e. g.~treatment) variable from a complex outcome model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pwshap-a-path-wise-explanation-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongCoder: A Long-Range Pre-trained Language Model for Code Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longcoder-a-long-range-pre-trained-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a new task for code completion that focuses on handling long code input and propose a sparse Transformer model, called LongCoder, to address this task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longcoder-a-long-range-pre-trained-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TCE: A Test-Based Approach to Measuring Calibration Error</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tce-a-test-based-approach-to-measuring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a new metric to measure the calibration error of probabilistic binary classifiers, called test-based calibration error (TCE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tce-a-test-based-approach-to-measuring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Trustworthy Explanation: On Causal Rationalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-trustworthy-explanation-on-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With recent advances in natural language processing, rationalization becomes an essential self-explaining diagram to disentangle the black box by selecting a subset of input texts to account for the major variation in prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-trustworthy-explanation-on-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEPNet: A Model-Driven Equivariant Proximal Network for Joint Sparse-View Reconstruction and Metal Artifact Reduction in CT Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mepnet-a-model-driven-equivariant-proximal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse-view computed tomography (CT) has been adopted as an important technique for speeding up data acquisition and decreasing radiation dose.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mepnet-a-model-driven-equivariant-proximal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computational Asymmetries in Robust Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-asymmetries-in-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of adversarial robustness, we make three strongly related contributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-asymmetries-in-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Second-place Solution for CVPR VISION 23 Challenge Track 1 -- Data Effificient Defect Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-second-place-solution-for-cvpr-vision-23</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Vision Challenge Track 1 for Data-Effificient Defect Detection requires competitors to instance segment 14 industrial inspection datasets in a data-defificient setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-second-place-solution-for-cvpr-vision-23</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative and Distributed Bayesian Optimization via Consensus: Showcasing the Power of Collaboration for Optimal Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-and-distributed-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirically, through simulated datasets and a real-world collaborative material discovery experiment, we show that our framework can effectively accelerate and improve the optimal design process and benefit all participants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-and-distributed-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic bSDD: Improving the GraphQL, JSON and RDF Representations of buildingSmart Data Dictionary</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-bsdd-improving-the-graphql-json-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The buildingSmart Data Dictionary (bSDD) is an important shared resource in the Architecture, Engineering, Construction, and Operations (AECO) domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-bsdd-improving-the-graphql-json-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When SAM Meets Sonar Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-sam-meets-sonar-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, there is a lack of research on the application of SAM to sonar imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-sam-meets-sonar-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stance Prediction and Analysis of Twitter data : A case study of Ghana 2020 Presidential Elections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stance-prediction-and-analysis-of-twitter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We utilized Logistic Regression to classify all the extracted tweets and subsequently conducted an analysis and discussion of the results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stance-prediction-and-analysis-of-twitter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RobuT: A Systematic Study of Table QA Robustness Against Human-Annotated Adversarial Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robut-a-systematic-study-of-table-qa</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant progress having been made in question answering on tabular data (Table QA), it's unclear whether, and to what extent existing Table QA models are robust to task-specific perturbations, e. g., replacing key question entities or shuffling table columns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robut-a-systematic-study-of-table-qa</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Data Redundancy in Real-world Image Classification through Data Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-data-redundancy-in-real-world-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning models often require large amounts of data for training, leading to increased costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-data-redundancy-in-real-world-image</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
