<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 21:06:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NLG Evaluation Metrics Beyond Correlation Analysis: An Empirical Metric Preference Checklist</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlg-evaluation-metrics-beyond-correlation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we analyze NLG automatic metrics based on whether human evaluation aspect is used as context or objective to compute the metrics: (i) Task-agnostic and (ii) Human-aligned.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlg-evaluation-metrics-beyond-correlation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back Translation for Speech-to-text Translation Without Transcripts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/back-translation-for-speech-to-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the remarkable success of back translation in MT, we develop a back translation algorithm for ST (BT4ST) to synthesize pseudo ST data from monolingual target data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/back-translation-for-speech-to-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIKI: Neural Inverse Kinematics with Invertible Neural Networks for 3D Human Pose and Shape Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/niki-neural-inverse-kinematics-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present NIKI (Neural Inverse Kinematics with Invertible Neural Network), which models bi-directional errors to improve the robustness to occlusions and obtain pixel-aligned accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/niki-neural-inverse-kinematics-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MV-Map: Offboard HD-Map Generation with Multi-view Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mv-map-offboard-hd-map-generation-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further enhance multi-view consistency, we augment the uncertainty network with the global 3D structure optimized by a voxelized neural radiance field (Voxel-NeRF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mv-map-offboard-hd-map-generation-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C-Eval: A Multi-Level Multi-Discipline Chinese Evaluation Suite for Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c-eval-a-multi-level-multi-discipline-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present C-Eval, the first comprehensive Chinese evaluation suite designed to assess advanced knowledge and reasoning abilities of foundation models in a Chinese context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c-eval-a-multi-level-multi-discipline-chinese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GCNSLIM: Graph Convolutional Network with Sparse Linear Methods for E-government Service Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gcnslim-graph-convolutional-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing GCN-based CF methods are mainly based on matrix factorization and incorporate some optimization tech-niques to enhance performance, which are not enough to handle the complexities of diverse real-world recommendation scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gcnslim-graph-convolutional-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperDialseg: A Large-scale Dataset for Supervised Dialogue Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superdialseg-a-large-scale-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide a feasible definition of dialogue segmentation points with the help of document-grounded dialogues and release a large-scale supervised dataset called SuperDialseg, containing 9K dialogues based on two prevalent document-grounded dialogue corpora, and also inherit their useful dialogue-related annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superdialseg-a-large-scale-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models are Zero-Shot Rankers for Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-zero-shot-rankers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Along this line of research, this work aims to investigate the capacity of LLMs that act as the ranking model for recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-zero-shot-rankers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>sustain.AI: a Recommender System to analyze Sustainability Reports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sustain-ai-a-recommender-system-to-analyze</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present sustain. AI, an intelligent, context-aware recommender system that assists auditors and financial investors as well as the general public to efficiently analyze companies' sustainability reports.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sustain-ai-a-recommender-system-to-analyze</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Better Contrastive View from Radiologist's Gaze</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-better-contrastive-view-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we propose a novel augmentation method, i. e., FocusContrast, to learn from radiologists' gaze in diagnosis and generate contrastive views for medical images with guidance from radiologists' visual attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-better-contrastive-view-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLCIFAR: CIFAR-Derived Benchmark Datasets with Human Annotated Complementary Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clcifar-cifar-derived-benchmark-datasets-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two datasets, CLCIFAR10 and CLCIFAR20, based on CIFAR10 and CIFAR100, respectively, are collected.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clcifar-cifar-derived-benchmark-datasets-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keras GPT Copilot: Integrating the Power of Large Language Models in Deep Learning Model Development</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/keras-gpt-copilot-integrating-the-power-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Keras GPT Copilot is the first Python package designed to integrate an LLM copilot within the model development workflow, offering iterative feedback options for enhancing the performance of your Keras deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/keras-gpt-copilot-integrating-the-power-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Multimodal Knowledge Graph Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-multimodal-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, the current continual setting for knowledge graph construction only consider entity and relation extraction from text data while neglecting other multi-modal sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-multimodal-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretability at Scale: Identifying Causal Mechanisms in Alpaca</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretability-at-scale-identifying-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With DAS, we discover that Alpaca does this by implementing a causal model with two interpretable boolean variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretability-at-scale-identifying-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Reproducible Extraction of Training Images from Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reproducible-extraction-of-training-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We release code to verify our extraction attack, perform the attack, as well as all extracted prompts at \url{https://github. com/ryanwebster90/onestep-extraction}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reproducible-extraction-of-training-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python Tool for Visualizing Variability of Pareto Fronts over Multiple Runs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/python-tool-for-visualizing-variability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperparameter optimization is crucial to achieving high performance in deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/python-tool-for-visualizing-variability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Similarity-weighted Construction of Contextualized Commonsense Knowledge Graphs for Knowledge-intense Argumentation Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/similarity-weighted-construction-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Arguments often do not make explicit how a conclusion follows from its premises.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/similarity-weighted-construction-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal Extractive Summarization of U.S. Court Opinions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/legal-extractive-summarization-of-u-s-court</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper tackles the task of legal extractive summarization using a dataset of 430K U. S. court opinions with key passages annotated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/legal-extractive-summarization-of-u-s-court</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMBRACE: Evaluation and Modifications for Boosting RACE</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embrace-evaluation-and-modifications-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When training and evaluating machine reading comprehension models, it is very important to work with high-quality datasets that are also representative of real-world reading comprehension tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embrace-evaluation-and-modifications-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mode Approximation Makes Good Vision-Language Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mode-approximation-makes-good-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advance of large-scale model technologies, parameter-efficient transfer learning (PETL) has swept across various fields of Artificial Intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mode-approximation-makes-good-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Consistency in Text-based Financial Forecasting Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-consistency-in-text-based-financial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using FinTrust, we show that the consistency of state-of-the-art NLP models for financial forecasting is poor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-consistency-in-text-based-financial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inverse Rendering of Translucent Objects using Physical and Neural Renderers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverse-rendering-of-translucent-objects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enhance the supervision of the proposed neural renderer, we also propose an augmented loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverse-rendering-of-translucent-objects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and Bridging the Modality Gap for Speech Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-bridging-the-modality-gap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to the differences between speech and text, there is always a gap between ST and MT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-bridging-the-modality-gap</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Semantic Variation Prediction using the Distribution of Sibling Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-semantic-variation-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, some of the previously associated meanings of a target word can become obsolete over time (e. g. meaning of gay as happy), while novel usages of existing words are observed (e. g. meaning of cell as a mobile phone).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-semantic-variation-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model Guided Tree-of-Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-guided-tree-of-thought</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To verify the effectiveness of the proposed technique, we implemented a ToT-based solver for the Sudoku Puzzle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-guided-tree-of-thought</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SRRM: Semantic Region Relation Model for Indoor Scene Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srrm-semantic-region-relation-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the remarkable success of convolutional neural networks in various computer vision tasks, recognizing indoor scenes still presents a significant challenge due to their complex composition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srrm-semantic-region-relation-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CQE: A Comprehensive Quantity Extractor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cqe-a-comprehensive-quantity-extractor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to other information extraction approaches, interestingly only a few works exist that describe methods for a proper extraction and representation of quantities in text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cqe-a-comprehensive-quantity-extractor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerated Algorithms for Nonlinear Matrix Decomposition with the ReLU function</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerated-algorithms-for-nonlinear-matrix</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the following nonlinear matrix decomposition (NMD) problem: given a sparse nonnegative matrix $X$, find a low-rank matrix $\Theta$ such that $X \approx f(\Theta)$, where $f$ is an element-wise nonlinear function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerated-algorithms-for-nonlinear-matrix</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Attributed Change Detection on Dynamic Graphs with Density of States</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-attributed-change-detection-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current solutions do not scale well to large real-world graphs, lack robustness to large amounts of node additions/deletions, and overlook changes in node attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-attributed-change-detection-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not All Pixels Are Equal: Learning Pixel Hardness for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-pixels-are-equal-learning-pixel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, most existing hard pixel mining strategies for semantic segmentation often rely on pixel's loss value, which tends to decrease during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-pixels-are-equal-learning-pixel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global and Local Mixture Consistency Cumulative Learning for Long-tailed Visual Recognitions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-and-local-mixture-consistency-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, our goal is to design a simple learning paradigm for long-tail visual recognition, which not only improves the robustness of the feature extractor but also alleviates the bias of the classifier towards head classes while reducing the training skills and overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-and-local-mixture-consistency-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RL4F: Generating Natural Language Feedback with Reinforcement Learning for Repairing Model Outputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl4f-generating-natural-language-feedback</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their unprecedented success, even the largest language models make mistakes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl4f-generating-natural-language-feedback</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Ensemble Approach for Automated Theorem Proving Based on Efficient Name Invariant Graph Neural Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ensemble-approach-for-automated-theorem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NIAGRA addresses this problem by using 1) improved Graph Neural Networks for learning name-invariant formula representations that is tailored for their unique characteristics and 2) an efficient ensemble approach for automated theorem proving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ensemble-approach-for-automated-theorem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning with Layer Pruning on Medical Report Summarization and Medical Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-with-layer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing size of language models raises great research interests in parameter-efficient fine-tuning (e. g. Adapter, LoRA and prompt tuning) that freezes the pre-trained model, and injects small-scale trainable parameters for multiple downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-with-layer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Uncertainty into Neural Network-based Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-uncertainty-into-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the benefits of modeling uncertainty in clean speech estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-uncertainty-into-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Boltzmann Machines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-boltzmann-machines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conditional generative models are capable of using contextual information as input to create new imaginative outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-boltzmann-machines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PMIndiaSum: Multilingual and Cross-lingual Headline Summarization for Languages in India</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pmindiasum-multilingual-and-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces PMIndiaSum, a new multilingual and massively parallel headline summarization corpus focused on languages in India.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pmindiasum-multilingual-and-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLIP: Language-Image Pre-training for Person Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plip-language-image-pre-training-for-person</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate that our model not only significantly improves existing methods on all these tasks, but also shows great ability in the few-shot and domain generalization settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plip-language-image-pre-training-for-person</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity-Preserving Talking Face Generation with Landmark and Appearance Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identity-preserving-talking-face-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior landmark characteristics of the speaker's face are employed to make the generated landmarks coincide with the facial outline of the speaker.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identity-preserving-talking-face-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FeatFSDA: Towards Few-shot Domain Adaptation for Video-based Activity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/featfsda-towards-few-shot-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address few-shot domain adaptation for video-based activity recognition (FSDA-AR), which leverages a very small amount of labeled target videos to achieve effective adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/featfsda-towards-few-shot-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeeQA: Natural Questions in Meeting Transcripts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meeqa-natural-questions-in-meeting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present MeeQA, a dataset for natural-language question answering over meeting transcripts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meeqa-natural-questions-in-meeting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A graph convolutional autoencoder approach to model order reduction for parametrized PDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-graph-convolutional-autoencoder-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we develop a non-intrusive and data-driven nonlinear reduction approach, exploiting GNNs to encode the reduced manifold and enable fast evaluations of parametrized PDEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-graph-convolutional-autoencoder-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Matter of Annotation: An Empirical Study on In Situ and Self-Recall Activity Annotations from Wearable Sensors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-matter-of-annotation-an-empirical-study-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we discuss the advantages and disadvantages of the methods compared in our study, the biases they may could introduce and the consequences of their usage on human activity recognition studies and as well as possible solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-matter-of-annotation-an-empirical-study-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEPR: Knowledge Enhancement and Plausibility Ranking for Generative Commonsense Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kepr-knowledge-enhancement-and-plausibility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within the experimental models, the T5-based GenCQA with KEPR obtains the best performance, which is up to 60. 91% at the primary canonical metric Inc@3.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kepr-knowledge-enhancement-and-plausibility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coreference-aware Double-channel Attention Network for Multi-party Dialogue Reading Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coreference-aware-double-channel-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The corresponding solutions contribute to the answer-oriented reasoning on a series of well-organized and thread-aware conversational contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coreference-aware-double-channel-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marsellus: A Heterogeneous RISC-V AI-IoT End-Node SoC with 2-to-8b DNN Acceleration and 30%-Boost Adaptive Body Biasing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marsellus-a-heterogeneous-risc-v-ai-iot-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Marsellus, an all-digital heterogeneous SoC for AI-IoT end-nodes fabricated in GlobalFoundries 22nm FDX that combines 1) a general-purpose cluster of 16 RISC-V Digital Signal Processing (DSP) cores attuned for the execution of a diverse range of workloads exploiting 4-bit and 2-bit arithmetic extensions (XpulpNN), combined with fused MAC&LOAD operations and floating-point support; 2) a 2-8bit Reconfigurable Binary Engine (RBE) to accelerate 3x3 and 1x1 (pointwise) convolutions in DNNs; 3) a set of On-Chip Monitoring (OCM) blocks connected to an Adaptive Body Biasing (ABB) generator and a hardware control loop, enabling on-the-fly adaptation of transistor threshold voltages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marsellus-a-heterogeneous-risc-v-ai-iot-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Non-linguistic Skills without Sacrificing Linguistic Proficiency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-non-linguistic-skills-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of Math-NLP has witnessed significant growth in recent years, motivated by the desire to expand LLM performance to the learning of non-linguistic notions (numerals, and subsequently, arithmetic reasoning).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-non-linguistic-skills-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MatSci-NLP: Evaluating Scientific Language Models on Materials Science Language Tasks Using Text-to-Schema Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matsci-nlp-evaluating-scientific-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments in this low-resource training setting show that language models pretrained on scientific text outperform BERT trained on general text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matsci-nlp-evaluating-scientific-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Generalize for Cross-domain QA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generalize-for-cross-domain-qa</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method has been theoretically and empirically shown to be effective in enhancing the generalization ability of both generative and discriminative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generalize-for-cross-domain-qa</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Models for Imperceptible and Transferable Adversarial Attack</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-for-imperceptible-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many existing adversarial attacks generate $L_p$-norm perturbations on image RGB space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-for-imperceptible-and</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
