<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 21:06:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Diffusion Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-diffusion-policy-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research has made significant progress in optimizing diffusion models for specific downstream objectives, which is an important pursuit in fields such as graph generation for drug design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-diffusion-policy-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCVSMNet: Double Cost Volume Stereo Matching Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcvsmnet-double-cost-volume-stereo-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Double Cost Volume Stereo Matching Network(DCVSMNet) which is a novel architecture characterised by by two small upper (group-wise) and lower (norm correlation) cost volumes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcvsmnet-double-cost-volume-stereo-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HumanEval-XL: A Multilingual Code Generation Benchmark for Cross-lingual Natural Language Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humaneval-xl-a-multilingual-code-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These benchmarks have overlooked the vast landscape of massively multilingual NL to multilingual code, leaving a critical gap in the evaluation of multilingual LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humaneval-xl-a-multilingual-code-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving LLM-based Machine Translation with Systematic Self-Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-llm-based-machine-translation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have achieved impressive results in Machine Translation (MT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-llm-based-machine-translation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Training of Normalizing Flows for High-dimensional Variational Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-training-of-normalizing-flows-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in practice, training deep normalizing flows for approximating high-dimensional posterior distributions is often infeasible due to the high variance of the stochastic gradients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-training-of-normalizing-flows-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Provably Accurate Randomized Sampling Algorithm for Logistic Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-provably-accurate-randomized-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When the number of observations greatly exceeds the number of predictor variables, we present a simple, randomized sampling-based algorithm for logistic regression problem that guarantees high-quality approximations to both the estimated probabilities and the overall discrepancy of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-provably-accurate-randomized-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOTEM: TOkenized Time Series EMbeddings for General Time Series Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/totem-tokenized-time-series-embeddings-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we explore the impact of discrete, learnt, time series data representations that enable generalist, cross-domain training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/totem-tokenized-time-series-embeddings-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-training Cross-lingual Open Domain Question Answering with Large-scale Synthetic Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-cross-lingual-open-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-lingual question answering (CLQA) is a complex problem, comprising cross-lingual retrieval from a multilingual knowledge base, followed by answer generation either in English or the query language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-cross-lingual-open-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Implicit Generative Models via an Invariant Statistical Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-implicit-generative-models-via-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop a discriminator-free method for training one-dimensional (1D) generative implicit models and subsequently expand this method to accommodate multivariate cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-implicit-generative-models-via-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoZIP: A Multilingual Benchmark to Evaluate Large Language Models in Intellectual Property</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mozip-a-multilingual-benchmark-to-evaluate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we contribute a new benchmark, the first Multilingual-oriented quiZ on Intellectual Property (MoZIP), for the evaluation of LLMs in the IP domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mozip-a-multilingual-benchmark-to-evaluate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-based deep reinforcement learning for accelerated learning from flow simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-based-deep-reinforcement-learning-for-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Employing simulation-based environments in reinforcement learning enables a priori end-to-end optimization of the control system, provides a virtual testbed for safety-critical control applications, and allows to gain a deep understanding of the control mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-based-deep-reinforcement-learning-for-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Integrated Data Processing Framework for Pretraining Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-integrated-data-processing-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability of the foundation models heavily relies on large-scale, diverse, and high-quality pretraining data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-integrated-data-processing-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MV-Swin-T: Mammogram Classification with Multi-view Swin Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mv-swin-t-mammogram-classification-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional deep learning approaches for breast cancer classification has predominantly concentrated on single-view analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mv-swin-t-mammogram-classification-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Rating Elicitation for New Users in Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-rating-elicitation-for-new-users-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent recommender systems started to use rating elicitation, which asks new users to rate a small seed itemset for inferring their preferences, to improve the quality of initial recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-rating-elicitation-for-new-users-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM Inference Unveiled: Survey and Roofline Model Insights</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-inference-unveiled-survey-and-roofline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our survey stands out from traditional literature reviews by not only summarizing the current state of research but also by introducing a framework based on roofline model for systematic analysis of LLM inference techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-inference-unveiled-survey-and-roofline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPINEPS -- Automatic Whole Spine Segmentation of T2-weighted MR images using a Two-Phase Approach to Multi-class Semantic and Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spineps-automatic-whole-spine-segmentation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training on auto-generated annotations and evaluating on manually corrected test data from the GNC yielded global dice scores of 0. 900 for vertebrae, 0. 960 for intervertebral discs, and 0. 947 for the spinal canal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spineps-automatic-whole-spine-segmentation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShieldLM: Empowering LLMs as Aligned, Customizable and Explainable Safety Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shieldlm-empowering-llms-as-aligned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The safety of Large Language Models (LLMs) has gained increasing attention in recent years, but there still lacks a comprehensive approach for detecting safety issues within LLMs' responses in an aligned, customizable and explainable manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shieldlm-empowering-llms-as-aligned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Placing Objects in Context via Inpainting for Out-of-distribution Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/placing-objects-in-context-via-inpainting-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our experiments, we present different anomaly segmentation datasets based on POC-generated data and show that POC can improve the performance of recent state-of-the-art anomaly fine-tuning methods in several standardized benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/placing-objects-in-context-via-inpainting-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiGPT: Heterogeneous Graph Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/higpt-heterogeneous-graph-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing frameworks for heterogeneous graph learning have limitations in generalizing across diverse heterogeneous graph datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/higpt-heterogeneous-graph-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget-Constrained Tool Learning with Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/budget-constrained-tool-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite intensive efforts devoted to tool learning, the problem of budget-constrained tool learning, which focuses on resolving user queries within a specific budget constraint, has been widely overlooked.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/budget-constrained-tool-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FuseChat: Knowledge Fusion of Chat Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusechat-knowledge-fusion-of-chat-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, \textsc{FuseLLM} introduced the concept of knowledge fusion to transfer the collective knowledge of multiple structurally varied LLMs into a target LLM through lightweight continual training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusechat-knowledge-fusion-of-chat-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-supervised Open-World Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-open-world-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the effectiveness of our SS-OWOD problem setting and approach for remote sensing object detection, proposing carefully curated splits and baseline performance evaluations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-open-world-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Machine-Generated Texts by Multi-Population Aware Optimization for Maximum Mean Discrepancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-machine-generated-texts-by-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, it is challenging to distinguish MGTs and human-written texts because the distributional discrepancy between them is often very subtle due to the remarkable performance of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-machine-generated-texts-by-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Resolution Land Cover Classification Using Outdated Products and Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-resolution-land-cover-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Transformerbased weakly supervised method for cross-resolution land cover classification using outdated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-resolution-land-cover-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Homography Estimation for Visual Place Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-homography-estimation-for-visual-place</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we design a re-projection error of inliers loss to train the DHE network without additional homography labels, which can also be jointly trained with the backbone network to help it extract the features that are more suitable for local matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-homography-estimation-for-visual-place</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASEM: Enhancing Empathy in Chatbot through Attention-based Sentiment and Emotion Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asem-enhancing-empathy-in-chatbot-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Effective feature representations play a critical role in enhancing the performance of text generation models that rely on deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asem-enhancing-empathy-in-chatbot-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Fair Graph Anomaly Detection: Problem, New Datasets, and Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-fair-graph-anomaly-detection-problem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Fair Graph Anomaly Detection (FairGAD) problem aims to accurately detect anomalous nodes in an input graph while ensuring fairness and avoiding biased predictions against individuals from sensitive subgroups such as gender or political leanings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-fair-graph-anomaly-detection-problem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROS-Causal: A ROS-based Causal Analysis Framework for Human-Robot Interaction Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ros-causal-a-ros-based-causal-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deploying robots in human-shared spaces requires understanding interactions among nearby agents and objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ros-causal-a-ros-based-causal-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructEdit: Instruction-based Knowledge Editing for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructedit-instruction-based-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge editing for large language models can offer an efficient solution to alter a model's behavior without negatively impacting the overall performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructedit-instruction-based-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Large Language Models Encode Context Knowledge? A Layer-Wise Probing Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-large-language-models-encode-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous work has showcased the intriguing capability of large language models (LLMs) in retrieving facts and processing context knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-large-language-models-encode-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say More with Less: Understanding Prompt Learning Behaviors through Gist Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/say-more-with-less-understanding-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It finetunes the compression plugin module and uses the representations of gist tokens to emulate the raw prompts in the vanilla language model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/say-more-with-less-understanding-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Accurate Post-training Quantization for Reparameterized Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-accurate-post-training-quantization-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our framework outperforms previous methods by approximately 1\% for 8-bit PTQ and 2\% for 6-bit PTQ, showcasing its superior performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-accurate-post-training-quantization-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Forget Your Reward Values: Language Model Alignment via Value-based Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-forget-your-reward-values-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Reinforcement Learning from Human Feedback (RLHF) significantly enhances the generation quality of Large Language Models (LLMs), recent studies have raised concerns regarding the complexity and instability associated with the Proximal Policy Optimization (PPO) algorithm, proposing a series of order-based calibration methods as viable alternatives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-forget-your-reward-values-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models for Code Completion: A Practical Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-for-code-completion-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[InCoder outperformed the other models across all programming languages, highlighting the significance of training data and objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-for-code-completion-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled Graph Variational Auto-Encoder for Multimodal Recommendation with Interpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-graph-variational-auto-encoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the incorporation of multimodal information could enhance the interpretability of these systems, current multimodal models represent users and items utilizing entangled numerical vectors, rendering them arduous to interpret.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-graph-variational-auto-encoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IR2: Information Regularization for Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ir2-information-regularization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach, representing a novel application of regularization techniques in synthetic data creation for IR, is tested on three recent IR tasks characterized by complex queries: DORIS-MAE, ArguAna, and WhatsThatBook.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ir2-information-regularization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Can LLM Guide RL? A Value-Based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-can-llm-guide-rl-a-value-based-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we develop an algorithm named LINVIT that incorporates LLM guidance as a regularization factor in value-based RL, leading to significant reductions in the amount of data needed for learning, particularly when the difference between the ideal policy and the LLM-informed policy is small, which suggests that the initial policy is close to optimal, reducing the need for further exploration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-can-llm-guide-rl-a-value-based-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diving Deep into Regions: Exploiting Regional Information Transformer for Single Image Deraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diving-deep-into-regions-exploiting-regional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our RTB is used for attention selection of rain-affected and unaffected regions and local modeling of mixed scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diving-deep-into-regions-exploiting-regional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StochCA: A Novel Approach for Exploiting Pretrained Models with Cross-Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochca-a-novel-approach-for-exploiting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By doing so, queries and channel-mixing multi-layer perceptron layers of a target model are fine-tuned to target tasks to learn how to effectively exploit rich representations of pretrained models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochca-a-novel-approach-for-exploiting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMT: Tri-Modal Translation between Speech, Image, and Text by Processing Different Modalities as Different Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tmt-tri-modal-translation-between-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel Tri-Modal Translation (TMT) model that translates between arbitrary modalities spanning speech, image, and text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tmt-tri-modal-translation-between-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LSTP: Language-guided Spatial-Temporal Prompt Learning for Long-form Video-Text Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lstp-language-guided-spatial-temporal-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite progress in video-language modeling, the computational challenge of interpreting long-form videos in response to task-specific linguistic queries persists, largely due to the complexity of high-dimensional video data and the misalignment between language and visual cues over space and time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lstp-language-guided-spatial-temporal-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study of Challenges in Machine Learning Asset Management</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-challenges-in-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In machine learning (ML), efficient asset management, including ML models, datasets, algorithms, and tools, is vital for resource optimization, consistent performance, and a streamlined development lifecycle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-challenges-in-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOLoc: Visual Place Recognition by Querying Compressed Lidar Map</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voloc-visual-place-recognition-by-querying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then the QPC is compressed by the same GPC, and is aggregated into a global descriptor by an attention-based aggregation module, to query the compressed Lidar map in the vector space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voloc-visual-place-recognition-by-querying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectrum Extraction and Clipping for Implicitly Linear Layers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectrum-extraction-and-clipping-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show the effectiveness of automatic differentiation in efficiently and correctly computing and controlling the spectrum of implicitly linear operators, a rich family of layer types including all standard convolutional and dense layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectrum-extraction-and-clipping-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PST-Bench: Tracing and Benchmarking the Source of Publications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pst-bench-tracing-and-benchmarking-the-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tracing the source of research papers is a fundamental yet challenging task for researchers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pst-bench-tracing-and-benchmarking-the-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A VAE-based Framework for Learning Multi-Level Neural Granger-Causal Connectivity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-vae-based-framework-for-learning-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Granger causality has been widely used in various application domains to capture lead-lag relationships amongst the components of complex dynamical systems, and the focus in extant literature has been on a single dynamical system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-vae-based-framework-for-learning-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Image Stitching: An Adaptive Resistance Learning against Compatible Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-image-stitching-an-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a pair of captured images, subtle perturbations and distortions which go unnoticed by the human visual system tend to attack the correspondence matching, impairing the performance of image stitching algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-image-stitching-an-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query Augmentation by Decoding Semantics from Brain Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-augmentation-by-decoding-semantics-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[If the quality of the initially retrieved documents is low, then the effectiveness of query augmentation would be limited as well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-augmentation-by-decoding-semantics-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhyPlan: Compositional and Adaptive Physical Task Reasoning with Physics-Informed Skill Networks for Robot Manipulators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phyplan-compositional-and-adaptive-physical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PhyPlan leverages PINNs to simulate and predict outcomes of actions in a fast and accurate manner and uses MCTS for planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phyplan-compositional-and-adaptive-physical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MATHWELL: Generating Educational Math Word Problems at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathwell-generating-educational-math-word</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Math word problems are critical K-8 educational tools, but writing them is time-consuming and requires domain expertise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathwell-generating-educational-math-word</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
