<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 21:06:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Top K Relevant Passage Retrieval for Biomedical Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/top-k-relevant-passage-retrieval-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we work on the existing DPR framework for the biomedical domain and retrieve answers from the Pubmed articles which is a reliable source to answer medical questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/top-k-relevant-passage-retrieval-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfeRE: Step-by-Step Regex Generation via Chain of Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infere-step-by-step-regex-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, InfeRE outperforms the popular tree-based generation approach by 18. 1% and 11. 3% on both datasets, respectively, in terms of DFA@5 accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infere-step-by-step-regex-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Vision-Language Models to Follow Interleaved Vision-Language Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-vision-language-models-to-follow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a generic and lightweight controllable knowledge re-injection module, which utilizes the sophisticated reasoning ability of LLMs to control the VPG to conditionally extract instruction-specific visual information and re-inject it into the LLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-vision-language-models-to-follow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Varying-coefficients for regional quantile via KNN-based LASSO with applications to health outcome study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/varying-coefficients-for-regional-quantile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Health outcomes, such as body mass index and cholesterol levels, are known to be dependent on age and exhibit varying effects with their associated risk factors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/varying-coefficients-for-regional-quantile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Context Alignment: Chat with Vanilla Language Models Before Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-alignment-chat-with-vanilla</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this note, we explore inference-time alignment through in-context learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-alignment-chat-with-vanilla</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Two-Stream Encoders with Transformers for Cross-Modal Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-two-stream-encoders-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, on two key tasks, \textit{i. e.}, image-to-text and text-to-image retrieval, HAT achieves 7. 6\% and 16. 7\% relative score improvement of Recall@1 on MSCOCO, and 4. 4\% and 11. 6\% on Flickr30k respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-two-stream-encoders-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConDistFL: Conditional Distillation for Federated Learning from Partially Annotated Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/condistfl-conditional-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) is a key technology enabling the collaborative development of a model without exchanging training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/condistfl-conditional-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDLFormer: A Sparse and Dense Locality-enhanced Transformer for Accelerated MR Image Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdlformer-a-sparse-and-dense-locality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The self-attention mechanism of the transformer enables transformers to capture long-range dependencies in the images, which might be desirable for accelerated MRI image reconstruction as the effect of undersampling is non-local in the image domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdlformer-a-sparse-and-dense-locality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Generalizable are Deepfake Detectors? An Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-generalizable-are-deepfake-detectors-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deepfake videos and images are becoming increasingly credible, posing a significant threat given their potential to facilitate fraud or bypass access control systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-generalizable-are-deepfake-detectors-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Natural-Language Based Audio Retrieval with PaSST and Large Audio-Caption Data Sets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-natural-language-based-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents a text-to-audio-retrieval system based on pre-trained text and spectrogram transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-natural-language-based-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under-Display Camera Image Restoration with Scattering Effect</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/under-display-camera-image-restoration-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the physical model of the scattering effect, we improve the image formation pipeline for the image synthesis to construct a realistic UDC dataset with ground truths.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/under-display-camera-image-restoration-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Top-Down Stereoscopic Image Quality Assessment via Stereo Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-top-down-stereoscopic-image-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel network for SIQA via stereo attention, employing a top-down perspective to guide the quality assessment process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-top-down-stereoscopic-image-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AICSD: Adaptive Inter-Class Similarity Distillation for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aicsd-adaptive-inter-class-similarity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With inference time being a crucial factor, particularly in dense prediction tasks such as semantic segmentation, knowledge distillation has emerged as a successful technique for improving the accuracy of lightweight student networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aicsd-adaptive-inter-class-similarity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MindDiffuser: Controlled Image Reconstruction from Human Brain Activity with Semantic and Structural Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minddiffuser-controlled-image-reconstruction-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Stage 2, we utilize the CLIP visual feature decoded from fMRI as supervisory information, and continually adjust the two feature vectors decoded in Stage 1 through backpropagation to align the structural information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minddiffuser-controlled-image-reconstruction-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimplyRetrieve: A Private and Lightweight Retrieval-Centric Generative AI Tool</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplyretrieve-a-private-and-lightweight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Model (LLM) based Generative AI systems have seen significant progress in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplyretrieve-a-private-and-lightweight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XGBD: Explanation-Guided Graph Backdoor Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xgbd-explanation-guided-graph-backdoor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An emerging detection strategy in the vision and NLP domains is based on an intriguing phenomenon: when training models on a mixture of backdoor and clean samples, the loss on backdoor samples drops significantly faster than on clean samples, allowing backdoor samples to be easily detected by selecting samples with the lowest loss values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xgbd-explanation-guided-graph-backdoor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V-DETR: DETR with Vertex Relative Position Encoding for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v-detr-detr-with-vertex-relative-position</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a highly performant 3D object detector for point clouds using the DETR framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v-detr-detr-with-vertex-relative-position</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Negative May not Be True Negative: Boosting Image-Text Matching with False Negative Elimination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/your-negative-may-not-be-true-negative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing image-text matching methods adopt triplet loss as the optimization objective, and choosing a proper negative sample for the triplet of <anchor, positive, negative> is important for effectively training the model, e. g., hard negatives make the model learn efficiently and effectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/your-negative-may-not-be-true-negative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collective Human Opinions in Semantic Textual Similarity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collective-human-opinions-in-semantic-textual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the subjective nature of semantic textual similarity (STS) and pervasive disagreements in STS annotation, existing benchmarks have used averaged human ratings as the gold standard.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collective-human-opinions-in-semantic-textual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Studying Socially Unacceptable Discourse Classification (SUD) through different eyes: "Are we on the same page ?"</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/studying-socially-unacceptable-discourse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study Socially Unacceptable Discourse (SUD) characterization and detection in online text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/studying-socially-unacceptable-discourse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Monotonic Aggregation for Open-domain QA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-monotonic-aggregation-for-open-domain-qa</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments show that our framework not only ensures monotonicity, but also outperforms state-of-the-art multi-source QA methods on Natural Questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-monotonic-aggregation-for-open-domain-qa</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAIF: Perception-Aware Infrared-Visible Image Fusion for Attack-Tolerant Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paif-perception-aware-infrared-visible-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first conduct systematic analyses about the components of image fusion, investigating the correlation with segmentation robustness under adversarial perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paif-perception-aware-infrared-visible-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SILO Language Models: Isolating Legal Risk In a Nonparametric Datastore</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/silo-language-models-isolating-legal-risk-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SILO is built by (1) training a parametric LM on Open License Corpus (OLC), a new corpus we curate with 228B tokens of public domain and permissively licensed text and (2) augmenting it with a more general and easily modifiable nonparametric datastore (e. g., containing copyrighted books or news) that is only queried during inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/silo-language-models-isolating-legal-risk-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSTFormer: Bridging Spiking Neural Network and Memory Support Transformer for Frame-Event based Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sstformer-bridging-spiking-neural-network-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, they adopt either Spiking Neural Networks (SNN) for energy-efficient recognition with suboptimal results, or Artificial Neural Networks (ANN) for energy-intensive, high-performance recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sstformer-bridging-spiking-neural-network-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Augmentation with Large-scale Unconditional Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-augmentation-with-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further reduce the dependency on annotated data, we propose a synthetic augmentation method called HistoDiffusion, which can be pre-trained on large-scale unlabeled datasets and later applied to a small-scale labeled dataset for augmented training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-augmentation-with-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lossy and Lossless (L$^2$) Post-training Model Size Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lossy-and-lossless-l-2-post-training-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, a dedicated differentiable counter is introduced to guide the optimization of lossy compression to arrive at a more suitable point for later lossless compression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lossy-and-lossless-l-2-post-training-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPCFormer: Expression Prompt Collaboration Transformer for Universal Referring Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epcformer-expression-prompt-collaboration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, we propose an Expression Alignment (EA) mechanism for audio and text expressions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epcformer-expression-prompt-collaboration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Distillation-enhanced Multi-modal Transformer for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-distillation-enhanced-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To be specific, we first introduce an ID-aware Multi-modal Transformer module in the item representation learning stage to facilitate information interaction among different features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-distillation-enhanced-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUG: Photorealistic and Semantically Controllable Synthetic Data for Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pug-photorealistic-and-semantically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthetic image datasets offer unmatched advantages for designing and evaluating deep neural networks: they make it possible to (i) render as many data samples as needed, (ii) precisely control each scene and yield granular ground truth labels (and captions), (iii) precisely control distribution shifts between training and testing to isolate variables of interest for sound experimentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pug-photorealistic-and-semantically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coarse-to-Fine: Learning Compact Discriminative Representation for Single-Stage Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse-to-fine-learning-compact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image retrieval targets to find images from a database that are visually similar to the query image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse-to-fine-learning-compact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class-level Structural Relation Modelling and Smoothing for Visual Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-level-structural-relation-modelling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representation learning for images has been advanced by recent progress in more complex neural models such as the Vision Transformers and new learning theories such as the structural causal models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-level-structural-relation-modelling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards an AI to Win Ghana's National Science and Maths Quiz</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-ai-to-win-ghana-s-national-science</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Can an AI win Ghana's National Science and Maths Quiz (NSMQ)?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-ai-to-win-ghana-s-national-science</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-shot Skeleton-based Action Recognition via Mutual Information Estimation and Maximization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-skeleton-based-action-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, 1) we maximize the MI between visual and semantic space for distribution alignment; 2) we leverage the temporal information for estimating the MI by encouraging MI to increase as more frames are observed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-skeleton-based-action-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable and Equitable Math Problem Solving Strategy Prediction in Big Educational Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-and-equitable-math-problem-solving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The strategy prediction model is trained on instances sampled from these clusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-and-equitable-math-problem-solving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KITLM: Domain-Specific Knowledge InTegration into Language Models for Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kitlm-domain-specific-knowledge-integration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our research contributes to advancing the field of domain-specific language understanding and showcases the potential of knowledge infusion techniques in improving the performance of language models on question-answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kitlm-domain-specific-knowledge-integration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zhongjing: Enhancing the Chinese Medical Capabilities of Large Language Model through Expert Feedback and Real-world Multi-turn Dialogue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zhongjing-enhancing-the-chinese-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RLHF further improves the model's instruction-following ability and safety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zhongjing-enhancing-the-chinese-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variable importance for causal forests: breaking down the heterogeneity of treatment effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-importance-for-causal-forests</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, we develop a new importance variable algorithm for causal forests, to quantify the impact of each input on the heterogeneity of treatment effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-importance-for-causal-forests</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple synthetic data reduces sycophancy in large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-synthetic-data-reduces-sycophancy-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adding these data in a lightweight finetuning step can significantly reduce sycophantic behavior on held-out prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-synthetic-data-reduces-sycophancy-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Benchmark Creation for Table Union Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-benchmark-creation-for-table-union</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We thoroughly evaluate recent existing table union search methods over existing benchmarks and our new benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-benchmark-creation-for-table-union</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributionally Robust Classification on a Data Budget</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributionally-robust-classification-on-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our knowledge, this is the first result showing (near) state-of-the-art distributional robustness on limited data budgets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributionally-robust-classification-on-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deterministic Neural Illumination Mapping for Efficient Auto-White Balance Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deterministic-neural-illumination-mapping-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method provides an efficient deep learning-based AWB correction solution, promising real-time, high-quality color correction for digital imaging applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deterministic-neural-illumination-mapping-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SciGraphQA: A Large-Scale Synthetic Multi-Turn Question-Answering Dataset for Scientific Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scigraphqa-a-large-scale-synthetic-multi-turn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We asked GPT-4 to assess the matching quality of our question-answer turns given the paper's context, obtaining an average rating of 8. 7/10 on our 3K test set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scigraphqa-a-large-scale-synthetic-multi-turn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FSD V2: Improving Fully Sparse 3D Object Detection with Virtual Voxels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fsd-v2-improving-fully-sparse-3d-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consequently, we develop a suite of components to complement the virtual voxel concept, including a virtual voxel encoder, a virtual voxel mixer, and a virtual voxel assignment strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fsd-v2-improving-fully-sparse-3d-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Model in Causal Inference with Unmeasured Confounders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-model-in-causal-inference-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study how to extend the use of the diffusion model to answer the causal question from the observational data under the existence of unmeasured confounders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-model-in-causal-inference-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubly Robust Estimator for Off-Policy Evaluation with Large Action Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doubly-robust-estimator-for-off-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, Marginalized Inverse Propensity Scoring (MIPS) was proposed to mitigate the estimator's variance via embeddings of an action.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doubly-robust-estimator-for-off-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Randomized algorithms for precise measurement of differentially-private, personalized recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randomized-algorithms-for-precise-measurement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized recommendations form an important part of today's internet ecosystem, helping artists and creators to reach interested users, and helping users to discover new and engaging content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randomized-algorithms-for-precise-measurement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmark for Chinese-English Scene Text Image Super-resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-chinese-english-scene-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scene Text Image Super-resolution (STISR) aims to recover high-resolution (HR) scene text images with visually pleasant and readable text content from the given low-resolution (LR) input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-chinese-english-scene-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bilevel Generative Learning for Low-Light Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilevel-generative-learning-for-low-light</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a generic low-light vision solution by introducing a generative block to convert data from the RAW to the RGB domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilevel-generative-learning-for-low-light</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Forgetting Compensation for Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-forgetting-compensation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To surmount the above challenges, we develop a novel Heterogeneous Forgetting Compensation (HFC) model, which can resolve heterogeneous forgetting of easy-to-forget and hard-to-forget old categories from both representation and gradient aspects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-forgetting-compensation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biomedical Knowledge Graph Embeddings with Negative Statements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomedical-knowledge-graph-embeddings-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Explicitly considering negative statements has been shown to improve performance on tasks such as entity summarization and question answering or domain-specific tasks such as protein function prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomedical-knowledge-graph-embeddings-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
