<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:06:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Robust CLIP-Based Detector for Exposing Diffusion Model-Generated Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-clip-based-detector-for-exposing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models (DMs) have revolutionized image generation, producing high-quality images with applications spanning various fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-clip-based-detector-for-exposing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grasper: A Generalist Pursuer for Pursuit-Evasion Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grasper-a-generalist-pursuer-for-pursuit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pursuit-evasion games (PEGs) model interactions between a team of pursuers and an evader in graph-based environments such as urban street networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grasper-a-generalist-pursuer-for-pursuit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling ID and Modality Effects for Session-based Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-id-and-modality-effects-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the item level, we introduce a co-occurrence representation schema to explicitly incorporate cooccurrence patterns into ID representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-id-and-modality-effects-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlagVNE: A Flexible and Generalizable Reinforcement Learning Framework for Network Resource Allocation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flagvne-a-flexible-and-generalizable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a FLexible And Generalizable RL framework for VNE, named FlagVNE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flagvne-a-flexible-and-generalizable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoVA: Adapting Mixture of Vision Experts to Multimodal Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mova-adapting-mixture-of-vision-experts-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although some large-scale pretrained vision encoders such as vision encoders in CLIP and DINOv2 have brought promising performance, we found that there is still no single vision encoder that can dominate various image content understanding, e. g., the CLIP vision encoder leads to outstanding results on general image understanding but poor performance on document or chart content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mova-adapting-mixture-of-vision-experts-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaPA: Latent Prompt Assist Model For Medical Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lapa-latent-prompt-assist-model-for-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the Latent Prompt Assist model (LaPA) for medical visual question answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lapa-latent-prompt-assist-model-for-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-Formula: Recommend Formulas in Spreadsheets using Contrastive Learning for Table Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-formula-recommend-formulas-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spreadsheets are widely recognized as the most popular end-user programming tools, which blend the power of formula-based computation, with an intuitive table-based interface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-formula-recommend-formulas-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Stable and Passive Neural Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-stable-and-passive-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We take a recently proposed Polyak Lojasiewicz network (PLNet) as an Lyapunov function and then parameterize the vector field as the descent directions of the Lyapunov function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-stable-and-passive-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-trained Vision-Language Models Learn Discoverable Visual Concepts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-trained-vision-language-models-learn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Do vision-language models (VLMs) pre-trained to caption an image of a "durian" learn visual concepts such as "brown" (color) and "spiky" (texture) at the same time?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-trained-vision-language-models-learn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sample Design Engineering: An Empirical Study of What Makes Good Downstream Fine-Tuning Samples for LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-design-engineering-an-empirical-study</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the burgeoning field of Large Language Models (LLMs) like ChatGPT and LLaMA, Prompt Engineering (PE) is renowned for boosting zero-shot or in-context learning (ICL) through prompt modifications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-design-engineering-an-empirical-study</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>decoupleQ: Towards 2-bit Post-Training Uniform Quantization via decoupling Parameters into Integer and Floating Points</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupleq-towards-2-bit-post-training-uniform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing quantization schemes suffer from significant accuracy degradation at very low bits, or require some additional computational overhead when deployed, making it difficult to be applied to large-scale applications in industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupleq-towards-2-bit-post-training-uniform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooperative Sentiment Agents for Multimodal Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-sentiment-agents-for-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new Multimodal Representation Learning (MRL) method for Multimodal Sentiment Analysis (MSA), which facilitates the adaptive interaction between modalities through Cooperative Sentiment Agents, named Co-SA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-sentiment-agents-for-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SA-Attack: Speed-adaptive stealthy adversarial attack on trajectory prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-attack-speed-adaptive-stealthy-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method searches the sensitive region of trajectory prediction models and generates the adversarial trajectories by using the vehicle-following method and incorporating information about forthcoming trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-attack-speed-adaptive-stealthy-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dubo-SQL: Diverse Retrieval-Augmented Generation and Fine Tuning for Text-to-SQL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dubo-sql-diverse-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce two new methods, Dubo-SQL v1 and v2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dubo-sql-diverse-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Co-navigation: Dynamic Designing of the Materials Digital Twins via Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-co-navigation-dynamic-designing-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, the integration of theory within automated and autonomous experimental setups, or theory in the loop automated experiment, is emerging as a crucial objective for accelerating scientific research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-co-navigation-dynamic-designing-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training-and-prompt-free General Painterly Harmonization Using Image-wise Attention Sharing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-prompt-free-general-painterly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To surmount these hurdles, we design a Training-and-prompt-Free General Painterly Harmonization method using image-wise attention sharing (TF-GPH), which integrates a novel "share-attention module".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-prompt-free-general-painterly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Character Understanding of Large Language Models via Character Profiling from Fictional Works</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-character-understanding-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These results strongly validate the character understanding capability of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-character-understanding-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COIN: Counterfactual inpainting for weakly supervised semantic segmentation for medical images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coin-counterfactual-inpainting-for-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This evidence suggests that COIN is a promising approach for semantic segmentation of tumors in CT images, and presents a step forward in making deep learning applications more accessible and effective in healthcare, where annotated data is scarce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coin-counterfactual-inpainting-for-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A visualization method for data domain changes in CNN networks and the optimization method for selecting thresholds in classification tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-visualization-method-for-data-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, Face Anti-Spoofing (FAS) has played a crucial role in preserving the security of face recognition technology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-visualization-method-for-data-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integer Programming for Learning Directed Acyclic Graphs from Non-identifiable Gaussian Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integer-programming-for-learning-directed-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of learning directed acyclic graphs from continuous observational data, generated according to a linear Gaussian structural equation model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integer-programming-for-learning-directed-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Learning of Fuzzy Logic Systems for Large-Scale Data Using Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-learning-of-fuzzy-logic-systems-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Type-1 and Interval Type-2 (IT2) Fuzzy Logic Systems (FLS) excel in handling uncertainty alongside their parsimonious rule-based structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-learning-of-fuzzy-logic-systems-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAexp: A Generic Platform for RL-based Multi-Agent Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maexp-a-generic-platform-for-rl-based-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The sim-to-real gap poses a significant challenge in RL-based multi-agent exploration due to scene quantization and action discretization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maexp-a-generic-platform-for-rl-based-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Temperature Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-temperature-knowledge-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temperature plays a pivotal role in moderating label softness in the realm of knowledge distillation (KD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-temperature-knowledge-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Few-Shot Meets Remote Sensing: Discovering Novel Classes in Land Cover Mapping via Hybrid Semantic Segmentation Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-few-shot-meets-remote-sensing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Land-cover mapping is one of the vital applications in Earth observation, aiming at classifying each pixel's land-cover type of remote-sensing images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-few-shot-meets-remote-sensing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Evaluation of Dialogue Systems: Effects of User Feedback on Crowdworkers and LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-evaluation-of-dialogue-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Workers are more susceptible to user feedback on usefulness and interestingness compared to LLMs on interestingness and relevance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-evaluation-of-dialogue-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MambaMOS: LiDAR-based 3D Moving Object Segmentation with Motion-aware State Space Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambamos-lidar-based-3d-moving-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel LiDAR-based 3D Moving Object Segmentation with Motion-aware State Space Model, termed MambaMOS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambamos-lidar-based-3d-moving-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-R2: A Large Language Model Enhanced Rule-based Rewrite System for Boosting Query Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-r2-a-large-language-model-enhanced-rule</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to maintain equivalence between the rewritten query and the original one during rewriting, traditional query rewrite methods always rewrite the queries following certain rewrite rules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-r2-a-large-language-model-enhanced-rule</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinLangNet: A Novel Deep Learning Framework for Credit Risk Prediction Using Linguistic Analogy in Financial Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finlangnet-a-novel-deep-learning-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our research demonstrates that FinLangNet surpasses traditional statistical methods in predicting credit risk and that its integration with these methods enhances credit card fraud prediction models, achieving a significant improvement of over 1. 5 points in the Kolmogorov-Smirnov metric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finlangnet-a-novel-deep-learning-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stronger Random Baselines for In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stronger-random-baselines-for-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating the in-context learning classification performance of language models poses challenges due to small dataset sizes, extensive prompt-selection using the validation set, and intentionally difficult tasks that lead to near-random performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stronger-random-baselines-for-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Data Assimilation with Message Passing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-data-assimilation-with-message</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data assimilation is a core component of numerical weather prediction systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-data-assimilation-with-message</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Domain Adaption Harnessing Vision-Language Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaption-harnessing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose a novel method called Cross-Modal Knowledge Distillation (CMKD), leveraging VLP models as teacher models to guide the learning process in the target domain, resulting in state-of-the-art performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaption-harnessing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Calibration by Gaining Aware of Prediction Correctness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-calibration-by-gaining-aware-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, for a narrow misclassification, a calibrator trained by the CE loss often produces high confidence on the wrongly predicted class (e. g., a test sample is wrongly classified and its softmax score on the ground truth class is around 0. 4), which is undesirable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-calibration-by-gaining-aware-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning on a Diet: Learning from Sparsely Labeled Streams Under Constrained Computation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-on-a-diet-learning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DietCL meticulously allocates computational budget for both types of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-on-a-diet-learning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Regularization of Representation Rank as an Implicit Constraint of Bellman Equation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-regularization-of-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then leverage this upper bound to propose a novel regularizer, namely BEllman Equation-based automatic rank Regularizer (BEER).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-regularization-of-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-cultural Inspiration Detection and Analysis in Real and LLM-generated Social Media Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-cultural-inspiration-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we compile and make publicly available the InspAIred dataset, which consists of 2, 000 real inspiring posts, 2, 000 real non-inspiring posts, and 2, 000 generated inspiring posts evenly distributed across India and the UK.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-cultural-inspiration-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sentiment-oriented Transformer-based Variational Autoencoder Network for Live Video Commenting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentiment-oriented-transformer-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, a batch attention module is also proposed in this paper to alleviate the problem of missing sentimental samples, caused by the data imbalance, which is common in live videos as the popularity of videos varies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentiment-oriented-transformer-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet sentiment exacerbates intraday overtrading, evidence from A-Share market</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internet-sentiment-exacerbates-intraday</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, the effect of sentiment on overtrading is observed to be more pronounced among individual investors in large-cap stocks compared to small- and mid-cap stocks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internet-sentiment-exacerbates-intraday</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning language models with human preferences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-language-models-with-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Chapter 3, I investigate the relation between two approaches to finetuning pretrained LMs using feedback given by a scoring function: reinforcement learning from human feedback (RLHF) and distribution matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-language-models-with-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing the Robustness of Large Language Models through Self-Denoised Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-the-robustness-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although large language models (LLMs) have achieved significant success, their vulnerability to adversarial perturbations, including recent jailbreak attacks, has raised considerable concerns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-the-robustness-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Length Generalization of Causal Transformers without Position Encoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/length-generalization-of-causal-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalizing to longer sentences is important for recent Transformer-based language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/length-generalization-of-causal-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EuSQuAD: Automatically Translated and Aligned SQuAD2.0 for Basque</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eusquad-automatically-translated-and-aligned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The widespread availability of Question Answering (QA) datasets in English has greatly facilitated the advancement of the Natural Language Processing (NLP) field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eusquad-automatically-translated-and-aligned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concept Induction: Analyzing Unstructured Text with High-Level Concepts Using LLooM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-induction-analyzing-unstructured-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data analysts have long sought to turn unstructured text data into meaningful concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-induction-analyzing-unstructured-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Diverse Criteria On-the-Fly to Improve Point-wise LLM Rankers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-diverse-criteria-on-the-fly-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The most recent pointwise Large Language Model (LLM) rankers have achieved remarkable ranking results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-diverse-criteria-on-the-fly-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeing Motion at Nighttime with an Event Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seeing-motion-at-nighttime-with-an-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a novel nighttime dynamic imaging method with an event camera.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seeing-motion-at-nighttime-with-an-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MolCRAFT: Structure-Based Drug Design in Continuous Parameter Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molcraft-structure-based-drug-design-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative models for structure-based drug design (SBDD) have shown promising results in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molcraft-structure-based-drug-design-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partial Large Kernel CNNs for Efficient Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-large-kernel-cnns-for-efficient-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, we introduce Partial Large Kernel CNNs for Efficient Super-Resolution (PLKSR), which achieves state-of-the-art performance on four datasets at a scale of $\times$4, with reductions of 68. 1\% in latency and 80. 2\% in maximum GPU memory occupancy compared to SRFormer-light.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-large-kernel-cnns-for-efficient-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TriForce: Lossless Acceleration of Long Sequence Generation with Hierarchical Speculative Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triforce-lossless-acceleration-of-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, key-value (KV) cache, which is stored to avoid re-computation, has emerged as a critical bottleneck by growing linearly in size with the sequence length.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triforce-lossless-acceleration-of-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sketch-guided Image Inpainting with Partial Discrete Diffusion Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sketch-guided-image-inpainting-with-partial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study the task of sketch-guided image inpainting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sketch-guided-image-inpainting-with-partial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleBooth: Image Style Editing with Multimodal Instruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylebooth-image-style-editing-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We integrate encoded textual instruction and image exemplar as a unified condition for diffusion model, enabling the editing of original image following multimodal instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylebooth-image-style-editing-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grammatical Error Correction for Code-Switched Sentences by Learners of English</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grammatical-error-correction-for-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through this exploration, we propose a novel method of generating synthetic CSW GEC datasets by translating different spans of text within existing GEC corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grammatical-error-correction-for-code</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
