<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 09:16:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MODNet: Multi-offset Point Cloud Denoising Network Customized for Multi-scale Patches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modnet-multi-offset-point-cloud-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, a multi-scale perception module is designed to embed multi-scale geometric information for each scale feature and regress multi-scale weights to guide a multi-offset denoising displacement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modnet-multi-offset-point-cloud-denoising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prior-Aware Synthetic Data to the Rescue: Animal Pose Estimation with Very Limited Real Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prior-aware-synthetic-data-to-the-rescue</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we present a very data efficient strategy targeted for pose estimation in quadrupeds that requires only a small amount of real images from the target animal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prior-aware-synthetic-data-to-the-rescue</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAKD: Feature Augmented Knowledge Distillation for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fakd-feature-augmented-knowledge-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the recent progress on semantic directions on feature-space, we propose to include augmentations in feature space for efficient distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fakd-feature-augmented-knowledge-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUAHN-VIO: Content-and-Uncertainty-Aware Homography Network for Visual-Inertial Odometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuahn-vio-content-and-uncertainty-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning-based visual ego-motion estimation is promising yet not ready for navigating agile mobile robots in the real world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuahn-vio-content-and-uncertainty-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDB: Fraud Dataset Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fdb-fraud-dataset-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope that FDB helps in the development of customized fraud detection techniques catered to different fraud modus operandi (MOs) as well as in the improvement of AutoML systems that can work well for all datasets in the benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fdb-fraud-dataset-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EchoGNN: Explainable Ejection Fraction Estimation with Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/echognn-explainable-ejection-fraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce EchoGNN, a model based on graph neural networks (GNNs) to estimate EF from echo videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/echognn-explainable-ejection-fraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable 3D Generative Adversarial Face Model via Disentangling Shape and Appearance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-3d-generative-adversarial-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D face modeling has been an active area of research in computer vision and computer graphics, fueling applications ranging from facial expression transfer in virtual avatars to synthetic data generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-3d-generative-adversarial-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compound Figure Separation of Biomedical Images: Mining Large Datasets for Self-supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compound-figure-separation-of-biomedical-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to extract and separate compound figures into usable individual images for downstream learning, we propose a simple compound figure separation (SimCFS) framework without using the traditionally required detection bounding box annotations, with a new loss function and a hard case simulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compound-figure-separation-of-biomedical-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Multi-User Delay-Constrained Scheduling with Deep Recurrent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-multi-user-delay-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-user delay constrained scheduling is important in many real-world applications including wireless communication, live streaming, and cloud computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-multi-user-delay-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Night-time Scene Parsing with Learnable Frequency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-night-time-scene-parsing-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this, we propose to exploit the image frequency distributions for night-time scene parsing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-night-time-scene-parsing-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiGNN: Hierarchical Informative Graph Neural Networks for Molecular Property Prediction Equipped with Feature-Wise Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hignn-hierarchical-informative-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Elucidating and accurately predicting the druggability and bioactivities of molecules plays a pivotal role in drug design and discovery and remains an open challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hignn-hierarchical-informative-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-scale Multi-granular Concept Extraction Based on Machine Reading Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-granular-concept-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to supply existing KGs with more fine-grained and new concepts, we propose a novel concept extraction framework, namely MRC-CE, to extract large-scale multi-granular concepts from the descriptive texts of entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-granular-concept-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANT: Exploiting Adaptive Numerical Data Type for Low-bit Deep Neural Network Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ant-exploiting-adaptive-numerical-data-type</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a fixed-length adaptive numerical data type called ANT to achieve low-bit quantization with tiny hardware overheads.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ant-exploiting-adaptive-numerical-data-type</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Pyramid Representation Learning for Multi-Label Visual Analysis and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-pyramid-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we present a cross-scale patch-level correlation learning in SS-PRL, which allows the model to aggregate and associate information learned across patch scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-pyramid-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAIR: Fast and Lightweight Multi-Scale Color Attention Network for Instagram Filter Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cair-fast-and-lightweight-multi-scale-color</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an accurate, fast, lightweight network with multi-scale and color attention for Instagram filter removal (CAIR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cair-fast-and-lightweight-multi-scale-color</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The case for fully Bayesian optimisation in small-sample trials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-case-for-fully-bayesian-optimisation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While sample efficiency is the main motive for use of Bayesian optimisation when black-box functions are expensive to evaluate, the standard approach based on type II maximum likelihood (ML-II) may fail and result in disappointing performance in small-sample trials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-case-for-fully-bayesian-optimisation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DLDNN: Deterministic Lateral Displacement Design Automation by Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dldnn-deterministic-lateral-displacement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, this tool is generalizable to other field-based problems and since the neural network is an integral part of this method, it enables transfer learning for similar physics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dldnn-deterministic-lateral-displacement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-based Cross-modal Auxiliary Network for Multimodal Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-based-cross-modal-auxiliary-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal sentiment analysis has a wide range of applications due to its information complementarity in multimodal interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-based-cross-modal-auxiliary-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Induced Transferability Representation for Source-Free Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-induced-transferability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, based on the UTR, we propose a novel Calibrated Adaption Framework (CAF) for SFUDA, including i)the source knowledge calibration module that guides the target model to learn the transferable source knowledge and discard the non-transferable one, and ii)the target semantics calibration module that calibrates the unreliable semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-induced-transferability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>k-MS: A novel clustering algorithm based on morphological reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-ms-a-novel-clustering-algorithm-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes a clusterization algorithm called k-Morphological Sets (k-MS), based on morphological reconstruction and heuristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-ms-a-novel-clustering-algorithm-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Representations for Hyper-Relational Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-for-hyper-relational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It motivates us to design a framework that utilizes multiple aggregators to learn representations for hyper-relational facts: one from the perspective of the base triple and the other one from the perspective of the qualifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-for-hyper-relational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MapTR: Structured Modeling and Learning for Online Vectorized HD Map Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maptr-structured-modeling-and-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We adopt a hierarchical query embedding scheme to flexibly encode structured map information and perform hierarchical bipartite matching for map element learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maptr-structured-modeling-and-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boundary-Aware Network for Abdominal Multi-Organ Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-aware-network-for-abdominal-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a boundary-aware network (BA-Net) to segment abdominal organs on CT scans and MRI scans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-aware-network-for-abdominal-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Explaining Demographic Bias through the Eyes of Face Recognition Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explaining-demographic-bias-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the trustfulness of such ML decision systems, it is crucial to be aware of the inherent biases in these solutions and to make them more transparent to the public and developers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explaining-demographic-bias-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The PWLR Graph Representation: A Persistent Weisfeiler-Lehman scheme with Random Walks for Graph Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-pwlr-graph-representation-a-persistent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the Persistent Weisfeiler-Lehman Random walk scheme (abbreviated as PWLR) for graph representations, a novel mathematical framework which produces a collection of explainable low-dimensional representations of graphs with discrete and continuous node features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-pwlr-graph-representation-a-persistent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reweighting Strategy based on Synthetic Data Identification for Sentence Similarity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reweighting-strategy-based-on-synthetic-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To analyze this, we first train a classifier that identifies machine-written sentences, and observe that the linguistic features of the sentences identified as written by a machine are significantly different from those of human-written sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reweighting-strategy-based-on-synthetic-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Tailed Classification of Thorax Diseases on Chest X-Ray: A New Benchmark Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-classification-of-thorax-diseases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Imaging exams, such as chest radiography, will yield a small set of common findings and a much larger set of uncommon findings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-classification-of-thorax-diseases</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying the COVID-19 vaccine discourse on Twitter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-the-covid-19-vaccine-discourse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While pro-vax tweets (37 million) far outnumbered anti-vax tweets (10 million), a majority of tweets from both stances (63% anti-vax and 53% pro-vax tweets) came from dual-stance users who posted both pro- and anti-vax tweets during the observation period.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-the-covid-19-vaccine-discourse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing Certified Regression to Certified Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-certified-regression-to-certified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lastly, we empirically demonstrate our approaches' effectiveness on both regression and classification data, where the accuracy of up to 50% of test predictions can be guaranteed under 1% training-set corruption and up to 30% of predictions under 4% corruption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-certified-regression-to-certified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affective Manifolds: Modeling Machine's Mind to Like, Dislike, Enjoy, Suffer, Worry, Fear, and Feel Like A Human</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affective-manifolds-modeling-machine-s-mind</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More affective manifolds in the machine's mind can make it more realistic and effective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affective-manifolds-modeling-machine-s-mind</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label Propagation for 3D Carotid Vessel Wall Segmentation and Atherosclerosis Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-propagation-for-3d-carotid-vessel-wall</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Carotid vessel wall segmentation is a crucial yet challenging task in the computer-aided diagnosis of atherosclerosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-propagation-for-3d-carotid-vessel-wall</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debiasing Word Embeddings with Nonlinear Geometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-word-embeddings-with-nonlinear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, this work studies biases associated with multiple social categories: joint biases induced by the union of different categories and intersectional biases that do not overlap with the biases of the constituent categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-word-embeddings-with-nonlinear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainability of Deep Learning models for Urban Space perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainability-of-deep-learning-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the blackbox nature of deep learning models hampers urban planners to understand what landscape objects contribute to a particularly high quality or low quality urban space perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainability-of-deep-learning-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Practical Calibration Method for RGB Micro-Grid Polarimetric Cameras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-calibration-method-for-rgb-micro</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new method to overcome the need for complex optical systems to efficiently calibrate these cameras.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-calibration-method-for-rgb-micro</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Teach: Learning Data-Free Knowledge Distillation from Curriculum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-teach-learning-data-free-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore how to teach students the model from a curriculum learning (CL) perspective and propose a new approach, namely "CuDFKD", i. e., "Data-Free Knowledge Distillation with Curriculum".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-teach-learning-data-free-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Vision-Language Pretraining with Visual Concepts and Hierarchical Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-vision-language-pretraining-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision and Language Pretraining has become the prevalent approach for tackling multimodal downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-vision-language-pretraining-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedEgo: Privacy-preserving Personalized Federated Graph Learning with Ego-graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedego-privacy-preserving-personalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As special information carriers containing both structure and feature information, graphs are widely used in graph mining, e. g., Graph Neural Networks (GNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedego-privacy-preserving-personalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIRCLe: Color Invariant Representation Learning for Unbiased Classification of Skin Lesions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circle-color-invariant-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While deep learning based approaches have demonstrated expert-level performance in dermatological diagnosis tasks, they have also been shown to exhibit biases toward certain demographic attributes, particularly skin types (e. g., light versus dark), a fairness concern that must be addressed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circle-color-invariant-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention-based Interpretable Regression of Gene Expression in Histology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-based-interpretable-regression-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interpretability of deep learning is widely used to evaluate the reliability of medical imaging models and reduce the risks of inaccurate patient recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-based-interpretable-regression-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Reliable Simulation-Based Inference with Balanced Neural Ratio Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-reliable-simulation-based-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Balanced Neural Ratio Estimation (BNRE), a variation of the NRE algorithm designed to produce posterior approximations that tend to be more conservative, hence improving their reliability, while sharing the same Bayes optimal solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-reliable-simulation-based-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boundary-Aware Network for Kidney Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-aware-network-for-kidney-parsing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although numerous deep learning models have achieved remarkable success in many medical image segmentation tasks, accurate segmentation of kidney structures on computed tomography angiography (CTA) images remains challenging, due to the variable sizes of kidney tumors and the ambiguous boundaries between kidney structures and their surroundings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-aware-network-for-kidney-parsing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>naab: A ready-to-use plug-and-play corpus for Farsi</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naab-a-ready-to-use-plug-and-play-corpus-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose naab, the biggest cleaned and ready-to-use open-source textual corpus in Farsi.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naab-a-ready-to-use-plug-and-play-corpus-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Normality-Guided Distributional Reinforcement Learning for Continuous Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normality-guided-distributional-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning a predictive model of the mean return, or value function, plays a critical role in many reinforcement learning algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normality-guided-distributional-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANDO: Multi-Level Heterogeneous Graph Embeddings for Fine-Grained Detection of Smart Contract Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mando-multi-level-heterogeneous-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, it develops a multi-metapath heterogeneous graph attention network to learn multi-level embeddings of different types of nodes and their metapaths in the heterogeneous contract graphs, which can capture the code semantics of smart contracts more accurately and facilitate both fine-grained line-level and coarse-grained contract-level vulnerability detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mando-multi-level-heterogeneous-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podcast Summary Assessment: A Resource for Evaluating Summary Assessment Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/podcast-summary-assessment-a-resource-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The podcast summary assessment data is available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/podcast-summary-assessment-a-resource-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grounded Affordance from Exocentric View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounded-affordance-from-exocentric-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the diversity of interactive affordance, the uniqueness of different individuals leads to diverse interactions, which makes it difficult to establish an explicit link between object parts and affordance labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounded-affordance-from-exocentric-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-domain Cross-architecture Black-box Attacks on Fine-tuned Models with Transferred Evolutionary Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-cross-architecture-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To successfully attack fine-tuned models under both settings, we propose to first train an adversarial generator against the source model, which adopts an encoder-decoder architecture and maps a clean input to an adversarial example.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-cross-architecture-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing high-dimensional loss landscapes with Hessian directions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualizing-high-dimensional-loss-landscapes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that saddle points in the original space are rarely correctly identified as such in lower-dimensional representations if random projections are used.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualizing-high-dimensional-loss-landscapes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Heterogeneous Interaction Strengths by Trajectory Prediction with Graph Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-heterogeneous-interaction-strengths</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model employs a novel pairwise attention (PA) mechanism to refine the trajectory representations and a graph transformer to extract heterogeneous interaction weights for each pair of agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-heterogeneous-interaction-strengths</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study on the Usage of Automated Machine Learning Tools</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-the-usage-of-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning (ML) practitioners use AutoML tools to automate and optimize the process of feature engineering, model training, and hyperparameter optimization and so on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-the-usage-of-automated</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
