<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 21:09:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Field-Mediated Semantic Organization in Large Language Models: Evidence for Quantum-Like Properties in Artificial Neural Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/field-mediated-semantic-organization-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we demonstrate that Phi-2 exhibits strongly quantum-like transitions between personality states (adaptability score: 1. 00), while Phi-4-mini-instruct shows balanced quantum properties across all dimensions (LQPI score: 0. 54), Llama-3. 2-1B-Instruct displays superior topological protection of semantic content (coherence score: 0. 50) and gemma-3-1b-it shows predominantly classical computational properties (LQPI score: 0. 16).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/field-mediated-semantic-organization-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure Is Not Enough: Leveraging Behavior for Neural Network Weight Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-is-not-enough-leveraging-behavior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This allows such models to be applied to a wide variety of downstream tasks, and they demonstrate strong predictive performance and low reconstruction error.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-is-not-enough-leveraging-behavior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dereflection Any Image with Diffusion Priors and Diversified Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dereflection-any-image-with-diffusion-priors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reflection removal of a single image remains a highly challenging task due to the complex entanglement between target scenes and unwanted reflections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dereflection-any-image-with-diffusion-priors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FFaceNeRF: Few-shot Face Editing in Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ffacenerf-few-shot-face-editing-in-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To utilize masks with a desired layout, an extensive training dataset is required, which is challenging to gather.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ffacenerf-few-shot-face-editing-in-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastCuRL: Curriculum Reinforcement Learning with Progressive Context Extension for Efficient Training R1-like Reasoning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastcurl-curriculum-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose \textbf{\textsc{FastCuRL}}, a simple yet efficient \textbf{Cu}rriculum \textbf{R}einforcement \textbf{L}earning approach with context window extending strategy to accelerate the reinforcement learning training efficiency for R1-like reasoning models while enhancing their performance in tackling complex reasoning tasks with long chain-of-thought rationales, particularly with a 1. 5B parameter language model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastcurl-curriculum-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-Bench: A Benchmark for AI Agents' Ability to Exploit Real-World Web Application Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cve-bench-a-benchmark-for-ai-agents-ability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language model (LLM) agents are increasingly capable of autonomously conducting cyberattacks, posing significant threats to existing applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cve-bench-a-benchmark-for-ai-agents-ability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIMI: Leveraging Future Knowledge and Personalization in Sparse Event Forecasting for Treatment Adherence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aimi-leveraging-future-knowledge-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, effective forecasting systems for treatment adherence based on wearable sensors are still not widely available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aimi-leveraging-future-knowledge-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptHash: Affinity-Prompted Collaborative Cross-Modal Learning for Adaptive Hashing Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompthash-affinity-prompted-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-modal hashing is a promising approach for efficient data retrieval and storage optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompthash-affinity-prompted-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuralFoil: An Airfoil Aerodynamics Analysis Tool Using Physics-Informed Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralfoil-an-airfoil-aerodynamics-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work discusses the methodology and performance of NeuralFoil with several case studies, including a practical airfoil design optimization study including both aerodynamic and non-aerodynamic constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralfoil-an-airfoil-aerodynamics-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing Vecset Diffusion Model for Fast Shape Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-vecset-diffusion-model-for-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we present FlashVDM, a systematic framework for accelerating both VAE and DiT in VDM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-vecset-diffusion-model-for-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design and Implementation of an FPGA-Based Tiled Matrix Multiplication Accelerator for Transformer Self-Attention on the Xilinx KV260 SoM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/design-and-implementation-of-an-fpga-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizing that the Q, K, and V linear projections within the Multi-Head Self-Attention (MHA) module represent a critical computational bottleneck, we strategically focused our efforts on accelerating these operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/design-and-implementation-of-an-fpga-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonata: Self-Supervised Learning of Reliable Point Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sonata-self-supervised-learning-of-reliable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we question whether we have a reliable self-supervised point cloud model that can be used for diverse 3D tasks via simple linear probing, even with limited data and minimal computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sonata-self-supervised-learning-of-reliable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameters vs. Context: Fine-Grained Control of Knowledge Reliance in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameters-vs-context-fine-grained-control-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) mitigates hallucinations in Large Language Models (LLMs) by integrating external knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameters-vs-context-fine-grained-control-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blend the Separated: Mixture of Synergistic Experts for Data-Scarcity Drug-Target Interaction Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blend-the-separated-mixture-of-synergistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on 3 real-world datasets under different extents of input data scarcity and/or label scarcity demonstrate our model outperforms states of the art significantly and steadily, with a maximum improvement of 53. 53%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blend-the-separated-mixture-of-synergistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating 3D Dataset Generation with Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-3d-dataset-generation-with-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By utilizing the universal 3D representation and rendering capabilities of Radiance Fields, our pipeline generates high quality 3D models for arbitrary objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-3d-dataset-generation-with-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M3: 3D-Spatial MultiModal Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3-3d-spatial-multimodal-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present 3D Spatial MultiModal Memory (M3), a multimodal memory system designed to retain information about medium-sized static scenes through video sources for visual perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3-3d-spatial-multimodal-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal-MAP: Unreal-Engine-Based General Platform for Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unreal-map-unreal-engine-based-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Unreal Multi-Agent Playground (Unreal-MAP), an MARL general platform based on the Unreal-Engine (UE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unreal-map-unreal-engine-based-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control Pneumatic Soft Bending Actuator with Online Learning Pneumatic Physical Reservoir Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/control-pneumatic-soft-bending-actuator-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed PRC-based online learning control framework provides a novel approach for harnessing physical systems' inherent nonlinearities to enhance the control of soft actuators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/control-pneumatic-soft-bending-actuator-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Reliability of Self-explanation and its Relationship with Classification in Language Model-driven Financial Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-reliability-of-self-explanation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models (LMs) have exhibited exceptional versatility in reasoning and in-depth financial analysis through their proprietary information processing capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-reliability-of-self-explanation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning-based Heuristics to Guide Domain-Independent Dynamic Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-based-heuristics-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose using reinforcement learning to obtain a heuristic function to guide the search in DIDP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-based-heuristics-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokenize Image as a Set</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenize-image-as-a-set</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a fundamentally new paradigm for image generation through set-based tokenization and distribution modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenize-image-as-a-set</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deconstructing Long Chain-of-Thought: A Structured Reasoning Optimization Framework for Long CoT Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deconstructing-long-chain-of-thought-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable reasoning capabilities through long chain-of-thought (CoT) reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deconstructing-long-chain-of-thought-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NuiScene: Exploring Efficient Generation of Unbounded Outdoor Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nuiscene-exploring-efficient-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore the task of generating expansive outdoor scenes, ranging from castles to high-rises.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nuiscene-exploring-efficient-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-1-to-A: Zero-Shot One Image to Animatable Head Avatars Using Video Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-1-to-a-zero-shot-one-image-to-animatable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose Zero-1-to-A, a robust method that synthesizes a spatial and temporal consistency dataset for 4D avatar reconstruction using the video diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-1-to-a-zero-shot-one-image-to-animatable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Optimal Attention and Local Model for Single Image Rain Streak Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-optimal-attention-and-local-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these limitations, we propose an Expectation Maximization Reconstruction Transformer (EMResformer) for single image rain streak removal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-optimal-attention-and-local-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XAttention: Block Sparse Attention with Antidiagonal Scoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xattention-block-sparse-attention-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce XAttention, a plug-and-play framework that dramatically accelerates long-context inference in Transformers models using sparse attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xattention-block-sparse-attention-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising-based Contractive Imitation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-based-contractive-imitation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide theoretical analysis showing that the denoising network acts as a local contraction mapping, reducing the error propagation of the state transition and improving stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-based-contractive-imitation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALT: Singular Value Adaptation with Low-Rank Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salt-singular-value-adaptation-with-low-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The complex nature of medical image segmentation calls for models that are specifically designed to capture detailed, domain-specific features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salt-singular-value-adaptation-with-low-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tuning LLMs by RAG Principles: Towards LLM-native Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tuning-llms-by-rag-principles-towards-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Memory, additional information beyond the training of large language models (LLMs), is crucial to various real-world applications, such as personal assistant.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tuning-llms-by-rag-principles-towards-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting LLM-Written Peer Reviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-llm-written-peer-reviews</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find a high success rate in the embedding of our watermarks in LLM-generated reviews across models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-llm-written-peer-reviews</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniCrossAdapter: Multimodal Adaptation of CLIP for Radiology Report Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unicrossadapter-multimodal-adaptation-of-clip</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated radiology report generation aims to expedite the tedious and error-prone reporting process for radiologists.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unicrossadapter-multimodal-adaptation-of-clip</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Prompt Distribution Learning for Animal Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-prompt-distribution-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a novel probabilistic prompting approach to fully explore textual descriptions, which could alleviate the diversity issues caused by long-tail property and increase the adaptability of prompts on unseen category instance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-prompt-distribution-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Fight Hallucinations, Use Them: Estimating Image Realism using NLI over Atomic Facts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-fight-hallucinations-use-them</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach is based on the premise that LVLMs may generate hallucinations when confronted with images that defy common sense.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-fight-hallucinations-use-them</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Guided Global-Local Collaborative Networks for Lightweight Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-guided-global-local-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Single-Image Super-Resolution (SISR) plays a pivotal role in enhancing the accuracy and reliability of measurement systems, which are integral to various vision-based instrumentation and measurement applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-guided-global-local-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Lighter and Robust Evaluation for Retrieval Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-lighter-and-robust-evaluation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose a study which demonstrates the interest of open-weight models for evaluating RAG hallucination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-lighter-and-robust-evaluation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agentic Keyframe Search for Video Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentic-keyframe-search-for-video-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video question answering (VideoQA) enables machines to extract and comprehend key information from videos through natural language interaction, which is a critical step towards achieving intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentic-keyframe-search-for-video-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UMIT: Unifying Medical Imaging Tasks via Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/umit-unifying-medical-imaging-tasks-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, it is applicable to multiple imaging modalities (e. g., X-ray, CT and PET), covering a wide range of applications from basic diagnostics to complex lesion analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/umit-unifying-medical-imaging-tasks-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSLoPrompt: Bridging Low-Supervision Challenges and Open-Set Domain Generalization in CLIP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/osloprompt-bridging-low-supervision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Low-Shot Open-Set Domain Generalization (LSOSDG), a novel paradigm unifying low-shot learning with open-set domain generalization (ODG).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/osloprompt-bridging-low-supervision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bokehlicious: Photorealistic Bokeh Rendering with Controllable Apertures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bokehlicious-photorealistic-bokeh-rendering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bokeh rendering methods play a key role in creating the visually appealing, softly blurred backgrounds seen in professional photography.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bokehlicious-photorealistic-bokeh-rendering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CausalCLIPSeg: Unlocking CLIP's Potential in Referring Medical Image Segmentation with Causal Intervention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalclipseg-unlocking-clip-s-potential-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by large-scale pre-trained vision-language models, we propose CausalCLIPSeg, an end-to-end framework for referring medical image segmentation that leverages CLIP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalclipseg-unlocking-clip-s-potential-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MapGlue: Multimodal Remote Sensing Image Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapglue-multimodal-remote-sensing-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes MapGlue, a universal MRSI matching framework, and MapData, a large-scale multimodal dataset addressing these gaps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapglue-multimodal-remote-sensing-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binarized Mamba-Transformer for Lightweight Quad Bayer HybridEVS Demosaicing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binarized-mamba-transformer-for-lightweight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quad Bayer demosaicing is the central challenge for enabling the widespread application of Hybrid Event-based Vision Sensors (HybridEVS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binarized-mamba-transformer-for-lightweight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MathFusion: Enhancing Mathematic Problem-solving of LLM through Instruction Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathfusion-enhancing-mathematic-problem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have shown impressive progress in mathematical reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathfusion-enhancing-mathematic-problem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SA-Occ: Satellite-Assisted 3D Occupancy Prediction in Real World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-occ-satellite-assisted-3d-occupancy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing vision-based 3D occupancy prediction methods are inherently limited in accuracy due to their exclusive reliance on street-view imagery, neglecting the potential benefits of incorporating satellite views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-occ-satellite-assisted-3d-occupancy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid patient-specific neural networks for intraoperative X-ray to volume registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-patient-specific-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The integration of artificial intelligence in image-guided interventions holds transformative potential, promising to extract 3D geometric and quantitative information from conventional 2D imaging modalities during complex procedures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-patient-specific-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single Image Iterative Subject-driven Generation and Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-image-iterative-subject-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalizing image generation and editing is particularly challenging when we only have a few images of the subject, or even a single image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-image-iterative-subject-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VerbDiff: Text-Only Diffusion Models with Enhanced Interaction Awareness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verbdiff-text-only-diffusion-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent large-scale text-to-image diffusion models generate photorealistic images but often struggle to accurately depict interactions between humans and objects due to their limited ability to differentiate various interaction words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verbdiff-text-only-diffusion-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Few-shot 3D Point Cloud Segmentation with Vision-Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-few-shot-3d-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a GFS-PCS framework that synergizes dense but noisy pseudo-labels from 3D VLMs with precise yet sparse few-shot samples to maximize the strengths of both, named GFS-VL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-few-shot-3d-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Emperor's New Clothes in Benchmarking? A Rigorous Examination of Mitigation Strategies for LLM Benchmark Data Contamination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-emperor-s-new-clothes-in-benchmarking-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we design a systematic and controlled pipeline along with two novel metrics-fidelity and contamination resistance-to provide a fine-grained and comprehensive assessment of existing BDC mitigation strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-emperor-s-new-clothes-in-benchmarking-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uni-3DAR: Unified 3D Generation and Understanding via Autoregression on Compressed Spatial Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni-3dar-unified-3d-generation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first is a two-level subtree compression strategy, which reduces the octree token sequence by up to 8x.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni-3dar-unified-3d-generation-and</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
