<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 09:13:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Symbolic Regression Datasets and Benchmarks for Scientific Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-symbolic-regression-datasets-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Focused on a set of formulas used in the existing datasets based on Feynman Lectures on Physics, we recreate 120 datasets to discuss the performance of symbolic regression for scientific discovery (SRSD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-symbolic-regression-datasets-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marginal Tail-Adaptive Normalizing Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marginal-tail-adaptive-normalizing-flows-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning the tail behavior of a distribution is a notoriously difficult problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marginal-tail-adaptive-normalizing-flows-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building an Endangered Language Resource in the Classroom: Universal Dependencies for Kakataibo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-an-endangered-language-resource-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we launch a new Universal Dependencies treebank for an endangered language from Amazonia: Kakataibo, a Panoan language spoken in Peru.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-an-endangered-language-resource-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Controllable Product Copywriting for E-Commerce</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-controllable-product-copywriting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic product description generation for e-commerce has witnessed significant advancement in the past decade.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-controllable-product-copywriting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Gap Between Indexing and Retrieval for Differentiable Search Index with Query Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-indexing-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Differentiable Search Index (DSI) is a new, emerging paradigm for information retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-indexing-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised learning of random quantum circuits via scalable neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-learning-of-random-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting the output of quantum circuits is a hard computational task that plays a pivotal role in the development of universal quantum computers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-learning-of-random-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the effectiveness of persistent homology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-persistent-homology</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of this work is to identify some types of problems on which PH performs well or even better than other methods in data analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-persistent-homology</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bi-Calibration Networks for Weakly-Supervised Video Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-calibration-networks-for-weakly-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The video-to-text/video-to-query projections over text prototypes/query vocabulary then start the text-to-query or query-to-text calibration to estimate the amendment to query or text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-calibration-networks-for-weakly-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling up Kernels in 3D CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-kernels-in-3d-cnns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that applying large convolutional kernels in 3D CNNs has more difficulties in both performance and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-kernels-in-3d-cnns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insights into Pre-training via Simpler Synthetic Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insights-into-pre-training-via-simpler</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, to our surprise, we find that pre-training on a simple and generic synthetic task defined by the Set function achieves $65\%$ of the benefits, almost matching LIME.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insights-into-pre-training-via-simpler</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Node Outlier Detection on Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-node-outlier-detection-on-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph outlier detection is an emerging but crucial machine learning task with numerous applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-node-outlier-detection-on-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pyramid Region-based Slot Attention Network for Temporal Action Proposal Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyramid-region-based-slot-attention-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on PRSlot modules, we present a novel Pyramid Region-based Slot Attention Network termed PRSA-Net to learn a unified visual representation with rich temporal and semantic context for better proposal generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyramid-region-based-slot-attention-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Unpaired Multi-modal Medical Image Segmentation via Learning Structured Semantic Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-unpaired-multi-modal-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from previous methods which adopted both modality-specific and modality-shared modules to accommodate the appearance variance of different modalities while extracting the common semantic information, our method is based on a single Transformer with a carefully designed External Attention Module (EAM) to learn the structured semantic consistency (i. e. semantic class representations and their correlations) between modalities in the training phase.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-unpaired-multi-modal-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Deep Reinforcement Learning through Bootstrapped Opportunistic Curriculum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-deep-reinforcement-learning-through-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite considerable advances in deep reinforcement learning, it has been shown to be highly vulnerable to adversarial perturbations to state observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-deep-reinforcement-learning-through-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer-Based Multi-modal Proposal and Re-Rank for Wikipedia Image-Caption Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-multi-modal-proposal-and-re</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increased accessibility of web and online encyclopedias, the amount of data to manage is constantly increasing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-multi-modal-proposal-and-re</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Task Representations for Offline Meta-Reinforcement Learning via Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-task-representations-for-offline-meta</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study offline meta-reinforcement learning, a practical reinforcement learning paradigm that learns from offline data to adapt to new tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-task-representations-for-offline-meta</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survival Kernets: Scalable and Interpretable Deep Kernel Survival Analysis with an Accuracy Guarantee</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survival-kernets-scalable-and-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On three standard survival analysis datasets of varying sizes (up to roughly 3 million data points), we show that survival kernets are highly competitive with the best of baselines tested in terms of concordance index.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survival-kernets-scalable-and-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KTN: Knowledge Transfer Network for Learning Multi-person 2D-3D Correspondences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ktn-knowledge-transfer-network-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human densepose estimation, aiming at establishing dense correspondences between 2D pixels of human body and 3D human body template, is a key technique in enabling machines to have an understanding of people in images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ktn-knowledge-transfer-network-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Position-prior Clustering-based Self-attention Module for Knee Cartilage Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-prior-clustering-based-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The morphological changes in knee cartilage (especially femoral and tibial cartilages) are closely related to the progression of knee osteoarthritis, which is expressed by magnetic resonance (MR) images and assessed on the cartilage segmentation results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-prior-clustering-based-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust SDE-Based Variational Formulations for Solving Linear PDEs via Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-sde-based-variational-formulations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The combination of Monte Carlo methods and deep learning has recently led to efficient algorithms for solving partial differential equations (PDEs) in high dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-sde-based-variational-formulations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Parking Lot Availability by Graph-to-Sequence Model: A Case Study with SmartSantander</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-parking-lot-availability-by-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nowadays, so as to improve services and urban areas livability, multiple smart city initiatives are being carried out throughout the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-parking-lot-availability-by-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Moving Horizon Estimation for Robust Flight Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-moving-horizon-estimation-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimating and reacting to external disturbances is crucial for robust flight control of quadrotors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-moving-horizon-estimation-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Localization for Semi-Supervised Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-localization-for-semi-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nowadays, Semi-Supervised Object Detection (SSOD) is a hot topic, since, while it is rather easy to collect images for creating a new dataset, labeling them is still an expensive and time-consuming task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-localization-for-semi-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensitivity of Average Precision to Bounding Box Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensitivity-of-average-precision-to-bounding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we quantify the sensitivity of AP to bounding box perturbations and show that AP is very sensitive to small translations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensitivity-of-average-precision-to-bounding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KE-RCNN: Unifying Knowledge based Reasoning into Part-level Attribute Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ke-rcnn-unifying-knowledge-based-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, we propose a Knowledge Embedded RCNN (KE-RCNN) to identify attributes by leveraging rich knowledges, including implicit knowledge (e. g., the attribute ``above-the-hip'' for a shirt requires visual/geometry relations of shirt-hip) and explicit knowledge (e. g., the part of ``shorts'' cannot have the attribute of ``hoodie'' or ``lining'').]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ke-rcnn-unifying-knowledge-based-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object Structural Points Representation for Graph-based Semantic Monocular Localization and Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-structural-points-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the use of an efficient representation, based on structural points, for the geometry of objects to be used as landmarks in a monocular semantic SLAM system based on the pose-graph formulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-structural-points-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using the Polar Transform for Efficient Deep Learning-Based Aorta Segmentation in CTA Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-the-polar-transform-for-efficient-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a general approach to improving the semantic segmentation performance of neural networks in these tasks and validate our approach on the task of aorta segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-the-polar-transform-for-efficient-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EnvPool: A Highly Parallel Reinforcement Learning Environment Execution Engine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/envpool-a-highly-parallel-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On a high-end machine, EnvPool achieves 1 million frames per second for the environment execution on Atari environments and 3 million frames per second on MuJoCo environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/envpool-a-highly-parallel-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimally Controllable Perceptual Lossy Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimally-controllable-perceptual-lossy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that arbitrary points of the D-P tradeoff bound can be achieved by a simple linear interpolation between the outputs of a minimum MSE decoder and a specifically constructed perfect perceptual decoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimally-controllable-perceptual-lossy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convex space learning improves deep-generative oversampling for tabular imbalanced classification on smaller datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convex-space-learning-improves-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art linear interpolation approaches, such as LoRAS and ProWRAS can be used to generate synthetic samples from the convex space of the minority class to improve classifier performance in such cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convex-space-learning-improves-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shuffle Gaussian Mechanism for Differential Privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shuffle-gaussian-mechanism-for-differential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study Gaussian mechanism in the shuffle model of differential privacy (DP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shuffle-gaussian-mechanism-for-differential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise Estimation in Gaussian Process Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-estimation-in-gaussian-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a computational procedure to estimate the covariance hyperparameters for semiparametric Gaussian process regression models with additive noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-estimation-in-gaussian-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPA: MultiPath++ Based Architecture for Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpa-multipath-based-architecture-for-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous driving technology is developing rapidly and nowadays first autonomous rides are being provided in city areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpa-multipath-based-architecture-for-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Adaptive Text Classification with Structured Knowledge from Unlabeled Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-text-classification-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then during training, DASK injects pivot-related knowledge graph information into source domain texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-text-classification-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextual Squeeze-and-Excitation for Efficient Few-Shot Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-squeeze-and-excitation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have seen a growth in user-centric applications that require effective knowledge transfer across tasks in the low-data regime.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-squeeze-and-excitation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saliency Guided Inter- and Intra-Class Relation Constraints for Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saliency-guided-inter-and-intra-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a saliency guided class-agnostic distance module to pull the intra-category features closer by aligning features to their class prototypes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saliency-guided-inter-and-intra-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KOLOMVERSE: KRISO open large-scale image dataset for object detection in the maritime universe</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kolomverse-kriso-open-large-scale-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dataset has images of 3840$\times$2160 pixels and to our knowledge, it is by far the largest publicly available dataset for object detection in the maritime domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kolomverse-kriso-open-large-scale-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voxel-MAE: Masked Autoencoders for Pre-training Large-scale Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voxel-mae-masked-autoencoders-for-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the point clouds in 3D object detection is large-scale, it is impossible to reconstruct the input point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voxel-mae-masked-autoencoders-for-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Time Transform Prediction for Open Set Histopathological Image Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-transform-prediction-for-open-set</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In test time, we measure model confidence in predicting this transform, which we expect to be lower for images in the Open Set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-transform-prediction-for-open-set</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Robust Learning through the Lens of Representation Similarities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-robust-learning-through-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representation learning, i. e. the generation of representations useful for downstream applications, is a task of fundamental importance that underlies much of the success of deep neural networks (DNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-robust-learning-through-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dense Representation Framework for Lexical and Semantic Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dense-representation-framework-for-lexical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, our work integrates lexical representations with dense semantic representations by densifying high-dimensional lexical representations into what we call low-dimensional dense lexical representations (DLRs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dense-representation-framework-for-lexical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking Down Out-of-Distribution Detection: Many Methods Based on OOD Training Data Estimate a Combination of the Same Core Quantities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-down-out-of-distribution-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we show that the confidence loss which is used by Outlier Exposure has an implicit scoring function which differs in a non-trivial fashion from the theoretically optimal scoring function in the case where training and test out-distribution are the same, which again is similar to the one used when training an Energy-Based OOD detector or when adding a background class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-down-out-of-distribution-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual HateCheck: Functional Tests for Multilingual Hate Speech Detection Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-hatecheck-functional-tests-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To help address this issue, we introduce Multilingual HateCheck (MHC), a suite of functional tests for multilingual hate speech detection models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-hatecheck-functional-tests-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shapley-NAS: Discovering Operation Contribution for Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapley-nas-discovering-operation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Differentiable architecture search (DARTS) acquires the optimal architectures by optimizing the architecture parameters with gradient descent, which significantly reduces the search cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapley-nas-discovering-operation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORFD: A Dataset and Benchmark for Off-Road Freespace Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orfd-a-dataset-and-benchmark-for-off-road</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Freespace detection is an essential component of autonomous driving technology and plays an important role in trajectory planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orfd-a-dataset-and-benchmark-for-off-road</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developing a Free and Open-source Automated Building Exterior Crack Inspection Software for Construction and Facility Managers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/developing-a-free-and-open-source-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From the raw output of the algorithm, the median Intersection over Unions for the test experiments is (1) 0. 686 for indoor crack detection experiment in a controlled lab environment using a commercial drone, (2) 0. 186 for indoor crack detection at a construction site using a smartphone and (3) 0. 958 for outdoor crack detection on university campus using a commercial drone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/developing-a-free-and-open-source-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nocturne: a scalable driving benchmark for bringing multi-agent learning one step closer to the real world</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nocturne-a-scalable-driving-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce \textit{Nocturne}, a new 2D driving simulator for investigating multi-agent coordination under partial observability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nocturne-a-scalable-driving-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and Flexible Sublabel-Accurate Energy Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-flexible-sublabel-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While discrete optimization methods are able to give theoretical optimality guarantees, they can only handle a finite number of labels and therefore suffer from label discretization bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-flexible-sublabel-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing and Understanding Self-Supervised Vision Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualizing-and-understanding-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the huge diversity of self-supervised vision pretext tasks, we narrow our focus on understanding paradigms which learn from two views of the same image, and mainly aim to understand the pretext task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualizing-and-understanding-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMT-DTA: Improving Drug-Target Affinity Prediction with Semi-supervised Multi-task Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smt-dta-improving-drug-target-affinity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This seriously hinders the application of deep learning based methods, which require a large scale of supervised data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smt-dta-improving-drug-target-affinity</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
