<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 09:21:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ViTag: Online WiFi Fine Time Measurements Aided Vision-Motion Identity Association in Multi-person Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitag-online-wifi-fine-time-measurements</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ViTag associates a sequence of vision tracker generated bounding boxes with Inertial Measurement Unit (IMU) data and Wi-Fi Fine Time Measurements (FTM) from smartphones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitag-online-wifi-fine-time-measurements</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LED down the rabbit hole: exploring the potential of global attention for biomedical multi-document summarisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/led-down-the-rabbit-hole-exploring-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we report on our submission to the Multidocument Summarisation for Literature Review (MSLR) shared task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/led-down-the-rabbit-hole-exploring-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Task Vision Transformer for Semi-Supervised Driver Distraction Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-vision-transformer-for-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driver distraction detection is an important computer vision problem that can play a crucial role in enhancing traffic safety and reducing traffic accidents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-vision-transformer-for-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLARE: A Dataset for Traffic Sign Detection in Sun Glare</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glare-a-dataset-for-traffic-sign-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-time machine learning detection algorithms are often found within autonomous vehicle technology and depend on quality datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glare-a-dataset-for-traffic-sign-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attentive Symmetric Autoencoder for Brain MRI Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attentive-symmetric-autoencoder-for-brain-mri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning methods based on image patch reconstruction have witnessed great success in training auto-encoders, whose pre-trained weights can be transferred to fine-tune other downstream tasks of image understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attentive-symmetric-autoencoder-for-brain-mri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure-Aware 3D VR Sketch to 3D Shape Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-aware-3d-vr-sketch-to-3d-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we propose to use a triplet loss with an adaptive margin value driven by a "fitting gap", which is the similarity of two shapes under structure-preserving deformations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-aware-3d-vr-sketch-to-3d-shape</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time Online Video Detection with Temporal Smoothing Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-online-video-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Streaming video recognition reasons about objects and their actions in every frame of a video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-online-video-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Metric Learning with Chance Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-metric-learning-with-chance-constraints</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To provide a scalable algorithm as well as exploiting more proxies, we consider the chance constraints implied by the minimizers of proxy-based DML instances and reformulate DML as finding a feasible point in intersection of such constraints, resulting in a problem to be approximately solved by iterative projections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-metric-learning-with-chance-constraints</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Optimization for Cardinality-constrained Minimum Sum-of-Squares Clustering via Semidefinite Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-optimization-for-cardinality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the upper bound, instead, we present a local search procedure that exploits the solution of the SDP relaxation solved at each node.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-optimization-for-cardinality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Vehicle Coordination: The Berkeley DeepDrive Drone Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-vehicle-coordination-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decentralized multiagent planning has been an important field of research in robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-vehicle-coordination-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D&amp;D: Learning Human Dynamics from Dynamic Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-d-learning-human-dynamics-from-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present D&D (Learning Human Dynamics from Dynamic Camera), which leverages the laws of physics to reconstruct 3D human motion from the in-the-wild videos with a moving camera.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-d-learning-human-dynamics-from-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiMFR: A Hybrid Masked Face Recognition Through Face Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/himfr-a-hybrid-masked-face-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the recent image inpainting methods, we propose an end-to-end hybrid masked face recognition system, namely HiMFR, consisting of three significant parts: masked face detector, face inpainting, and face recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/himfr-a-hybrid-masked-face-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Robust Cross-View Consistency in Self-Supervised Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-robust-cross-view-consistency-in-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared with the photometric consistency loss as well as the rigid point cloud alignment loss, the proposed DFA and VDA losses are more robust owing to the strong representation power of deep features as well as the high tolerance of voxel density to the aforementioned challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-robust-cross-view-consistency-in-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimberTrek: Exploring and Curating Sparse Decision Trees with Interactive Visualization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timbertrek-exploring-and-curating-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given thousands of equally accurate machine learning (ML) models, how can users choose among them?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timbertrek-exploring-and-curating-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batch Layer Normalization, A new normalization layer for CNNs and RNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batch-layer-normalization-a-new-normalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a combined version of batch and layer normalization, BLN adaptively puts appropriate weight on mini-batch and feature normalization based on the inverse size of mini-batches to normalize the input to a layer during the learning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batch-layer-normalization-a-new-normalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probing Spurious Correlations in Popular Event-Based Rumor Detection Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-spurious-correlations-in-popular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As social media becomes a hotbed for the spread of misinformation, the crucial task of rumor detection has witnessed promising advances fostered by open-source benchmark datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-spurious-correlations-in-popular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGC-Net: A Lightweight Gyroscope Calibration Network for Efficient Attitude Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgc-net-a-lightweight-gyroscope-calibration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a lightweight, efficient calibration neural network model for denoising low-cost microelectromechanical system (MEMS) gyroscope and estimating the attitude of a robot in real-time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgc-net-a-lightweight-gyroscope-calibration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Face Inpainting Through Residual Attention UNet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-face-inpainting-through-residual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Realistic image restoration with high texture areas such as removing face masks is challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-face-inpainting-through-residual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Adapt Pre-trained Vision-and-Language Models to a Text-only Input?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-adapt-pre-trained-vision-and-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To find the best approach, we investigate and compare seven possible methods for adapting three different pre-trained VL models to text-only input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-adapt-pre-trained-vision-and-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Biased Artist: Exploiting Cultural Biases via Homoglyphs in Text-Guided Image Generation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-biased-artist-exploiting-cultural-biases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results further indicate that text encoders trained on multilingual data provide a way to mitigate the effects of homoglyph replacements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-biased-artist-exploiting-cultural-biases</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Knowledge Graph Evaluation Under the Open-World Assumption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-knowledge-graph-evaluation-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, evaluation of knowledge graph completion (KGC) models often ignores the incompleteness -- facts in the test set are ranked against all unknown triplets which may contain a large number of missing facts not included in the KG yet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-knowledge-graph-evaluation-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Language Semantic and Structure Embedding for Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-language-semantic-and-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike previous approaches that rely on either the structures or semantics of the knowledge graphs, we propose to jointly embed the semantics in the natural language description of the knowledge triplets with their structure information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-language-semantic-and-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D-PL: Domain Adaptive Depth Estimation with 3D-aware Pseudo-Labeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-pl-domain-adaptive-depth-estimation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we develop a domain adaptation framework via generating reliable pseudo ground truths of depth from real data to provide direct supervisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-pl-domain-adaptive-depth-estimation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust leave-one-out cross-validation for high-dimensional Bayesian models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-leave-one-out-cross-validation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method retains the simplicity and computational convenience of classical approaches, while guaranteeing finite variance of the resulting estimators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-leave-one-out-cross-validation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Fusion of Multi-object Densities Using Transfomer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fusion-of-multi-object-densities-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the performance of the transformer-based fusion method with a well-performing model-based Bayesian fusion method in several simulated scenarios with different parameter settings using synthetic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fusion-of-multi-object-densities-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of the SV-Ident 2022 Shared Task on Survey Variable Identification in Social Science Publications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overview-of-the-sv-ident-2022-shared-task-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide an overview of the SV-Ident shared task as part of the 3rd Workshop on Scholarly Document Processing (SDP) at COLING 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overview-of-the-sv-ident-2022-shared-task-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiPart: Hierarchical Divisive Clustering Toolbox</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hipart-hierarchical-divisive-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the HiPart package, an open-source native python library that provides efficient and interpret-able implementations of divisive hierarchical clustering algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hipart-hierarchical-divisive-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distribution inference risks: Identifying and mitigating sources of leakage</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-inference-risks-identifying-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We identify three sources of leakage: (1) memorizing specific information about the $\mathbb{E}[Y|X]$ (expected label given the feature values) of interest to the adversary, (2) wrong inductive bias of the model, and (3) finiteness of the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-inference-risks-identifying-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATITUDE: Robotic Global Localization with Truncated Dynamic Low-pass Filter in City-scale NeRF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latitude-robotic-global-localization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present LATITUDE: Global Localization with Truncated Dynamic Low-pass Filter, which introduces a two-stage localization mechanism in city-scale NeRF.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latitude-robotic-global-localization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SegNeXt: Rethinking Convolutional Attention Design for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segnext-rethinking-convolutional-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, SegNeXt outperforms EfficientNet-L2 w/ NAS-FPN and achieves 90. 6% mIoU on the Pascal VOC 2012 test leaderboard using only 1/10 parameters of it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segnext-rethinking-convolutional-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming Language Priors in Visual Question Answering via Distinguishing Superficially Similar Instances</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-language-priors-in-visual-question-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we define the training instances with the same question type but different answers as \textit{superficially similar instances}, and attribute the language priors to the confusion of VQA model on such instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-language-priors-in-visual-question-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allocation Schemes in Analytic Evaluation: Applicant-Centric Holistic or Attribute-Centric Segmented?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/allocation-schemes-in-analytic-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, in the often-used holistic allocation, each evaluator is assigned a subset of the applicants, and is asked to assess all relevant information for their assigned applicants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/allocation-schemes-in-analytic-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RankFeat: Rank-1 Feature Removal for Out-of-distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankfeat-rank-1-feature-removal-for-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of out-of-distribution (OOD) detection is crucial for deploying machine learning models in real-world settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankfeat-rank-1-feature-removal-for-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RVSL: Robust Vehicle Similarity Learning in Real Hazy Scenes Based on Semi-supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rvsl-robust-vehicle-similarity-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, vehicle similarity learning, also called re-identification (ReID), has attracted significant attention in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rvsl-robust-vehicle-similarity-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical fuzzy neural networks with privacy preservation for heterogeneous big data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-fuzzy-neural-networks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The network is trained with a two-stage optimization algorithm, and the parameters at low levels of the hierarchy are learned with a scheme based on the well-known alternating direction method of multipliers, which does not reveal local data to other agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-fuzzy-neural-networks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepTOP: Deep Threshold-Optimal Policy for MDPs and RMABs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deeptop-deep-threshold-optimal-policy-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of learning the optimal threshold policy for control problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deeptop-deep-threshold-optimal-policy-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Global Memory for Document-level Argument Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-global-memory-for-document-level-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extracting informative arguments of events from news articles is a challenging problem in information extraction, which requires a global contextual understanding of each document.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-global-memory-for-document-level-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honor of Kings Arena: an Environment for Generalization in Competitive Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/honor-of-kings-arena-an-environment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to other environments studied in most previous work, ours presents new generalization challenges for competitive reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/honor-of-kings-arena-an-environment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changer: Feature Interaction is What You Need for Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/changer-feature-interaction-is-what-you-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To verify the effectiveness of MetaChanger, we propose two derived models, ChangerAD and ChangerEx with simple interaction strategies: Aggregation-Distribution (AD) and "exchange".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/changer-feature-interaction-is-what-you-need</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Answer Semantic Queries over Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-answer-semantic-queries-over-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that while a neural model can be resilient to minor syntax errors in code, increasing size of code, presence of code that is not relevant to the query, and reduced number of training examples limit the model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-answer-semantic-queries-over-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Disfluency Detection to Intent Detection and Slot Filling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-disfluency-detection-to-intent-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the first empirical study investigating the influence of disfluency detection on downstream tasks of intent detection and slot filling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-disfluency-detection-to-intent-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Lexical Substitution with Decontextualised Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-lexical-substitution-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new unsupervised method for lexical substitution using pre-trained language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-lexical-substitution-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Generated Scientific Papers using an Ensemble of Transformer Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-generated-scientific-papers-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper describes neural models developed for the DAGPap22 shared task hosted at the Third Workshop on Scholarly Document Processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-generated-scientific-papers-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPDIA: A Discourse-aware Transformer-based Style Transfer Model for Offensive Social Media Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/appdia-a-discourse-aware-transformer-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we introduce the first discourse-aware style-transfer models that can effectively reduce offensiveness in Reddit text while preserving the meaning of the original text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/appdia-a-discourse-aware-transformer-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pFedDef: Defending Grey-Box Attacks for Personalized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pfeddef-defending-grey-box-attacks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We are the first to characterize the transferability of such internal evasion attacks for different learning methods and analyze the trade-off between model accuracy and robustness depending on the degree of personalization and similarities in client data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pfeddef-defending-grey-box-attacks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FR: Folded Rationalization with a Unified Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fr-folded-rationalization-with-a-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional works generally employ a two-phase model in which a generator selects the most important pieces, followed by a predictor that makes predictions based on the selected pieces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fr-folded-rationalization-with-a-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introspective Learning : A Two-Stage Approach for Inference in Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introspective-learning-a-two-stage-approach-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we ground the proposed machine introspection to human introspection for the application of image quality assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introspective-learning-a-two-stage-approach-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DytanVO: Joint Refinement of Visual Odometry and Motion Segmentation in Dynamic Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dytanvo-joint-refinement-of-visual-odometry</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning-based visual odometry (VO) algorithms achieve remarkable performance on common static scenes, benefiting from high-capacity models and massive annotated data, but tend to fail in dynamic, populated environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dytanvo-joint-refinement-of-visual-odometry</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How can voting mechanisms improve the robustness and generalizability of toponym disambiguation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-can-voting-mechanisms-improve-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A vast amount of geographic information exists in natural language texts, such as tweets and news.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-can-voting-mechanisms-improve-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Plug-and-Play Prior for Hyperspectral Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-plug-and-play-prior-for-hyperspectral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep-learning-based hyperspectral image (HSI) restoration methods have gained great popularity for their remarkable performance but often demand expensive network retraining whenever the specifics of task changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-plug-and-play-prior-for-hyperspectral</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
