<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 09:11:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Effect of prolonged use of Smartphones on neck and wrist muscle fatigue using surface EMG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-prolonged-use-of-smartphones-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prolonged smartphone usage is prevalent among young adults in Lima, Peru, with potential implications for musculoskeletal health.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-prolonged-use-of-smartphones-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlignBench: Benchmarking Chinese Alignment of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignbench-benchmarking-chinese-alignment-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Alignment has become a critical step for instruction-tuned Large Language Models (LLMs) to become helpful assistants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignbench-benchmarking-chinese-alignment-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlgym: Large-Scale Safety-Critical Control Environments for Benchmarking Reinforcement Learning Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlgym-large-scale-safety-critical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This project serves the learning for dynamics & control (L4DC) community, aiming to explore key questions: the convergence of RL algorithms in learning control policies; the stability and robustness issues of learning-based controllers; and the scalability of RL algorithms to high- and potentially infinite-dimensional systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlgym-large-scale-safety-critical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$\mathbb{Z}_2\times \mathbb{Z}_2$ Equivariant Quantum Neural Networks: Benchmarking against Classical Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathbb-z-2-times-mathbb-z-2-equivariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that the $\mathbb{Z}_2\times \mathbb{Z}_2$ EQNN and the QNN provide superior performance for smaller parameter sets and modest training data samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathbb-z-2-times-mathbb-z-2-equivariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Diffusion Prior for Generalizable Pixel-Level Semantic Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-diffusion-prior-for-generalizable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contents generated by recent advanced Text-to-Image (T2I) diffusion models are sometimes too imaginative for existing off-the-shelf property semantic predictors to estimate due to the immitigable domain gap.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-diffusion-prior-for-generalizable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Assessing and Benchmarking Risk-Return Tradeoff of Off-Policy Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-assessing-and-benchmarking-risk</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This efficient estimator is characterized by its capability to form the most advantageous policy portfolios, maximizing returns while minimizing risks during online deployment, a nuance that existing metrics typically overlook.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-assessing-and-benchmarking-risk</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ElasticDiffusion: Training-free Arbitrary Size Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elasticdiffusion-training-free-arbitrary-size</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose ElasticDiffusion, a novel training-free decoding method that enables pretrained text-to-image diffusion models to generate images with various sizes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elasticdiffusion-training-free-arbitrary-size</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Model Agents Suffer from Compositional Generalization in Web Automation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-model-agents-suffer-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that while existing prompted LMAs (gpt-3. 5-turbo or gpt-4) achieve 94. 0% average success rate on base tasks, their performance degrades to 24. 9% success rate on compositional tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-model-agents-suffer-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Routing-Guided Learned Product Quantization for Graph-Based Approximate Nearest Neighbor Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/routing-guided-learned-product-quantization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It suffers from the large-scale $\mathcal{X}$ because a PG with full vectors is too large to fit into the memory, e. g., a billion-scale $\mathcal{X}$ in 128 dimensions would consume nearly 600 GB memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/routing-guided-learned-product-quantization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compact3D: Compressing Gaussian Splat Radiance Field Models with Vector Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact3d-compressing-gaussian-splat-radiance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D Gaussian Splatting is a new method for modeling and rendering 3D radiance fields that achieves much faster learning and rendering time compared to SOTA NeRF methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact3d-compressing-gaussian-splat-radiance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do Llamas Really Think? Revealing Preference Biases in Language Model Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-llamas-really-think-revealing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a logistic Bradley-Terry probe which predicts word pair preferences of LLMs from the words' hidden vectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-llamas-really-think-revealing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MotionEditor: Editing Video Motion via Content-Aware Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motioneditor-editing-video-motion-via-content</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This mechanism enables the editing branch to query the key and value from the reconstruction branch in a decoupled manner, making the editing branch retain the original background and protagonist appearance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motioneditor-editing-video-motion-via-content</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLVMs4Protest: Harnessing the Power of Large Language and Vision Models for Deciphering Protests in the News</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llvms4protest-harnessing-the-power-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, the longformer model was fine-tuned using the Dynamic of Collective Action (DoCA) Corpus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llvms4protest-harnessing-the-power-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LMRL Gym: Benchmarks for Multi-Turn Reinforcement Learning with Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmrl-gym-benchmarks-for-multi-turn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Developing such algorithms requires tasks that can gauge progress on algorithm design, provide accessible and reproducible evaluations for multi-turn interactions, and cover a range of task properties and challenges in improving reinforcement learning algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmrl-gym-benchmarks-for-multi-turn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Segmentation of Optic Disc And Cup from Multiple Pseudo-labels by Noise-Aware Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-segmentation-of-optic-disc-and-cup</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The training framework of the MPNN is constructed by a teacher-student architecture to learn segmentation from clean pixels and noisy pixels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-segmentation-of-optic-disc-and-cup</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRC-GIF: Frame Ranking-based Personalized Artistic Media Generation Method for Resource Constrained Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frc-gif-frame-ranking-based-personalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating video highlights in the form of animated graphics interchange formats (GIFs) has significantly simplified the process of video browsing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frc-gif-frame-ranking-based-personalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the convergence of adaptive first order methods: proximal gradient and alternating minimization algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-convergence-of-adaptive-first-order</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon recent works on linesearch-free adaptive proximal gradient methods, this paper proposes AdaPG$^{\pi, r}$, a framework that unifies and extends existing results by providing larger stepsize policies and improved lower bounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-convergence-of-adaptive-first-order</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAST: Cross-Attention in Space and Time for Video Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cast-cross-attention-in-space-and-time-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel two-stream architecture, called Cross-Attention in Space and Time (CAST), that achieves a balanced spatio-temporal understanding of videos using only RGB input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cast-cross-attention-in-space-and-time-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparison Between Invariant and Equivariant Classical and Quantum Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-between-invariant-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we perform a fair and comprehensive comparison between classical graph neural networks (GNNs) and equivariant graph neural networks (EGNNs) and their quantum counterparts: quantum graph neural networks (QGNNs) and equivariant quantum graph neural networks (EQGNN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-between-invariant-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CritiqueLLM: Scaling LLM-as-Critic for Effective and Explainable Evaluation of Large Language Model Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/critiquellm-scaling-llm-as-critic-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the natural language processing (NLP) community started to make large language models (LLMs), such as GPT-4, act as a critic to evaluate the quality of generated texts, most of them only train a critique generation model of a specific scale on specific datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/critiquellm-scaling-llm-as-critic-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mPLUG-PaperOwl: Scientific Diagram Analysis with the Multimodal Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mplug-paperowl-scientific-diagram-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, towards a more versatile copilot for academic paper writing, we mainly focus on strengthening the multi-modal diagram analysis ability of Multimodal LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mplug-paperowl-scientific-diagram-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLD: Category-agnostic 3D Reconstruction of Interacting Hands and Objects from Video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hold-category-agnostic-3d-reconstruction-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since humans interact with diverse objects every day, the holistic 3D capture of these interactions is important to understand and model human behaviour.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hold-category-agnostic-3d-reconstruction-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perturbation-based Analysis of Compositional Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perturbation-based-analysis-of-compositional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing statistical methods for compositional data analysis are inadequate for many modern applications for two reasons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perturbation-based-analysis-of-compositional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steering Deep Feature Learning with Backward Aligned Feature Updates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steering-deep-feature-learning-with-backward</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning succeeds by doing hierarchical feature learning, yet tuning Hyper-Parameters (HP) such as initialization scales, learning rates etc., only give indirect control over this behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steering-deep-feature-learning-with-backward</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoRec: An Easy Approach for Coordination Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/corec-an-easy-approach-for-coordination</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we observe and address the challenges of the coordination recognition task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/corec-an-easy-approach-for-coordination</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructSeq: Unifying Vision Tasks with Instruction-conditioned Multi-modal Sequence Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructseq-unifying-vision-tasks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce InstructSeq, an instruction-conditioned multi-modal modeling framework that unifies diverse vision tasks through flexible natural language control and handling of both visual and textual data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructseq-unifying-vision-tasks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing ZX-Diagrams with Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-zx-diagrams-with-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ZX-diagrams are a powerful graphical language for the description of quantum processes with applications in fundamental quantum mechanics, quantum circuit optimization, tensor network simulation, and many more.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-zx-diagrams-with-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LL3DA: Visual Interactive Instruction Tuning for Omni-3D Understanding, Reasoning, and Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ll3da-visual-interactive-instruction-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, developing LMMs that can comprehend, reason, and plan in complex and diverse 3D environments remains a challenging topic, especially considering the demand for understanding permutation-invariant point cloud 3D representations of the 3D scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ll3da-visual-interactive-instruction-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCOPE-RL: A Python Library for Offline Reinforcement Learning and Off-Policy Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scope-rl-a-python-library-for-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces SCOPE-RL, a comprehensive open-source Python software designed for offline reinforcement learning (offline RL), off-policy evaluation (OPE), and selection (OPS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scope-rl-a-python-library-for-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hubness Reduction Improves Sentence-BERT Semantic Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hubness-reduction-improves-sentence-bert</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that when hubness is high, we can reduce error rate and hubness using hubness reduction methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hubness-reduction-improves-sentence-bert</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detection of tonic-clonic seizures in children with epilepsy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-of-tonic-clonic-seizures-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Epilepsy, a neurological condition characterized by recurrent, unprovoked seizures, profoundly impacts the lives of approximately 50 million individuals worldwide.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-of-tonic-clonic-seizures-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaskBench: Benchmarking Large Language Models for Task Automation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskbench-benchmarking-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce TaskBench to evaluate the capability of LLMs in task automation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskbench-benchmarking-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Underwater Image Enhancement All Object Detectors Need?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-underwater-image-enhancement-all-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Coupled with 7 object detection models retrained using raw underwater images, we employ these 133 models to comprehensively analyze the effect of underwater image enhancement on underwater object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-underwater-image-enhancement-all-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TLDR: Text Based Last-layer Retraining for Debiasing Image Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tldr-text-based-last-layer-retraining-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, Last Layer Retraining (LLR) with group-balanced datasets is known to be efficient in mitigating the spurious correlation of classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tldr-text-based-last-layer-retraining-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-InstructBLIP: A Framework for aligning X-Modal instruction-aware representations to LLMs and Emergent Cross-modal Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-instructblip-a-framework-for-aligning-x</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language pre-training and instruction tuning have demonstrated general-purpose capabilities in 2D visual reasoning tasks by aligning visual encoders with state-of-the-art large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-instructblip-a-framework-for-aligning-x</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TCP:Textual-based Class-aware Prompt tuning for Visual-Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tcp-textual-based-class-aware-prompt-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, those textual tokens have a limited generalization ability regarding unseen domains, as they cannot dynamically adjust to the distribution of testing classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tcp-textual-based-class-aware-prompt-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ArcMMLU: A Library and Information Science Benchmark for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arcmmlu-a-library-and-information-science</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response to this need, this paper introduces ArcMMLU, a specialized benchmark tailored for the Library & Information Science (LIS) domain in Chinese.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arcmmlu-a-library-and-information-science</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A data-science pipeline to enable the Interpretability of Many-Objective Feature Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-science-pipeline-to-enable-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The methodology supports the data scientist in the selection of an optimal feature subset by providing her with high-level information at three different levels: objectives, solutions, and individual features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-science-pipeline-to-enable-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dichotomy of Early and Late Phase Implicit Biases Can Provably Induce Grokking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dichotomy-of-early-and-late-phase-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work by Power et al. (2022) highlighted a surprising "grokking" phenomenon in learning arithmetic tasks: a neural net first "memorizes" the training set, resulting in perfect training accuracy but near-random test accuracy, and after training for sufficiently longer, it suddenly transitions to perfect test accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dichotomy-of-early-and-late-phase-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransCORALNet: A Two-Stream Transformer CORAL Networks for Supply Chain Credit Assessment Cold Start</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transcoralnet-a-two-stream-transformer-coral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to the domain adaptation capability of the proposed model, the domain shift between the source and target domain is minimized.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transcoralnet-a-two-stream-transformer-coral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the hierarchical structure of human plans via program generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-hierarchical-structure-of-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that humans are sensitive to both metrics, but that both accounts fail to predict a qualitative feature of human-created programs, namely that people prefer programs with reuse over and above the predictions of MDL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-hierarchical-structure-of-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt-Based Exemplar Super-Compression and Regeneration for Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-based-exemplar-super-compression-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Replay-based methods in class-incremental learning (CIL) have attained remarkable success, as replaying the exemplars of old classes can significantly mitigate catastrophic forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-based-exemplar-super-compression-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Impact of Flaky Simulators on Testing Autonomous Driving Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-impact-of-flaky-simulators-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our empirical results, obtained from two widely-used open-source ADS simulators and five diverse ADS test setups, show that test flakiness in ADS is a common occurrence and can significantly impact the test results obtained by randomized algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-impact-of-flaky-simulators-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLLMs-Augmented Visual-Language Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mllms-augmented-visual-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual-language pre-training (VLP) have achieved remarkable success in multi-modal tasks, largely attributed to the availability of large-scale image-text datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mllms-augmented-visual-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Robust Precipitation Forecaster by Temporal Frame Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-precipitation-forecaster-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in deep learning have propelled the field of weather prediction models to new heights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-precipitation-forecaster-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaXTron: Mask Transformer with Trajectory Attention for Video Panoptic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maxtron-mask-transformer-with-trajectory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate the issue, we propose to adapt the trajectory attention for both the dense pixel features and object queries, aiming to improve the short-term and long-term tracking results, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maxtron-mask-transformer-with-trajectory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving the Team Orienteering Problem with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-the-team-orienteering-problem-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This problem is usually modeled as a Combinatorial Optimization problem named as Team Orienteering Problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-the-team-orienteering-problem-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIDE: Test Time Few Shot Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tide-test-time-few-shot-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few-shot object detection (FSOD) aims to extract semantic knowledge from limited object instances of novel categories within a target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tide-test-time-few-shot-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAT-DM: Controllable Accelerated Virtual Try-on with Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-dm-controllable-accelerated-virtual-try</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image-based virtual try-on enables users to virtually try on different garments by altering original clothes in their photographs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-dm-controllable-accelerated-virtual-try</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FFT: Towards Harmlessness Evaluation and Analysis for LLMs with Factuality, Fairness, Toxicity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fft-towards-harmlessness-evaluation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The widespread of generative artificial intelligence has heightened concerns about the potential harms posed by AI-generated texts, primarily stemming from factoid, unfair, and toxic content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fft-towards-harmlessness-evaluation-and</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
