<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 21:10:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>EffiBench-X: A Multi-Language Benchmark for Measuring Efficiency of LLM-Generated Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effibench-x-a-multi-language-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLMs show better efficiency in Python, Ruby, and JavaScript than in Java, C++, and Golang.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effibench-x-a-multi-language-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JNLP at SemEval-2025 Task 11: Cross-Lingual Multi-Label Emotion Detection Using Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jnlp-at-semeval-2025-task-11-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our paper focuses on two sub-tracks of this task: (1) Track A: Multi-label emotion detection, and (2) Track B: Emotion intensity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jnlp-at-semeval-2025-task-11-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIE: Controlling Language Model Text Generations Using Continuous Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cie-controlling-language-model-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This calls for designing methods that can allow users to control the properties of the language that LMs generate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cie-controlling-language-model-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEALLM: Advancing Facial Emotion Analysis in Multimodal Large Language Models with Emotional Synergy and Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feallm-advancing-facial-emotion-analysis-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial Emotion Analysis (FEA) plays a crucial role in visual affective computing, aiming to infer a person's emotional state based on facial data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feallm-advancing-facial-emotion-analysis-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Transformer via Unrolling of Mixed Graph Algorithms for Traffic Forecast</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-transformer-via-unrolling-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To forecast traffic with both spatial and temporal dimensions, we unroll a mixed-graph-based optimization algorithm into a lightweight and interpretable transformer-like neural net.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-transformer-via-unrolling-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Adapt to Position Bias in Vision Transformer Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-adapt-to-position-bias-in-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show various levels of position bias in different datasets, and find that the optimal choice of position embedding depends on the position bias apparent in the dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-adapt-to-position-bias-in-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Degradation-Aware Feature Perturbation for All-in-One Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/degradation-aware-feature-perturbation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, motivated by the routing strategy, we propose DFPIR, a novel all-in-one image restorer that introduces Degradation-aware Feature Perturbations(DFP) to adjust the feature space to align with the unified parameter space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/degradation-aware-feature-perturbation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoMat: Enabling Automated Crystal Structure Reconstruction from Microscopy via Agentic Tool Use</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automat-enabling-automated-crystal-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning-based interatomic potentials and force fields depend critically on accurate atomic structures, yet such data are scarce due to the limited availability of experimentally resolved crystals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automat-enabling-automated-crystal-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Turn-Taking and Backchannel in Human-Machine Conversations Using Linguistic, Acoustic, and Visual Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-turn-taking-and-backchannel-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From this, we construct a Multi-Modal Face-to-Face (MM-F2F) human conversation dataset, including over 1. 5M words and corresponding turn-taking and backchannel annotations from approximately 20M frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-turn-taking-and-backchannel-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text2midi-InferAlign: Improving Symbolic Music Generation with Inference-Time Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2midi-inferalign-improving-symbolic-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Text2midi-InferAlign, a novel technique for improving symbolic music generation at inference time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2midi-inferalign-improving-symbolic-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Token is Worth over 1,000 Tokens: Efficient Knowledge Distillation through Low-Rank Clone</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-token-is-worth-over-1000-tokens-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training high-performing Small Language Models (SLMs) remains costly, even with knowledge distillation and pruning from larger teacher models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-token-is-worth-over-1000-tokens-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recollection from Pensieve: Novel View Synthesis via Learning from Uncalibrated Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recollection-from-pensieve-novel-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first stage, we learn to reconstruct the scene implicitly in a latent space without relying on any explicit 3D representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recollection-from-pensieve-novel-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPRet: A Dataset, Benchmark, and Model for Retrieval in Competitive Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cpret-a-dataset-benchmark-and-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the lack of both data and models, solving this problem is challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cpret-a-dataset-benchmark-and-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMAR: A Challenging Benchmark for Deep Reasoning in Speech, Audio, Music, and Their Mix</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmar-a-challenging-benchmark-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Each item in the benchmark demands multi-step deep reasoning beyond surface-level understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmar-a-challenging-benchmark-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Higher fidelity perceptual image and video compression with a latent conditioned residual denoising diffusion model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/higher-fidelity-perceptual-image-and-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a hybrid compression scheme optimized for perceptual quality, extending the approach of the CDC model with a decoder network in order to reduce the impact on distortion metrics such as PSNR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/higher-fidelity-perceptual-image-and-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DD-Ranking: Rethinking the Evaluation of Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dd-ranking-rethinking-the-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, dataset distillation has provided a reliable solution for data compression, where models trained on the resulting smaller synthetic datasets achieve performance comparable to those trained on the original datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dd-ranking-rethinking-the-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MA-COIR: Leveraging Semantic Search Index and Generative Models for Ontology-Driven Biomedical Concept Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ma-coir-leveraging-semantic-search-index-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizing biomedical concepts in the text is vital for ontology refinement, knowledge graph construction, and concept relationship discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ma-coir-leveraging-semantic-search-index-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G1: Bootstrapping Perception and Reasoning Abilities of Vision-Language Model via Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g1-bootstrapping-perception-and-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-Language Models (VLMs) excel in many direct multimodal tasks but struggle to translate this prowess into effective decision-making within interactive, visually rich environments like games.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g1-bootstrapping-perception-and-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Step Diffusion via Score identity Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-step-diffusion-via-score-identity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comprehensive experiments on SD1. 5 and SDXL demonstrate state-of-the-art performance in both one-step and few-step generation settings, along with robustness to the absence of real images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-step-diffusion-via-score-identity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Speech Language Modeling via Energy Distance in Continuous Latent Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-speech-language-modeling-via-energy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce SLED, an alternative approach to speech language modeling by encoding speech waveforms into sequences of continuous latent representations and modeling them autoregressively using an energy distance objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-speech-language-modeling-via-energy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Reward Model Evaluation Through the Lens of Reward Overoptimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-reward-model-evaluation-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reward models (RMs) play a crucial role in reinforcement learning from human feedback (RLHF), aligning model behavior with human preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-reward-model-evaluation-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRAbench and GenEval: Scaling Fine-Grained Aspect Evaluation across Tasks, Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frabench-and-geneval-scaling-fine-grained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating the open-ended outputs of large language models (LLMs) has become a bottleneck as model capabilities, task diversity, and modality coverage rapidly expand.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frabench-and-geneval-scaling-fine-grained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GuRE:Generative Query REwriter for Legal Passage Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gure-generative-query-rewriter-for-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One primary reason is the significant vocabulary mismatch between the query and the target passage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gure-generative-query-rewriter-for-legal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-PRM: Enhancing Multimodal Mathematical Reasoning with Scalable Step-Level Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-prm-enhancing-multimodal-mathematical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) have achieved impressive progress in vision-language understanding, they still struggle with complex multi-step reasoning, often producing logically inconsistent or partially correct solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-prm-enhancing-multimodal-mathematical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlearning for Federated Online Learning to Rank: A Reproducibility Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlearning-for-federated-online-learning-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper reports on findings from a comparative study on the effectiveness and efficiency of federated unlearning strategies within Federated Online Learning to Rank (FOLTR), with specific attention to systematically analysing the unlearning capabilities of methods in a verifiable manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlearning-for-federated-online-learning-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Local Details to Global Context: Advancing Vision-Language Models with Attention-Based Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-local-details-to-global-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pretrained vision-language models (VLMs), e. g., CLIP, demonstrate impressive zero-shot capabilities on downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-local-details-to-global-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'll believe it when I see it: Images increase misinformation sharing in Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-ll-believe-it-when-i-see-it-images-increase</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In humans, visual content is known to boost credibility and shareability of information, yet its effect on vision-language models (VLMs) remains unclear.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-ll-believe-it-when-i-see-it-images-increase</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow-FT: Tuning Instruct via Base</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadow-ft-tuning-instruct-via-base</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key insight is to fine-tune the BASE model, and then directly graft the learned weight updates to the INSTRUCT model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadow-ft-tuning-instruct-via-base</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StarFT: Robust Fine-tuning of Zero-shot Models via Spuriosity Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/starft-robust-fine-tuning-of-zero-shot-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a regularization that aligns the output distribution for spuriosity-injected labels with the original zero-shot model, ensuring that the model is not induced to extract irrelevant features further from these descriptions. We leverage recent language models to get such spuriosity-injected labels by generating alternative textual descriptions that highlight potentially confounding features. Extensive experiments validate the robust generalization of StarFT and its emerging properties: zero-shot group robustness and improved zero-shot classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/starft-robust-fine-tuning-of-zero-shot-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGI-1: Autoregressive Video Generation at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magi-1-autoregressive-video-generation-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present MAGI-1, a world model that generates videos by autoregressively predicting a sequence of video chunks, defined as fixed-length segments of consecutive frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magi-1-autoregressive-video-generation-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Low-Latency Event Stream-based Visual Object Tracking: A Slow-Fast Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-low-latency-event-stream-based-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing tracking algorithms typically rely on low-frame-rate RGB cameras coupled with computationally intensive deep neural network architectures to achieve effective tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-low-latency-event-stream-based-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-KG-Bench 3.0: A Compass for SemanticTechnology Capabilities in the Ocean of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-kg-bench-3-0-a-compass-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper the LLM-KG-Bench framework is presented in Version 3 along with a dataset of prompts, answers and evaluations generated with it and several state-of-the-art LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-kg-bench-3-0-a-compass-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Graph Induced Contour-aware Heat Conduction Network for Event-based Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-graph-induced-contour-aware-heat</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, this paper proposes a novel dynamic graph induced contour-aware heat conduction network for event stream based object detection, termed CvHeat-DET.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-graph-induced-contour-aware-heat</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Low Rank Adaptation Lead to Lower Robustness against Training-Time Attacks?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-low-rank-adaptation-lead-to-lower</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we theoretically investigate the security implications of LoRA's low-rank structure during fine-tuning, in the context of its robustness against data poisoning and backdoor attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-low-rank-adaptation-lead-to-lower</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MindOmni: Unleashing Reasoning Generation in Vision Language Models with RGPO</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mindomni-unleashing-reasoning-generation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent text-to-image systems face limitations in handling multimodal inputs and complex reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mindomni-unleashing-reasoning-generation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardware-Adaptive and Superlinear-Capacity Memristor-based Associative Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardware-adaptive-and-superlinear-capacity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we introduce and experimentally demonstrate on integrated memristor hardware a new hardware-adaptive learning algorithm for associative memories that significantly improves defect tolerance and capacity, and naturally extends to scalable multilayer architectures capable of handling both binary and continuous patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardware-adaptive-and-superlinear-capacity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Arena: Towards Democratic and Scalable Automatic Evaluation of Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-arena-towards-democratic-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent explosion of large language models (LLMs), each with its own general or specialized strengths, makes scalable, reliable benchmarking more urgent than ever.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-arena-towards-democratic-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Agent Reinforcement Learning for Automated Feature Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-agent-reinforcement-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose a novel dual-agent reinforcement learning method for feature generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-agent-reinforcement-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Study on the Refining Handwritten Font by Mixing Font Styles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-study-on-the-refining-handwritten-font-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Handwritten fonts have a distinct expressive character, but they are often difficult to read due to unclear or inconsistent handwriting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-study-on-the-refining-handwritten-font-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Occult: Optimizing Collaborative Communication across Experts for Accelerated Parallel MoE Training and Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occult-optimizing-collaborative-communication</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It motivates us to strategically optimize collaborative communication for accelerated MoE training and inference, dubbed Occult.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occult-optimizing-collaborative-communication</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEM: Gaussian Embedding Modeling for Out-of-Distribution Detection in GUI Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gem-gaussian-embedding-modeling-for-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional OOD detection methods perform suboptimally in this domain due to the complex embedding space and evolving GUI environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gem-gaussian-embedding-modeling-for-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ineq-Comp: Benchmarking Human-Intuitive Compositional Reasoning in Automated Theorem Proving on Inequalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ineq-comp-benchmarking-human-intuitive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLM-based formal proof assistants (e. g., in Lean) hold great promise for automating mathematical discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ineq-comp-benchmarking-human-intuitive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The role of data partitioning on the performance of EEG-based deep learning models in supervised cross-subject analysis: a preliminary study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-role-of-data-partitioning-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To assist researchers in identifying optimal experimental strategies, this paper thoroughly investigates the role of data partitioning and cross-validation in evaluating EEG deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-role-of-data-partitioning-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uniformity First: Uniformity-aware Test-time Adaptation of Vision-language Models against Image Corruption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniformity-first-uniformity-aware-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We found that this is because image embeddings are "corrupted" in terms of uniformity, a measure related to the amount of information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniformity-first-uniformity-aware-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picturized and Recited with Dialects: A Multimodal Chinese Representation Framework for Sentiment Analysis of Classical Chinese Poetry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/picturized-and-recited-with-dialects-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a dialect-enhanced multimodal framework for classical Chinese poetry sentiment analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/picturized-and-recited-with-dialects-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MatPredict: a dataset and benchmark for learning material properties of diverse indoor objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matpredict-a-dataset-and-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To support this, we introduce MatPredict, a dataset that combines the high-quality synthetic objects from Replica dataset with MatSynth dataset's material properties classes - to create objects with diverse material properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matpredict-a-dataset-and-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Functional: Learning Function to Scalar Maps for Neural PDE Surrogates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-functional-learning-function-to-scalar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many architectures for neural PDE surrogates have been proposed in recent years, largely based on neural networks or operator learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-functional-learning-function-to-scalar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Explanations for Continuous Action Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanations-for-continuous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning (RL) has shown great promise in domains like healthcare and robotics but often struggles with adoption due to its lack of interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanations-for-continuous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VTBench: Evaluating Visual Tokenizers for Autoregressive Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vtbench-evaluating-visual-tokenizers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we introduce VTBench, a comprehensive benchmark that systematically evaluates VTs across three core tasks: Image Reconstruction, Detail Preservation, and Text Preservation, and covers a diverse range of evaluation scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vtbench-evaluating-visual-tokenizers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Step Offline Distillation of Diffusion-based Models via Koopman Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-step-offline-distillation-of-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide theoretical justification for our approach: (1) under mild assumptions, the learned diffusion dynamics admit a finite-dimensional Koopman representation; and (2) proximity in the Koopman latent space correlates with semantic similarity in the generated outputs, allowing for effective trajectory alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-step-offline-distillation-of-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
