<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 21:07:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-Encoding Morph-Tokens for Multimodal LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-encoding-morph-tokens-for-multimodal-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For multimodal LLMs, the synergy of visual comprehension (textual output) and generation (visual output) presents an ongoing challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-encoding-morph-tokens-for-multimodal-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe-Eval: A hard evaluation suite for measuring progress of multimodal language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vibe-eval-a-hard-evaluation-suite-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Vibe-Eval: a new open benchmark and framework for evaluating multimodal chat models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vibe-eval-a-hard-evaluation-suite-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Context Flows for Learning Generalizable Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-context-flows-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Ordinary Differential Equations typically struggle to generalize to new dynamical behaviors created by parameter changes in the underlying system, even when the dynamics are close to previously seen behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-context-flows-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Attention Based Pipeline for Identifying Pre-Cancer Lesions in Head and Neck Clinical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attention-based-pipeline-for-identifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Early detection of cancer can help improve patient prognosis by early intervention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attention-based-pipeline-for-identifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Flow-Based Model for Conditional and Probabilistic Electricity Consumption Profile Generation and Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-flow-based-model-for-conditional-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Residential Load Profile (RLP) generation and prediction are critical for the operation and planning of distribution networks, particularly as diverse low-carbon technologies are increasingly integrated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-flow-based-model-for-conditional-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the test-time zero-shot generalization of vision-language models: Do we really need prompt learning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-test-time-zero-shot-generalization-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, our method does not rely on ad hoc rules (e. g., confidence threshold) used in some previous test-time augmentation techniques to filter the augmented views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-test-time-zero-shot-generalization-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-level projection with exponential parallel speedup; Application to sparse auto-encoders neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-projection-with-exponential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new bi-level projection method for which we show that the time complexity for the $\ell_{1,\infty}$ norm is only $\mathcal{O}\big(n m \big)$ for a matrix in $\mathbb{R}^{n\times m}$, and $\mathcal{O}\big(n + m \big)$ with full parallel power.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-projection-with-exponential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SFFNet: A Wavelet-Based Spatial and Frequency Domain Fusion Network for Remote Sensing Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sffnet-a-wavelet-based-spatial-and-frequency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to fully utilize spatial information for segmentation and address the challenge of handling areas with significant grayscale variations in remote sensing segmentation, we propose the SFFNet (Spatial and Frequency Domain Fusion Network) framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sffnet-a-wavelet-based-spatial-and-frequency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Detection of Source Code Clones via an Ensemble of Unsupervised Similarity Measures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advanced-detection-of-source-code-clones-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The capability of accurately determining code similarity is crucial in many tasks related to software development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advanced-detection-of-source-code-clones-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Micro Gesture Recognition for Emotion Understanding via Context-aware Visual-Text Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-micro-gesture-recognition-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, instead of using handcrafted prompts for visual-text contrastive learning, we propose a novel module called Adaptive prompting to generate context-aware prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-micro-gesture-recognition-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Learning for Real-World Super-Resolution from Dual and Multiple Zoomed Observations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-for-real-world-super-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we further take multiple zoomed observations to explore self-supervised RefSR, and present a progressive fusion scheme for the effective utilization of reference images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-for-real-world-super-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Pre-trained Teacher: Towards Robust Feature Discrepancy for Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-pre-trained-teacher-towards-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of knowledge distillation mainly relies on how to keep the feature discrepancy between the teacher and student model, in which it assumes that: (1) the teacher model can jointly represent two different distributions for the normal and abnormal patterns, while (2) the student model can only reconstruct the normal distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-pre-trained-teacher-towards-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinySeg: Model Optimizing Framework for Image Segmentation on Tiny Embedded Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyseg-model-optimizing-framework-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work implements TinySeg on top of the existing tiny machine learning framework and demonstrates that TinySeg can reduce the peak memory usage of an image segmentation model by 39. 3% for tiny embedded systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyseg-model-optimizing-framework-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlotGAT: Slot-based Message Passing for Heterogeneous Graph Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slotgat-slot-based-message-passing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We identify a potential semantic mixing issue in existing message passing processes, where the representations of the neighbors of a node $v$ are forced to be transformed to the feature space of $v$ for aggregation, though the neighbors are in different types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slotgat-slot-based-message-passing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Concept Alignment in Vision-Language Concept Bottleneck Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-concept-alignment-in-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concept Bottleneck Models (CBM) map the input image to a high-level human-understandable concept space and then make class predictions based on these concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-concept-alignment-in-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probablistic Restoration with Adaptive Noise Sampling for 3D Human Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probablistic-restoration-with-adaptive-noise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The accuracy and robustness of 3D human pose estimation (HPE) are limited by 2D pose detection errors and 2D to 3D ill-posed challenges, which have drawn great attention to Multi-Hypothesis HPE research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probablistic-restoration-with-adaptive-noise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning control strategies for Electric Vehicles and Renewable energy sources Virtual Power Plants</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-control-strategies-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research on Reinforcement Learning control strategies for Electric Vehicles and Renewable energy sources Virtual Power Plants focuses on providing solutions for such energy supply optimization models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-control-strategies-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularized Q-learning through Robust Averaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularized-q-learning-through-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new Q-learning variant, called 2RA Q-learning, that addresses some weaknesses of existing Q-learning methods in a principled manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularized-q-learning-through-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stabilizing Backpropagation Through Time to Learn Complex Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stabilizing-backpropagation-through-time-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Of all the vector fields surrounding the minima of recurrent learning setups, the gradient field with its exploding and vanishing updates appears a poor choice for optimization, offering little beyond efficient computability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stabilizing-backpropagation-through-time-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOPICAL: TOPIC Pages AutomagicaLly</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topical-topic-pages-automagically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topic pages aggregate useful information about an entity or concept into a single succinct and accessible article.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topical-topic-pages-automagically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Koopman Data-Driven Predictive Control with Robust Stability and Recursive Feasibility Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/koopman-data-driven-predictive-control-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we consider the design of data-driven predictive controllers for nonlinear systems from input-output data via linear-in-control input Koopman lifted models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/koopman-data-driven-predictive-control-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Random Pareto front surfaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-pareto-front-surfaces</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a motivating example, we investigate how these statistics can be used within a design of experiments setting, where the goal is to both infer and use the Pareto front surface distribution in order to make effective decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-pareto-front-surfaces</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community-Invariant Graph Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/community-invariant-graph-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph augmentation has received great attention in recent years for graph contrastive learning (GCL) to learn well-generalized node/graph representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/community-invariant-graph-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MFDS-Net: Multi-Scale Feature Depth-Supervised Network for Remote Sensing Change Detection with Global Semantic and Detail Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mfds-net-multi-scale-feature-depth-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose MFDS-Net: Multi-Scale Feature Depth-Supervised Network for Remote Sensing Change Detection with Global Semantic and Detail Information (MFDS-Net) with the aim of achieving a more refined description of changing buildings as well as geographic information, enhancing the localisation of changing targets and the acquisition of weak features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mfds-net-multi-scale-feature-depth-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMON: A Simple yet Effective Approach for Argument Structure Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dmon-a-simple-yet-effective-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Argument structure learning~(ASL) entails predicting relations between arguments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dmon-a-simple-yet-effective-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less is More: on the Over-Globalizing Problem in Graph Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-on-the-over-globalizing-problem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then we propose a novel Bi-Level Global Graph Transformer with Collaborative Training (CoBFormer), including the inter-cluster and intra-cluster Transformers, to prevent the over-globalizing problem while keeping the ability to extract valuable information from distant nodes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-on-the-over-globalizing-problem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing the Role of Semantic Representations in the Era of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-role-of-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that it is difficult to predict which input examples AMR may help or hurt on, but errors tend to arise with multi-word expressions, named entities, and in the final inference step where the LLM must connect its reasoning over the AMR to its prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-role-of-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard-Thresholding Meets Evolution Strategies in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-thresholding-meets-evolution-strategies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evolution Strategies (ES) have emerged as a competitive alternative for model-free reinforcement learning, showcasing exemplary performance in tasks like Mujoco and Atari.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-thresholding-meets-evolution-strategies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correcting Biased Centered Kernel Alignment Measures in Biological and Artificial Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correcting-biased-centered-kernel-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using fMRI and MEG data from the THINGS project, we show that if biased CKA is applied to representations of different sizes in the low-data high-dimensionality domain, they are not directly comparable due to biased CKA's sensitivity to differing feature-sample ratios and not stimuli-driven responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correcting-biased-centered-kernel-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeMo-Aligner: Scalable Toolkit for Efficient Model Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nemo-aligner-scalable-toolkit-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, building efficient tools to perform alignment can be challenging, especially for the largest and most competent LLMs which often contain tens or hundreds of billions of parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nemo-aligner-scalable-toolkit-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UQA: Corpus for Urdu Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uqa-corpus-for-urdu-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces UQA, a novel dataset for question answering and text comprehension in Urdu, a low-resource language with over 70 million native speakers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uqa-corpus-for-urdu-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-distribution detection based on subspace projection of high-dimensional features output by the last convolutional layer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon this, we have modified the batch normalization (BN) and ReLU layer preceding the fully connected layer, diminishing their impact on the output feature distributions and thereby widening the distribution gap between ID and OOD data features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Consistent Object Detection via LiDAR-Camera Synergy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-consistent-object-detection-via-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In light of this, this paper introduces an end-to-end Consistency Object Detection (COD) algorithm framework that requires only a single forward inference to simultaneously obtain an object's position in both point clouds and images and establish their correlation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-consistent-object-detection-via-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S$^2$AC: Energy-Based Reinforcement Learning with Stein Soft Actor Critic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-2-ac-energy-based-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We derive a closed-form expression of the entropy of such policies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-2-ac-energy-based-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Purify Unlearnable Examples via Rate-Constrained Variational Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/purify-unlearnable-examples-via-rate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this network, a two-stage purification approach is naturally developed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/purify-unlearnable-examples-via-rate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prometheus 2: An Open Source Language Model Specialized in Evaluating Other Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prometheus-2-an-open-source-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Proprietary LMs such as GPT-4 are often employed to assess the quality of responses from various LMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prometheus-2-an-open-source-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Switching for Reset-Free RL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intelligent-switching-for-reset-free-rl</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the real world, the strong episode resetting mechanisms that are needed to train agents in simulation are unavailable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intelligent-switching-for-reset-free-rl</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test-time Assessment of a Model's Performance on Unseen Domains via Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-assessment-of-a-model-s-performance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, our metric characterizes the model's performance on unseen domains using only a small amount of unlabeled data from these domains and data or statistics from the training (source) domain(s).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-assessment-of-a-model-s-performance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long Tail Image Generation Through Feature Space Augmentation and Iterated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tail-image-generation-through-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image and multimodal machine learning tasks are very challenging to solve in the case of poorly distributed data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tail-image-generation-through-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FeNNol: an Efficient and Flexible Library for Building Force-field-enhanced Neural Network Potentials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fennol-an-efficient-and-flexible-library-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural network interatomic potentials (NNPs) have recently proven to be powerful tools to accurately model complex molecular systems while bypassing the high numerical cost of ab-initio molecular dynamics simulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fennol-an-efficient-and-flexible-library-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D2PO: Discriminator-Guided DPO with Response Evaluation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d2po-discriminator-guided-dpo-with-response</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Varied approaches for aligning language models have been proposed, including supervised fine-tuning, RLHF, and direct optimization methods such as DPO.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d2po-discriminator-guided-dpo-with-response</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Model Inspection for Better Understanding Performance Characteristics of Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-importance-of-model-inspection-for-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study highlights the importance of conducting comprehensive model inspection as part of comparative performance analyses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-importance-of-model-inspection-for-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Jailbreak Attack with Momentum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-jailbreak-attack-with-momentum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, the Greedy Coordinate Gradient (GCG) attack has demonstrated efficacy in exploiting this vulnerability by optimizing adversarial prompts through a combination of gradient heuristics and greedy search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-jailbreak-attack-with-momentum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spider: A Unified Framework for Context-dependent Concept Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spider-a-unified-framework-for-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from the context-independent (CI) concepts such as human, car, and airplane, context-dependent (CD) concepts require higher visual understanding ability, such as camouflaged object and medical lesion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spider-a-unified-framework-for-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StoryDiffusion: Consistent Self-Attention for Long-Range Image and Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/storydiffusion-consistent-self-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This module converts the generated sequence of images into videos with smooth transitions and consistent subjects that are significantly more stable than the modules based on latent spaces only, especially in the context of long video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/storydiffusion-consistent-self-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sample-efficient neural likelihood-free Bayesian inference of implicit HMMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-efficient-neural-likelihood-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Naive application of these methods to a HMM, ignoring the inference of this joint posterior distribution, will thus produce an inaccurate estimate of the posterior predictive distribution, in turn hampering the assessment of goodness-of-fit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-efficient-neural-likelihood-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Privacy Power of Correlated Noise in Decentralized Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-privacy-power-of-correlated-noise-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decentralized learning is appealing as it enables the scalable usage of large amounts of distributed data and resources (without resorting to any central entity), while promoting privacy since every user minimizes the direct exposure of their data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-privacy-power-of-correlated-noise-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development of Skip Connection in Deep Neural Networks for Computer Vision and Medical Image Analysis: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/development-of-skip-connection-in-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning has made significant progress in computer vision, specifically in image classification, object detection, and semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/development-of-skip-connection-in-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair Recommendations with Limited Sensitive Attributes: A Distributionally Robust Optimization Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-recommendations-with-limited-sensitive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose Distributionally Robust Fair Optimization (DRFO), which minimizes the worst-case unfairness over all potential probability distributions of missing sensitive attributes instead of the reconstructed one to account for the impact of the reconstruction errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-recommendations-with-limited-sensitive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explaining models relating objects and privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-models-relating-objects-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To explain the decision of these models, we use feature-attribution to identify and quantify which objects (and which of their features) are more relevant to privacy classification with respect to a reference input (i. e., no objects localised in an image) predicted as public.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-models-relating-objects-and</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
