<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 09:12:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Towards the Law of Capacity Gap in Distilling Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-law-of-capacity-gap-in-distilling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pain is mainly resulted by the curse of capacity gap, which describes that a larger teacher LM cannot always lead to a better student LM than one distilled from a smaller teacher LM due to the affect of capacity gap increment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-law-of-capacity-gap-in-distilling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volcano: Mitigating Multimodal Hallucination through Self-Feedback Guided Revision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volcano-mitigating-multimodal-hallucination</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through a qualitative analysis, we show that Volcano's feedback is properly grounded on the image than the initial response.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volcano-mitigating-multimodal-hallucination</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Multi-Pivot Ensembling with Massively Multilingual Machine Translation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-multi-pivot-ensembling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Massively multilingual machine translation models allow for the translation of a large number of languages with a single model, but have limited performance on low- and very-low-resource translation directions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-multi-pivot-ensembling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context Consistency between Training and Testing in Simultaneous Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-consistency-between-training-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Simultaneous Machine Translation (SiMT) aims to yield a real-time partial translation with a monotonically growing the source-side context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-consistency-between-training-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MonoDiffusion: Self-Supervised Monocular Depth Estimation Using Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monodiffusion-self-supervised-monocular-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because the depth ground-truth is unavailable in the training phase, we develop a pseudo ground-truth diffusion process to assist the diffusion in MonoDiffusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monodiffusion-self-supervised-monocular-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explaining black boxes with a SMILE: Statistical Model-agnostic Interpretability with Local Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-black-boxes-with-a-smile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning is currently undergoing an explosion in capability, popularity, and sophistication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-black-boxes-with-a-smile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Musical Object Discovery from Audio</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-musical-object-discovery-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our novel MusicSlots method adapts SlotAttention to the audio domain, to achieve unsupervised music decomposition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-musical-object-discovery-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-4V in Wonderland: Large Multimodal Models for Zero-Shot Smartphone GUI Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-4v-in-wonderland-large-multimodal-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first benchmark MM-Navigator on our collected iOS screen dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-4v-in-wonderland-large-multimodal-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>calamanCy: A Tagalog Natural Language Processing Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calamancy-a-tagalog-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce calamanCy, an open-source toolkit for constructing natural language processing (NLP) pipelines for Tagalog.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calamancy-a-tagalog-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Extensive Study on Adversarial Attack against Pre-trained Models of Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-extensive-study-on-adversarial-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although several approaches have been proposed to generate adversarial examples for PTMC, the effectiveness and efficiency of such approaches, especially on different code intelligence tasks, has not been well understood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-extensive-study-on-adversarial-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting As Labeling: Rethinking LiDAR-camera Fusion in 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-as-labeling-rethinking-lidar-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D object Detection with LiDAR-camera encounters overfitting in algorithm development which is derived from the violation of some fundamental rules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-as-labeling-rethinking-lidar-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing Value Imputation for Multi-attribute Sensor Data Streams via Message Propagation (Extended Version)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/missing-value-imputation-for-multi-attribute</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we propose a message propagation imputation network (MPIN) that is able to recover the missing values of data instances in a time window.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/missing-value-imputation-for-multi-attribute</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Not Easy Being Wrong: Evaluating Process of Elimination Reasoning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/it-s-not-easy-being-wrong-evaluating-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chain-of-thought (COT) prompting can help large language models (LLMs) reason toward correct answers, but its efficacy in reasoning toward incorrect answers is unexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/it-s-not-easy-being-wrong-evaluating-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WaterBench: Towards Holistic Evaluation of Watermarks for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/waterbench-towards-holistic-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the potential misuse of large language models (LLMs), recent research has developed watermarking algorithms, which restrict the generation process to leave an invisible trace for watermark detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/waterbench-towards-holistic-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROPANE: Prompt design as an inverse problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/propane-prompt-design-as-an-inverse-problem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Carefully-designed prompts are key to inducing desired behavior in Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/propane-prompt-design-as-an-inverse-problem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do large language models and humans have similar behaviors in causal inference with script knowledge?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-large-language-models-and-humans-have</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, reading times remain similar when cause A is not explicitly mentioned, indicating that humans can easily infer event B from their script knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-large-language-models-and-humans-have</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention-Challenging Multiple Instance Learning for Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-challenging-multiple-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overfitting remains a significant challenge in the application of Multiple Instance Learning (MIL) methods for Whole Slide Image (WSI) analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-challenging-multiple-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transpose Attack: Stealing Datasets with Bidirectional Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transpose-attack-stealing-datasets-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, in this work we show that neural networks can be taught to systematically memorize and retrieve specific samples from datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transpose-attack-stealing-datasets-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective In-vehicle Intrusion Detection via Multi-view Statistical Graph Learning on CAN Messages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-in-vehicle-intrusion-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose StatGraph: an Effective Multi-view Statistical Graph Learning Intrusion Detection to implement the fine-grained intrusion detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-in-vehicle-intrusion-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPHINX: The Joint Mixing of Weights, Tasks, and Visual Embeddings for Multi-modal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sphinx-the-joint-mixing-of-weights-tasks-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SPHINX, a versatile multi-modal large language model (MLLM) with a joint mixing of model weights, tuning tasks, and visual embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sphinx-the-joint-mixing-of-weights-tasks-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>arfpy: A python package for density estimation and generative modeling with adversarial random forests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arfpy-a-python-package-for-density-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces $\textit{arfpy}$, a python implementation of Adversarial Random Forests (ARF) (Watson et al., 2023), which is a lightweight procedure for synthesizing new data that resembles some given data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arfpy-a-python-package-for-density-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-4V(ision) as A Social Media Analysis Engine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-4v-ision-as-a-social-media-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our investigation begins with a preliminary quantitative analysis for each task using existing benchmark datasets, followed by a careful review of the results and a selection of qualitative samples that illustrate GPT-4V's potential in understanding multimodal social media content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-4v-ision-as-a-social-media-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADAMM: Anomaly Detection of Attributed Multi-graphs with Metadata: A Unified Neural Network Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adamm-anomaly-detection-of-attributed-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a complex graph database of node- and edge-attributed multi-graphs as well as associated metadata for each graph, how can we spot the anomalous instances?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adamm-anomaly-detection-of-attributed-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploration via linearly perturbed loss minimisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploration-via-linearly-perturbed-loss</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that, for the case of generalised linear bandits, EVILL reduces to perturbed history exploration (PHE), a method where exploration is done by training on randomly perturbed rewards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploration-via-linearly-perturbed-loss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explain-then-Translate: An Analysis on Improving Program Translation with Self-generated Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explain-then-translate-an-analysis-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work explores the use of self-generated natural language explanations as an intermediate step for code-to-code translation with language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explain-then-translate-an-analysis-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An LLM-free Multi-dimensional Benchmark for MLLMs Hallucination Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-llm-free-multi-dimensional-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite making significant progress in multi-modal tasks, current Multi-modal Large Language Models (MLLMs) encounter the significant challenge of hallucination, which may lead to harmful consequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-llm-free-multi-dimensional-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Symmetrization for Equivariance with Orbit Distance Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-symmetrization-for-equivariance-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a general framework for symmetrizing an arbitrary neural-network architecture and making it equivariant with respect to a given group.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-symmetrization-for-equivariance-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Search of the Long-Tail: Systematic Generation of Long-Tail Knowledge via Logical Rule Guided Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-search-of-the-long-tail-systematic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a Logic-Induced-Knowledge-Search (LINK) framework for systematically generating long-tail knowledge statements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-search-of-the-long-tail-systematic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connecting the Dots: Graph Neural Network Powered Ensemble and Classification of Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/connecting-the-dots-graph-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning models have demonstrated remarkable results for various computer vision tasks, including the realm of medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/connecting-the-dots-graph-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpNote: Black-box Large Language Models are Better Task Solvers with Experience Notebook</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expnote-black-box-large-language-models-are</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Black-box Large Language Models (LLMs) have shown great power in solving various tasks and are considered general problem solvers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expnote-black-box-large-language-models-are</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDDepth: Normal-Distance Assisted Monocular Depth Estimation and Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nddepth-normal-distance-assisted-monocular-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we develop a normal-distance head that outputs pixel-level surface normal and distance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nddepth-normal-distance-assisted-monocular-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Multiple Teachers for Test-Time Adaptation of Language-Guided Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-multiple-teachers-for-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent approaches have explored language-guided classifiers capable of classifying examples from novel tasks when provided with task-specific natural language explanations, instructions or prompts (Sanh et al., 2022; R. Menon et al., 2022).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-multiple-teachers-for-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple and Effective Input Reformulations for Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-and-effective-input-reformulations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we reformulate inputs during finetuning for challenging translation tasks, leveraging model strengths from pretraining in novel ways to improve downstream performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-and-effective-input-reformulations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Robustness of Question Rewriting Systems to Questions of Varying Hardness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-robustness-of-question-rewriting-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In conversational question answering (CQA), the task of question rewriting~(QR) in context aims to rewrite a context-dependent question into an equivalent self-contained question that gives the same answer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-robustness-of-question-rewriting-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfMLLM: A Unified Framework for Visual-Language Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infmllm-a-unified-framework-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments demonstrate that preserving the positional information of visual embeddings through the pool-adapter is particularly beneficial for tasks like visual grounding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infmllm-a-unified-framework-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DialMAT: Dialogue-Enabled Transformer with Moment-Based Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialmat-dialogue-enabled-transformer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper focuses on the DialFRED task, which is the task of embodied instruction following in a setting where an agent can actively ask questions about the task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialmat-dialogue-enabled-transformer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setting a Baseline for long-shot real-time Player and Ball detection in Soccer Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/setting-a-baseline-for-long-shot-real-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Players and ball detection are among the first required steps on a football analytics platform.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/setting-a-baseline-for-long-shot-real-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Perspective Transformation Based Vehicle Localization on Bird's Eye View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-perspective-transformation-based-vehicle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An accurate understanding of a self-driving vehicle's surrounding environment is crucial for its navigation system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-perspective-transformation-based-vehicle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CD-COCO: A Versatile Complex Distorted COCO Database for Scene-Context-Aware Computer Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cd-coco-a-versatile-complex-distorted-coco</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These new local distortions are generated by considering the scene context of the images that guarantees a high level of photo-realism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cd-coco-a-versatile-complex-distorted-coco</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tunable Soft Prompts are Messengers in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tunable-soft-prompts-are-messengers-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the global model itself is not required to be shared and the local training is conducted based on an auxiliary model with fewer parameters than the global model, the proposed approach provides protection for the global model while reducing communication and computation costs in FL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tunable-soft-prompts-are-messengers-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sampler Scheduler for Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampler-scheduler-for-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, only a single sampler algorithm can be specified on all sampling steps in the generative process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampler-scheduler-for-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Textual Normalization for Hate Speech Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-textual-normalization-for-hate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our dataset is accessible for research purposes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-textual-normalization-for-hate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning for Generalization, Robustness, Fairness: A Survey and Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-for-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this survey, we provide a systematic overview of the important and recent developments of research on federated learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-for-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Large Language Models Augment a Biomedical Ontology with missing Concepts and Relations?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-augment-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ontologies play a crucial role in organizing and representing knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-augment-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stain Consistency Learning: Handling Stain Variation for Automatic Digital Pathology Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stain-consistency-learning-handling-stain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerous methods have been developed to improve the robustness of machine learning methods to stain variation, but comparative studies have demonstrated limited benefits to performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stain-consistency-learning-handling-stain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Template Is All You Meme</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-template-is-all-you-meme</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, to aid understanding of memes, we release a knowledge base of memes and information found on www. knowyourmeme. com, which we call the Know Your Meme Knowledge Base (KYMKB), composed of more than 54, 000 images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-template-is-all-you-meme</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey: Image Resolution and Text Label Are Important Things for Large Multi-modal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monkey-image-resolution-and-text-label-are</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Multimodal Models have demonstrated impressive capabilities in understanding general vision-language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monkey-image-resolution-and-text-label-are</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generation Of Colors using Bidirectional Long Short Term Memory Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generation-of-colors-using-bidirectional-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research endeavors to bridge the gap between our visual perception of countless shades and our ability to articulate and name them accurately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generation-of-colors-using-bidirectional-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 3D Conditional Diffusion Model for Image Quality Transfer -- An Application to Low-Field MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-3d-conditional-diffusion-model-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-field (LF) MRI scanners (<1T) are still prevalent in settings with limited resources or unreliable power supply.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-3d-conditional-diffusion-model-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimum Description Length Hopfield Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimum-description-length-hopfield-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Associative memory architectures are designed for memorization but also offer, through their retrieval method, a form of generalization to unseen inputs: stored memories can be seen as prototypes from this point of view.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimum-description-length-hopfield-networks</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
