<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 09:11:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Fighting Fire with Fire: Can ChatGPT Detect AI-generated Text?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fighting-fire-with-fire-can-chatgpt-detect-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) such as ChatGPT are increasingly being used for various use cases, including text content generation at scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fighting-fire-with-fire-can-chatgpt-detect-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Generic: Enhancing Image Captioning with Real-World Knowledge using Vision-Language Pre-Training Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-generic-enhancing-image-captioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering that Vision-Language Pre-Training (VLP) models master massive such knowledge from large-scale web-harvested data, it is promising to utilize the generalizability of VLP models to incorporate knowledge into image descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-generic-enhancing-image-captioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Representation Learning for Periodic Time Series with Floss: A Frequency Domain Regularization Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-representation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we propose an unsupervised method called Floss that automatically regularizes learned representations in the frequency domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-representation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADS-Cap: A Framework for Accurate and Diverse Stylized Captioning with Unpaired Stylistic Corpora</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ads-cap-a-framework-for-accurate-and-diverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating visually grounded image captions with specific linguistic styles using unpaired stylistic corpora is a challenging task, especially since we expect stylized captions with a wide variety of stylistic patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ads-cap-a-framework-for-accurate-and-diverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FusionAD: Multi-modality Fusion for Prediction and Planning Tasks of Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusionad-multi-modality-fusion-for-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building a multi-modality multi-task neural network toward accurate and robust performance is a de-facto standard in perception task of autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusionad-multi-modality-fusion-for-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRNES: Enabling Security and Privacy-aware Experience Sharing in Multiagent Robotic and Autonomous Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brnes-enabling-security-and-privacy-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nevertheless, in a real-world setting, some Byzantine attackers, disguised as advisors, may provide false advice to the advisee and catastrophically degrade the overall learning performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brnes-enabling-security-and-privacy-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Multilingual Language Models Think Better in English?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-multilingual-language-models-think-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a new approach called self-translate, which overcomes the need of an external translation system by leveraging the few-shot translation capabilities of multilingual language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-multilingual-language-models-think-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point Anywhere: Directed Object Estimation from Omnidirectional Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-anywhere-directed-object-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the intuitive instruction methods in robot navigation is a pointing gesture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-anywhere-directed-object-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chat Translation Error Detection for Assisting Cross-lingual Communications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chat-translation-error-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we describe the development of a communication support system that detects erroneous translations to facilitate crosslingual communications due to the limitations of current machine chat translation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chat-translation-error-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Context, Less Distraction: Visual Classification by Inferring and Conditioning on Contextual Attributes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-context-less-distraction-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper draws inspiration from the human visual perception process: a modern neuroscience view suggests that in classifying an object, humans first infer its class-independent attributes (e. g., background and orientation) which help separate the foreground object from the background, and then make decisions based on this information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-context-less-distraction-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs Understand Glass-Box Models, Discover Surprises, and Suggest Repairs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-understand-glass-box-models-discover</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that large language models (LLMs) are remarkably good at working with interpretable models that decompose complex outcomes into univariate graph-represented components.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-understand-glass-box-models-discover</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-Temporal Branching for Motion Prediction using Motion Increments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-branching-for-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human motion prediction (HMP) has emerged as a popular research topic due to its diverse applications, but it remains a challenging task due to the stochastic and aperiodic nature of future poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-branching-for-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUANT: A Minimalist Interval Method for Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quant-a-minimalist-interval-method-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that it is possible to achieve the same accuracy, on average, as the most accurate existing interval methods for time series classification on a standard set of benchmark datasets using a single type of feature (quantiles), fixed intervals, and an 'off the shelf' classifier.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quant-a-minimalist-interval-method-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User-Controllable Recommendation via Counterfactual Retrospective and Prospective Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-controllable-recommendation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Acknowledging the recent advancements in explainable recommender systems that enhance users' understanding of recommendation mechanisms, we propose leveraging these advancements to improve user controllability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-controllable-recommendation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can We Transfer Noise Patterns? An Multi-environment Spectrum Analysis Model Using Generated Cases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-transfer-noise-patterns-an-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To make the analysis model applicable to more environments, we propose a noise patterns transferring model, which takes the spectrum of standard water samples in different environments as cases and learns the differences in their noise patterns, thus enabling noise patterns to transfer to unknown samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-transfer-noise-patterns-an-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UCDFormer: Unsupervised Change Detection Using a Transformer-driven Image Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ucdformer-unsupervised-change-detection-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, a transformer-driven image translation composed of a light-weight transformer and a domain-specific affinity weight is first proposed to mitigate domain shift between two images with real-time efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ucdformer-unsupervised-change-detection-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorporating Season and Solar Specificity into Renderings made by a NeRF Architecture using Satellite Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-season-and-solar-specificity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result of Shadow NeRF and Sat-NeRF, it is possible to take the solar angle into account in a NeRF-based framework for rendering a scene from a novel viewpoint using satellite images for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-season-and-solar-specificity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation-based inference using surjective sequential neural likelihood estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-based-inference-using-surjective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Surjective Sequential Neural Likelihood (SSNL) estimation, a novel method for simulation-based inference in models where the evaluation of the likelihood function is not tractable and only a simulator that can generate synthetic data is available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-based-inference-using-surjective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextual Emotion Recognition Using Transformer-Based Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-emotion-recognition-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to increase the precision of emotion identification in text, this research suggests a context-aware emotion recognition system employing transformer models, especially BERT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-emotion-recognition-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training-Free Instance Segmentation from Semantic Image Segmentation Masks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-free-instance-segmentation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TFISeg does not require training a semantic or/and instance segmentation model and avoids the need for instance-level image annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-free-instance-segmentation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMUNeXt: An Efficient Medical Image Segmentation Network based on Large Kernel and Skip Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmunext-an-efficient-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to extract global context information while taking advantage of the inductive bias, we propose CMUNeXt, an efficient fully convolutional lightweight medical image segmentation network, which enables fast and accurate auxiliary diagnosis in real scene scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmunext-an-efficient-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked and Swapped Sequence Modeling for Next Novel Basket Recommendation in Grocery Shopping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-and-swapped-sequence-modeling-for-next</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In next basket recommendation (NBR), it is useful to distinguish between repeat items, i. e., items that a user has consumed before, and explore items, i. e., items that a user has not consumed before.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-and-swapped-sequence-modeling-for-next</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrast-augmented Diffusion Model with Fine-grained Sequence Alignment for Markup-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrast-augmented-diffusion-model-with-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recently rising markup-to-image generation poses greater challenges as compared to natural image generation, due to its low tolerance for errors as well as the complex sequence and context correlations between markup and rendered image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrast-augmented-diffusion-model-with-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Domain Adaptation on Aerial Images under Gradually Degrading Weather</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-domain-adaptation-on-aerial-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We synthesize two such gradually worsening weather conditions on real images from two existing aerial imagery datasets, generating a total of four benchmark datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-domain-adaptation-on-aerial-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiscale Global and Regional Feature Learning Using Co-Tuplet Loss for Offline Handwritten Signature Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiscale-global-and-regional-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose a multiscale global and regional feature learning network (MGRNet) with the co-tuplet loss, a new metric learning loss, for offline handwritten signature verification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiscale-global-and-regional-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDBImages: A Command Line Tool for Automated Macromolecular Structure Visualization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdbimages-a-command-line-tool-for-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Availability and Implementation: PDBImages is available as an npm package from https://www. npmjs. com/package/pdb-images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdbimages-a-command-line-tool-for-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DriveAdapter: Breaking the Coupling Barrier of Perception and Planning in End-to-End Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/driveadapter-breaking-the-coupling-barrier-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that even equipped with a SOTA perception model, directly letting the student model learn the required inputs of the teacher model leads to poor driving performance, which comes from the large distribution gap between predicted privileged inputs and the ground-truth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/driveadapter-breaking-the-coupling-barrier-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SkullGAN: Synthetic Skull CT Generation with Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skullgan-synthetic-skull-ct-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning offers potential for various healthcare applications involving the human skull but requires extensive datasets of curated medical images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skullgan-synthetic-skull-ct-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bias Amplification Paradox in Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-bias-amplification-paradox-in-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bias amplification is a phenomenon in which models increase imbalances present in the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-bias-amplification-paradox-in-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classes are not Clusters: Improving Label-based Evaluation of Dimensionality Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classes-are-not-clusters-improving-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce two novel quality measures -- Label-Trustworthiness and Label-Continuity (Label-T&C) -- advancing the process of DR evaluation based on class labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classes-are-not-clusters-improving-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SelfCheck: Using LLMs to Zero-Shot Check Their Own Step-by-Step Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selfcheck-using-llms-to-zero-shot-check-their</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a zero-shot verification scheme to recognize such errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selfcheck-using-llms-to-zero-shot-check-their</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Challenging the Myth of Graph Collaborative Filtering: a Reasoned and Reproducibility-driven Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenging-the-myth-of-graph-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of graph neural network-based models (GNNs) has significantly advanced recommender systems by effectively modeling users and items as a bipartite, undirected graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenging-the-myth-of-graph-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape Completion with Prediction of Uncertain Regions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-completion-with-prediction-of-uncertain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We train on this dataset and test each method in shape completion and prediction of uncertain regions for known and novel object instances and on synthetic and real data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-completion-with-prediction-of-uncertain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Image Harmonization with Learnable Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-image-harmonization-with-learnable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, our designed SYthetic COmposite Network (SycoNet) takes in a real image with foreground mask and a random vector to learn suitable color transformation, which is applied to the foreground of this real image to produce a synthetic composite image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-image-harmonization-with-learnable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-Driven Spectrum-Consistent Federated Learning for Palmprint Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-driven-spectrum-consistent-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, we introduce anchor models for short- and long-spectrum, which constrain the optimization directions of local models associated with long- and short-spectrum images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-driven-spectrum-consistent-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Generation of a Synthetic Event-Based Vision Dataset for Navigation and Landing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-generation-of-a-synthetic-event-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We anticipate that novel event-based vision datasets can be generated using this pipeline to support various spacecraft pose reconstruction problems given events as input, and we hope that the proposed methodology would attract the attention of researchers working at the intersection of neuromorphic vision and guidance navigation and control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-generation-of-a-synthetic-event-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELFNet: Evidential Local-global Fusion for Stereo Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elfnet-evidential-local-global-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although existing stereo matching models have achieved continuous improvement, they often face issues related to trustworthiness due to the absence of uncertainty estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elfnet-evidential-local-global-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaGPT: Meta Programming for Multi-Agent Collaborative Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metagpt-meta-programming-for-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, remarkable progress has been made in automated task-solving through the use of multi-agents driven by large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metagpt-meta-programming-for-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LISA: Reasoning Segmentation via Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lisa-reasoning-segmentation-via-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new segmentation task -- reasoning segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lisa-reasoning-segmentation-via-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relational Contrastive Learning for Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-contrastive-learning-for-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that such prior contextual information can be interpreted as the relations of textual primitives due to the heterogeneous text and background, which can provide effective self-supervised labels for representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-contrastive-learning-for-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLatten Transformer: Vision Transformer using Focused Linear Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flatten-transformer-vision-transformer-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The quadratic computation complexity of self-attention has been a persistent challenge when applying Transformer models to vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flatten-transformer-vision-transformer-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Hallucinations in Neural Chart Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-hallucinations-in-neural-chart</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hallucinations in text generation occur when the system produces text that is not grounded in the input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-hallucinations-in-neural-chart</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An L2-Normalized Spatial Attention Network For Accurate And Fast Classification Of Brain Tumors In 2D T1-Weighted CE-MRI Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-l2-normalized-spatial-attention-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare our results against the state-of-the-art on this dataset and show that by integrating l2-normalized spatial attention into a baseline network we achieve a performance gain of 1. 79 percentage points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-l2-normalized-spatial-attention-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Green's Function Efficiently Using Low-Rank Approximations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-green-s-function-efficiently-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning the Green's function using deep learning models enables to solve different classes of partial differential equations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-green-s-function-efficiently-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Majority Invariant Approach to Patch Robustness Certification for Deep Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-majority-invariant-approach-to-patch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Patch robustness certification ensures no patch within a given bound on a sample can manipulate a deep learning model to predict a different label.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-majority-invariant-approach-to-patch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnyLoc: Towards Universal Visual Place Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anyloc-towards-universal-visual-place</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop a universal solution to VPR -- a technique that works across a broad range of structured and unstructured environments (urban, outdoors, indoors, aerial, underwater, and subterranean environments) without any re-training or fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anyloc-towards-universal-visual-place</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NormKD: Normalized Logits for Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normkd-normalized-logits-for-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we restudy the hyper-parameter temperature and figure out its incapability to distill the knowledge from each sample sufficiently when it is a single value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normkd-normalized-logits-for-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiERL: A Meta Evolutionary Reinforcement Learning Framework via Bilevel Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bierl-a-meta-evolutionary-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evolutionary reinforcement learning (ERL) algorithms recently raise attention in tackling complex reinforcement learning (RL) problems due to high parallelism, while they are prone to insufficient exploration or model collapse without carefully tuning hyperparameters (aka meta-parameters).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bierl-a-meta-evolutionary-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Ultra-High-Definition Image Reflection Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-ultra-high-definition-image-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, these two datasets are the first largest-scale UHD datasets for SIRR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-ultra-high-definition-image-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boundary Difference Over Union Loss For Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-difference-over-union-loss-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, current losses for medical image segmentation mainly focus on overall segmentation results, with fewer losses proposed to guide boundary segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-difference-over-union-loss-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
