<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 09:11:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sequential Latent Variable Models for Few-Shot High-Dimensional Time-Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-latent-variable-models-for-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compared the presented framework with a comprehensive set of baseline models trained 1) globally on the large meta-training set with diverse dynamics, and 2) individually on single dynamics, both with and without fine-tuning to k-shot support series used by the meta-models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-latent-variable-models-for-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiance Field Gradient Scaling for Unbiased Near-Camera Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radiance-field-gradient-scaling-for-unbiased</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NeRF acquisition typically requires careful choice of near planes for the different cameras or suffers from background collapse, creating floating artifacts on the edges of the captured scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radiance-field-gradient-scaling-for-unbiased</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT-steered Editing Instructor for Customization of Abstractive Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-steered-editing-instructor-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tailoring outputs of large language models, such as ChatGPT, to specific user needs remains a challenge despite their impressive generation quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-steered-editing-instructor-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RCP-RF: A Comprehensive Road-car-pedestrian Risk Management Framework based on Driving Risk Potential Field</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rcp-rf-a-comprehensive-road-car-pedestrian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have witnessed the proliferation of traffic accidents, which led wide researches on Automated Vehicle (AV) technologies to reduce vehicle accidents, especially on risk assessment framework of AV technologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rcp-rf-a-comprehensive-road-car-pedestrian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faithful Question Answering with Monte-Carlo Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithful-question-answering-with-monte-carlo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose FAME (FAithful question answering with MontE-carlo planning) to answer questions based on faithful reasoning steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithful-question-answering-with-monte-carlo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boundary-aware Backward-Compatible Representation via Adversarial Learning in Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-aware-backward-compatible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For traditional model upgrades, the old model will not be replaced by the new one until the embeddings of all the images in the database are re-computed by the new model, which takes days or weeks for a large amount of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-aware-backward-compatible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LatentAugment: Dynamically Optimized Latent Probabilities of Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latentaugment-dynamically-optimized-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although data augmentation is a powerful technique for improving the performance of image classification tasks, it is difficult to identify the best augmentation policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latentaugment-dynamically-optimized-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Personalized Federated Learning via Sparse Model-Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-personalized-federated-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these challenges, we propose a novel approach named pFedGate for efficient personalized FL by adaptively and efficiently learning sparse local models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-personalized-federated-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caption Anything: Interactive Image Description with Diverse Multimodal Controls</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caption-anything-interactive-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Controllable image captioning is an emerging multimodal topic that aims to describe the image with natural language following human purpose, $\textit{e. g.}$, looking at the specified regions or telling in a particular text style.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caption-anything-interactive-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RetroMAE-2: Duplex Masked Auto-Encoder For Pre-Training Retrieval-Oriented Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retromae-2-duplex-masked-auto-encoder-for-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is designed to improve the quality of semantic representation where all contextualized embeddings of the pre-trained model can be leveraged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retromae-2-duplex-masked-auto-encoder-for-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Expressivity Role of LayerNorm in Transformers' Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-expressivity-role-of-layernorm-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Layer Normalization (LayerNorm) is an inherent component in all Transformer-based models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-expressivity-role-of-layernorm-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Trajectory Models for Prediction, Representation, and Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-trajectory-models-for-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Masked Trajectory Models (MTM) as a generic abstraction for sequential decision making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-trajectory-models-for-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Space Grounded Weighted Decoding for Multi-Attribute Controllable Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-space-grounded-weighted-decoding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Controlling chatbot utterance generation with multiple attributes such as personalities, emotions and dialogue acts is a practically useful but under-studied problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-space-grounded-weighted-decoding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panda LLM: Training Data and Evaluation for Open-Sourced Chinese Instruction-Following Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panda-llm-training-data-and-evaluation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This project focuses on enhancing open-source large language models through instruction-tuning and providing comprehensive evaluations of their performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panda-llm-training-data-and-evaluation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised 3D Scene Flow Estimation Guided by Superpoints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-3d-scene-flow-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our superpoint generation module, we utilize the bidirectional flow information at the previous iteration to obtain the matching points of points and superpoint centers for soft point-to-superpoint association construction, in which the superpoints are generated for pairwise point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-3d-scene-flow-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarially-Guided Portrait Matting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarially-guided-portrait-matting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We utilize this model to provide image-mask pairs for the StyleGAN3- based network (StyleMatteGAN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarially-guided-portrait-matting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Dialogue Topic Segmentation with Topic-aware Utterance Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-dialogue-topic-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dialogue Topic Segmentation (DTS) plays an essential role in a variety of dialogue modeling tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-dialogue-topic-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuttlefish: Low-rank Model Training without All The Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuttlefish-low-rank-model-training-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cuttlefish leverages the observation that after a few epochs of full-rank training, the stable rank (i. e., an approximation of the true rank) of each layer stabilizes at a constant value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuttlefish-low-rank-model-training-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Graph Learning and Model Fitting in Laplacian Regularized Stratified Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-graph-learning-and-model-fitting-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Laplacian regularized stratified models (LRSM) are models that utilize the explicit or implicit network structure of the sub-problems as defined by the categorical features called strata (e. g., age, region, time, forecast horizon, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-graph-learning-and-model-fitting-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedCBO: Reaching Group Consensus in Clustered Federated Learning through Consensus-based Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedcbo-reaching-group-consensus-in-clustered</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is an important framework in modern machine learning that seeks to integrate the training of learning models from multiple users, each user having their own local data set, in a way that is sensitive to data privacy and to communication loss constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedcbo-reaching-group-consensus-in-clustered</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled Contrastive Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-contrastive-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies show that graph neural networks (GNNs) are prevalent to model high-order relationships for collaborative filtering (CF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-contrastive-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZipIt! Merging Models from Different Tasks without Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipit-merging-models-from-different-tasks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While this works for models trained on the same task, we find that this fails to account for the differences in models trained on disjoint tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipit-merging-models-from-different-tasks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FUSegNet: A Deep Convolutional Neural Network for Foot Ulcer Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusegnet-a-deep-convolutional-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the top decoder stage carries a limited number of feature maps, max-out scSE is bypassed there to form a shorted P-scSE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusegnet-a-deep-convolutional-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Graph Contrastive Learning for Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-graph-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the paper, we delve into the misconception and propose Multi-GNN and Augmented Graph contrastive framework MAG, which unified the existing GCAD methods in the contrastive self-supervised perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-graph-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lift Yourself Up: Retrieval-augmented Text Generation with Self Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lift-yourself-up-retrieval-augmented-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, by exploring the duality of the primal problem: better generation also prompts better memory, we propose a framework called Selfmem, which iteratively adopts a retrieval-augmented generator itself to generate an unbounded memory pool and uses a memory selector to pick one generated memory for the next generation round.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lift-yourself-up-retrieval-augmented-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastAMI -- a Monte Carlo Approach to the Adjustment for Chance in Clustering Comparison Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastami-a-monte-carlo-approach-to-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clustering is at the very core of machine learning, and its applications proliferate with the increasing availability of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastami-a-monte-carlo-approach-to-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling-up Remote Sensing Segmentation Dataset with Segment Anything Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-remote-sensing-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of the Segment Anything Model (SAM) demonstrates the significance of data-centric machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-remote-sensing-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeGen2: Lessons for Training LLMs on Programming and Natural Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codegen2-lessons-for-training-llms-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we attempt to render the training of LLMs for program synthesis more efficient by unifying four key components: (1) model architectures, (2) learning methods, (3) infill sampling, and, (4) data distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codegen2-lessons-for-training-llms-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Contrastive Learning of Sentence Embeddings from AI Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-contrastive-learning-of-sentence-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method utilizes AI feedback from large pre-trained language models (LLMs) to construct sample pairs with fine-grained sample similarity scores to improve contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-contrastive-learning-of-sentence-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysing the Impact of Audio Quality on the Use of Naturalistic Long-Form Recordings for Infant-Directed Speech Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysing-the-impact-of-audio-quality-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that the use of modest and high audio quality naturalistic speech data result in largely similar conclusions on IDS and ADS in terms of acoustic analyses and modelling experiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysing-the-impact-of-audio-quality-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Neural Divide-and-Conquer Reasoning Framework for Image Retrieval from Linguistically Complex Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-divide-and-conquer-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the Divide-and-Conquer algorithm and dual-process theory, in this paper, we regard linguistically complex texts as compound proposition texts composed of multiple simple proposition sentences and propose an end-to-end Neural Divide-and-Conquer Reasoning framework, dubbed NDCR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-divide-and-conquer-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Natural Language Watermarking through Invariant Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-natural-language-watermarking-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have witnessed a proliferation of valuable original natural language contents found in subscription-based media outlets, web novel platforms, and outputs of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-natural-language-watermarking-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lightweight CNN-Transformer Model for Learning Traveling Salesman Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-cnn-transformer-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model consumes approximately 20% less GPU memory usage and has 45% faster inference time compared with other state-of-the-art Transformer-based models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-cnn-transformer-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Supervised Segmentation of Functional Tissue Units at the Cellular Level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-segmentation-of-functional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new method for functional tissue unit segmentation at the cellular level, which utilizes the latest deep learning semantic segmentation approaches together with domain adaptation and semi-supervised learning techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-segmentation-of-functional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Sparse Training with Structured Sparsity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-sparse-training-with-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DST methods achieve state-of-the-art results in sparse neural network training, matching the generalization of dense models while enabling sparse training and inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-sparse-training-with-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Safety Validation for Black-Box Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-safety-validation-for-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurately estimating the probability of failure for safety-critical systems is important for certification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-safety-validation-for-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approximating CKY with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximating-cky-with-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the ability of transformer models to approximate the CKY algorithm, using them to directly predict a parse and thus avoid the CKY algorithm's cubic dependence on sentence length.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximating-cky-with-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DocLangID: Improving Few-Shot Training to Identify the Language of Historical Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doclangid-improving-few-shot-training-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose DocLangID, a transfer learning approach to identify the language of unlabeled historical documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doclangid-improving-few-shot-training-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Glitch in the Matrix!": A Large Scale Benchmark for Content Driven Audio-Visual Forgery Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glitch-in-the-matrix-a-large-scale-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed baseline method, Boundary Aware Temporal Forgery Detection (BA-TFD), is a 3D Convolutional Neural Network-based architecture which efficiently captures multimodal manipulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glitch-in-the-matrix-a-large-scale-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>District-scale surface temperatures generated from high-resolution longitudinal thermal infrared images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/district-scale-surface-temperatures-generated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rooftop infrared thermography observatory with a multi-modal platform that is capable of assessing a wide range of dynamic processes in urban systems was deployed in Singapore.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/district-scale-surface-temperatures-generated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding cirrus clouds using explainable machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-cirrus-clouds-using-explainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Their dependencies on meteorological and aerosol conditions are among the largest uncertainties in global climate models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-cirrus-clouds-using-explainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NorQuAD: Norwegian Question Answering Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/norquad-norwegian-question-answering-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present NorQuAD: the first Norwegian question answering dataset for machine reading comprehension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/norquad-norwegian-question-answering-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AttenWalker: Unsupervised Long-Document Question Answering via Attention-based Graph Walking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attenwalker-unsupervised-long-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate the problem, it might be possible to generate long-document QA pairs via unsupervised question answering (UQA) methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attenwalker-unsupervised-long-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of Label-Description Training for Zero-Shot Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-benefits-of-label-description-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models have improved zero-shot text classification by allowing the transfer of semantic knowledge from the training data in order to classify among specific label sets in downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-benefits-of-label-description-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Encoding of Satellite Image Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-encoding-of-satellite-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representation learning of Satellite Image Time Series (SITS) presents its unique challenges, such as prohibitive computation burden caused by high spatiotemporal resolutions, irregular acquisition times, and complex spatiotemporal interactions, leading to highly-specialized neural network architectures for SITS analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-encoding-of-satellite-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shap-E: Generating Conditional 3D Implicit Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shap-e-generating-conditional-3d-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Shap-E, a conditional generative model for 3D assets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shap-e-generating-conditional-3d-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causality-aware Concept Extraction based on Knowledge-guided Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-aware-concept-extraction-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prompt adopts the topic of the given entity from the existing knowledge in KGs to mitigate the spurious co-occurrence correlations between entities and biased concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-aware-concept-extraction-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shotgun crystal structure prediction using machine-learned formation energies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shotgun-crystal-structure-prediction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stable or metastable crystal structures of assembled atoms can be predicted by finding the global or local minima of the energy surface with respect to the atomic configurations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shotgun-crystal-structure-prediction-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-train and Search: Efficient Embedding Table Sharding with Pre-trained Neural Cost Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-train-and-search-efficient-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore a "pre-train, and search" paradigm for efficient sharding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-train-and-search-efficient-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering ChatGPT's Capabilities in Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-chatgpt-s-capabilities-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The debut of ChatGPT has recently attracted the attention of the natural language processing (NLP) community and beyond.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-chatgpt-s-capabilities-in</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
