<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 09:17:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Detection, Pose Estimation and Segmentation for Multiple Bodies: Closing the Virtuous Circle</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-pose-estimation-and-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We condition pose estimation model by segmentation masks instead of bounding boxes to improve instance separation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-pose-estimation-and-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detection, Pose Estimation and Segmentation for Multiple Bodies: Closing the Virtuous Circle</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-pose-estimation-and-segmentation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We condition pose estimation model by segmentation masks instead of bounding boxes to improve instance separation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-pose-estimation-and-segmentation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoLights: Feature Refinement and Cross-Task Alignment Transformer for Joint Video Highlight Detection and Moment Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videolights-feature-refinement-and-cross-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video Highlight Detection and Moment Retrieval (HD/MR) are essential in video analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videolights-feature-refinement-and-cross-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CellSeg1: Robust Cell Segmentation with One Training Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cellseg1-robust-cell-segmentation-with-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce CellSeg1, a practical solution for segmenting cells of arbitrary morphology and modality with a few dozen cell annotations in 1 image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cellseg1-robust-cell-segmentation-with-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextSSR: Diffusion-based Data Synthesis for Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textssr-diffusion-based-data-synthesis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments show that models trained on added TextSSR-F data exhibit better accuracy compared to models trained on 4 million existing synthetic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textssr-diffusion-based-data-synthesis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R-Bot: An LLM-based Query Rewrite System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-bot-an-llm-based-query-rewrite-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Query rewrite is essential for optimizing SQL queries to improve their execution efficiency without changing their results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-bot-an-llm-based-query-rewrite-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Much Can Time-related Features Enhance Time Series Forecasting?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-much-can-time-related-features-enhance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in long-term time series forecasting (LTSF) have primarily focused on capturing cross-time and cross-variate (channel) dependencies within historical data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-much-can-time-related-features-enhance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pluggable Style Representation Learning for Multi-Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pluggable-style-representation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, for style modeling, we propose a style representation learning scheme to encode the style information into a compact representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pluggable-style-representation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Explainable AI: From Classical Models to LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-guide-to-explainable-ai-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Explainable Artificial Intelligence (XAI) addresses the growing need for transparency and interpretability in AI systems, enabling trust and accountability in decision-making processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-guide-to-explainable-ai-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Differentiation-based Full Waveform Inversion with Flexible Workflows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-differentiation-based-full-waveform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The AD-based framework not only includes forword modeling and associated gradient computations for wave equations in various types of media from isotropic acoustic to vertically or horizontally transverse isotropic elastic, but also incorporates a suite of objective functions, regularization techniques, and optimization algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-differentiation-based-full-waveform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wafer2Spike: Spiking Neural Network for Wafer Map Pattern Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wafer2spike-spiking-neural-network-for-wafer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In integrated circuit design, the analysis of wafer map patterns is critical to improve yield and detect manufacturing issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wafer2spike-spiking-neural-network-for-wafer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAFcounter: An efficient tool for counting the occurrences of k-mers in MAF files</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mafcounter-an-efficient-tool-for-counting-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MAFcounter is multithreaded, fast, and memory efficient, enabling k-mer counting in DNA and protein sequence alignment files.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mafcounter-an-efficient-tool-for-counting-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handling irresolvable conflicts in the Semantic Web: an RDF-based conflict-tolerant version of the Deontic Traditional Scheme</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handling-irresolvable-conflicts-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new ontology that implements the well-known Deontic Traditional Scheme in RDFs and SPARQL, fit to handle irresolvable conflicts, i. e., situations in which two or more statements prescribe conflicting obligations, prohibitions, or permissions, with none of them being "stronger" than the other one(s).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handling-irresolvable-conflicts-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCUCoder: Adaptive Bitrate Learned Video Compression for IoT Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcucoder-adaptive-bitrate-learned-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid growth of camera-based IoT devices demands the need for efficient video compression, particularly for edge applications where devices face hardware constraints, often with only 1 or 2 MB of RAM and unstable internet connections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcucoder-adaptive-bitrate-learned-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM Teacher-Student Framework for Text Classification With No Manually Annotated Data: A Case Study in IPTC News Topic Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-teacher-student-framework-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose a teacher-student framework based on large language models (LLMs) for developing multilingual news classification models of reasonable size with no need for manual data annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-teacher-student-framework-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextual Checkerboard Denoise -- A Novel Neural Network-Based Approach for Classification-Aware OCT Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-checkerboard-denoise-a-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to non-medical image denoising, where enhancing image clarity is the primary goal, medical image denoising warrants preservation of crucial features without introduction of new artifacts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-checkerboard-denoise-a-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth or Mirage? Towards End-to-End Factuality Evaluation with LLM-Oasis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truth-or-mirage-towards-end-to-end-factuality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After the introduction of Large Language Models (LLMs), there have been substantial improvements in the performance of Natural Language Generation (NLG) tasks, including Text Summarization and Machine Translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truth-or-mirage-towards-end-to-end-factuality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ContextGNN: Beyond Two-Tower Recommendation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextgnn-beyond-two-tower-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommendation systems predominantly utilize two-tower architectures, which evaluate user-item rankings through the inner product of their respective embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextgnn-beyond-two-tower-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GuardSplat: Efficient and Robust Watermarking for 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guardsplat-robust-and-efficient-watermarking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, 1) We first propose a CLIP-guided Message Decoupling Optimization module for training the message decoder, leveraging CLIP's aligning capability and rich representations to achieve a high extraction accuracy with minimal optimization costs, presenting exceptional capability and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guardsplat-robust-and-efficient-watermarking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Sparse Matrix Vector Multiplication Approach to Padded Convolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-sparse-matrix-vector-multiplication</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an algorithm for efficiently representing convolution with zero-padding and stride as a sparse transformation matrix, applied to a vectorized input through sparse matrix-vector multiplication (SpMV).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-sparse-matrix-vector-multiplication</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Large Language Models Reason about the Region Connection Calculus?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-reason-about-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Qualitative Spatial Reasoning is a well explored area of Knowledge Representation and Reasoning and has multiple applications ranging from Geographical Information Systems to Robotics and Computer Vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-reason-about-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T2Vid: Translating Long Text into Multi-Image is the Catalyst for Video-LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t2vid-translating-long-text-into-multi-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, our study of these approaches harvests an effective data augmentation method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t2vid-translating-long-text-into-multi-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChineseWebText 2.0: Large-Scale High-quality Chinese Web Text with Multi-dimensional and fine-grained information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chinesewebtext-2-0-large-scale-high-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With this approach, we release the largest, high-quality and fine-grained Chinese text ChineseWebText2. 0, which consists of 3. 8TB and each text is associated with a quality score, domain labels, a toxicity label and a toxicity score, facilitating the LLM researchers to select data based on various types of fine-grained information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chinesewebtext-2-0-large-scale-high-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Whole Slide Foundation Model for Pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-whole-slide-foundation-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of computational pathology has been transformed with recent advances in foundation models that encode histopathology region-of-interests (ROIs) into versatile and transferable feature representations via self-supervised learning (SSL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-whole-slide-foundation-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Risk Minimization: Towards Next-Level Robustness in Fine-tuning Zero-Shot Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-risk-minimization-towards-next-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning foundation models often compromises their robustness to distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-risk-minimization-towards-next-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Transformers for Low-Bitrate High-Quality Speech Coding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-transformers-for-low-bitrate-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The tokenization of speech with neural audio codec models is a vital part of modern AI pipelines for the generation or understanding of speech, alone or in a multimodal context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-transformers-for-low-bitrate-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Loss Strategy for Vehicle Trajectory Prediction: Combining Off-Road, Diversity, and Directional Consistency Losses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-loss-strategy-for-vehicle-trajectory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trajectory prediction is essential for the safety and efficiency of planning in autonomous vehicles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-loss-strategy-for-vehicle-trajectory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICPR 2024 Competition on Multilingual Claim-Span Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icpr-2024-competition-on-multilingual-claim</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A lot of claims are made in social media posts, which may contain misinformation or fake news.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icpr-2024-competition-on-multilingual-claim</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Mutual Information Computation for Large Binary Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-mutual-information-computation-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mutual Information (MI) is a powerful statistical measure that quantifies shared information between random variables, particularly valuable in high-dimensional data analysis across fields like genomics, natural language processing, and network science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-mutual-information-computation-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another look at inference after prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/another-look-at-inference-after-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our extensive theoretical and numerical analyses indicate that the Chen and Chen (CC) estimator offers a balance between robustness to ML model specification and statistical efficiency, making it the preferred choice for use in practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/another-look-at-inference-after-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Surface Structure: A Causal Assessment of LLMs' Comprehension Ability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-surface-structure-a-causal-assessment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further apply the ADCE to evaluate a series of mainstream LLMs, showing that most of them exhibit deep structure comprehension ability, which grows along with the prediction accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-surface-structure-a-causal-assessment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LDA-AQU: Adaptive Query-guided Upsampling via Local Deformable Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lda-aqu-adaptive-query-guided-upsampling-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we introduce local self-attention into the upsampling task and demonstrate that the majority of existing upsamplers can be regarded as special cases of upsamplers based on local self-attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lda-aqu-adaptive-query-guided-upsampling-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensemble Watermarks for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-watermarks-for-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, we combine acrostica and sensorimotor norms with the established red-green watermark to achieve a 98% detection rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-watermarks-for-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeMo: Decoupled Momentum Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demo-decoupled-momentum-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training large neural networks typically requires sharing gradients between accelerators through specialized high-speed interconnects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demo-decoupled-momentum-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classical and Quantum Algorithms for the Deterministic L-system Inductive Inference Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classical-and-quantum-algorithms-for-the-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It would be significant if this could be done automatically from data, such as from sequences of images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classical-and-quantum-algorithms-for-the-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Initialization using Update Approximation is a Silver Bullet for Extremely Efficient Low-Rank Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/initialization-using-update-approximation-is</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-rank adapters have become a standard approach for efficiently fine-tuning large language models (LLMs), but they often fall short of achieving the performance of full fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/initialization-using-update-approximation-is</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForgerySleuth: Empowering Multimodal Large Language Models for Image Manipulation Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forgerysleuth-empowering-multimodal-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we construct the ForgeryAnalysis dataset through the Chain-of-Clues prompt, which includes analysis and reasoning text to upgrade the image manipulation detection task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forgerysleuth-empowering-multimodal-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAREL: Instruction-guided reinforcement learning with cross-modal auxiliary objectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/carel-instruction-guided-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Grounding the instruction in the environment is a key step in solving language-guided goal-reaching reinforcement learning problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/carel-instruction-guided-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Interactive Segmentation for Multimodal Medical Imaging via Selection Engine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-interactive-segmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate memory bottlenecks and optimize prompt frame selection during the inference of 2D image sequences, we developed an automated system, the Adaptive Frame Selection Engine (AFSE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-interactive-segmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks for Heart Failure Prediction on an EHR-Based Patient Similarity Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-for-heart-failure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the Random Forest (RF) baseline achieved a similar AUPRC value, the GT model offered enhanced interpretability due to the use of patient relationships in the graph structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-for-heart-failure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uniform Attention Maps: Boosting Image Fidelity in Reconstruction and Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniform-attention-maps-boosting-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study underscores the potential of uniform attention maps to enhance the fidelity and versatility of diffusion-based image processing methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniform-attention-maps-boosting-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feedback-driven object detection and iterative model improvement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feedback-driven-object-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present the development and evaluation of a platform designed to interactively improve object detection models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feedback-driven-object-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Multimodal Large Language Models via Dynamic Visual-Token Exit and the Empirical Findings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-multimodal-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we reveal that visual tokens will stop contributing to reasoning when the text tokens receive enough image information, yielding obvious visual redundancy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-multimodal-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIDetx: a compression-based method for identification of machine-learning generated text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aidetx-a-compression-based-method-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces AIDetx, a novel method for detecting machine-generated text using data compression techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aidetx-a-compression-based-method-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Domain Recommendation Meets Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-recommendation-meets-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-domain recommendation (CDR) has emerged as a promising solution to the cold-start problem, faced by single-domain recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-recommendation-meets-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELT: A Simple Diversity-driven EarlyLate Training for Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delt-a-simple-diversity-driven-earlylate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The conventional batch-to-batch matching mechanism is ideal for small-scale datasets and includes bi-level optimization methods on models and syntheses, such as FRePo, RCIG, and RaT-BPTT, as well as other methods like distribution matching, gradient matching, and weight trajectory matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delt-a-simple-diversity-driven-earlylate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced anomaly detection in well log data through the application of ensemble GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-anomaly-detection-in-well-log-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study extends the ensemble GANs (EGANs) framework to capture the distribution of well log data and detect anomalies that fall outside of these distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-anomaly-detection-in-well-log-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-RAG: Autonomous Retrieval-Augmented Generation for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-rag-autonomous-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Iterative retrieval refers to the process in which the model continuously queries the retriever during generation to enhance the relevance of the retrieved knowledge, thereby improving the performance of Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-rag-autonomous-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURE-VQA: Systematic Understanding of Robustness Evaluation in Medical VQA Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sure-vqa-systematic-understanding-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-Language Models (VLMs) have great potential in medical tasks, like Visual Question Answering (VQA), where they could act as interactive assistants for both patients and clinicians.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sure-vqa-systematic-understanding-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Visual Abstract Reasoning through Dual-Stream Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-visual-abstract-reasoning-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual abstract reasoning tasks present challenges for deep neural networks, exposing limitations in their capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-visual-abstract-reasoning-through</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
