<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 09:10:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sequential Latent Variable Models for Few-Shot High-Dimensional Time-Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-latent-variable-models-for-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compared the presented framework with a comprehensive set of baseline models trained 1) globally on the large meta-training set with diverse dynamics, and 2) individually on single dynamics, both with and without fine-tuning to k-shot support series used by the meta-models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-latent-variable-models-for-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable Visual-Tactile Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-visual-tactile-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep generative models have various content creation applications such as graphic design, e-commerce, and virtual Try-on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-visual-tactile-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VendorLink: An NLP approach for Identifying &amp; Linking Vendor Migrants &amp; Potential Aliases on Darknet Markets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vendorlink-an-nlp-approach-for-identifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The anonymity on the Darknet allows vendors to stay undetected by using multiple vendor aliases or frequently migrating between markets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vendorlink-an-nlp-approach-for-identifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PGB: A PubMed Graph Benchmark for Heterogeneous Network Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgb-a-pubmed-graph-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although graph mining research via heterogeneous graph neural networks has taken center stage, it remains unclear whether these approaches capture the heterogeneity of the PubMed database, a vast digital repository containing over 33 million articles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgb-a-pubmed-graph-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuttlefish: Low-rank Model Training without All The Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuttlefish-low-rank-model-training-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cuttlefish leverages the observation that after a few epochs of full-rank training, the stable rank (i. e., an approximation of the true rank) of each layer stabilizes at a constant value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuttlefish-low-rank-model-training-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Space Grounded Weighted Decoding for Multi-Attribute Controllable Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-space-grounded-weighted-decoding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Controlling chatbot utterance generation with multiple attributes such as personalities, emotions and dialogue acts is a practically useful but under-studied problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-space-grounded-weighted-decoding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Expressivity Role of LayerNorm in Transformers' Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-expressivity-role-of-layernorm-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Layer Normalization (LayerNorm) is an inherent component in all Transformer-based models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-expressivity-role-of-layernorm-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Personalized Federated Learning via Sparse Model-Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-personalized-federated-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these challenges, we propose a novel approach named pFedGate for efficient personalized FL by adaptively and efficiently learning sparse local models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-personalized-federated-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RetroMAE-2: Duplex Masked Auto-Encoder For Pre-Training Retrieval-Oriented Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retromae-2-duplex-masked-auto-encoder-for-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is designed to improve the quality of semantic representation where all contextualized embeddings of the pre-trained model can be leveraged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retromae-2-duplex-masked-auto-encoder-for-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiance Field Gradient Scaling for Unbiased Near-Camera Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radiance-field-gradient-scaling-for-unbiased</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NeRF acquisition typically requires careful choice of near planes for the different cameras or suffers from background collapse, creating floating artifacts on the edges of the captured scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radiance-field-gradient-scaling-for-unbiased</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-supervised Domain Adaptation via Prototype-based Multi-level Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-domain-adaptation-via-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the inter-domain level, we propose a cross-domain alignment loss to help the model use the target prototype for cross-domain knowledge transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-domain-adaptation-via-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sentence Embedding Leaks More Information than You Expect: Generative Embedding Inversion Attack to Recover the Whole Sentence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentence-embedding-leaks-more-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we further investigate the information leakage issue and propose a generative embedding inversion attack (GEIA) that aims to reconstruct input sequences based only on their sentence embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentence-embedding-leaks-more-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boundary-aware Backward-Compatible Representation via Adversarial Learning in Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-aware-backward-compatible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For traditional model upgrades, the old model will not be replaced by the new one until the embeddings of all the images in the database are re-computed by the new model, which takes days or weeks for a large amount of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-aware-backward-compatible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Bird-Eye View Representation of Point Cloud Sequences using Scene Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-bird-eye-view-representation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such concatenation is possible thanks to the removal of ego vehicle motion using its odometry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-bird-eye-view-representation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Trajectory Models for Prediction, Representation, and Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-trajectory-models-for-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Masked Trajectory Models (MTM) as a generic abstraction for sequential decision making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-trajectory-models-for-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Do Neural Nets Outperform Boosted Trees on Tabular Data?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-do-neural-nets-outperform-boosted-trees</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tabular data is one of the most commonly used types of data in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-do-neural-nets-outperform-boosted-trees</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT-steered Editing Instructor for Customization of Abstractive Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-steered-editing-instructor-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tailoring outputs of large language models, such as ChatGPT, to specific user needs remains a challenge despite their impressive generation quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-steered-editing-instructor-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FUSegNet: A Deep Convolutional Neural Network for Foot Ulcer Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusegnet-a-deep-convolutional-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the top decoder stage carries a limited number of feature maps, max-out scSE is bypassed there to form a shorted P-scSE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusegnet-a-deep-convolutional-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faithful Question Answering with Monte-Carlo Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithful-question-answering-with-monte-carlo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose FAME (FAithful question answering with MontE-carlo planning) to answer questions based on faithful reasoning steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithful-question-answering-with-monte-carlo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Graph Contrastive Learning for Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-graph-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the paper, we delve into the misconception and propose Multi-GNN and Augmented Graph contrastive framework MAG, which unified the existing GCAD methods in the contrastive self-supervised perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-graph-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LatentAugment: Dynamically Optimized Latent Probabilities of Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latentaugment-dynamically-optimized-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although data augmentation is a powerful technique for improving the performance of image classification tasks, it is difficult to identify the best augmentation policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latentaugment-dynamically-optimized-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Oops, Did I Just Say That?" Testing and Repairing Unethical Suggestions of Large Language Models with Suggest-Critique-Reflect Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oops-did-i-just-say-that-testing-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we propose a novel on-the-fly (OTF) repairing scheme that repairs unethical suggestions made by LLMs in real-time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oops-did-i-just-say-that-testing-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised 3D Scene Flow Estimation Guided by Superpoints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-3d-scene-flow-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our superpoint generation module, we utilize the bidirectional flow information at the previous iteration to obtain the matching points of points and superpoint centers for soft point-to-superpoint association construction, in which the superpoints are generated for pairwise point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-3d-scene-flow-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Graph Learning and Model Fitting in Laplacian Regularized Stratified Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-graph-learning-and-model-fitting-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Laplacian regularized stratified models (LRSM) are models that utilize the explicit or implicit network structure of the sub-problems as defined by the categorical features called strata (e. g., age, region, time, forecast horizon, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-graph-learning-and-model-fitting-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalize Segment Anything Model with One Shot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalize-segment-anything-model-with-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driven by large-data pre-training, Segment Anything Model (SAM) has been demonstrated as a powerful and promptable framework, revolutionizing the segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalize-segment-anything-model-with-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panda LLM: Training Data and Evaluation for Open-Sourced Chinese Instruction-Following Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panda-llm-training-data-and-evaluation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This project focuses on enhancing open-source large language models through instruction-tuning and providing comprehensive evaluations of their performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panda-llm-training-data-and-evaluation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Dialogue Topic Segmentation with Topic-aware Utterance Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-dialogue-topic-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dialogue Topic Segmentation (DTS) plays an essential role in a variety of dialogue modeling tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-dialogue-topic-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperNOVA: Design Strategies and Opportunities for Interactive Visualization in Computational Notebooks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supernova-design-strategies-and-opportunities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through this work, we identify unique design opportunities and considerations for future notebook VA tools, such as using and manipulating multimodal data in notebooks as well as balancing the degree of visualization-notebook integration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supernova-design-strategies-and-opportunities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZipIt! Merging Models from Different Tasks without Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipit-merging-models-from-different-tasks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While this works for models trained on the same task, we find that this fails to account for the differences in models trained on disjoint tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipit-merging-models-from-different-tasks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional and Residual Methods in Scalable Coding for Humans and Machines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-and-residual-methods-in-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present methods for conditional and residual coding in the context of scalable coding for humans and machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-and-residual-methods-in-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-aware Generation of Multi-view Portrait Drawings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-generation-of-multi-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our motivation is that facial semantic labels are view-consistent and correlate with drawing techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-generation-of-multi-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled Contrastive Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-contrastive-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies show that graph neural networks (GNNs) are prevalent to model high-order relationships for collaborative filtering (CF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-contrastive-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarially-Guided Portrait Matting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarially-guided-portrait-matting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We utilize this model to provide image-mask pairs for the StyleGAN3- based network (StyleMatteGAN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarially-guided-portrait-matting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caption Anything: Interactive Image Description with Diverse Multimodal Controls</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caption-anything-interactive-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Controllable image captioning is an emerging multimodal topic that aims to describe the image with natural language following human purpose, $\textit{e. g.}$, looking at the specified regions or telling in a particular text style.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caption-anything-interactive-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RCP-RF: A Comprehensive Road-car-pedestrian Risk Management Framework based on Driving Risk Potential Field</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rcp-rf-a-comprehensive-road-car-pedestrian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have witnessed the proliferation of traffic accidents, which led wide researches on Automated Vehicle (AV) technologies to reduce vehicle accidents, especially on risk assessment framework of AV technologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rcp-rf-a-comprehensive-road-car-pedestrian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedCBO: Reaching Group Consensus in Clustered Federated Learning through Consensus-based Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedcbo-reaching-group-consensus-in-clustered</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is an important framework in modern machine learning that seeks to integrate the training of learning models from multiple users, each user having their own local data set, in a way that is sensitive to data privacy and to communication loss constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedcbo-reaching-group-consensus-in-clustered</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding cirrus clouds using explainable machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-cirrus-clouds-using-explainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Their dependencies on meteorological and aerosol conditions are among the largest uncertainties in global climate models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-cirrus-clouds-using-explainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>System Neural Diversity: Measuring Behavioral Heterogeneity in Multi-Agent Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/system-neural-diversity-measuring-behavioral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When a system of learning agents is not constrained to homogeneous policies, individual agents may develop diverse behaviors, resulting in emergent complementarity that benefits the system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/system-neural-diversity-measuring-behavioral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zenseact Open Dataset: A large-scale and diverse multimodal dataset for autonomous driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zenseact-open-dataset-a-large-scale-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing datasets for autonomous driving (AD) often lack diversity and long-range capabilities, focusing instead on 360{\deg} perception and temporal reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zenseact-open-dataset-a-large-scale-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causality-aware Concept Extraction based on Knowledge-guided Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-aware-concept-extraction-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prompt adopts the topic of the given entity from the existing knowledge in KGs to mitigate the spurious co-occurrence correlations between entities and biased concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-aware-concept-extraction-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NorQuAD: Norwegian Question Answering Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/norquad-norwegian-question-answering-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present NorQuAD: the first Norwegian question answering dataset for machine reading comprehension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/norquad-norwegian-question-answering-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approximating CKY with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximating-cky-with-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the ability of transformer models to approximate the CKY algorithm, using them to directly predict a parse and thus avoid the CKY algorithm's cubic dependence on sentence length.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximating-cky-with-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Natural Language Watermarking through Invariant Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-natural-language-watermarking-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have witnessed a proliferation of valuable original natural language contents found in subscription-based media outlets, web novel platforms, and outputs of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-natural-language-watermarking-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastAMI -- a Monte Carlo Approach to the Adjustment for Chance in Clustering Comparison Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastami-a-monte-carlo-approach-to-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clustering is at the very core of machine learning, and its applications proliferate with the increasing availability of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastami-a-monte-carlo-approach-to-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards the Decarbonization of the Mobility Sector: Promoting Renewable-Based Charging in Green Ride-Sharing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-decarbonization-of-the-mobility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new mechanism to promote EV charging during hours of high renewable generation, and we introduce the concept of charge request, which is issued by a power utility company.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-decarbonization-of-the-mobility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling-up Remote Sensing Segmentation Dataset with Segment Anything Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-remote-sensing-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of the Segment Anything Model (SAM) demonstrates the significance of data-centric machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-remote-sensing-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lift Yourself Up: Retrieval-augmented Text Generation with Self Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lift-yourself-up-retrieval-augmented-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, by exploring the duality of the primal problem: better generation also prompts better memory, we propose a framework called Selfmem, which iteratively adopts a retrieval-augmented generator itself to generate an unbounded memory pool and uses a memory selector to pick one generated memory for the next generation round.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lift-yourself-up-retrieval-augmented-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lightweight CNN-Transformer Model for Learning Traveling Salesman Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-cnn-transformer-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model consumes approximately 20% less GPU memory usage and has 45% faster inference time compared with other state-of-the-art Transformer-based models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-cnn-transformer-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Contrastive Learning of Sentence Embeddings from AI Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-contrastive-learning-of-sentence-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method utilizes AI feedback from large pre-trained language models (LLMs) to construct sample pairs with fine-grained sample similarity scores to improve contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-contrastive-learning-of-sentence-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of Label-Description Training for Zero-Shot Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-benefits-of-label-description-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models have improved zero-shot text classification by allowing the transfer of semantic knowledge from the training data in order to classify among specific label sets in downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-benefits-of-label-description-training</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
