<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 21:08:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Learning for Long-Horizon Planning via Neuro-Symbolic Abductive Imitation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-for-long-horizon-planning-via-neuro</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, traditional symbolic planning excels in long-horizon tasks through logical reasoning over human-defined symbolic spaces but struggles to handle observations beyond symbolic states, such as high-dimensional visual inputs encountered in real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-for-long-horizon-planning-via-neuro</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning optimal objective values for MILP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-optimal-objective-values-for-milp</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern Mixed Integer Linear Programming (MILP) solvers use the Branch-and-Bound algorithm together with a plethora of auxiliary components that speed up the search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-optimal-objective-values-for-milp</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLS: Geometry-aware 3D Language Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gls-geometry-aware-3d-language-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, 3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) has achieved significant performance on indoor surface reconstruction and open-vocabulary segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gls-geometry-aware-3d-language-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Multispectral Object Detection: A Bag of Tricks and Comprehensive Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-multispectral-object-detection-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multispectral object detection, utilizing RGB and TIR (thermal infrared) modalities, is widely recognized as a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-multispectral-object-detection-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Mamba Distillation for Low-resolution Fine-grained Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-mamba-distillation-for-low-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-resolution fine-grained image classification has recently made significant progress, largely thanks to the super-resolution techniques and knowledge distillation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-mamba-distillation-for-low-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating and Improving the Robustness of Security Attack Detectors Generated by LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-and-improving-the-robustness-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are increasingly used in software development to generate functions, such as attack detectors, that implement security requirements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-and-improving-the-robustness-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Fourier-embedded Network for Bi-modal Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fourier-embedded-network-for-bi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of deep learning provides a significant improvement of salient object detection combining both RGB and thermal images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fourier-embedded-network-for-bi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Knowledge Concepts to Whole Slide Images for Precise Histopathology Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-knowledge-concepts-to-whole-slide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the large size and lack of fine-grained annotation, Whole Slide Images (WSIs) analysis is commonly approached as a Multiple Instance Learning (MIL) problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-knowledge-concepts-to-whole-slide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RITA: Automatic Framework for Designing of Resilient IoT Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rita-automatic-framework-for-designing-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing resilient Internet of Things (IoT) systems requires i) identification of IoT Critical Objects (ICOs) such as services, devices, and resources, ii) threat analysis, and iii) mitigation strategy selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rita-automatic-framework-for-designing-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatRex: Taming Multimodal LLM for Joint Perception and Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatrex-taming-multimodal-llm-for-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From the data perspective, we build a fully automated data engine and construct the Rexverse-2M dataset which possesses multiple granularities to support the joint training of perception and understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatrex-taming-multimodal-llm-for-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Surface Priors for Editable Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-surface-priors-for-editable-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike other methods, our pipeline allows modifications applied to the extracted mesh to be propagated to the proxy representation, from which we recover the updated parameters of the Gaussians.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-surface-priors-for-editable-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Neural Networks Do Work with Pre-Defined Filters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-do-work-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel class of Convolutional Neural Networks called Pre-defined Filter Convolutional Neural Networks (PFCNNs), where all nxn convolution kernels with n>1 are pre-defined and constant during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-do-work-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RL for Mitigating Cascading Failures: Targeted Exploration via Sensitivity Factors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-for-mitigating-cascading-failures-targeted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Electricity grid's resiliency and climate change strongly impact one another due to an array of technical and policy-related decisions that impact both.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-for-mitigating-cascading-failures-targeted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoLLM Knows When to Speak: Enhancing Time-Sensitive Video Comprehension with Video-Text Duet Interaction Format</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videollm-knows-when-to-speak-enhancing-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We construct MMDuetIT, a video-text training dataset designed to adapt VideoLLMs to video-text duet interaction format.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videollm-knows-when-to-speak-enhancing-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model-Brained GUI Agents: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-brained-gui-agents-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This has paved the way for a new generation of LLM-brained GUI agents capable of interpreting complex GUI elements and autonomously executing actions based on natural language instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-brained-gui-agents-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergence of Self-Identity in AI: A Mathematical Framework and Empirical Study with Generative Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-self-identity-in-ai-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a mathematical framework for defining and quantifying self-identity in artificial intelligence (AI) systems, addressing a critical gap in the theoretical foundations of artificial consciousness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-self-identity-in-ai-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Confidence in Deep Generative Protein Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-confidence-in-deep-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep generative models show promise for de novo protein design, but their effectiveness within specific protein families remains underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-confidence-in-deep-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUPE: Heuristic Underwater Perceptual Enhancement with Semantic Collaborative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hupe-heuristic-underwater-perceptual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To strike a balance between visual quality and application, we propose a heuristic invertible network for underwater perception enhancement, dubbed HUPE, which enhances visual quality and demonstrates flexibility in handling other downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hupe-heuristic-underwater-perceptual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helvipad: A Real-World Dataset for Omnidirectional Stereo Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helvipad-a-real-world-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite considerable progress in stereo depth estimation, omnidirectional imaging remains underexplored, mainly due to the lack of appropriate data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helvipad-a-real-world-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Path: Multi-modal, Multi-granularity Path Representation Learning -- Extended Version</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-path-multi-modal-multi-granularity-path</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel Multi-modal, Multi-granularity Path Representation Learning Framework (MM-Path), which can learn a generic path representation by integrating modalities from both road paths and image paths.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-path-multi-modal-multi-granularity-path</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectral-Spatial Transformer with Active Transfer Learning for Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-spatial-transformer-with-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a novel multi-stage active transfer learning (ATL) framework that integrates a Spatial-Spectral Transformer (SST) with an active learning process for efficient HSI classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-spatial-transformer-with-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monocular Obstacle Avoidance Based on Inverse PPO for Fixed-wing UAVs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-obstacle-avoidance-based-on-inverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After that, a reinforcement learning controller with a novel reward function is designed to balance the target approach and flight trajectory smoothness, satisfying the specific dynamic constraints and stability requirements of a fixed-wing UAV platform.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-obstacle-avoidance-based-on-inverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuaLLM-Health: An Adaptation of an LLM-Based Framework for Quantitative Data Extraction from Online Health Discussions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quallm-health-an-adaptation-of-an-llm-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present an adapted framework from QuaLLM into QuaLLM-Health for extracting clinically relevant quantitative data from Reddit discussions about glucagon-like peptide-1 (GLP-1) receptor agonists using large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quallm-health-an-adaptation-of-an-llm-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Learning for Deep Learning-based Prediction of Lattice Thermal Conductivity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-deep-learning-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interestingly, we also show that a much greater improvement is obtained when first fine-tuning it on a large datasets of low-quality approximations of LTC (based on the AGL model) and then applying a second phase of fine-tuning with our high-quality, smaller-scale datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-deep-learning-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The more, the better? Evaluating the role of EEG preprocessing for deep learning applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-more-the-better-evaluating-the-role-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The last decade has witnessed a notable surge in deep learning applications for the analysis of electroencephalography (EEG) data, thanks to its demonstrated superiority over conventional statistical techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-more-the-better-evaluating-the-role-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isometry pursuit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isometry-pursuit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Isometry pursuit is a convex algorithm for identifying orthonormal column-submatrices of wide matrices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isometry-pursuit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoCATe-GAT: Modeling Multi-Scale Local Context and Action Relationships for Zero-Shot Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locate-gat-modeling-multi-scale-local-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we obtain relative gains of 3. 8% and 4. 8% on these datasets in conventional and 16. 6% on UCF101in generalized ZSAR settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locate-gat-modeling-multi-scale-local-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Open Vocabulary to Open World: Teaching Vision Language Models to Detect Novel Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-open-vocabulary-to-open-world-teaching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address theses limitations, we propose a framework that enables OVD models to operate in open world settings, by identifying and incrementally learning novel objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-open-vocabulary-to-open-world-teaching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuMapper: Towards Automatic Verification of Large-Scale POIs with Street Views at Baidu Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dumapper-towards-automatic-verification-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increased popularity of mobile devices, Web mapping services have become an indispensable tool in our daily lives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dumapper-towards-automatic-verification-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Runtime-Adaptive Transformer Neural Network Accelerator on FPGAs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-runtime-adaptive-transformer-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, it achieves a speedup of 1. 7 to 2. 25$\times$ compared to some state-of-the-art FPGA-based accelerators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-runtime-adaptive-transformer-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training and Evaluating Language Models with Template-based Data Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-evaluating-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we introduce Template-based Data Generation (TDG), a novel approach that leverages LLMs (GPT-4) to automatically generate parameterized meta-templates, which are then used to synthesize a vast array of high-quality problems and solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-evaluating-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaVLN: Towards Visual Language Navigation in Continuous Indoor Environments with Moving Humans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adavln-towards-visual-language-navigation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Language Navigation is a task that challenges robots to navigate in realistic environments based on natural language instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adavln-towards-visual-language-navigation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeneQuery: A General QA-based Framework for Spatial Gene Expression Predictions from Histology Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genequery-a-general-qa-based-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gene expression profiling provides profound insights into molecular mechanisms, but its time-consuming and costly nature often presents significant challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genequery-a-general-qa-based-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metric-DST: Mitigating Selection Bias Through Diversity-Guided Semi-Supervised Metric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metric-dst-mitigating-selection-bias-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Selection bias poses a critical challenge for fairness in machine learning, as models trained on data that is less representative of the population might exhibit undesirable behavior for underrepresented profiles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metric-dst-mitigating-selection-bias-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing MMDiT-Based Text-to-Image Models for Similar Subject Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-mmdit-based-text-to-image-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant improvements, we observe that semantic ambiguity persists when generating multiple similar subjects, as the guidance provided by overlap loss is not explicit enough.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-mmdit-based-text-to-image-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveying the space of descriptions of a composite system with machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surveying-the-space-of-descriptions-of-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By integrating machine learning into a fine-grained information theoretic analysis of composite random variables, our framework opens a new avenues for probing the structure of real-world complex systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surveying-the-space-of-descriptions-of-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Noise Token Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-noise-token-pruning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the present work we present Training Noise Token (TNT) Pruning for vision transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-noise-token-pruning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature-Factory: Automating Software Feature Integration Using Generative AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-factory-automating-software-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Integrating new features into existing software projects can be a complex and time-consuming process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-factory-automating-software-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning with Fairness Guarantees using Lorenz Dominance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-multi-objective-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning (MORL) aims to learn a set of policies that optimize trade-offs between multiple, often conflicting objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-multi-objective-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Blind All-in-One Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-blind-all-in-one-image-restoration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Blind all-in-one image restoration models aim to recover a high-quality image from an input degraded with unknown distortions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-blind-all-in-one-image-restoration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimeMarker: A Versatile Video-LLM for Long and Short Video Understanding with Superior Temporal Localization Ability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timemarker-a-versatile-video-llm-for-long-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rapid development of large language models (LLMs) has significantly advanced multimodal large language models (LMMs), particularly in vision-language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timemarker-a-versatile-video-llm-for-long-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Draft Model Knows When to Stop: A Self-Verification Length Policy for Speculative Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/draft-model-knows-when-to-stop-a-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speculative Decoding (SD) has become an important technique in accelerating the inference speed of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/draft-model-knows-when-to-stop-a-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulating Tabular Datasets through LLMs to Rapidly Explore Hypotheses about Real-World Entities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-tabular-datasets-through-llms-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Do horror writers have worse childhoods than other writers?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-tabular-datasets-through-llms-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Hamiltonian neural networks without backpropagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-hamiltonian-neural-networks-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks that synergistically integrate data and physical laws offer great promise in modeling dynamical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-hamiltonian-neural-networks-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grounding-IQA: Multimodal Language Grounding Model for Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-iqa-multimodal-language-grounding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments demonstrate that our proposed task paradigm, dataset, and benchmark facilitate the more fine-grained IQA application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-iqa-multimodal-language-grounding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling nnU-Net for CBCT Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-nnu-net-for-cbct-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents our approach to scaling the nnU-Net framework for multi-structure segmentation on Cone Beam Computed Tomography (CBCT) images, specifically in the scope of the ToothFairy2 Challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-nnu-net-for-cbct-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSDFace: One-Step Diffusion Model for Face Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/osdface-one-step-diffusion-model-for-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, existing methods often struggle to generate face images that are harmonious, realistic, and consistent with the subject's identity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/osdface-one-step-diffusion-model-for-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$H^3$Fusion: Helpful, Harmless, Honest Fusion of Aligned LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h-3-fusion-helpful-harmless-honest-fusion-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The former penalizes the selection errors of the expert-router, and the latter mediates the expert weights drifting during fine-tuning and dynamically adjusts the fusion behavior of the resulting model by canalizing the activations on the experts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h-3-fusion-helpful-harmless-honest-fusion-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Efficiency of NLP-Inspired Methods for Tabular Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-efficiency-of-nlp-inspired-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in tabular deep learning (DL) have led to substantial performance improvements, surpassing the capabilities of traditional models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-efficiency-of-nlp-inspired-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Decoding Makes Visual Auto-Regressive Modeling Efficient</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-decoding-makes-visual-auto</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The large model serves as the 'drafter', specializing in generating low-frequency content at smaller scales, while the smaller model serves as the 'refiner', solely focusing on predicting high-frequency details at larger scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-decoding-makes-visual-auto</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
