<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 09:12:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Optimising Event-Driven Spiking Neural Network with Regularisation and Cutoff</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimising-event-driven-spiking-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two novel optimisation techniques are presented to achieve AOI-SNNs: a regularisation and a cutoff.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimising-event-driven-spiking-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Non-deterministic Human Behaviors in Discrete Food Choices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-non-deterministic-human-behaviors-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We establish a non-deterministic model that predicts a user's food preferences from their demographic information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-non-deterministic-human-behaviors-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximum Mean Discrepancy Kernels for Predictive and Prognostic Modeling of Whole Slide Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximum-mean-discrepancy-kernels-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How similar are two images?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximum-mean-discrepancy-kernels-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Expressive Power of Geometric Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-expressive-power-of-geometric-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The expressive power of Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) has been studied extensively through the Weisfeiler-Leman (WL) graph isomorphism test.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-expressive-power-of-geometric-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triplet Contrastive Learning for Unsupervised Vehicle Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triplet-contrastive-learning-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the inter-class instance, a hybrid contrastive loss (HCL) re-defines the sample correlations by approaching the positive cluster features and leaving the all negative instance features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triplet-contrastive-learning-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleGAN-T: Unlocking the Power of GANs for Fast Large-Scale Text-to-Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylegan-t-unlocking-the-power-of-gans-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image synthesis has recently seen significant progress thanks to large pretrained language models, large-scale training data, and the introduction of scalable model families such as diffusion and autoregressive models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylegan-t-unlocking-the-power-of-gans-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensemaking About Contraceptive Methods Across Online Platforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensemaking-about-contraceptive-methods</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Selecting a birth control method is a complex healthcare decision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensemaking-about-contraceptive-methods</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Active 3D Object Detection from a Generalization Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-active-3d-object-detection-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate the high annotation cost in LiDAR-based 3D object detection, active learning is a promising solution that learns to select only a small portion of unlabeled data to annotate, without compromising model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-active-3d-object-detection-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ddml: Double/debiased machine learning in Stata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddml-double-debiased-machine-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the package ddml for Double/Debiased Machine Learning (DDML) in Stata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddml-double-debiased-machine-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StockEmotions: Discover Investor Emotions for Financial Sentiment Analysis and Multivariate Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stockemotions-discover-investor-emotions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There has been growing interest in applying NLP techniques in the financial domain, however, resources are extremely limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stockemotions-discover-investor-emotions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prediction-Powered Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-powered-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce prediction-powered inference $\unicode{x2013}$ a framework for performing valid statistical inference when an experimental data set is supplemented with predictions from a machine-learning system such as AlphaFold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-powered-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debiasing the Cloze Task in Sequential Recommendation with Bidirectional Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-the-cloze-task-in-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The most common approach to mitigating exposure bias in recommendation has been Inverse Propensity Scoring (IPS), which consists of down-weighting the interacted predictions in the loss function in proportion to their propensities of exposure, yielding a theoretically unbiased learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-the-cloze-task-in-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy Prediction using Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-prediction-using-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we demonstrate the viability of using federated learning to successfully predict energy consumption as well as solar production for all households within a certain network using low-power and low-space consuming embedded devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-prediction-using-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPEC5G: A Dataset for 5G Cellular Network Protocol Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spec5g-a-dataset-for-5g-cellular-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[5G is the 5th generation cellular network protocol.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spec5g-a-dataset-for-5g-cellular-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidirectional Propagation for Cross-Modal 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-propagation-for-cross-modal-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works have revealed the superiority of feature-level fusion for cross-modal 3D object detection, where fine-grained feature propagation from 2D image pixels to 3D LiDAR points has been widely adopted for performance improvement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-propagation-for-cross-modal-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Champion Solution for the WSDM2023 Toloka VQA Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/champion-solution-for-the-wsdm2023-toloka-vqa</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we present our champion solution to the WSDM2023 Toloka Visual Question Answering (VQA) Challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/champion-solution-for-the-wsdm2023-toloka-vqa</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Propagation of Linear Uncertainties through Multiline Thru-Reflect-Line Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/propagation-of-linear-uncertainties-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study proposes a linear approach for propagating uncertainties in the multiline thru-reflect-line (TRL) calibration method for vector network analyzers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/propagation-of-linear-uncertainties-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study of Metrics to Measure Representational Harms in Pre-Trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-metrics-to-measure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale Pre-Trained Language Models (PTLMs) capture knowledge from massive human-written data which contains latent societal biases and toxic contents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-metrics-to-measure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Data Selection for TTS: Using Arabic Broadcast News as a Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-data-selection-for-tts-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several high-resource Text to Speech (TTS) systems currently produce natural, well-established human-like speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-data-selection-for-tts-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tier Balancing: Towards Dynamic Fairness over Underlying Causal Factors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tier-balancing-towards-dynamic-fairness-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pursuit of long-term fairness involves the interplay between decision-making and the underlying data generating process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tier-balancing-towards-dynamic-fairness-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting a Language Model While Preserving its General Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-a-language-model-while-preserving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper shows that the existing methods are suboptimal and proposes a novel method to perform a more informed adaptation of the knowledge in the LM by (1) soft-masking the attention heads based on their importance to best preserve the general knowledge in the LM and (2) contrasting the representations of the general and the full (both general and domain knowledge) to learn an integrated representation with both general and domain-specific knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-a-language-model-while-preserving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Deep Regression with Ordinal Entropy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-deep-regression-with-ordinal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In computer vision, it is often observed that formulating regression problems as a classification task often yields better performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-deep-regression-with-ordinal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poor Man's Quality Estimation: Predicting Reference-Based MT Metrics Without the Reference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poor-man-s-quality-estimation-predicting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine translation quality estimation (QE) predicts human judgements of a translation hypothesis without seeing the reference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poor-man-s-quality-estimation-predicting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Methods for Building Dialects-Mandarin Code-Mixing Corpora: A Case Study in Taiwanese Hokkien</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-methods-for-building-dialects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In natural language processing (NLP), code-mixing (CM) is a challenging task, especially when the mixed languages include dialects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-methods-for-building-dialects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Explanation and Instance-Generation using Cycle-Consistent Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanation-and-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, since it is often not straight forward to obtain the labels in many application domains such as in medical image, classification-based approaches have become the de facto standard to perform the diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanation-and-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recurrent Contour-based Instance Segmentation with Progressive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrent-contour-based-instance-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel deep network architecture, i. e., PolySnake, for contour-based instance segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrent-contour-based-instance-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExClaim: Explainable Neural Claim Verification Using Rationalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exclaim-explainable-neural-claim-verification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel claim verification approach, namely: ExClaim, that attempts to provide an explainable claim verification system with foundational evidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exclaim-explainable-neural-claim-verification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transforming Unstructured Text into Data with Context Rule Assisted Machine Learning (CRAML)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transforming-unstructured-text-into-data-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe a method and new no-code software tools enabling domain experts to build custom structured, labeled datasets from the unstructured text of documents and build niche machine learning text classification models traceable to expert-written rules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transforming-unstructured-text-into-data-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is ChatGPT A Good Translator? A Preliminary Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-chatgpt-a-good-translator-a-preliminary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report provides a preliminary evaluation of ChatGPT for machine translation, including translation prompt, multilingual translation, and translation robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-chatgpt-a-good-translator-a-preliminary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massively Parallel Genetic Optimization through Asynchronous Propagation of Populations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/massively-parallel-genetic-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Propulate, an evolutionary optimization algorithm and software package for global optimization and in particular hyperparameter search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/massively-parallel-genetic-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Organization Towards $1/f$ Noise in Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-organization-towards-1-f-noise-in-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite $1/f$ noise being ubiquitous in both natural and artificial systems, no general explanations for the phenomenon have received widespread acceptance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-organization-towards-1-f-noise-in-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Learning for Data Scarcity in a Fatigue Damage Prognostic Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-for-data-scarcity-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper aims to investigate whether pre-training DL models in a self-supervised way on unlabelled sensors data can be useful for RUL estimation with only Few-Shots Learning, i. e. with scarce labelled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-for-data-scarcity-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differential Privacy in Cooperative Multiagent Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-privacy-in-cooperative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We synthesize policies that are robust to privacy by reducing the value of the total correlation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-privacy-in-cooperative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Semantic Relatedness Dataset for Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-semantic-relatedness-dataset-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern image captioning system relies heavily on extracting knowledge from images to capture the concept of a static story.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-semantic-relatedness-dataset-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Skill Learning Via Classical Robotics-Based Generated Datasets: Advantages, Disadvantages, and Future Improvement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robot-skill-learning-via-classical-robotics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article argues that a dataset created using a classical robotics algorithm is a crucial part of future development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robot-skill-learning-via-classical-robotics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Source-free Subject Adaptation for EEG-based Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/source-free-subject-adaptation-for-eeg-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel and practical problem setup, namely source-free subject adaptation, where the source subject data are unavailable and only the pre-trained model parameters are provided for subject adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/source-free-subject-adaptation-for-eeg-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan To Predict: Learning an Uncertainty-Foreseeing Model for Model-Based Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plan-to-predict-learning-an-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Model-based Reinforcement Learning (MBRL), model learning is critical since an inaccurate model can bias policy learning via generating misleading samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plan-to-predict-learning-an-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Frequency-Specific Quantization Scaling in VVC for Standard-Compliant Task-driven Image Coding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-frequency-specific-quantization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is a well-known method for the human visual system, where scaling lists are derived from psycho-visual models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-frequency-specific-quantization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>causalgraph: A Python Package for Modeling, Persisting and Visualizing Causal Graphs Embedded in Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalgraph-a-python-package-for-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes a novel Python package, named causalgraph, for modeling and saving causal graphs embedded in knowledge graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalgraph-a-python-package-for-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Multilayer Graph Neural Network for Cancer Gene Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-multilayer-graph-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The identification of cancer genes is a critical, yet challenging problem in cancer genomics research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-multilayer-graph-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Sketch Colorization using Adversarial Segmentation Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-sketch-colorization-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We leverage semantic image segmentation from a general-purpose panoptic segmentation network to generate an additional adversarial loss function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-sketch-colorization-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Should I Engage with At What Time? A Missing Event Aware Temporal Graph Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/who-should-i-engage-with-at-what-time-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In real-world applications, events are not always observable, and estimating event time is as important as predicting future events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/who-should-i-engage-with-at-what-time-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Private Online Bayesian Estimation With Adaptive Truncation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-online-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel online and adaptive truncation method for differentially private Bayesian online estimation of a static parameter regarding a population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-online-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Inference in Denoising Diffusion Models via MMD Finetuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-inference-in-denoising-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings show that the proposed method is able to produce high-quality samples in a fraction of the time required by widely-used diffusion models, and outperforms state-of-the-art techniques for accelerated sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-inference-in-denoising-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Deep Learning with Scenario-Based Override Rules: a Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-deep-learning-with-scenario-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNNs) have become a crucial instrument in the software development toolkit, due to their ability to efficiently solve complex problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-deep-learning-with-scenario-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FECANet: Boosting Few-Shot Semantic Segmentation with Feature-Enhanced Context-Aware Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fecanet-boosting-few-shot-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few-shot semantic segmentation is the task of learning to locate each pixel of the novel class in the query image with only a few annotated support images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fecanet-boosting-few-shot-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooperative Distributed MPC via Decentralized Real-Time Optimization: Implementation Results for Robot Formations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-distributed-mpc-via-decentralized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discuss the implementation via decentralized optimization algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-distributed-mpc-via-decentralized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEnt: An Entropy-based Model-agnostic Explainability Framework to Contrast Classifiers' Decisions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cent-an-entropy-based-model-agnostic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our Contrastive Entropy-based explanation method, CEnt, approximates a model locally by a decision tree to compute entropy information of different feature splits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cent-an-entropy-based-model-agnostic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The role of noise in denoising models for anomaly detection in medical images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-role-of-noise-in-denoising-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Denoising methods, for instance classical denoising autoencoders (DAEs) and more recently emerging diffusion models, are a promising approach, however naive application of pixelwise noise leads to poor anomaly detection performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-role-of-noise-in-denoising-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpreting CNN Predictions using Conditional Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-cnn-predictions-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Supplying that information has two main challenges: how to represent this information in a form that is feedable to the GANs and how to effectively feed the representation to the GAN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-cnn-predictions-using</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
