<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 21:08:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Multiview Object Consistency in Humans and Image Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-multiview-object-consistency-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a benchmark to directly evaluate the alignment between human observers and vision models on a 3D shape inference task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-multiview-object-consistency-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RotCAtt-TransUNet++: Novel Deep Neural Network for Sophisticated Cardiac Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rotcatt-transunet-novel-deep-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cardiovascular disease is a major global health concern, contributing significantly to global mortality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rotcatt-transunet-novel-deep-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Atmospheric Scattering-driven Attention via Channel and Gamma Correction Priors for Low-Light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-atmospheric-scattering-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-light image enhancement remains a critical challenge in computer vision, as does the lightweight design for edge devices with the computational burden for deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-atmospheric-scattering-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAN-Based Fusion of Dual-Domain for Audio-Driven Facial Landmarks Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kan-based-fusion-of-dual-domain-for-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the KFusion of Dual-Domain model, a robust model that generates landmarks from audio.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kan-based-fusion-of-dual-domain-for-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A general reduced-order neural operator for spatio-temporal predictive learning on complex spatial domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-reduced-order-neural-operator-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predictive learning for spatio-temporal processes (PL-STP) on complex spatial domains plays a critical role in various scientific and engineering fields, with its essence being the construction of operators between infinite-dimensional function spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-reduced-order-neural-operator-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototype-Driven Multi-Feature Generation for Visible-Infrared Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-driven-multi-feature-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The primary challenges in visible-infrared person re-identification arise from the differences between visible (vis) and infrared (ir) images, including inter-modal and intra-modal variations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-driven-multi-feature-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extracting the U.S. building types from OpenStreetMap data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extracting-the-u-s-building-types-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A major result of this work is the resulting dataset of classifying 67, 705, 475 buildings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extracting-the-u-s-building-types-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatially-Aware Speaker for Vision-and-Language Navigation Instruction Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatially-aware-speaker-for-vision-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Embodied AI aims to develop robots that can \textit{understand} and execute human language instructions, as well as communicate in natural languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatially-aware-speaker-for-vision-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting English Winogender Schemas for Consistency, Coverage, and Grammatical Case</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-english-winogender-schemas-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While measuring bias and robustness in coreference resolution are important goals, such measurements are only as good as the tools we use to measure them with.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-english-winogender-schemas-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedBrain-Distill: Communication-Efficient Federated Brain Tumor Classification Using Ensemble Knowledge Distillation on Non-IID Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedbrain-distill-communication-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose FedBrain-Distill, an approach that leverages Knowledge Distillation (KD) in an FL setting that maintains the users privacy and ensures the independence of FL clients in terms of model architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedbrain-distill-communication-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Chinese Knowledge Rectification in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-chinese-knowledge-rectification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Large Language Models (LLMs) exhibit remarkable generative capabilities, they are not without flaws, particularly in the form of hallucinations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-chinese-knowledge-rectification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Tree Probability Estimation with Stochastic Optimization and Variance Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-tree-probability-estimation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Probability estimation of tree topologies is one of the fundamental tasks in phylogenetic inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-tree-probability-estimation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrofitting Temporal Graph Neural Networks with Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrofitting-temporal-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also adapt Transformer codebase to train TF-TGN efficiently with multiple GPUs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrofitting-temporal-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IndicVoices-R: Unlocking a Massive Multilingual Multi-speaker Speech Corpus for Scaling Indian TTS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indicvoices-r-unlocking-a-massive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our pipeline leverages the cross-lingual generalization of denoising and speech enhancement models trained on English and applied to Indian languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indicvoices-r-unlocking-a-massive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STLM Engineering Report: Dropout</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stlm-engineering-report-dropout</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we explore the relevance of dropout for modern language models, particularly in the context of models on the scale of <100M parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stlm-engineering-report-dropout</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEROjD: Lidar Extended Radar-Only Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lerojd-lidar-extended-radar-only-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore two strategies to transfer knowledge from the lidar to the radar domain and radar-only object detectors: 1. multi-stage training with sequential lidar point cloud thin-out, and 2. cross-modal knowledge distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lerojd-lidar-extended-radar-only-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Intrinsic Language-specific Subspaces in Fine-tuning Multilingual Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-intrinsic-language-specific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose architecture learning techniques and introduce a gradual pruning schedule during fine-tuning to exhaustively explore the optimal setting and the minimal intrinsic subspaces for each language, resulting in a lightweight yet effective fine-tuning procedure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-intrinsic-language-specific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Low-Computational Video Synopsis Framework with a Standard Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-low-computational-video-synopsis-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This technique begins with the detection and tracking of objects, followed by the creation of object tubes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-low-computational-video-synopsis-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can OOD Object Detectors Learn from Foundation Models?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-ood-object-detectors-learn-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-distribution (OOD) object detection is a challenging task due to the absence of open-set OOD data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-ood-object-detectors-learn-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Mixup Augmentations and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-mixup-augmentations-and-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As Deep Neural Networks have achieved thrilling breakthroughs in the past decade, data augmentations have garnered increasing attention as regularization techniques when massive labeled data are unavailable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-mixup-augmentations-and-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision-fused Attack: Advancing Aggressive and Stealthy Adversarial Text against Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-fused-attack-advancing-aggressive-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing studies on adversarial attacks are insufficient in both attacking ability and human imperceptibility due to their sole focus on the scope of language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-fused-attack-advancing-aggressive-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first Cadenza challenges: using machine learning competitions to improve music for listeners with a hearing loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-first-cadenza-challenges-using-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper details the first application of the open challenge methodology to use machine learning to improve audio quality of music for those with hearing loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-first-cadenza-challenges-using-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBS: Bi-directional Bit-level Sparsity for Deep Learning Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bbs-bi-directional-bit-level-sparsity-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the hardware side, we demonstrate the potential of BBS through BitVert, a bitserial architecture with an efficient PE design to accelerate DNNs with low overhead, exploiting our proposed binary pruning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bbs-bi-directional-bit-level-sparsity-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PatchAlign:Fair and Accurate Skin Disease Image Classification by Alignment with Clinical Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchalign-fair-and-accurate-skin-disease</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reduce the effect of noise and artifacts in clinical dermatology images, we propose a learnable Masked Graph Optimal Transport for cross-domain alignment that further improves fairness metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchalign-fair-and-accurate-skin-disease</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time-independent Spiking Neuron via Membrane Potential Estimation for Efficient Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-independent-spiking-neuron-via-membrane</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The computational inefficiency of spiking neural networks (SNNs) is primarily due to the sequential updates of membrane potential, which becomes more pronounced during extended encoding periods compared to artificial neural networks (ANNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-independent-spiking-neuron-via-membrane</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Grounding with Multi-modal Conditional Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-grounding-with-multi-modal-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then we utilize a set of weighting coefficients, which generated from the multimodal embeddings, to reorganize the weight update matrices and apply them to the visual encoder of the visual grounding model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-grounding-with-multi-modal-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natias: Neuron Attribution based Transferable Image Adversarial Steganography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natias-neuron-attribution-based-transferable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Steganalysis, on the contrary, aims to detect the presence of secret messages within images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natias-neuron-attribution-based-transferable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Patronizing and Condescending Language in Chinese Videos: A Multimodal Dataset and Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-patronizing-and-condescending</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Patronizing and Condescending Language (PCL) is a form of discriminatory toxic speech targeting vulnerable groups, threatening both online and offline safety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-patronizing-and-condescending</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NGD converges to less degenerate solutions than SGD</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ngd-converges-to-less-degenerate-solutions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The number of free parameters, or dimension, of a model is a straightforward way to measure its complexity: a model with more parameters can encode more information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ngd-converges-to-less-degenerate-solutions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centralized Selection with Preferences in the Presence of Biases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centralized-selection-with-preferences-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A central entity evaluates the utility of each candidate to the institutions, and the goal is to select candidates for each institution in a way that maximizes utility while also considering the candidates' preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centralized-selection-with-preferences-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Disentangling: Fine-grained representation learning through multi-level contrastive learning without class priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-disentangling-fine-grained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this reliance on class priors limits the applicability of such methods in real-world scenarios where class information is unavailable or ambiguous.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-disentangling-fine-grained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just ASR + LLM? A Study on Speech Large Language Models' Ability to Identify and Understand Speaker in Spoken Dialogue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/just-asr-llm-a-study-on-speech-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, after carefully examining Gaokao's questions, we find the correct answers to many questions can be inferred from the conversation context alone without identifying the speaker asked in the question.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/just-asr-llm-a-study-on-speech-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Line Aerial Image Restoration under dverse Weather: Datasets and Baselines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/power-line-aerial-image-restoration-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To circumvent this problem, we propose a new task of Power Line Aerial Image Restoration under Adverse Weather (PLAIR-AW), which aims to recover clean and high-quality images from degraded images with bad weather thus improving detection performance for PLAI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/power-line-aerial-image-restoration-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-stream Feature Augmentation for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-stream-feature-augmentation-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, the causality in discriminative features is not involved in these methods, which harms the generalization ability of model due to the spurious correlations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-stream-feature-augmentation-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SGSeg: Enabling Text-free Inference in Language-guided Segmentation of Chest X-rays via Self-guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgseg-enabling-text-free-inference-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segmentation of infected areas in chest X-rays is pivotal for facilitating the accurate delineation of pulmonary structures and pathological anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgseg-enabling-text-free-inference-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSFam: Scribble Supervised Salient Object Detection Family</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssfam-scribble-supervised-salient-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scribble supervised salient object detection (SSSOD) constructs segmentation ability of attractive objects from surroundings under the supervision of sparse scribble labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssfam-scribble-supervised-salient-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILE: A Mutation Testing Framework of In-Context Learning Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mile-a-mutation-testing-framework-of-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, inspired by the foundations of adopting testing techniques in machine learning (ML) systems, we propose a mutation testing framework designed to characterize the quality and effectiveness of test data for ICL systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mile-a-mutation-testing-framework-of-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metadata augmented deep neural networks for wild animal classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metadata-augmented-deep-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Camera trap imagery has become an invaluable asset in contemporary wildlife surveillance, enabling researchers to observe and investigate the behaviors of wild animals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metadata-augmented-deep-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Sparse Representation Clustering for High-Dimensional Data Streams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-sparse-representation-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, these algorithms are highly sensitive to the noise contained in high-dimensional data streams.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-sparse-representation-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Image Segmentation via Single-Source Domain Generalization with Random Amplitude Spectrum Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-image-segmentation-via-single-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed Random Amplitude Spectrum Synthesis for Single-Source Domain Generalization (RAS^4DG) is validated on 3D fetal brain images and 2D fundus photography, and achieves an improved DG segmentation performance compared to other SSDG models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-image-segmentation-via-single-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Finite Sample Performance of Double/Debiased Machine Learning with Propensity Score Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-finite-sample-performance-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning techniques are widely used for estimating causal effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-finite-sample-performance-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Shot Diffusion Mimicker for Handwritten Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-diffusion-mimicker-for-handwritten</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate that our method can successfully generate handwriting scripts with just one sample reference in multiple languages, even outperforming previous methods using over ten samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-diffusion-mimicker-for-handwritten</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnyMatch -- Efficient Zero-Shot Entity Matching with a Small Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anymatch-efficient-zero-shot-entity-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, our approach exhibits major cost benefits: the average prediction quality of AnyMatch is within 4. 4% of the state-of-the-art method MatchGPT with the proprietary trillion-parameter model GPT-4, yet AnyMatch requires four orders of magnitude less parameters and incurs a 3, 899 times lower inference cost (in dollars per 1, 000 tokens).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anymatch-efficient-zero-shot-entity-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoxKAN: Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks for Interpretable, High-Performance Survival Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coxkan-kolmogorov-arnold-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluation on the 9 real datasets show that CoxKAN consistently outperforms the Cox proportional hazards model and achieves performance that is superior or comparable to that of tuned MLPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coxkan-kolmogorov-arnold-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Approach to Inferring Chemical Compounds with the Desired Aqueous Solubility</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-approach-to-inferring-chemical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aqueous solubility (AS) is a key physiochemical property that plays a crucial role in drug discovery and material design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-approach-to-inferring-chemical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smooth-edged Perturbations Improve Perturbation-based Image Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smooth-edged-perturbations-improve</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the intractability of perturbing each pixel individually, images are typically attributed to larger segments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smooth-edged-perturbations-improve</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FS-MedSAM2: Exploring the Potential of SAM2 for Few-Shot Medical Image Segmentation without Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fs-medsam2-exploring-the-potential-of-sam2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Segment Anything Model 2 (SAM2) has recently demonstrated exceptional performance in zero-shot prompt segmentation for natural images and videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fs-medsam2-exploring-the-potential-of-sam2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixNet: Joining Force of Classical and Modern Approaches Toward the Comprehensive Pipeline in Motor Imagery EEG Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixnet-joining-force-of-classical-and-modern</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in deep learning (DL) have significantly impacted motor imagery (MI)-based brain-computer interface (BCI) systems, enhancing the decoding of electroencephalography (EEG) signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixnet-joining-force-of-classical-and-modern</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Programming Language Ensemble for Code Generation in Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-programming-language-ensemble-for-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This multi-language ensemble strategy leverages the complementary strengths of different programming languages, enabling the model to produce more accurate and robust code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-programming-language-ensemble-for-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influence of Early through Late Fusion on Pancreas Segmentation from Imperfectly Registered Multimodal MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/influence-of-early-through-late-fusion-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We trained a collection of basic UNets with different fusion points, spanning from early to late, to assess how early through late fusion influenced segmentation performance on imperfectly aligned images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/influence-of-early-through-late-fusion-on</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
