<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 21:06:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>How to Unleash the Power of Large Language Models for Few-shot Relation Extraction?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-unleash-the-power-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scaling language models have revolutionized widespread NLP tasks, yet little comprehensively explored few-shot relation extraction with large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-unleash-the-power-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-similarity-based super-resolution of photoacoustic angiography from hand-drawn doodles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-similarity-based-super-resolution-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose a novel approach that employs a super-resolution PAA method trained with forged PAA images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-similarity-based-super-resolution-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PU-EdgeFormer: Edge Transformer for Dense Prediction in Point Cloud Upsampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pu-edgeformer-edge-transformer-for-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We employ graph convolution using EdgeConv, which learns the local geometry and global structure of point cloud better than existing point-to-feature method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pu-edgeformer-edge-transformer-for-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Local to Global: Navigating Linguistic Diversity in the African Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-local-to-global-navigating-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The focus is on critical problems in NLP related to linguistic diversity and variation across the African continent, specifically with regards to African local di- alects and Arabic dialects that have received little attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-local-to-global-navigating-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complex Logical Reasoning over Knowledge Graphs using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-logical-reasoning-over-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reasoning over knowledge graphs (KGs) is a challenging task that requires a deep understanding of the complex relationships between entities and the underlying logic of their relations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-logical-reasoning-over-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Mask Annotation for Video Text Spotting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-mask-annotation-for-video-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video text spotting refers to localizing, recognizing, and tracking textual elements such as captions, logos, license plates, signs, and other forms of text within consecutive video frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-mask-annotation-for-video-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Visual Prompt Generator across LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-visual-prompt-generator-across-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While developing a new vision-language LLM (VL-LLM) by pre-training on tremendous image-text pairs from scratch can be exceedingly resource-consuming, connecting an existing LLM with a comparatively lightweight visual prompt generator (VPG) becomes a feasible paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-visual-prompt-generator-across-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Uni-Modal Feature Learning in Supervised Multi-Modal Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-uni-modal-feature-learning-in-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We abstract the features~(\textit{i. e.} learned representations) of multi-modal data into 1)~\emph{uni-modal features}, which can be learned from uni-modal training, and 2) \emph{paired features}, which can \emph{only} be learned from cross-modal interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-uni-modal-feature-learning-in-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Dataset Distillation via Deep Generative Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-dataset-distillation-via-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dataset Distillation aims to distill an entire dataset's knowledge into a few synthetic images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-dataset-distillation-via-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Neural Self-Improvement via Bootstrapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-neural-self-improvement-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few-shot learning with sequence-processing neural networks (NNs) has recently attracted a new wave of attention in the context of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-neural-self-improvement-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Neurons in a Haystack: Case Studies with Sparse Probing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-neurons-in-a-haystack-case-studies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite rapid adoption and deployment of large language models (LLMs), the internal computations of these models remain opaque and poorly understood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-neurons-in-a-haystack-case-studies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Machine Learning for Science with PySR and SymbolicRegression.jl</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-machine-learning-for-science</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PySR was developed to democratize and popularize symbolic regression for the sciences, and is built on a high-performance distributed back-end, a flexible search algorithm, and interfaces with several deep learning packages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-machine-learning-for-science</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Neural Databases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-neural-databases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise in loosely-structured data available through text, images, and other modalities has called for new ways of querying them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-neural-databases</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stratified Adversarial Robustness with Rejection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stratified-adversarial-robustness-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We theoretically analyze the stratified rejection setting and propose a novel defense method -- Adversarial Training with Consistent Prediction-based Rejection (CPR) -- for building a robust selective classifier.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stratified-adversarial-robustness-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geometric Latent Diffusion Models for 3D Molecule Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-latent-diffusion-models-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative models, especially diffusion models (DMs), have achieved promising results for generating feature-rich geometries and advancing foundational science problems such as molecule design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-latent-diffusion-models-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Generalization Ability of Deep Learning Algorithms: A Kernelized Renyi's Entropy Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-generalization-ability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the current generalization error bounds within this framework are still far from optimal, while substantial improvements on these bounds are quite challenging due to the intractability of high-dimensional information quantities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-generalization-ability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of Bad Advice: Autocontrastive Decoding across Model Layers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-benefits-of-bad-advice-autocontrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applying language models to natural language processing tasks typically relies on the representations in the final model layer, as intermediate hidden layer representations are presumed to be less informative.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-benefits-of-bad-advice-autocontrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PGrad: Learning Principal Gradients For Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgrad-learning-principal-gradients-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop a novel DG training strategy, we call PGrad, to learn a robust gradient direction, improving models' generalization ability on unseen domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgrad-learning-principal-gradients-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pick-a-Pic: An Open Dataset of User Preferences for Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pick-a-pic-an-open-dataset-of-user</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using this web app we build Pick-a-Pic, a large, open dataset of text-to-image prompts and real users' preferences over generated images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pick-a-pic-an-open-dataset-of-user</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-ended search for environments and adapted agents using MAP-Elites</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-ended-search-for-environments-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We want to move one step closer to creating simulated environments similar to the diverse real world, where agents can both find solvable tasks, and adapt to them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-ended-search-for-environments-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Tailed Recognition by Mutual Information Maximization between Latent Features and Ground-Truth Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-recognition-by-mutual-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although contrastive learning methods have shown prevailing performance on a variety of representation learning tasks, they encounter difficulty when the training dataset is long-tailed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-recognition-by-mutual-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil Spill Segmentation using Deep Encoder-Decoder models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oil-spill-segmentation-using-deep-encoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even though oil spills are in and themselves difficult to clean up, the first and foremost challenge is to detect spills.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oil-spill-segmentation-using-deep-encoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory of recurrent networks: Do we compute it right?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-of-recurrent-networks-do-we-compute-it</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerical evaluations of the memory capacity (MC) of recurrent neural networks reported in the literature often contradict well-established theoretical bounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-of-recurrent-networks-do-we-compute-it</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RT-K-Net: Revisiting K-Net for Real-Time Panoptic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rt-k-net-revisiting-k-net-for-real-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our resulting RT-K-Net sets a new state-of-the-art performance for real-time panoptic segmentation methods on the Cityscapes dataset and shows promising results on the challenging Mapillary Vistas dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rt-k-net-revisiting-k-net-for-real-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt as Triggers for Backdoor Attack: Examining the Vulnerability in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-as-triggers-for-backdoor-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method does not require external triggers and ensures correct labeling of poisoned samples, improving the stealthy nature of the backdoor attack.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-as-triggers-for-backdoor-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing Parameter Choice Issues in Unsupervised Domain Adaptation by Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-parameter-choice-issues-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method outperforms deep embedded validation (DEV) and importance weighted validation (IWV) on all datasets, setting a new state-of-the-art performance for solving parameter choice issues in unsupervised domain adaptation with theoretical error guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-parameter-choice-issues-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster OreFSDet : A Lightweight and Effective Few-shot Object Detector for Ore Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-orefsdet-a-lightweight-and-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the ore particle size detection, obtaining a sizable amount of high-quality ore labeled data is time-consuming and expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-orefsdet-a-lightweight-and-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiLegalSBD: A Multilingual Legal Sentence Boundary Detection Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilegalsbd-a-multilingual-legal-sentence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sentence Boundary Detection (SBD) is one of the foundational building blocks of Natural Language Processing (NLP), with incorrectly split sentences heavily influencing the output quality of downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilegalsbd-a-multilingual-legal-sentence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlimiformer: Long-Range Transformers with Unlimited Length Input</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlimiformer-long-range-transformers-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This way, we can index extremely long input sequences, while every attention head in every decoder layer retrieves its top-$k$ keys, instead of attending to every key.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlimiformer-long-range-transformers-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Summarizing Multiple Documents with Hierarchical Relationships</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-summarizing-multiple-documents-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing multi-document summarization (MDS) datasets lack human-generated and genuine (i. e., not synthetic) summaries or source documents with explicit inter-document relationships that a summary must capture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-summarizing-multiple-documents-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARBEx: Attentive Feature Extraction with Reliability Balancing for Robust Facial Expression Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbex-attentive-feature-extraction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also employ learnable anchor points in the embedding space with label distributions and multi-head self-attention mechanism to optimize performance against weak predictions with reliability balancing, which is a strategy that leverages anchor points, attention scores, and confidence values to enhance the resilience of label predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbex-attentive-feature-extraction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sample Efficient Model-free Reinforcement Learning from LTL Specifications with Optimality Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-efficient-model-free-reinforcement-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Linear Temporal Logic (LTL) is widely used to specify high-level objectives for system policies, and it is highly desirable for autonomous systems to learn the optimal policy with respect to such specifications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-efficient-model-free-reinforcement-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stress and heat flux via automatic differentiation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stress-and-heat-flux-via-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine-learning potentials provide computationally efficient and accurate approximations of the Born-Oppenheimer potential energy surface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stress-and-heat-flux-via-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Guided Traversal for Fast Learned Sparse Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-guided-traversal-for-fast-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies show that BM25-driven dynamic index skipping can greatly accelerate MaxScore-based document retrieval based on the learned sparse representation derived by DeepImpact.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-guided-traversal-for-fast-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huatuo-26M, a Large-scale Chinese Medical QA Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/huatuo-26m-a-large-scale-chinese-medical-qa</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we also experimentally show the benefit of the proposed dataset in many aspects: (i) trained models for other QA datasets in a zero-shot fashion; and (ii) as external knowledge for retrieval-augmented generation (RAG); and (iii) improving existing pre-trained language models by using the QA pairs as a pre-training corpus in continued training manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/huatuo-26m-a-large-scale-chinese-medical-qa</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SelfDocSeg: A Self-Supervised vision-based Approach towards Document Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selfdocseg-a-self-supervised-vision-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Document layout analysis is a known problem to the documents research community and has been vastly explored yielding a multitude of solutions ranging from text mining, and recognition to graph-based representation, visual feature extraction, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selfdocseg-a-self-supervised-vision-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Context Learning Unlocked for Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-learning-unlocked-for-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this, we propose a vision-language prompt that can model a wide range of vision-language tasks and a diffusion model that takes it as input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-learning-unlocked-for-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaskPrompter: Spatial-Channel Multi-Task Prompting for Dense Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskprompter-spatial-channel-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Each task prompt learns task-specific representation for one task, while all the prompts can jointly contribute to the learning of the shared image token representations, and the interactions between different task prompts model the cross-task relationship.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskprompter-spatial-channel-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Controllable Adaptive Simulation for Multi-resolution Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-controllable-adaptive-simulation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Learning controllable Adaptive simulation for Multi-resolution Physics (LAMP) as the first full deep learning-based surrogate model that jointly learns the evolution model and optimizes appropriate spatial resolutions that devote more compute to the highly dynamic regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-controllable-adaptive-simulation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZeroSearch: Local Image Search from Text with Zero Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zerosearch-local-image-search-from-text-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The algorithm's output is a list of images sorted in descending order of similarity, helping users to locate specific images more efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zerosearch-local-image-search-from-text-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Language Representation for Material Recommendation, Ranking, and Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-language-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data-driven approaches for material discovery and design have been accelerated by emerging efforts in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-language-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Institutional Transfer Learning for Educational Models: Implications for Model Performance, Fairness, and Equity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-institutional-transfer-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also find that stacked ensembling provides no additional benefits to overall performance or fairness compared to either a local model or the zero-shot transfer procedure we tested.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-institutional-transfer-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCA: Taming Long-tailed Federated Medical Image Classification by Classifier Anchoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fca-taming-long-tailed-federated-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this, we propose federated classifier anchoring (FCA) by adding a personalized classifier at each client to guide and debias the federated model through consistency learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fca-taming-long-tailed-federated-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full Scaling Automation for Sustainable Development of Green Data Centers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/full-scaling-automation-for-sustainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid rise in cloud computing has resulted in an alarming increase in data centers' carbon emissions, which now accounts for >3% of global greenhouse gas emissions, necessitating immediate steps to combat their mounting strain on the global climate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/full-scaling-automation-for-sustainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthening structural baselines for graph classification using Local Topological Profile</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strengthening-structural-baselines-for-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the analysis of the topological graph descriptor Local Degree Profile (LDP), which forms a widely used structural baseline for graph classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strengthening-structural-baselines-for-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SafeWebUH at SemEval-2023 Task 11: Learning Annotator Disagreement in Derogatory Text: Comparison of Direct Training vs Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safewebuh-at-semeval-2023-task-11-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subjectivity and difference of opinion are key social phenomena, and it is crucial to take these into account in the annotation and detection process of derogatory textual content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safewebuh-at-semeval-2023-task-11-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decomposition Enhances Reasoning via Self-Evaluation Guided Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decomposition-enhances-reasoning-via-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the self-evaluation guided stochastic beam search, we also balance the quality-diversity trade-off in the generation of reasoning chains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decomposition-enhances-reasoning-via-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part Aware Contrastive Learning for Self-Supervised Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/part-aware-contrastive-learning-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes an attention-based contrastive learning framework for skeleton representation learning, called SkeAttnCLR, which integrates local similarity and global features for skeleton-based action representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/part-aware-contrastive-learning-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISAAC Newton: Input-based Approximate Curvature for Newton's Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isaac-newton-input-based-approximate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present ISAAC (Input-baSed ApproximAte Curvature), a novel method that conditions the gradient using selected second-order information and has an asymptotically vanishing computational overhead, assuming a batch size smaller than the number of neurons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isaac-newton-input-based-approximate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poisoning Language Models During Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poisoning-language-models-during-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show that adversaries can contribute poison examples to these datasets, allowing them to manipulate model predictions whenever a desired trigger phrase appears in the input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poisoning-language-models-during-instruction</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
