<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 09:10:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Incremental Constrained Clustering by Minimal Weighted Modification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incremental-constrained-clustering-by-minimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clustering is a well-known task in Data Mining that aims at grouping data instances according to their similarity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incremental-constrained-clustering-by-minimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving In-Context Learning with Differentially Private Few-Shot Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-in-context-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results demonstrate that our algorithm can achieve competitive performance with strong privacy levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-in-context-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A class-weighted supervised contrastive learning long-tailed bearing fault diagnosis approach using quadratic neural network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-class-weighted-supervised-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a supervised contrastive learning approach with a class-aware loss function to enhance the feature extraction capability of neural networks for fault diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-class-weighted-supervised-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMac: Temporal Multi-Modal Graph Learning for Acoustic Event Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tmac-temporal-multi-modal-graph-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that these audiovisual data naturally have temporal attributes, such as the time information for each frame in the video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tmac-temporal-multi-modal-graph-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemEval-2022 Task 7: Identifying Plausible Clarifications of Implicit and Underspecified Phrases in Instructional Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semeval-2022-task-7-identifying-plausible-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe SemEval-2022 Task 7, a shared task on rating the plausibility of clarifications in instructional texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semeval-2022-task-7-identifying-plausible-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Phylogenetics via Hyperbolic Embeddings with Dodonaphy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-phylogenetics-via-hyperbolic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present soft-NJ, a differentiable version of neighbour-joining that enables gradient-based optimisation over the space of trees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-phylogenetics-via-hyperbolic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dictionary Attack on IMU-based Gait Authentication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dictionary-attack-on-imu-based-gait</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel adversarial model for authentication systems that use gait patterns recorded by the inertial measurement unit (IMU) built into smartphones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dictionary-attack-on-imu-based-gait</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolution and Attention Mixer for Synthetic Aperture Radar Image Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolution-and-attention-mixer-for-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this letter, we explore Transformer-like architecture for SAR change detection to incorporate global attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolution-and-attention-mixer-for-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FGFusion: Fine-Grained Lidar-Camera Fusion for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fgfusion-fine-grained-lidar-camera-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Fine-Grained Lidar-Camera Fusion (FGFusion) that make full use of multi-scale features of image and point cloud and fuse them in a fine-grained way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fgfusion-fine-grained-lidar-camera-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotion-Aware Prosodic Phrasing for Expressive Text-to-Speech</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotion-aware-prosodic-phrasing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prosodic phrasing is crucial to the naturalness and intelligibility of end-to-end Text-to-Speech (TTS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotion-aware-prosodic-phrasing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly-supervised Automated Audio Captioning via text only training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-automated-audio-captioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach leverages the similarity between audio and text embeddings in CLAP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-automated-audio-captioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>t-EER: Parameter-Free Tandem Evaluation of Countermeasures and Biometric Comparators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-eer-parameter-free-tandem-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed approach is a strong candidate metric for the tandem evaluation of PAD systems and biometric comparators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-eer-parameter-free-tandem-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ContextRef: Evaluating Referenceless Metrics For Image Description Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextref-evaluating-referenceless-metrics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[None of the methods is successful with ContextRef, but we show that careful fine-tuning yields substantial improvements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextref-evaluating-referenceless-metrics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongLoRA: Efficient Fine-tuning of Long-Context Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longlora-efficient-fine-tuning-of-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LongLoRA adopts LLaMA2 7B from 4k context to 100k, or LLaMA2 70B to 32k on a single 8x A100 machine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longlora-efficient-fine-tuning-of-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Soliloquies for Accurate Calculations in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/code-soliloquies-for-accurate-calculations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach notably enhances the quality of synthetic conversation datasets, especially for subjects that are calculation-intensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/code-soliloquies-for-accurate-calculations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smooth ECE: Principled Reliability Diagrams via Kernel Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smooth-ece-principled-reliability-diagrams</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that a simple modification fixes both constructions: first smooth the observations using an RBF kernel, then compute the Expected Calibration Error (ECE) of this smoothed function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smooth-ece-principled-reliability-diagrams</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uplift vs. predictive modeling: a theoretical analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uplift-vs-predictive-modeling-a-theoretical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the growing popularity of machine-learning techniques in decision-making, the added value of causal-oriented strategies with respect to pure machine-learning approaches has rarely been quantified in the literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uplift-vs-predictive-modeling-a-theoretical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Hierarchical Structures for Improved Time Series Classification Using Stochastic Splitting Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-hierarchical-structures-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study introduces a novel hierarchical divisive clustering approach with stochastic splitting functions (SSFs) to enhance classification performance in multi-class datasets through hierarchical classification (HC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-hierarchical-structures-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Stereo Without Pattern Projector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-stereo-without-pattern-projector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel framework integrating the principles of active stereo in standard passive camera systems without a physical pattern projector.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-stereo-without-pattern-projector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Hidden Realm: Self-supervised Skeleton-based Action Recognition in Occluded Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-hidden-realm-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To integrate action recognition methods into autonomous robotic systems, it is crucial to consider adverse situations involving target occlusions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-hidden-realm-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-OCTA: A Fine-Tuning Strategy for Applying Foundation Model to OCTA Image Segmentation Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-octa-a-fine-tuning-strategy-for-applying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the analysis of optical coherence tomography angiography (OCTA) images, the operation of segmenting specific targets is necessary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-octa-a-fine-tuning-strategy-for-applying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Robust is Google's Bard to Adversarial Image Attacks?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-robust-is-google-s-bard-to-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By attacking white-box surrogate vision encoders or MLLMs, the generated adversarial examples can mislead Bard to output wrong image descriptions with a 22% success rate based solely on the transferability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-robust-is-google-s-bard-to-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Endoscopic Ultrasound Station Recognition with Limited Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-endoscopic-ultrasound-station</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pancreatic cancer is a lethal form of cancer that significantly contributes to cancer-related deaths worldwide.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-endoscopic-ultrasound-station</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEFLUT: Unsupervised 1D Lookup Tables for Multi-exposure Image Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meflut-unsupervised-1d-lookup-tables-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a new approach for high-quality multi-exposure image fusion (MEF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meflut-unsupervised-1d-lookup-tables-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad Actor, Good Advisor: Exploring the Role of Large Language Models in Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bad-actor-good-advisor-exploring-the-role-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To instantiate this proposal, we design an adaptive rationale guidance network for fake news detection (ARG), in which SLMs selectively acquire insights on news analysis from the LLMs' rationales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bad-actor-good-advisor-exploring-the-role-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FluentEditor: Text-based Speech Editing by Considering Acoustic and Prosody Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fluenteditor-text-based-speech-editing-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-based speech editing (TSE) techniques are designed to enable users to edit the output audio by modifying the input text transcript instead of the audio itself.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fluenteditor-text-based-speech-editing-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activation Compression of Graph Neural Networks using Block-wise Quantization with Improved Variance Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activation-compression-of-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, we present a correction to the assumptions on the distribution of intermediate activation maps in EXACT (assumed to be uniform) and show improved variance estimations of the quantization and dequantization steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activation-compression-of-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Transformers for Wireless Communications: A Case Study in Beam Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-transformers-for-wireless</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wireless communications at high-frequency bands with large antenna arrays face challenges in beam management, which can potentially be improved by multimodality sensing information from cameras, LiDAR, radar, and GPS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-transformers-for-wireless</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Image Borders: Learning Feature Extrapolation for Unbounded Image Composition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-image-borders-learning-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we circumvent this issue by presenting a joint framework for both unbounded recommendation of camera view and image composition (i. e., UNIC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-image-borders-learning-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Vision-Centric Approach for Static Map Element Annotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-vision-centric-approach-for-static-map</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent development of online static map element (a. k. a.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-vision-centric-approach-for-static-map</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoPET Challenge 2023: Sliding Window-based Optimization of U-Net</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopet-challenge-2023-sliding-window-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tumor segmentation in medical imaging is crucial and relies on precise delineation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopet-challenge-2023-sliding-window-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic stiffness identification and response estimation of Timoshenko beams via physics-informed Gaussian processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-stiffness-identification-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed approach has potential applications in the field of structural health monitoring (SHM) for both mechanical and structural systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-stiffness-identification-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focal Inferential Infusion Coupled with Tractable Density Discrimination for Implicit Hate Speech Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focal-inferential-infusion-coupled-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although pre-trained large language models (PLMs) have achieved state-of-the-art on many NLP tasks, they lack understanding of subtle expressions of implicit hate speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focal-inferential-infusion-coupled-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Reversal Curse: LLMs trained on "A is B" fail to learn "B is A"</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-reversal-curse-llms-trained-on-a-is-b</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This shows a failure of logical deduction that we hypothesize is caused by the Reversal Curse.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-reversal-curse-llms-trained-on-a-is-b</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TCOVIS: Temporally Consistent Online Video Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tcovis-temporally-consistent-online-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core of our method consists of a global instance assignment strategy and a spatio-temporal enhancement module, which improve the temporal consistency of the features from two aspects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tcovis-temporally-consistent-online-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AceGPT, Localizing Large Language Models in Arabic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acegpt-localizing-large-language-models-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the imperative need and methodology for developing a localized Large Language Model (LLM) tailored for Arabic, a language with unique cultural characteristics that are not adequately addressed by current mainstream models like ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acegpt-localizing-large-language-models-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructERC: Reforming Emotion Recognition in Conversation with a Retrieval Multi-task LLMs Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructerc-reforming-emotion-recognition-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of emotion recognition in dialogue (ERC) has been consistently hindered by the complexity of pipeline designs, leading to ERC models that often overfit to specific datasets and dialogue patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructerc-reforming-emotion-recognition-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALSA-CLRS: A Sparse and Scalable Benchmark for Algorithmic Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salsa-clrs-a-sparse-and-scalable-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an extension to the CLRS algorithmic learning benchmark, prioritizing scalability and the utilization of sparse representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salsa-clrs-a-sparse-and-scalable-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boolformer: Symbolic Regression of Logic Functions with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boolformer-symbolic-regression-of-logic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Boolformer, the first Transformer architecture trained to perform end-to-end symbolic regression of Boolean functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boolformer-symbolic-regression-of-logic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphEcho: Graph-Driven Unsupervised Domain Adaptation for Echocardiogram Video Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphecho-graph-driven-unsupervised-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the unsupervised domain adaption (UDA) for echocardiogram video segmentation, where the goal is to generalize the model trained on the source domain to other unlabelled target domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphecho-graph-driven-unsupervised-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limitations in odour recognition and generalisation in a neuromorphic olfactory circuit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/limitations-in-odour-recognition-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neuromorphic computing is one of the few current approaches that have the potential to significantly reduce power consumption in Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/limitations-in-odour-recognition-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenChat: Advancing Open-source Language Models with Mixed-Quality Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openchat-advancing-open-source-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we consider the general SFT training data, consisting of a small amount of expert data mixed with a large proportion of sub-optimal data, without any preference labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openchat-advancing-open-source-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Joint Modeling of Dialogue Response and Speech Synthesis based on Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-joint-modeling-of-dialogue-response</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the potential of constructing an AI spoken dialogue system that "thinks how to respond" and "thinks how to speak" simultaneously, which more closely aligns with the human speech production process compared to the current cascade pipeline of independent chatbot and Text-to-Speech (TTS) modules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-joint-modeling-of-dialogue-response</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoT-BERT: Enhancing Unsupervised Sentence Representation through Chain-of-Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cot-bert-enhancing-unsupervised-sentence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For further performance enhancement, we meticulously refine both the contrastive learning loss function and the template denoising technique for prompt engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cot-bert-enhancing-unsupervised-sentence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using deep learning to construct stochastic local search SAT solvers with performance bounds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-deep-learning-to-construct-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Boolean Satisfiability problem (SAT) is the most prototypical NP-complete problem and of great practical relevance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-deep-learning-to-construct-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical Probabilistic Model-based Deep Reinforcement Learning by Integrating Dropout Uncertainty and Trajectory Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-probabilistic-model-based-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Its loss function is designed to correct the fitting error of neural networks for more accurate prediction of probabilistic models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-probabilistic-model-based-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partition-A-Medical-Image: Extracting Multiple Representative Sub-regions for Few-shot Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partition-a-medical-image-extracting-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present an approach to extract multiple representative sub-regions from a given support medical image, enabling fine-grained selection over the generated image regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partition-a-medical-image-extracting-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-tail Augmented Graph Contrastive Learning for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tail-augmented-graph-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To make the data augmentation schema learnable, we design an auto drop module to generate pseudo-tail nodes from head nodes and a knowledge transfer module to reconstruct the head nodes from pseudo-tail nodes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tail-augmented-graph-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Article Classification with Edge-Heterogeneous Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-article-classification-with-edge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On PubMed, we closely trail SOTA GNN architectures using a 2-layer GraphSAGE by including additional co-authorship edges in the graph (accuracy 89. 88%).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-article-classification-with-edge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-free tracking control of complex dynamical trajectories with machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-free-tracking-control-of-complex-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a model-free, machine-learning framework to control a two-arm robotic manipulator using only partially observed states, where the controller is realized by reservoir computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-free-tracking-control-of-complex-1</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
