<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 21:09:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CDChat: A Large Multimodal Model for Remote Sensing Change Description</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdchat-a-large-multimodal-model-for-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to achieve this, we introduce a change description instruction dataset that can be utilized to finetune an LMM and provide better change descriptions for RS images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdchat-a-large-multimodal-model-for-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Context Ensemble Improves Video-Language Models for Low-Level Workflow Understanding from Human Demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-ensemble-improves-video-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore in-context learning with video-language models for SOP generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-ensemble-improves-video-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iGAiVA: Integrated Generative AI and Visual Analytics in a Machine Learning Workflow for Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/igaiva-integrated-generative-ai-and-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In developing machine learning (ML) models for text classification, one common challenge is that the collected data is often not ideally distributed, especially when new classes are introduced in response to changes of data and tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/igaiva-integrated-generative-ai-and-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LTNtorch: PyTorch Implementation of Logic Tensor Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ltntorch-pytorch-implementation-of-logic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This makes learning by logical reasoning possible as the parameters of the model are optimized by minimizing a loss function composed of a set of logical formulas expressing facts about the learning task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ltntorch-pytorch-implementation-of-logic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HelloBench: Evaluating Long Text Generation Capabilities of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hellobench-evaluating-long-text-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we introduce the Hierarchical Long Text Generation Benchmark (HelloBench), a comprehensive, in-the-wild, and open-ended benchmark to evaluate LLMs' performance in generating long text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hellobench-evaluating-long-text-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aided design of bridge aesthetics based on Stable Diffusion fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aided-design-of-bridge-aesthetics-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stable Diffusion fine-tuning technique is tried to assist bridge-type innovation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aided-design-of-bridge-aesthetics-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EnIGMA: Enhanced Interactive Generative Model Agent for CTF Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enigma-enhanced-interactive-generative-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although language model (LM) agents are demonstrating growing potential in many domains, their success in cybersecurity has been limited due to simplistic design and the lack of fundamental features for this domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enigma-enhanced-interactive-generative-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DataGpt-SQL-7B: An Open-Source Language Model for Text-to-SQL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/datagpt-sql-7b-an-open-source-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addressing the pivotal role of translating natural language queries into SQL commands, we propose a suite of compact, fine-tuned models and self-refine mechanisms to democratize data access and analysis for non-expert users, mitigating risks associated with closed-source Large Language Models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/datagpt-sql-7b-an-open-source-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stage-Wise Reward Shaping for Acrobatic Robots: A Constrained Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stage-wise-reward-shaping-for-acrobatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the complexity of tasks addressed through reinforcement learning (RL) increases, the definition of reward functions also has become highly complicated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stage-wise-reward-shaping-for-acrobatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Evaluation Benchmarks for NLP Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-evaluation-benchmarks-for-nlp-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a privacy attack and defense evaluation benchmark in the field of NLP, which includes the conventional/small models and large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-evaluation-benchmarks-for-nlp-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Shape Completion via Involution and Implicit Correspondences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-shape-completion-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D shape completion is traditionally solved using supervised training or by distribution learning on complete shape examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-shape-completion-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XTRUST: On the Multilingual Trustworthiness of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xtrust-on-the-multilingual-trustworthiness-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable capabilities across a range of natural language processing (NLP) tasks, capturing the attention of both practitioners and the broader public.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xtrust-on-the-multilingual-trustworthiness-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Robotics Dataset and Benchmark for Continual Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiny-robotics-dataset-and-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a novel benchmark to evaluate the continual learning capabilities of object detection systems in tiny robotic platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiny-robotics-dataset-and-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Zero-Shot Open-Vocabulary Pipeline for Dialogue Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-zero-shot-open-vocabulary-pipeline-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dialogue State Tracking (DST) is crucial for understanding user needs and executing appro- priate system actions in task-oriented dialogues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-zero-shot-open-vocabulary-pipeline-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHBench: A Chinese Dataset for Evaluating Health in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chbench-a-chinese-dataset-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid development of large language models (LLMs), assessing their performance on health-related inquiries has become increasingly essential.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chbench-a-chinese-dataset-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ManiNeg: Manifestation-guided Multimodal Pretraining for Mammography Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manineg-manifestation-guided-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Breast cancer is a significant threat to human health.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manineg-manifestation-guided-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Robustness of Endoscopic Depth Estimation with Synthetically Corrupted Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-robustness-of-endoscopic-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this issue, our study presents a benchmark for assessing the robustness of endoscopic depth estimation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-robustness-of-endoscopic-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Hint Generation Approaches in Open-Domain Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-hint-generation-approaches-in-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that hints enhance the accuracy of answers more than retrieved and generated contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-hint-generation-approaches-in-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ComiCap: A VLMs pipeline for dense captioning of Comic Panels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comicap-a-vlms-pipeline-for-dense-captioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The comic domain is rapidly advancing with the development of single- and multi-page analysis and synthesis models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comicap-a-vlms-pipeline-for-dense-captioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ducho meets Elliot: Large-scale Benchmarks for Multimodal Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ducho-meets-elliot-large-scale-benchmarks-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In specific domains like fashion, music, and movie recommendation, the multi-faceted features characterizing products and services may influence each customer on online selling platforms differently, paving the way to novel multimodal recommendation models that can learn from such multimodal content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ducho-meets-elliot-large-scale-benchmarks-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-CamObj: A Comprehensive Multimodal Dataset for Camouflaged Object Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-camobj-a-comprehensive-multimodal-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CamObj-Instruct is collected for fine-tuning the LVLMs with improved instruction-following capabilities, and it includes 11, 363 images and 68, 849 conversations with diverse instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-camobj-a-comprehensive-multimodal-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning for Precision Agriculture: Post-Spraying Evaluation and Deposition Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-precision-agriculture-post</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the pipeline, inference-only feature fusion is used to allow for further interpretability and to enable the automation of precision spraying evaluation post-spray.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-precision-agriculture-post</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViKL: A Mammography Interpretation Framework via Multimodal Aggregation of Visual-knowledge-linguistic Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vikl-a-mammography-interpretation-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this dataset, we focus on the challanging task of unsupervised pretraining and propose ViKL, a innovative framework that synergizes Visual, Knowledge, and Linguistic features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vikl-a-mammography-interpretation-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSFeatLIME: An Online User Study in Enhancing Explainability in Univariate Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsfeatlime-an-online-user-study-in-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series forecasting, while vital in various applications, often employs complex models that are difficult for humans to understand.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsfeatlime-an-online-user-study-in-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAD: Memory Efficient Convolutional Adapter for Segment Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cad-memory-efficient-convolutional-adapter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This architecture connects in parallel with SAM's image encoder, eliminating the need to store activations and gradients of the image encoder during model training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cad-memory-efficient-convolutional-adapter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDT: Uav Target Detection Dataset for Pests and Diseases Tree</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdt-uav-target-detection-dataset-for-pests</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We re-evaluate the state-of-the-art detection models with our proposed PDT dataset and CWC dataset, showing the completeness of the dataset and the effectiveness of the YOLO-DP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdt-uav-target-detection-dataset-for-pests</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Semantic Leakage in Cross-lingual Embeddings via Orthogonality Constraint</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-semantic-leakage-in-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurately aligning contextual representations in cross-lingual sentence embeddings is key for effective parallel data mining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-semantic-leakage-in-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM Echo Chamber: personalized and automated disinformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-echo-chamber-personalized-and-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements have showcased the capabilities of Large Language Models like GPT4 and Llama2 in tasks such as summarization, translation, and content review.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-echo-chamber-personalized-and-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing the Potential of Synthetic Images: A Study on Histopathology Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-potential-of-synthetic-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Histopathology image classification is crucial for the accurate identification and diagnosis of various diseases but requires large and diverse datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-potential-of-synthetic-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Confidence: Training Better Classifiers from Soft Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-confidence-training-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we evaluate the methods on a real-world dataset with confidence scores, where the SLL methods are shown to match the traditional methods for predicting the (noisy) hard labels while providing more accurate confidence estimates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-confidence-training-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOSS: Enabling Code-Driven Evolution and Context Management for AI Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moss-enabling-code-driven-evolution-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSS ensures consistency and adaptability by using a mechanism that maintains the Python context across interactions, including isolation of local variables and preservation of runtime integrity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moss-enabling-code-driven-evolution-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating Healthy Friction: Determining Stakeholder Requirements of Job Recommendation Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creating-healthy-friction-determining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fulfill this requirement, the stakeholders' exact preferences and needs need to be determined.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creating-healthy-friction-determining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DepMamba: Progressive Fusion Mamba for Multimodal Depression Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depmamba-progressive-fusion-mamba-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although promising, current multimodal methods hinge on aligned or aggregated multimodal fusion, suffering two significant limitations: (i) inefficient long-range temporal modeling, and (ii) sub-optimal multimodal fusion between intermodal fusion and intramodal processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depmamba-progressive-fusion-mamba-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleSinger 2: Zero-Shot Singing Voice Synthesis with Style Transfer and Multi-Level Style Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylesinger-2-zero-shot-singing-voice</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we introduce StyleSinger 2, the first zero-shot SVS model for style transfer across cross-lingual speech and singing styles, along with multi-level style control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylesinger-2-zero-shot-singing-voice</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoPatchCore: An Effective Method to Memorize Normality for Video Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videopatchcore-an-effective-method-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by PatchCore, our approach introduces a structure that prioritizes memory optimization and configures three types of memory tailored to the characteristics of video data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videopatchcore-an-effective-method-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep chroma compression of tone-mapped images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-chroma-compression-of-tone-mapped-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Acquisition of high dynamic range (HDR) images is thriving due to the increasing use of smart devices and the demand for high-quality output.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-chroma-compression-of-tone-mapped-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-based Audio Moment Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-based-audio-moment-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we provide manually annotated datasets to properly measure the effectiveness and robustness of our methods on real data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-based-audio-moment-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Text Embedders Few-Shot Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-text-embedders-few-shot-learners</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce a novel model bge-en-icl, which employs few-shot examples to produce high-quality text embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-text-embedders-few-shot-learners</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Any-Point Tracking by Contrastive Random Walks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-any-point-tracking-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a simple, self-supervised approach to the Tracking Any Point (TAP) problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-any-point-tracking-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CJEval: A Benchmark for Assessing Large Language Models Using Chinese Junior High School Exam Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cjeval-a-benchmark-for-assessing-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online education platforms have significantly transformed the dissemination of educational resources by providing a dynamic and digital infrastructure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cjeval-a-benchmark-for-assessing-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLIMER-IT: Zero-Shot NER on Italian Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slimer-it-zero-shot-ner-on-italian-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional approaches to Named Entity Recognition (NER) frame the task into a BIO sequence labeling problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slimer-it-zero-shot-ner-on-italian-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Konstruktor: A Strong Baseline for Simple Knowledge Graph Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/konstruktor-a-strong-baseline-for-simple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While being one of the most popular question types, simple questions such as "Who is the author of Cinderella?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/konstruktor-a-strong-baseline-for-simple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time-MoE: Billion-Scale Time Series Foundation Models with Mixture of Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-moe-billion-scale-time-series-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, despite the success of large-scale pre-training in language and vision domains, pre-trained time series models remain limited in scale and operate at a high cost, hindering the development of larger capable forecasting models in real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-moe-billion-scale-time-series-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the calibration of powerset speaker diarization models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-calibration-of-powerset-speaker</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to study the calibration of a powerset speaker diarization model, and explore some of its uses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-calibration-of-powerset-speaker</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ducho meets Elliot: Large-scale Benchmarks for Multimodal Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ducho-meets-elliot-large-scale-benchmarks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In specific domains like fashion, music, and movie recommendation, the multi-faceted features characterizing products and services may influence each customer on online selling platforms differently, paving the way to novel multimodal recommendation models that can learn from such multimodal content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ducho-meets-elliot-large-scale-benchmarks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOFI: Multi-Scale Deformable Transformer for Camera Calibration with Enhanced Line Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sofi-multi-scale-deformable-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Camera calibration consists of estimating camera parameters such as the zenith vanishing point and horizon line.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sofi-multi-scale-deformable-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RMCBench: Benchmarking Large Language Models' Resistance to Malicious Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmcbench-benchmarking-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their benefits, LLMs also pose notable risks, including the potential to generate harmful content and being abused by malicious developers to create malicious code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmcbench-benchmarking-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FineCops-Ref: A new Dataset and Task for Fine-Grained Compositional Referring Expression Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finecops-ref-a-new-dataset-and-task-for-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Referring Expression Comprehension (REC) is a crucial cross-modal task that objectively evaluates the capabilities of language understanding, image comprehension, and language-to-image grounding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finecops-ref-a-new-dataset-and-task-for-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matérn Kernels for Tunable Implicit Surface Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matern-kernels-for-tunable-implicit-surface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose to use the family of Mat\'ern kernels for tunable implicit surface reconstruction, building upon the recent success of kernel methods for 3D reconstruction of oriented point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matern-kernels-for-tunable-implicit-surface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autonomous Exploration and Semantic Updating of Large-Scale Indoor Environments with Mobile Robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autonomous-exploration-and-semantic-updating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new robotic system that enables a mobile robot to autonomously explore an unknown environment, build a semantic map of the environment, and subsequently update the semantic map to reflect environment changes, such as location changes of objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autonomous-exploration-and-semantic-updating</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
