<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 09:15:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Detection of Unobserved Common Causes based on NML Code in Discrete, Mixed, and Continuous Variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-of-unobserved-common-causes-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal discovery in the presence of unobserved common causes from observational data only is a crucial but challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-of-unobserved-common-causes-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Online Exploration via Coverability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-online-exploration-via-coverability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose exploration objectives -- policy optimization objectives that enable downstream maximization of any reward function -- as a conceptual framework to systematize the study of exploration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-online-exploration-via-coverability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Generalist Anomaly Detection via In-context Residual Learning with Few-shot Sample Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-generalist-anomaly-detection-via-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose to train a GAD model with few-shot normal images as sample prompts for AD on diverse datasets on the fly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-generalist-anomaly-detection-via-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Generalizable Remote Physiological Measurement through the Integration of Explicit and Implicit Prior Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-generalizable-remote-physiological</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remote photoplethysmography (rPPG) is a promising technology that captures physiological signals from face videos, with potential applications in medical health, emotional computing, and biosecurity recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-generalizable-remote-physiological</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elephants Never Forget: Testing Language Models for Memorization of Tabular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elephants-never-forget-testing-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While many have shown how Large Language Models (LLMs) can be applied to a diverse set of tasks, the critical issues of data contamination and memorization are often glossed over.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elephants-never-forget-testing-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNGaussian: Optimizing Sparse-View 3D Gaussian Radiance Fields with Global-Local Depth Normalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dngaussian-optimizing-sparse-view-3d-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our motivation stems from the highly efficient representation and surprising quality of the recent 3D Gaussian Splatting, despite it will encounter a geometry degradation when input views decrease.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dngaussian-optimizing-sparse-view-3d-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaceChain-SuDe: Building Derived Class to Inherit Category Attributes for One-shot Subject-Driven Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facechain-sude-building-derived-class-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, motivated by object-oriented programming, we model the subject as a derived class whose base class is its semantic category.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facechain-sude-building-derived-class-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V3D: Video Diffusion Models are Effective 3D Generators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v3d-video-diffusion-models-are-effective-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fully unleash the potential of video diffusion to perceive the 3D world, we further introduce geometrical consistency prior and extend the video diffusion model to a multi-view consistent 3D generator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v3d-video-diffusion-models-are-effective-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can LLMs Separate Instructions From Data? And What Do We Even Mean By That?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llms-separate-instructions-from-data-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instruction-tuned Large Language Models (LLMs) have achieved breakthrough results, opening countless new possibilities for many practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llms-separate-instructions-from-data-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point Mamba: A Novel Point Cloud Backbone Based on State Space Model with Octree-Based Ordering Strategy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-mamba-a-novel-point-cloud-backbone</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel SSM-based point cloud processing backbone, named Point Mamba, with a causality-aware ordering mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-mamba-a-novel-point-cloud-backbone</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MambaMIL: Enhancing Long Sequence Modeling with Sequence Reordering in Computational Pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambamil-enhancing-long-sequence-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiple Instance Learning (MIL) has emerged as a dominant paradigm to extract discriminative feature representations within Whole Slide Images (WSIs) in computational pathology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambamil-enhancing-long-sequence-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PCLD: Point Cloud Layerwise Diffusion for Adversarial Purification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcld-point-cloud-layerwise-diffusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A typical way to assess a model's robustness is through adversarial attacks, where test-time examples are generated based on gradients to deceive the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcld-point-cloud-layerwise-diffusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributionally Generative Augmentation for Fair Facial Attribute Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributionally-generative-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes a novel, generation-based two-stage framework to train a fair FAC model on biased data without additional annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributionally-generative-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RecAI: Leveraging Large Language Models for Next-Generation Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recai-leveraging-large-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces RecAI, a practical toolkit designed to augment or even revolutionize recommender systems with the advanced capabilities of Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recai-leveraging-large-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Text-to-3D-Aware Face Generation and Manipulation via Direct Cross-modal Mapping and Geometric Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-text-to-3d-aware-face-generation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-3D-aware face (T3D Face) generation and manipulation is an emerging research hot spot in machine learning, which still suffers from low efficiency and poor quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-text-to-3d-aware-face-generation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoMamba: State Space Model for Efficient Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videomamba-state-space-model-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing the dual challenges of local redundancy and global dependencies in video understanding, this work innovatively adapts the Mamba to the video domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videomamba-state-space-model-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sliced-Wasserstein Distances and Flows on Cartan-Hadamard Manifolds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliced-wasserstein-distances-and-flows-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On Euclidean spaces, a popular alternative is the Sliced-Wasserstein distance, which leverages a closed-form solution of the Wasserstein distance in one dimension, but which is not readily available on manifolds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliced-wasserstein-distances-and-flows-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Split to Merge: Unifying Separated Modalities for Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/split-to-merge-unifying-separated-modalities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a Unified Modality Separation (UniMoS) framework for unsupervised domain adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/split-to-merge-unifying-separated-modalities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car Damage Detection and Patch-to-Patch Self-supervised Image Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/car-damage-detection-and-patch-to-patch-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most computer vision applications aim to identify pixels in a scene and use them for diverse purposes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/car-damage-detection-and-patch-to-patch-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Generation of Python Programs Using Context-Free Grammars</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-generation-of-python-programs-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, data has emerged as the new gold, serving as a powerful tool for creating intelligent systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-generation-of-python-programs-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Reasoning with Knowledge Graph Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-reasoning-with-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further observe that KGEs adapted with COULDD solidly detect plausible counterfactual changes to the graph that follow these patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-reasoning-with-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERA-CoT: Improving Chain-of-Thought through Entity Relationship Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/era-cot-improving-chain-of-thought-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have achieved commendable accomplishments in various natural language processing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/era-cot-improving-chain-of-thought-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restoring Ancient Ideograph: A Multimodal Multitask Neural Network Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/restoring-ancient-ideograph-a-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cultural heritage serves as the enduring record of human thought and history.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/restoring-ancient-ideograph-a-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SARDet-100K: Towards Open-Source Benchmark and ToolKit for Large-Scale SAR Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sardet-100k-towards-open-source-benchmark-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, SARDet-100K is the first COCO-level large-scale multi-class SAR object detection dataset ever created.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sardet-100k-towards-open-source-benchmark-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConspEmoLLM: Conspiracy Theory Detection Using an Emotion-Based Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conspemollm-conspiracy-theory-detection-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driven by a comprehensive analysis of conspiracy text that reveals its distinctive affective features, we propose ConspEmoLLM, the first open-source LLM that integrates affective information and is able to perform diverse tasks relating to conspiracy theories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conspemollm-conspiracy-theory-detection-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Diminishing Returns of Width for Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-diminishing-returns-of-width-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While deep neural networks have demonstrated groundbreaking performance in various settings, these models often suffer from \emph{catastrophic forgetting} when trained on new tasks in sequence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-diminishing-returns-of-width-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Understandings and Configurations in MaxSAT Local Search Solvers via Anytime Performance Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-understandings-and-configurations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though numerous solvers have been proposed for the MaxSAT problem, and the benchmark environment such as MaxSAT Evaluations provides a platform for the comparison of the state-of-the-art solvers, existing assessments were usually evaluated based on the quality, e. g., fitness, of the best-found solutions obtained within a given running time budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-understandings-and-configurations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DivCon: Divide and Conquer for Progressive Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divcon-divide-and-conquer-for-progressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further improve T2I models' capability in numerical and spatial reasoning, the layout is employed as an intermedium to bridge large language models and layout-based diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divcon-divide-and-conquer-for-progressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Independent Operator: A Training-Free Artifact Representation Extractor for Generalizable Deepfake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-independent-operator-a-training-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to its unbias towards both the training and test sources, we define it as Data-Independent Operator (DIO) to achieve appealing improvements on unseen sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-independent-operator-a-training-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pulling back symmetric Riemannian geometry for data analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pulling-back-symmetric-riemannian-geometry</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The second part then uses these best practices to guide construction of such diffeomorphisms through deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pulling-back-symmetric-riemannian-geometry</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eliminating Warping Shakes for Unsupervised Online Video Stitching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eliminating-warping-shakes-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we retarget video stitching to an emerging issue, named warping shake, when extending image stitching to video stitching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eliminating-warping-shakes-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Study of Perceptual Quality Metrics for Audio-driven Talking Head Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-perceptual-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, performance evaluation research lags behind the development of talking head generation techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-perceptual-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FeatAug: Automatic Feature Augmentation From One-to-Many Relationship Tables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feataug-automatic-feature-augmentation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this limitation, we propose FEATAUG, a new feature augmentation framework that automatically extracts predicate-aware SQL queries from one-to-many relationship tables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feataug-automatic-feature-augmentation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constructing Variables Using Classifiers as an Aid to Regression: An Empirical Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-variables-using-classifiers-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a method for the automatic creation of variables (in the case of regression) that complement the information contained in the initial input vector.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-variables-using-classifiers-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention Prompt Tuning: Parameter-efficient Adaptation of Pre-trained Models for Spatiotemporal Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-prompt-tuning-parameter-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach greatly reduces the number of learnable parameters compared to full tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-prompt-tuning-parameter-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RA-ISF: Learning to Answer and Understand from Retrieval Augmentation via Iterative Self-Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ra-isf-learning-to-answer-and-understand-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) demonstrate exceptional performance in numerous tasks but still heavily rely on knowledge stored in their parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ra-isf-learning-to-answer-and-understand-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalising Multi-Agent Cooperation through Task-Agnostic Communication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalising-multi-agent-cooperation-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our objective is to learn a fixed-size latent Markov state from a variable number of agent observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalising-multi-agent-cooperation-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average Calibration Error: A Differentiable Loss for Improved Reliability in Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/average-calibration-error-a-differentiable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using mL1-ACE, we reduce average and maximum calibration error by 45% and 55% respectively, maintaining a Dice score of 87% on the BraTS 2021 dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/average-calibration-error-a-differentiable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Transformer Prototypes for Medical Diagnoses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-transformer-prototypes-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deployments of artificial intelligence in medical diagnostics mandate not just accuracy and efficacy but also trust, emphasizing the need for explainability in machine decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-transformer-prototypes-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distribution-Aware Data Expansion with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-aware-data-expansion-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose DistDiff, an effective data expansion framework based on the distribution-aware diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-aware-data-expansion-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academically intelligent LLMs are not necessarily socially intelligent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/academically-intelligent-llms-are-not</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The academic intelligence of large language models (LLMs) has made remarkable progress in recent times, but their social intelligence performance remains unclear.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/academically-intelligent-llms-are-not</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EarthLoc: Astronaut Photography Localization by Indexing Earth from Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/earthloc-astronaut-photography-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Astronaut photography, spanning six decades of human spaceflight, presents a unique Earth observations dataset with immense value for both scientific research and disaster response.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/earthloc-astronaut-photography-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart-Infinity: Fast Large Language Model Training using Near-Storage Processing on a Real System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-infinity-fast-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work, Smart-Infinity, addresses the storage bandwidth bottleneck of storage-offloaded LLM training using near-storage processing devices on a real system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-infinity-fast-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOAB: Multi-Modal Outer Arithmetic Block For Fusion Of Histopathological Images And Genetic Data For Brain Tumor Grading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moab-multi-modal-outer-arithmetic-block-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel Multi-modal Outer Arithmetic Block (MOAB) based on arithmetic operations to combine latent representations of the different modalities for predicting the tumor grade (Grade \rom{2}, \rom{3} and \rom{4}).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moab-multi-modal-outer-arithmetic-block-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Semantic Consensus For Deterministic Geometric Model Fitting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-semantic-consensus-for-deterministic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The principle of LSC is to preserve the latent semantic consensus in both data points and model hypotheses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-semantic-consensus-for-deterministic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAM Back Again: Large Kernel CNNs from a Weakly Supervised Object Localization Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cam-back-again-large-kernel-cnns-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The reason for the high-performance of large kernel CNNs in downstream tasks has been attributed to the large effective receptive field (ERF) produced by large size kernels, but this view has not been fully tested.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cam-back-again-large-kernel-cnns-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forest Inspection Dataset for Aerial Semantic Segmentation and Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forest-inspection-dataset-for-aerial-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Humans use UAVs to monitor changes in forest environments since they are lightweight and provide a large variety of surveillance data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forest-inspection-dataset-for-aerial-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Target-constrained Bidirectional Planning for Generation of Target-oriented Proactive Dialogue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-constrained-bidirectional-planning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by decision-making theories in cognitive science, we propose a novel target-constrained bidirectional planning (TRIP) approach, which plans an appropriate dialogue path by looking ahead and looking back.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-constrained-bidirectional-planning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bit-mask Robust Contrastive Knowledge Distillation for Unsupervised Semantic Hashing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bit-mask-robust-contrastive-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an innovative Bit-mask Robust Contrastive knowledge Distillation (BRCD) method, specifically devised for the distillation of semantic hashing models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bit-mask-robust-contrastive-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Random Semantic Data Augmentation for Medical Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-random-semantic-data-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these approaches encounter notable limitations: image transformation-based and automated data augmentation techniques cannot implement semantic transformations, leading to a constrained variety of augmented samples, and generative data augmentation methods are computationally expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-random-semantic-data-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
