<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 21:07:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>InternImage: Exploring Large-Scale Vision Foundation Models with Deformable Convolutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internimage-exploring-large-scale-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to the great progress of large-scale vision transformers (ViTs) in recent years, large-scale models based on convolutional neural networks (CNNs) are still in an early state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internimage-exploring-large-scale-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DisentQA: Disentangling Parametric and Contextual Knowledge with Counterfactual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentqa-disentangling-parametric-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Question answering models commonly have access to two sources of "knowledge" during inference time: (1) parametric knowledge - the factual knowledge encoded in the model weights, and (2) contextual knowledge - external knowledge (e. g., a Wikipedia passage) given to the model to generate a grounded answer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentqa-disentangling-parametric-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSDT: Masked Language Model Scoring Defense in Text Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msdt-masked-language-model-scoring-defense-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such easily-downloaded language models from various websites empowered the public users as well as some major institutions to give a momentum to their real-life application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msdt-masked-language-model-scoring-defense-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LERT: A Linguistically-motivated Pre-trained Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lert-a-linguistically-motivated-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose LERT, a pre-trained language model that is trained on three types of linguistic features along with the original MLM pre-training task, using a linguistically-informed pre-training (LIP) strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lert-a-linguistically-motivated-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-shot Visual Commonsense Immorality Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-visual-commonsense-immorality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we propose a model that predicts visual commonsense immorality in a zero-shot manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-visual-commonsense-immorality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Multi-scale Mean Teacher Network for Semi-supervised Infection Segmentation in Chest CT Volume for COVID-19</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-multi-scale-mean-teacher-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated detecting lung infections from computed tomography (CT) data plays an important role for combating COVID-19.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-multi-scale-mean-teacher-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Randomized Response for Differential Privacy in Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-randomized-response-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) are susceptible to privacy inference attacks (PIAs), given their ability to learn joint representation from features and edges among nodes in graph data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-randomized-response-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Real Time Exploration and Optimization for Safety-Critical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-real-time-exploration-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of decision-making under uncertainty in an environment with safety constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-real-time-exploration-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer-Net BCa: Breast Cancer Pathologic Complete Response Prediction using Volumetric Deep Radiomic Features from Synthetic Correlated Diffusion Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cancer-net-bca-breast-cancer-pathologic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Breast cancer is the second most common type of cancer in women in Canada and the United States, representing over 25% of all new female cancer cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cancer-net-bca-breast-cancer-pathologic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vis2Mus: Exploring Multimodal Representation Mapping for Controllable Music Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vis2mus-exploring-multimodal-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we explore the representation mapping from the domain of visual arts to the domain of music, with which we can use visual arts as an effective handle to control music generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vis2mus-exploring-multimodal-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stay Home Safe with Starving Federated Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stay-home-safe-with-starving-federated-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the past few years, the field of adversarial attack received numerous attention from various researchers with the help of successful attack success rate against well-known deep neural networks that were acknowledged to achieve high classification ability in various tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stay-home-safe-with-starving-federated-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiSC: Differential Spectral Clustering of Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disc-differential-spectral-clustering-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Selecting subsets of features that differentiate between two conditions is a key task in a broad range of scientific domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disc-differential-spectral-clustering-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness and bias correction in machine learning for depression prediction: results from four different study populations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-and-bias-correction-in-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A significant level of stigma and inequality exists in mental healthcare, especially in under-served populations, which spreads through collected data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-and-bias-correction-in-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Flow, Stereo and Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-flow-stereo-and-depth-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a unified formulation and model for three motion and 3D perception tasks: optical flow, rectified stereo matching and unrectified stereo depth estimation from posed images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-flow-stereo-and-depth-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Transformers Reason in Fragments of Natural Language?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-transformers-reason-in-fragments-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art deep-learning-based approaches to Natural Language Processing (NLP) are credited with various capabilities that involve reasoning with natural language texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-transformers-reason-in-fragments-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient brain age prediction from 3D MRI volumes using 2D projections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-brain-age-prediction-from-3d-mri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using 3D CNNs on high resolution medical volumes is very computationally demanding, especially for large datasets like the UK Biobank which aims to scan 100, 000 subjects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-brain-age-prediction-from-3d-mri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystify Transformers &amp; Convolutions in Modern Image Deep Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystify-transformers-convolutions-in-modern</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the novel feature transformation designs are often claimed as the source of gain, some backbones may benefit from advanced engineering techniques, which makes it hard to identify the real gain from the key feature transformation operators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystify-transformers-convolutions-in-modern</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmarking Dataset with 2440 Organic Molecules for Volume Distribution at Steady State</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmarking-dataset-with-2440-organic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conclusions: To the best of our knowledge, this is the largest dataset for VDss, which can be used as the benchmark for computational studies of VDss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmarking-dataset-with-2440-organic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nano: Nested Human-in-the-Loop Reward Learning for Few-shot Language Model Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nano-nested-human-in-the-loop-reward-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing techniques for controlling the distribution of generated text only work with quantified distributions, which require pre-defined categories, proportions of the distribution, or an existing corpus following the desired distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nano-nested-human-in-the-loop-reward-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnimeRun: 2D Animation Visual Correspondence from Open Source 3D Movies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animerun-2d-animation-visual-correspondence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing correspondence datasets for two-dimensional (2D) cartoon suffer from simple frame composition and monotonic movements, making them insufficient to simulate real animations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animerun-2d-animation-visual-correspondence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleNAT: Giving Each Head a New Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylenat-giving-each-head-a-new-perspective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image generation has been a long sought-after but challenging task, and performing the generation task in an efficient manner is similarly difficult.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylenat-giving-each-head-a-new-perspective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMDialog: A Large-scale Multi-turn Dialogue Dataset Towards Multi-modal Open-domain Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmdialog-a-large-scale-multi-turn-dialogue</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, it is the largest multi-modal conversation dataset by the number of dialogues by 8x.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmdialog-a-large-scale-multi-turn-dialogue</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning in an Adaptable Chess Environment for Detecting Human-understandable Concepts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-in-an-adaptable-chess</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-trained autonomous agents developed using machine learning are showing great promise in a variety of control settings, perhaps most remarkably in applications involving autonomous vehicles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-in-an-adaptable-chess</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perfectly predicting ICU length of stay: too good to be true</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perfectly-predicting-icu-length-of-stay-too</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A paper of Alsinglawi et al was recently accepted and published in Scientific Reports.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perfectly-predicting-icu-length-of-stay-too</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributional Shift Adaptation using Domain-Specific Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-shift-adaptation-using-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning algorithms typically assume that the training and test samples come from the same distributions, i. e., in-distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-shift-adaptation-using-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Vision-Language Transformers for Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-vision-language-transformers-for-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MVLT is trained in two stages: in the first stage, we design a STR-tailored pretraining method based on a masking strategy; in the second stage, we fine-tune our model and adopt an iterative correction method to improve the performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-vision-language-transformers-for-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trackerless freehand ultrasound with sequence modelling and auxiliary transformation over past and future frames</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trackerless-freehand-ultrasound-with-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Little benefit was observed by adding frames more than one second away from the predicted transformation, with or without LSTM-based RNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trackerless-freehand-ultrasound-with-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Zero-shot Event Extraction with Context-Definition Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-zero-shot-event-extraction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that using the static embedding of the event type name might not be enough because a single word could be ambiguous, and we need a sentence to define the type semantics accurately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-zero-shot-event-extraction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning for Time Series Anomaly Detection: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-time-series-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series anomaly detection has applications in a wide range of research fields and applications, including manufacturing and healthcare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-time-series-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask More and Mask Later: Efficient Pre-training of Masked Language Models by Disentangling the [MASK] Token</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-more-and-mask-later-efficient-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show: (1) [MASK]s can indeed be appended at a later layer, being disentangled from the word embedding; (2) The gathering of contextualized information from unmasked tokens can be conducted with a few layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-more-and-mask-later-efficient-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepE: a deep neural network for knowledge graph embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepe-a-deep-neural-network-for-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, DeepE allows deep functions to learn deep features, and shallow functions to learn shallow features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepe-a-deep-neural-network-for-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks with Adaptive Readouts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-with-adaptive-readouts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that in some problems such as binding affinity prediction where molecules are typically presented in a canonical form it might be possible to relax the constraints on permutation invariance of the hypothesis space and learn a more effective model of the affinity by employing an adaptive readout function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-with-adaptive-readouts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimalist Data Wrangling with Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimalist-data-wrangling-with-python</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Minimalist Data Wrangling with Python is envisaged as a student's first introduction to data science, providing a high-level overview as well as discussing key concepts in detail.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimalist-data-wrangling-with-python</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Named Entity Linking: A New Dataset and A Baseline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-named-entity-linking-a-new-dataset-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since each entity often contains rich visual and textual information in KBs, we thus propose three different sub-tasks, i. e., visual to visual entity linking (V2VEL), visual to textual entity linking (V2TEL), and visual to visual-textual entity linking (V2VTEL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-named-entity-linking-a-new-dataset-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Shot Character Understanding in Movies as an Assessment to Meta-Learning of Theory-of-Mind</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-character-understanding-in-movies-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When reading a story, humans can rapidly understand new fictional characters with a few observations, mainly by drawing analogy to fictional and real people they met before in their lives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-character-understanding-in-movies-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bit-depth enhancement detection for compressed video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bit-depth-enhancement-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This problem is complex; it involves detecting outcomes of different dequantization algorithms in the presence of compression that strongly affects the least-significant bits (LSBs) in the video frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bit-depth-enhancement-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collateral facilitation in humans and language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collateral-facilitation-in-humans-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Are the predictions of humans and language models affected by similar things?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collateral-facilitation-in-humans-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe Latent Diffusion: Mitigating Inappropriate Degeneration in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-latent-diffusion-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-conditioned image generation models have recently achieved astonishing results in image quality and text alignment and are consequently employed in a fast-growing number of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-latent-diffusion-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimation of Signal Parameters using Deep Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimation-of-signal-parameters-using-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a Deep Learning approach for signal parameter estimation in the context of wireless channel modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimation-of-signal-parameters-using-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Aesthetic and Technical Effects for Video Quality Assessment of User Generated Content</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-aesthetic-and-technical-effects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better explain the quality perception mechanisms and learn more robust representations, we aim to disentangle the effects of aesthetic quality issues and technical quality issues risen by the complicated video generation processes in the UGC-VQA problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-aesthetic-and-technical-effects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Point Cloud Registration Framework Based on Deep Graph Matching(TPAMI Version)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-point-cloud-registration-framework-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel deep graph matching-based framework for point cloud registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-point-cloud-registration-framework-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformal Frequency Estimation with Sketched Data under Relaxed Exchangeability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-frequency-estimation-with-sketched</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A flexible method is developed to construct a confidence interval for the frequency of a queried object in a very large data set, based on a much smaller sketch of the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-frequency-estimation-with-sketched</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcome-Oriented Prescriptive Process Monitoring Based on Temporal Logic Patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outcome-oriented-prescriptive-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such encoded log is used to train a Machine Learning classifier to learn a mapping between the temporal patterns and the outcome of a process execution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outcome-oriented-prescriptive-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord Questions: A Computational Approach To Diversity Analysis in News Coverage</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discord-questions-a-computational-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are many potential benefits to news readers accessing diverse sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discord-questions-a-computational-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distribution-based Emotion Recognition in Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-based-emotion-recognition-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic emotion recognition in conversation (ERC) is crucial for emotion-aware conversational artificial intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-based-emotion-recognition-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affordance detection with Dynamic-Tree Capsule Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affordance-detection-with-dynamic-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the experimental evaluation we will show that our algorithm is superior to current affordance detection methods when faced with grasping previously unseen objects thanks to our Capsule Network enforcing a parts-to-whole representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affordance-detection-with-dynamic-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACSum: Controllable Summarization with Mixed Attributes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/macsum-controllable-summarization-with-mixed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose two simple and effective parameter-efficient approaches for the new task of mixed controllable summarization based on hard prompt tuning and soft prefix tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/macsum-controllable-summarization-with-mixed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novel structural-scale uncertainty measures and error retention curves: application to multiple sclerosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-structural-scale-uncertainty-measures</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper focuses on the uncertainty estimation of white matter lesions (WML) segmentation in magnetic resonance imaging (MRI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-structural-scale-uncertainty-measures</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreeFlow: probabilistic programming and automatic differentiation for phylogenetics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treeflow-probabilistic-programming-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Probabilistic programming frameworks are powerful tools for statistical modelling and inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treeflow-probabilistic-programming-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Solution for a Fundamental Problem of 3D Inference based on 2D Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-solution-for-a-fundamental-problem-of-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, I discuss a problem that I hope will come to be known as a generalization of the Blind Perspective-n-Point (Blind PnP) problem for object-driven 3D inference based on 2D representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-solution-for-a-fundamental-problem-of-3d</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
