<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 09:15:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Spectral Mapping of Singing Voices: U-Net-Assisted Vocal Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-mapping-of-singing-voices-u-net</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The combination of frequency-axis normalization with Min/Max scaling and the Mean Absolute Error (MAE) loss function achieved the highest Source-to-Distortion Ratio (SDR) of 7. 1 dB, indicating a high level of accuracy in preserving the quality of the original signal during separation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-mapping-of-singing-voices-u-net</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easy Problems That LLMs Get Wrong</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easy-problems-that-llms-get-wrong</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a comprehensive Linguistic Benchmark designed to evaluate the limitations of Large Language Models (LLMs) in domains such as logical reasoning, spatial intelligence, and linguistic understanding, among others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easy-problems-that-llms-get-wrong</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CycleFormer : TSP Solver Based on Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cycleformer-tsp-solver-based-on-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating these ideas, CycleFormer outperforms state-of-the-art (SOTA) transformer models for TSP from TSP-50 to TSP-500.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cycleformer-tsp-solver-based-on-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting CNNs for Trajectory Similarity Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-cnns-for-trajectory-similarity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the computational burden for long trajectories, neural networks have been widely employed for similarity learning and each trajectory is encoded as a high-dimensional vector for similarity search with linear complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-cnns-for-trajectory-similarity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Aspect Controllable Text Generation with Disentangled Counterfactual Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-aspect-controllable-text-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We alleviate the issue of imbalanced attribute correlations during training using counterfactual feature vectors in the attribute latent space by disentanglement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-aspect-controllable-text-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Large Language Model Biases in Persona-Steered Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-large-language-model-biases-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Models that we evaluate that are fine-tuned with Reinforcement Learning from Human Feedback (RLHF) are more steerable, especially towards stances associated with political liberals and women, but present significantly less diverse views of personas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-large-language-model-biases-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grokfast: Accelerated Grokking by Amplifying Slow Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grokfast-accelerated-grokking-by-amplifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One puzzling artifact in machine learning dubbed grokking is where delayed generalization is achieved tenfolds of iterations after near perfect overfitting to the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grokfast-accelerated-grokking-by-amplifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models Need Inductive Biases to Count Inductively</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-need-inductive-biases-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that while traditional RNNs trivially achieve inductive counting, Transformers have to rely on positional embeddings to count out-of-domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-need-inductive-biases-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Optimizers Are Better Than One: LLM Catalyst for Enhancing Gradient-Based Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-optimizers-are-better-than-one-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning a skill generally relies on both practical experience by doer and insightful high-level guidance by instructor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-optimizers-are-better-than-one-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heidelberg-Boston @ SIGTYP 2024 Shared Task: Enhancing Low-Resource Language Analysis With Character-Aware Hierarchical Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heidelberg-boston-sigtyp-2024-shared-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work describes our submission to the constrained subtask of the SIGTYP 2024 shared task, focusing on PoS tagging, morphological tagging, and lemmatization for 13 historical languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heidelberg-boston-sigtyp-2024-shared-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Set Domain Adaptation for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-set-domain-adaptation-for-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised domain adaptation (UDA) for semantic segmentation aims to transfer the pixel-wise knowledge from the labeled source domain to the unlabeled target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-set-domain-adaptation-for-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemFlow: Binding Semantic Segmentation and Image Synthesis via Rectified Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semflow-binding-semantic-segmentation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For image synthesis, we propose a finite perturbation approach to enhance the diversity of generated results without changing the semantic categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semflow-binding-semantic-segmentation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeMamba: AI-Generated Video Detection on Million-Scale GenVideo Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demamba-ai-generated-video-detection-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe that the GenVideo dataset and the DeMamba module will significantly advance the field of AI-generated video detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demamba-ai-generated-video-detection-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KITRO: Refining Human Mesh by 2D Clues and Kinematic-tree Rotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kitro-refining-human-mesh-by-2d-clues-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these, we introduce Kinematic-Tree Rotation (KITRO), a novel mesh refinement strategy that explicitly models depth and human kinematic-tree structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kitro-refining-human-mesh-by-2d-clues-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SparseDrive: End-to-End Autonomous Driving via Sparse Scene Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsedrive-end-to-end-autonomous-driving-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we explore the sparse representation and review the task design for end-to-end autonomous driving, proposing a new paradigm named SparseDrive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsedrive-end-to-end-autonomous-driving-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Training of Rectified Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-training-of-rectified-flows</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose improved techniques for training rectified flows, allowing them to compete with knowledge distillation methods even in the low NFE setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-training-of-rectified-flows</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-View People Detection in Large Scenes via Supervised View-Wise Contribution Weighting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-people-detection-in-large-scenes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent deep learning-based multi-view people detection (MVD) methods have shown promising results on existing datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-people-detection-in-large-scenes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-Instruction: Aligning Language Model in Low-resource Languages with Self-curated Cross-lingual Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-instruction-aligning-language-model-in-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we find that models tuned on cross-lingual instruction following samples can follow the instruction in the output language without further tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-instruction-aligning-language-model-in-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Reinforcement Learning with Label-Sensitive Reward for Natural Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-reinforcement-learning-with-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose a novel Reinforcement Learning framework enhanced with Label-sensitive Reward (RLLR) to amplify the performance of LLMs in NLU tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-reinforcement-learning-with-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETHER: Efficient Finetuning of Large-Scale Models with Hyperplane Reflections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ether-efficient-finetuning-of-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parameter-efficient finetuning (PEFT) has become ubiquitous to adapt foundation models to downstream task requirements while retaining their generalization ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ether-efficient-finetuning-of-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improve Student's Reasoning Generalizability through Cascading Decomposed CoTs Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improve-student-s-reasoning-generalizability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, by restructuring the training objectives -- removing the answer from outputs and concatenating the question with the rationale as input -- CasCoD's two-step learning process ensures that students focus on learning rationales without interference from the preset answers, thus improving reasoning generalizability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improve-student-s-reasoning-generalizability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Token Can Help! Learning Scalable and Pluggable Virtual Tokens for Retrieval-Augmented Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-token-can-help-learning-scalable-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose a novel method that involves learning scalable and pluggable virtual tokens for RAG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-token-can-help-learning-scalable-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Near Optimal Decentralized Optimization with Compression and Momentum Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-optimal-decentralized-optimization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Communication efficiency has garnered significant attention as it is considered the main bottleneck for large-scale decentralized Machine Learning applications in distributed and federated settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-optimal-decentralized-optimization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANAH: Analytical Annotation of Hallucinations in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anah-analytical-annotation-of-hallucinations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reducing the `$\textit{hallucination}$' problem of Large Language Models (LLMs) is crucial for their wide applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anah-analytical-annotation-of-hallucinations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Advantage-Guided Policy Regularization for Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-advantage-guided-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirically, we conduct a series of experiments on the D4RL benchmark, where A2PR demonstrates state-of-the-art performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-advantage-guided-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDS-VSS: Moving Camera Dynamic Scene Video Semantic Segmentation by Filtering with Self-Supervised Geometry and Motion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcds-vss-moving-camera-dynamic-scene-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous systems, such as self-driving cars, rely on reliable semantic environment perception for decision making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcds-vss-moving-camera-dynamic-scene-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autonomous Driving with Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autonomous-driving-with-spiking-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous driving demands an integrated approach that encompasses perception, prediction, and planning, all while operating under strict energy constraints to enhance scalability and environmental sustainability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autonomous-driving-with-spiking-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OccSora: 4D Occupancy Generation Models as World Simulators for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occsora-4d-occupancy-generation-models-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose a diffusion-based 4D occupancy generation model, OccSora, to simulate the development of the 3D world for autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occsora-4d-occupancy-generation-models-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-In-One Medical Image Restoration via Task-Adaptive Routing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-in-one-medical-image-restoration-via-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on the task of all-in-one medical image restoration, aiming to address multiple distinct MedIR tasks with a single universal model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-in-one-medical-image-restoration-via-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating annotation shift in cancer classification using single image generative models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-annotation-shift-in-cancer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the success of AI applications in this domain is restricted by the quantity and quality of available data, posing challenges due to limited and costly data annotation procedures that often lead to annotation shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-annotation-shift-in-cancer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Hallucinations in Large Language Model Generation: A Token Probability Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-hallucinations-in-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concerns regarding the propensity of Large Language Models (LLMs) to produce inaccurate outputs, also known as hallucinations, have escalated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-hallucinations-in-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoSy: Evaluating Textual Explanations of Neurons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosy-evaluating-textual-explanations-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A crucial aspect of understanding the complex nature of Deep Neural Networks (DNNs) is the ability to explain learned concepts within their latent representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosy-evaluating-textual-explanations-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVFT: Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning with Singular Vectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svft-parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on language and vision benchmarks show that SVFT recovers up to 96% of full fine-tuning performance while training only 0. 006 to 0. 25% of parameters, outperforming existing methods that only recover up to 85% performance using 0. 03 to 0. 8% of the trainable parameter budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svft-parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Adaptation with Cauchy-Schwarz Divergence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptation-with-cauchy-schwarz</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we illustrate that the CS divergence enables a simple estimator on the discrepancy of both marginal and conditional distributions between source and target domains in the representation space, without requiring any distributional assumptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptation-with-cauchy-schwarz</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PixOOD: Pixel-Level Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixood-pixel-level-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a dense image prediction out-of-distribution detection algorithm, called PixOOD, which does not require training on samples of anomalous data and is not designed for a specific application which avoids traditional training biases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixood-pixel-level-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threshold-Independent Fair Matching through Score Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/threshold-independent-fair-matching-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These are typically addressed by generating matching scores and apply thresholds to balance false positives and negatives in various contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/threshold-independent-fair-matching-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$\textit{S}^3$Gaussian: Self-Supervised Street Gaussians for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textit-s-3-gaussian-self-supervised-street</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Photorealistic 3D reconstruction of street scenes is a critical technique for developing real-world simulators for autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textit-s-3-gaussian-self-supervised-street</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CausalQuest: Collecting Natural Causal Questions for AI Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalquest-collecting-natural-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Humans have an innate drive to seek out causality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalquest-collecting-natural-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPARE: Symmetrized Point-to-Plane Distance for Robust Non-Rigid Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spare-symmetrized-point-to-plane-distance-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing optimization-based methods for non-rigid registration typically minimize an alignment error metric based on the point-to-point or point-to-plane distance between corresponding point pairs on the source surface and target surface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spare-symmetrized-point-to-plane-distance-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Consistency and Role-Specific Knowledge Capturing by Rebuilding Fictional Character's Persona</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-consistency-and-role-specific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the recent introduction of Assistants API, it is expected that document-based language models will be actively used in various domains, especially Role-playing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-consistency-and-role-specific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Occam Gradient Descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occam-gradient-descent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning neural network models must be large enough to adapt to their problem domain, while small enough to avoid overfitting training data during gradient descent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occam-gradient-descent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Feature Boosting for Explainable Speech Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-feature-boosting-for-explainable-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In speech emotion recognition (SER), using predefined features without considering their practical importance may lead to high dimensional datasets, including redundant and irrelevant information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-feature-boosting-for-explainable-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Power of Spatial and Temporal Information in Medical Multimodal Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-power-of-spatial-and-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce the Med-ST framework for fine-grained spatial and temporal modeling to exploit information from multiple spatial views of chest radiographs and temporal historical records.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-power-of-spatial-and-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformers and Slot Encoding for Sample Efficient Physical World Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-and-slot-encoding-for-sample</link>
      <description><![CDATA[World modelling, i. e. building a representation of the rules that govern the world so as to predict its evolution, is an essential ability for any agent interacting with the physical world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-and-slot-encoding-for-sample</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xwin-LM: Strong and Scalable Alignment Practice for LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xwin-lm-strong-and-scalable-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Xwin-LM, a comprehensive suite of alignment methodologies for large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xwin-lm-strong-and-scalable-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Zero to Hero: Cold-Start Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-zero-to-hero-cold-start-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the realistic but underexplored cold-start setting where an anomaly detection model is initialized using zero-shot guidance, but subsequently receives a small number of contaminated observations (namely, that may include anomalies).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-zero-to-hero-cold-start-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flexible SE(2) graph neural networks with applications to PDE surrogates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-se-2-graph-neural-networks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel approach for constructing graph neural networks equivariant to 2D rotations and translations and leveraging them as PDE surrogates on non-gridded domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-se-2-graph-neural-networks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CV-VAE: A Compatible Video VAE for Latent Generative Video Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cv-vae-a-compatible-video-vae-for-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, since current diffusion-based approaches are often implemented using pre-trained text-to-image (T2I) models, directly training a video VAE without considering the compatibility with existing T2I models will result in a latent space gap between them, which will take huge computational resources for training to bridge the gap even with the T2I models as initialization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cv-vae-a-compatible-video-vae-for-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DP-IQA: Utilizing Diffusion Prior for Blind Image Quality Assessment in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dp-iqa-utilizing-diffusion-prior-for-blind</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image quality assessment (IQA) plays a critical role in selecting high-quality images and guiding compression and enhancement methods in a series of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dp-iqa-utilizing-diffusion-prior-for-blind</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Imitation: Learning Key Reasoning Steps from Dual Chain-of-Thoughts in Reasoning Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-imitation-learning-key-reasoning-steps</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further analysis shows that EDIT can generate high-quality CoTs with more correct key reasoning steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-imitation-learning-key-reasoning-steps</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
