<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 21:06:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saliency-Augmented Memory Completion for Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saliency-augmented-memory-completion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we innovatively propose to store the part of the image most important to the tasks in episodic memory by saliency map extraction and memory encoding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saliency-augmented-memory-completion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Kernel Alignment Regret Bound for Online Kernel Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-kernel-alignment-regret-bound-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[If the eigenvalues of the kernel matrix decay exponentially, then our algorithm enjoys a regret of $O(\sqrt{\mathcal{A}_T})$ at a computational complexity of $O(\ln^2{T})$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-kernel-alignment-regret-bound-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fewer is More: Efficient Object Detection in Large Aerial Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fewer-is-more-efficient-object-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current mainstream object detection methods for large aerial images usually divide large images into patches and then exhaustively detect the objects of interest on all patches, no matter whether there exist objects or not.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fewer-is-more-efficient-object-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simultaneously Optimizing Perturbations and Positions for Black-box Adversarial Patch Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simultaneously-optimizing-perturbations-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments are conducted on the Face Recognition (FR) task, and results on four representative FR models show that our method can significantly improve the attack success rate and query efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simultaneously-optimizing-perturbations-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Complex Knowledge Base Question Answering via Question-to-Action and Question-to-Question Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-complex-knowledge-base-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Complex knowledge base question answering can be achieved by converting questions into sequences of predefined actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-complex-knowledge-base-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMMix: Self-Motivated Image Mixing for Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smmix-self-motivated-image-mixing-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the subtle designs of the self-motivated paradigm, our SMMix is significant in its smaller training overhead and better performance than other CutMix variants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smmix-self-motivated-image-mixing-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orientation-Shared Convolution Representation for CT Metal Artifact Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orientation-shared-convolution-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During X-ray computed tomography (CT) scanning, metallic implants carrying with patients often lead to adverse artifacts in the captured CT images and then impair the clinical treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orientation-shared-convolution-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skit-S2I: An Indian Accented Speech to Intent dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skit-s2i-an-indian-accented-speech-to-intent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional conversation assistants extract text transcripts from the speech signal using automatic speech recognition (ASR) and then predict intent from the transcriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skit-s2i-an-indian-accented-speech-to-intent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextBox 2.0: A Text Generation Library with Pre-trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textbox-2-0-a-text-generation-library-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate research on text generation, this paper presents a comprehensive and unified library, TextBox 2. 0, focusing on the use of pre-trained language models (PLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textbox-2-0-a-text-generation-library-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Generalizable Representations for Reinforcement Learning via Adaptive Meta-learner of Behavioral Similarities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-generalizable-representations-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How to learn an effective reinforcement learning-based model for control tasks from high-level visual observations is a practical and challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-generalizable-representations-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAE-ISumm: Unsupervised Graph-Based Summarization of Indian Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gae-isumm-unsupervised-graph-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, we experiment with the most publicly available Indian language summarization datasets to investigate the effectiveness of GAE-ISumm on other Indian languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gae-isumm-unsupervised-graph-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closed-form control with spike coding networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closed-form-control-with-spike-coding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The neuroscience theory of Spike Coding Networks (SCNs) offers a fully analytical solution for implementing dynamical systems in recurrent spiking neural networks -- while maintaining irregular, sparse, and robust spiking activity -- but it's not clear how to directly apply it to control problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closed-form-control-with-spike-coding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Representation Learning for Cognitive Diagnosis in Late-Life Depression Over 5 Years with Structural MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-representation-learning-for-cognitive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we describe the development of a hybrid representation learning (HRL) framework for predicting cognitive diagnosis over 5 years based on T1-weighted sMRI data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-representation-learning-for-cognitive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Uncertainty Quantification of Variance Networks by Tree-Structured Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-uncertainty-quantification-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A tree is built upon giving the training data, whose leaf nodes represent different regions where region-specific neural networks are trained to predict both the mean and the variance for quantifying uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-uncertainty-quantification-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Pupil Dilation for Data Augmentation in Iris Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artificial-pupil-dilation-for-data-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results indicate that our data augmentation method can improve segmentation accuracy up to 15% for images with high pupil dilation, which creates a more reliable iris recognition pipeline, even under extreme dilation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artificial-pupil-dilation-for-data-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Gadget Discovery in Science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-gadget-discovery-in-science</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This process of gadget discovery develops in three stages: First, we use an RL agent to generate data, then, we employ a mining algorithm to extract gadgets and finally, the obtained gadgets are grouped by a density-based clustering algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-gadget-discovery-in-science</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Blind Watermarking: Combining Invertible and Non-invertible Mechanisms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-blind-watermarking-combining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The CIN is composed of the invertible part to achieve high imperceptibility and the non-invertible part to strengthen the robustness against strong noise attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-blind-watermarking-combining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Realization of Intelligent Decision-Making in the Real World: A Foundation Decision Model Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-realization-of-intelligent-decision-making</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We therefore argue that a foundation decision model (FDM) can be established by formulating various decision-making tasks as a sequence decoding task using the Transformer architecture; this would be a promising solution to advance the applications of IDM in more complex real world tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-realization-of-intelligent-decision-making</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Stands Alone: Relational Fake News Detection with Hypergraph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nothing-stands-alone-relational-fake-news-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nowadays, fake news easily propagates through online social networks and becomes a grand threat to individuals and society.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nothing-stands-alone-relational-fake-news-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real or Fake Text?: Investigating Human Ability to Detect Boundaries Between Human-Written and Machine-Generated Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-or-fake-text-investigating-human-ability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As text generated by large language models proliferates, it becomes vital to understand how humans engage with such text, and whether or not they are able to detect when the text they are reading did not originate with a human writer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-or-fake-text-investigating-human-ability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLT: Cyclic Overlapping Lottery Tickets for Faster Pruning of Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colt-cyclic-overlapping-lottery-tickets-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research aims to generate winning lottery tickets from a set of lottery tickets that can achieve similar accuracy to the original unpruned network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colt-cyclic-overlapping-lottery-tickets-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Quadratic Hedging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-quadratic-hedging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel computational approach for quadratic hedging in a high-dimensional incomplete market.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-quadratic-hedging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avicenna: a challenge dataset for natural language generation toward commonsense syllogistic reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avicenna-a-challenge-dataset-for-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Avicenna corpus was developed as a benchmark for syllogistic NLG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avicenna-a-challenge-dataset-for-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROS-Based Multi-Agent Systems COntrol Simulation Testbed (MASCOT)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ros-based-multi-agent-systems-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a simulation testbed developed for testing and demonstration of decentralized control algorithms designed for multi-agent systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ros-based-multi-agent-systems-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A-NeSI: A Scalable Approximate Method for Probabilistic Neurosymbolic Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-nesi-a-scalable-approximate-method-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Approximate Neurosymbolic Inference (A-NeSI): a new framework for PNL that uses neural networks for scalable approximate inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-nesi-a-scalable-approximate-method-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The choice of scaling technique matters for classification performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-choice-of-scaling-technique-matters-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we execute a broad experiment comparing the impact of 5 scaling techniques on the performances of 20 classification algorithms among monolithic and ensemble models, applying them to 82 publicly available datasets with varying imbalance ratios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-choice-of-scaling-technique-matters-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmark for Uncertainty &amp; Robustness in Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-for-uncertainty-robustness-in-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-Supervised Learning (SSL) is crucial for real-world applications, especially in data-hungry domains such as healthcare and self-driving cars.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-for-uncertainty-robustness-in-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finetuning for Sarcasm Detection with a Pruned Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finetuning-for-sarcasm-detection-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sarcasm is usually conveyed through tone of voice, facial expressions, or other forms of nonverbal communication, but it can also be indicated by the use of certain words or phrases that are typically associated with irony or humor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finetuning-for-sarcasm-detection-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-Informed Gaussian Process Regression Generalizes Linear PDE Solvers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-gaussian-process-regression-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Crucially, this probabilistic viewpoint allows to (1) quantify the inherent discretization error; (2) propagate uncertainty about the model parameters to the solution; and (3) condition on noisy measurements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-gaussian-process-regression-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using MM principles to deal with incomplete data in K-means clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-mm-principles-to-deal-with-incomplete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Among many clustering algorithms, the K-means clustering algorithm is widely used because of its simple algorithm and fast convergence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-mm-principles-to-deal-with-incomplete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precise Location Matching Improves Dense Contrastive Learning in Digital Pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precise-location-matching-improves-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method outperforms previous dense matching methods by up to 7. 2 % in average precision for detection and 5. 6 % in average precision for instance segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precise-location-matching-improves-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NARS vs. Reinforcement learning: ONA vs. Q-Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nars-vs-reinforcement-learning-ona-vs-q</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the realistic scenarios is taking a sequence of optimal actions to do a task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nars-vs-reinforcement-learning-ona-vs-q</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Raw Emotional Dataset with Aggregation Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-raw-emotional-dataset-with-aggregation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new data set for speech emotion recognition (SER) tasks called Dusha.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-raw-emotional-dataset-with-aggregation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rule Learning by Modularity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rule-learning-by-modularity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a modular methodology that combines state-of-the-art methods in (stochastic) machine learning with traditional methods in rule learning to provide efficient and scalable algorithms for the classification of vast data sets, while remaining explainable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rule-learning-by-modularity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Close Look at Spatial Modeling: From Attention to Convolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-close-look-at-spatial-modeling-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision Transformers have shown great promise recently for many vision tasks due to the insightful architecture design and attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-close-look-at-spatial-modeling-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring Your Own View: Graph Neural Networks for Link Prediction with Personalized Subgraph Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bring-your-own-view-graph-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge the gap, we introduce a Personalized Subgraph Selector (PS2) as a plug-and-play framework to automatically, personally, and inductively identify optimal subgraphs for different edges when performing GNNLP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bring-your-own-view-graph-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Survival of Tongue Cancer Patients by Machine Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-survival-of-tongue-cancer-patients</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prognostic factors identified by our method are consistent with previous clinical studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-survival-of-tongue-cancer-patients</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAC-Net: A Hybrid Attention-Based Convolutional Neural Network for Highly Accurate Protein-Ligand Binding Affinity Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hac-net-a-hybrid-attention-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applying deep learning concepts from image detection and graph theory has greatly advanced protein-ligand binding affinity prediction, a challenge with enormous ramifications for both drug discovery and protein engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hac-net-a-hybrid-attention-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroBERT: Effective Training of Low-resource Monolingual BERTs through Parameter Reduction and Multitask Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/microbert-effective-training-of-low-resource</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer language models (TLMs) are critical for most NLP tasks, but they are difficult to create for low-resource languages because of how much pretraining data they require.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/microbert-effective-training-of-low-resource</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Unfolding-based Weighted Averaging for Federated Learning under Heterogeneous Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-unfolding-based-weighted-averaging-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is a collaborative model training method by iterating model updates at multiple clients and aggregation of the updates at a central server.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-unfolding-based-weighted-averaging-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProgNet: A Transferable Deep Network for Aircraft Engine Damage Propagation Prognosis under Real Flight Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prognet-a-transferable-deep-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, ProgNet is transferred to the target domain of obtained degradation features for fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prognet-a-transferable-deep-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Classification with Small Datasets: Overview and Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-classification-with-small-datasets-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, as research in this scope is still in its infancy, two key ingredients are missing for ensuring reliable and truthful progress: a systematic and extensive overview of the state of the art, and a common benchmark to allow for objective comparisons between published methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-classification-with-small-datasets-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDO calibration via Magnus Expansion and Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdo-calibration-via-magnus-expansion-and-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of the large basket approximation, it is assumed that this is sufficiently large to approximate it by a limit SPDE describing the portfolio loss of a basket with size $K\rightarrow \infty$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdo-calibration-via-magnus-expansion-and-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Meta-Representation Learning via Global Label Inference and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-meta-representation-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirically, MeLa outperforms existing methods across a diverse range of benchmarks, in particular under a more challenging setting where the number of training tasks is limited and labels are task-specific.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-meta-representation-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SiteFerret: beyond simple pocket identification in proteins</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siteferret-beyond-simple-pocket</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel method for the automatic detection of pockets on protein molecular surfaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siteferret-beyond-simple-pocket</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predictive Coding Based Multiscale Network with Encoder-Decoder LSTM for Video Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictive-coding-based-multiscale-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a predictive coding model, it is updated by a combination of bottom-up and top-down information flows, which is different from traditional bottom-up training style.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictive-coding-based-multiscale-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-High-Definition Low-Light Image Enhancement: A Benchmark and Transformer-Based Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-high-definition-low-light-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we consider the task of low-light image enhancement (LLIE) and introduce a large-scale database consisting of images at 4K and 8K resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-high-definition-low-light-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electromagnetic Based Communication Model for Dynamic Metasurface Antennas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/electromagnetic-based-communication-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic metasurface antennas (DMAs) arise as a promising technology in the field of massive multiple-input multiple-output (mMIMO) systems, offering the possibility of integrating a large number of antennas in a limited -- and potentially large -- aperture while keeping the required number of radio-frequency (RF) chains under control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/electromagnetic-based-communication-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certified Policy Smoothing for Cooperative Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certified-policy-smoothing-for-cooperative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results show that our method produces meaningful guaranteed robustness for all models and environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certified-policy-smoothing-for-cooperative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confidence-Aware Paced-Curriculum Learning by Label Smoothing for Surgical Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-aware-paced-curriculum-learning-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we design a paced curriculum by label smoothing (P-CBLS) using paced learning with uniform label smoothing (ULS) for classification tasks and fuse uniform and spatially varying label smoothing (SVLS) for semantic segmentation tasks in a curriculum manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-aware-paced-curriculum-learning-by</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
