<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:10:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing EG-IPT and ipt~: a novel electric guitar dataset and a new Max/MSP object for real-time classification of instrumental playing techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introducing-eg-ipt-and-ipt-a-novel-electric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents two key contributions to the real-time classification of Instrumental Playing Techniques (IPTs) in the context of NIME and human-machine interactive systems: the EG-IPT dataset and the ipt∼ Max/MSP object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introducing-eg-ipt-and-ipt-a-novel-electric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConciseHint: Boosting Efficient Reasoning via Continuous Concise Hints during Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concisehint-boosting-efficient-reasoning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to fill the blank, we propose a framework dubbed ConciseHint, which continuously encourages the reasoning model to speak concisely by injecting the textual hint (manually designed or trained on the concise data) during the token generation of the reasoning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concisehint-boosting-efficient-reasoning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-modal Anchor Gated Transformer with Knowledge Distillation for Emotion Recognition in Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-anchor-gated-transformer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we introduce a multi-modal anchor gated transformer to effectively integrate utterance-level representations across modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-anchor-gated-transformer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud-Aware SAR Fusion for Enhanced Optical Sensing in Space Missions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cloud-aware-sar-fusion-for-enhanced-optical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cloud contamination significantly impairs the usability of optical satellite imagery, affecting critical applications such as environmental monitoring, disaster response, and land-use analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cloud-aware-sar-fusion-for-enhanced-optical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniFork: Exploring Modality Alignment for Unified Multimodal Understanding and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifork-exploring-modality-alignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our analysis reveals a crucial observation: understanding tasks benefit from a progressively increasing modality alignment across network depth, which helps build up semantic information for better comprehension; In contrast, generation tasks follow a different trend: modality alignment increases in the early layers but decreases in the deep layers to recover spatial details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifork-exploring-modality-alignment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acquiring and Accumulating Knowledge from Diverse Datasets for Multi-label Driving Scene Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acquiring-and-accumulating-knowledge-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Of this, KAA accounts for 31. 3% of the gain, and CAL contributes 24. 8%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acquiring-and-accumulating-knowledge-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Data to Knowledge: Evaluating How Efficiently Language Models Learn Facts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-data-to-knowledge-evaluating-how</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sample efficiency is a crucial property of language models with practical implications for training efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-data-to-knowledge-evaluating-how</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Generality to Mastery: Composer-Style Symbolic Music Generation via Large-Scale Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-generality-to-mastery-composer-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate how general music knowledge learned from a broad corpus can enhance the mastery of specific composer styles, with a focus on piano piece generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-generality-to-mastery-composer-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEXA: Towards General Multimodal Reasoning with Dynamic Multi-Expert Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mexa-towards-general-multimodal-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combining pre-trained expert models offers substantial potential for scalable multimodal reasoning, but building a unified framework remains challenging due to the increasing diversity of input modalities and task complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mexa-towards-general-multimodal-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instituto de Telecomunicações at IWSLT 2025: Aligning Small-Scale Speech and Language Models for Speech-to-Text Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instituto-de-telecomunicacoes-at-iwslt-2025</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the IT-IST submission to the IWSLT 2025 Shared Task on Instruction Following Speech Processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instituto-de-telecomunicacoes-at-iwslt-2025</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeXpert: A Multi-Level Benchmark for Evaluating LaTeX Code Generation by LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texpert-a-multi-level-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LaTeX's precision and flexibility in typesetting have made it the gold standard for the preparation of scientific documentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texpert-a-multi-level-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-Seg++: Mutual Prompt-Guided Collaborative Learning for Versatile Medical Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-seg-mutual-prompt-guided-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image analysis is critical yet challenged by the need of jointly segmenting organs or tissues, and numerous instances for anatomical structures and tumor microenvironment analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-seg-mutual-prompt-guided-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Mental Imagery: Empower Multimodal Reasoning with Latent Visual Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-mental-imagery-empower-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language models (VLMs) excel at multimodal understanding, yet their text-only decoding forces them to verbalize visual reasoning, limiting performance on tasks that demand visual imagination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-mental-imagery-empower-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YASMOT: Yet another stereo image multi-object tracker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yasmot-yet-another-stereo-image-multi-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There now exists many popular object detectors based on deep learning that can analyze images and extract locations and class labels for occurrences of objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yasmot-yet-another-stereo-image-multi-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergent Temporal Correspondences from Video Diffusion Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergent-temporal-correspondences-from-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in video diffusion models based on Diffusion Transformers (DiTs) have achieved remarkable success in generating temporally coherent videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergent-temporal-correspondences-from-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Minimalist Optimizer Design for LLM Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-minimalist-optimizer-design-for-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the LLaMA 7B model, SCALE outperforms the state-of-the-art method APOLLO in terms of both perplexity and memory consumption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-minimalist-optimizer-design-for-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LunarLoc: Segment-Based Global Localization on the Moon</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lunarloc-segment-based-global-localization-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Global localization is necessary for autonomous operations on the lunar surface where traditional Earth-based navigation infrastructure, such as GPS, is unavailable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lunarloc-segment-based-global-localization-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-Generated Feedback Supports Learning If Learners Choose to Use It</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-generated-feedback-supports-learning-if</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After adjusting for this effect, two out of seven lessons showed statistically significant learning benefits from LLM feedback with standardized effect sizes of 0. 28 and 0. 33.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-generated-feedback-supports-learning-if</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAWIFlow Benchmark: Realistic Flow-Based Evaluation for Network Intrusion Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mawiflow-benchmark-realistic-flow-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces MAWIFlow, a flow-based benchmark derived from the MAWILAB v1. 1 dataset, designed to enable realistic and reproducible evaluation of anomaly detection methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mawiflow-benchmark-realistic-flow-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Music Representations? Evaluating Foundation Models on World Music Corpora</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-music-representations-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foundation models have revolutionized music information retrieval, but questions remain about their ability to generalize across diverse musical traditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-music-representations-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedFitTech: A Baseline in Federated Learning for Fitness Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedfittech-a-baseline-in-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For instance, this system allows wearable devices to optimize the trade-off between capturing common fitness activity patterns and preserving individuals' nuances, thereby enhancing both the scalability and efficiency of privacy-aware fitness tracking applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedfittech-a-baseline-in-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAGentA: Multi-Agent Retrieval-Augmented Generation for Attributed Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ragenta-multi-agent-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Central to the framework is a hybrid retrieval strategy that combines sparse and dense methods, improving Recall@20 by 12. 5% compared to the best single retrieval model, resulting in more correct and well-supported answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ragenta-multi-agent-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and faithful reconstruction of dynamical attractors using homogeneous differentiators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-faithful-reconstruction-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstructing the attractors of complex nonlinear dynamical systems from available measurements is key to analyse and predict their time evolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-faithful-reconstruction-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransDreamerV3: Implanting Transformer In DreamerV3</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transdreamerv3-implanting-transformer-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces TransDreamerV3, a reinforcement learning model that enhances the DreamerV3 architecture by integrating a transformer encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transdreamerv3-implanting-transformer-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Step-by-Step and Verifiable Medical Reasoning in MLLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-step-by-step-and-verifiable-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The reasoning performance is determined by an MICS-Score, which assesses the quality of generated reasoning paths.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-step-by-step-and-verifiable-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Reinforcement Learning for Discrete Compositional Generation via General Soft Operators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-reinforcement-learning-for-discrete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show that existing methods, often framed as sampling proportional to a reward function, are inadequate and yield suboptimal candidates, especially in large search spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-reinforcement-learning-for-discrete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reward-Agnostic Prompt Optimization for Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reward-agnostic-prompt-optimization-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate a general approach for improving user prompts in text-to-image (T2I) diffusion models by finding prompts that maximize a reward function specified at test-time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reward-agnostic-prompt-optimization-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network Sparsity Unlocks the Scaling Potential of Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-sparsity-unlocks-the-scaling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Effectively scaling up deep reinforcement learning models has proven notoriously difficult due to network pathologies during training, motivating various targeted interventions such as periodic reset and architectural advances such as layer normalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-sparsity-unlocks-the-scaling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Neural Operator based Hybrid Microscale Model for Multiscale Simulation of Rate-Dependent Materials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-operator-based-hybrid-microscale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The behavior of materials is influenced by a wide range of phenomena occurring across various time and length scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-operator-based-hybrid-microscale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual-Instructed Degradation Diffusion for All-in-One Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-instructed-degradation-diffusion-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image restoration tasks like deblurring, denoising, and dehazing usually need distinct models for each degradation type, restricting their generalization in real-world scenarios with mixed or unknown degradations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-instructed-degradation-diffusion-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain-inspired interpretable reservoir computing with resonant recurrent neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-inspired-interpretable-reservoir</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to existing artificial neural network approaches, the proposed resonant reservoir network (RRN) utilizes oscillatory dynamics expressed as a straightforward extension of traditional artificial neural networks, produces interpretable features for classification, avoids computationally expensive training (e. g., backpropagation), and performs well with few parameters in different classification scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-inspired-interpretable-reservoir</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mesh-Informed Neural Operator : A Transformer Generative Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesh-informed-neural-operator-a-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative models in function spaces, situated at the intersection of generative modeling and operator learning, are attracting increasing attention due to their immense potential in diverse scientific and engineering applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesh-informed-neural-operator-a-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ParkFormer: A Transformer-Based Parking Policy with Goal Embedding and Pedestrian-Aware Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parkformer-a-transformer-based-parking-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous parking plays a vital role in intelligent vehicle systems, particularly in constrained urban environments where high-precision control is required.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parkformer-a-transformer-based-parking-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Dynamic Material Handling via Adaptive Constrained Evolutionary Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-dynamic-material-handling-via-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, making the best use of limited computational resources and historical records for training a robust policy is crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-dynamic-material-handling-via-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Shot Generalized Category Discovery With Retrieval-Guided Decision Boundary Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-generalized-category-discovery-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we use a decision boundary pre-training module to mitigate the overfitting of pre-trained information on known category boundaries and improve the learning of these decision boundaries using labeled samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-generalized-category-discovery-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Impact of Model Accuracy for Optimizing Battery Energy Storage Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-impact-of-model-accuracy-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study investigates two models of varying complexity for optimizing intraday arbitrage energy trading of a battery energy storage system using a model predictive control approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-impact-of-model-accuracy-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextBraTS: Text-Guided Volumetric Brain Tumor Segmentation with Innovative Dataset Development and Fusion Module Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textbrats-text-guided-volumetric-brain-tumor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning has demonstrated remarkable success in medical image segmentation and computer-aided diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textbrats-text-guided-volumetric-brain-tumor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loupe: A Generalizable and Adaptive Framework for Image Forgery Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loupe-a-generalizable-and-adaptive-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proliferation of generative models has raised serious concerns about visual content forgery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loupe-a-generalizable-and-adaptive-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mathematical Proof as a Litmus Test: Revealing Failure Modes of Advanced Large Reasoning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathematical-proof-as-a-litmus-test-revealing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large reasoning models (e. g., R1, o3) have demonstrated remarkable mathematical problem-solving abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathematical-proof-as-a-litmus-test-revealing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise-Informed Diffusion-Generated Image Detection with Anomaly Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-informed-diffusion-generated-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon this insight, we introduce a novel Noise-Aware Self-Attention (NASA) module that focuses on noise regions to capture anomalous patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-informed-diffusion-generated-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simultaneous Translation with Offline Speech and LLM Models in CUNI Submission to IWSLT 2025</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simultaneous-translation-with-offline-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The backbone of our systems is the offline Whisper speech model, which we use for both translation and transcription in simultaneous mode with the state-of-the-art simultaneous policy AlignAtt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simultaneous-translation-with-offline-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable Agent Modeling for Agent Collaboration-Competition Adaptation with Multi-Retrieval and Dynamic Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-agent-modeling-for-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adapting a single agent to a new multi-agent system brings challenges, necessitating adjustments across various tasks, environments, and interactions with unknown teammates and opponents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-agent-modeling-for-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camera Calibration via Circular Patterns: A Comprehensive Framework with Measurement Uncertainty and Unbiased Projection Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camera-calibration-via-circular-patterns-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core concept of this approach is to model the boundary points of a two-dimensional shape as a Markov random field, considering its connectivity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camera-calibration-via-circular-patterns-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Modeling of Full-Atom Protein Conformations using Latent Diffusion on Graph Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-modeling-of-full-atom-protein</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using D2R-MD, a 2-microsecond MD trajectory (12 000 frames) of the human dopamine D2 receptor in a membrane environment, the sequential and residue-based pooling strategy reproduces the reference ensemble with high structural fidelity (all-atom lDDT of approximately 0. 7; C-alpha-lDDT of approximately 0. 8) and recovers backbone and side-chain dihedral-angle distributions with a Jensen-Shannon divergence of less than 0. 03 compared to the MD data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-modeling-of-full-atom-protein</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistent Sampling and Simulation: Molecular Dynamics with Energy-Based Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistent-sampling-and-simulation-molecular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have recently gained significant attention due to their effectiveness in various scientific domains, including biochemistry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistent-sampling-and-simulation-molecular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RealSR-R1: Reinforcement Learning for Real-World Image Super-Resolution with Vision-Language Chain-of-Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realsr-r1-reinforcement-learning-for-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-World Image Super-Resolution is one of the most challenging task in image restoration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realsr-r1-reinforcement-learning-for-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off-Policy Actor-Critic for Adversarial Observation Robustness: Virtual Alternative Training via Symmetric Policy Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/off-policy-actor-critic-for-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, robust reinforcement learning (RL) methods designed to handle adversarial input observations have received significant attention, motivated by RL's inherent vulnerabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/off-policy-actor-critic-for-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cache Me If You Can: How Many KVs Do You Need for Effective Long-Context LMs?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cache-me-if-you-can-how-many-kvs-do-you-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the *KV footprint* as a unified metric, which accounts for both the amount of KV entries stored and their lifespan in memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cache-me-if-you-can-how-many-kvs-do-you-need</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Training-Test (Mis)alignment in Unsupervised Combinatorial Optimization: Observation, Empirical Exploration, and Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-training-test-mis-alignment-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In unsupervised combinatorial optimization (UCO), during training, one aims to have continuous decisions that are promising in a probabilistic sense for each training instance, which enables end-to-end training on initially discrete and non-differentiable problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-training-test-mis-alignment-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-term Traffic Simulation with Interleaved Autoregressive Motion and Scenario Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-term-traffic-simulation-with-interleaved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior models and benchmarks focus on closed-loop motion simulation for initial agents in a scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-term-traffic-simulation-with-interleaved</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
