<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 21:06:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DiffUTE: Universal Text Editing Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffute-universal-text-editing-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we build our model on a diffusion model and carefully modify the network structure to enable the model for drawing multilingual characters with the help of glyph and position information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffute-universal-text-editing-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FunASR: A Fundamental End-to-End Speech Recognition Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/funasr-a-fundamental-end-to-end-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FunASR offers models trained on large-scale industrial corpora and the ability to deploy them in applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/funasr-a-fundamental-end-to-end-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adjusting Logit in Gaussian Form for Long-Tailed Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjusting-logit-in-gaussian-form-for-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on these perturbed features, two novel logit adjustment methods are proposed to improve model performance at a modest computational overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjusting-logit-in-gaussian-form-for-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take a Break in the Middle: Investigating Subgoals towards Hierarchical Script Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-a-break-in-the-middle-investigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Goal-oriented Script Generation is a new task of generating a list of steps that can fulfill the given goal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-a-break-in-the-middle-investigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEPrompt: Task Enlightenment Prompt Learning for Implicit Discourse Relation Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teprompt-task-enlightenment-prompt-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although an auxiliary task is not used to directly output final prediction, we argue that during the joint training some of its learned features can be useful to boost the main task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teprompt-task-enlightenment-prompt-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextDiffuser: Diffusion Models as Text Painters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textdiffuser-diffusion-models-as-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have gained increasing attention for their impressive generation abilities but currently struggle with rendering accurate and coherent text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textdiffuser-diffusion-models-as-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLEME: Debiasing Multi-reference Evaluation for Grammatical Error Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cleme-debiasing-multi-reference-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed CLEME approach consistently and substantially outperforms existing reference-based GEC metrics on multiple reference sets in both corpus-level and sentence-level settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cleme-debiasing-multi-reference-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Off-Target Problem of Zero-Shot Multilingual Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-off-target-problem-of-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct experiments on a multilingual machine translation benchmark in 11 languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-off-target-problem-of-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Search Meets Recommendation: Learning Disentangled Search Representation for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-search-meets-recommendation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our paper, we propose a Search-Enhanced framework for the Sequential Recommendation (SESRec) that leverages users' search interests for recommendation, by disentangling similar and dissimilar representations within S&R behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-search-meets-recommendation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAPIR: Learning Adaptive Revision for Incremental Natural Language Understanding with a Two-Pass Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tapir-learning-adaptive-revision-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RNNs are fast but monotonic (cannot correct earlier output, which can be necessary in incremental processing).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tapir-learning-adaptive-revision-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiraBest: A Dataset of Morphologically Classified Radio Galaxies for Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mirabest-a-dataset-of-morphologically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing applications that utilise the MiraBest dataset are reviewed, and an extended dataset of 2100 sources is created by cross-matching MiraBest with other catalogues of radio-loud AGN that have been used more widely in the literature for machine learning applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mirabest-a-dataset-of-morphologically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Instruction Tasks Unlocks Large Language Models as Zero-Shot Relation Extractors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-instruction-tasks-unlocks-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work has shown that fine-tuning large language models (LLMs) on large-scale instruction-following datasets substantially improves their performance on a wide range of NLP tasks, especially in the zero-shot setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-instruction-tasks-unlocks-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StawGAN: Structural-Aware Generative Adversarial Networks for Infrared Image Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stawgan-structural-aware-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We test our model on aerial images of the DroneVeichle dataset containing RGB-IR paired images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stawgan-structural-aware-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PPDONet: Deep Operator Networks for Fast Prediction of Steady-State Solutions in Disk-Planet Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppdonet-deep-operator-networks-for-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a tool, which we name Protoplanetary Disk Operator Network (PPDONet), that can predict the solution of disk-planet interactions in protoplanetary disks in real-time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppdonet-deep-operator-networks-for-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacks on Online Learners: a Teacher-Student Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attacks-on-online-learners-a-teacher-student</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning models are famously vulnerable to adversarial attacks: small ad-hoc perturbations of the data that can catastrophically alter the model predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attacks-on-online-learners-a-teacher-student</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepEdit: Deep Editable Learning for Interactive Segmentation of 3D Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepedit-deep-editable-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic segmentation of medical images is a key step for diagnostic and interventional tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepedit-deep-editable-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STREAMLINE: Streaming Active Learning for Realistic Multi-Distributional Settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streamline-streaming-active-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, learning unbiased models depends on building a dataset that is representative of a diverse range of realistic scenarios for a given task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streamline-streaming-active-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature-Balanced Loss for Long-Tailed Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-balanced-loss-for-long-tailed-visual-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks frequently suffer from performance degradation when the training data is long-tailed because several majority classes dominate the training, resulting in a biased model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-balanced-loss-for-long-tailed-visual-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segment Any Anomaly without Training via Hybrid Prompt Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-any-anomaly-without-training-via-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel framework, i. e., Segment Any Anomaly + (SAA+), for zero-shot anomaly segmentation with hybrid prompt regularization to improve the adaptability of modern foundation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-any-anomaly-without-training-via-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scribble-Supervised Target Extraction Method Based on Inner Structure-Constraint for Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scribble-supervised-target-extraction-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly supervised learning based on scribble annotations in target extraction of remote sensing images has drawn much interest due to scribbles' flexibility in denoting winding objects and low cost of manually labeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scribble-supervised-target-extraction-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning In-context Learning for Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-in-context-learning-for-named-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[M}$, and a new entity extractor can be implicitly constructed by applying new instruction and demonstrations to PLMs, i. e., $\mathcal{ (\lambda .]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-in-context-learning-for-named-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-CrossRE A Multi-Lingual Multi-Domain Dataset for Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-crossre-a-multi-lingual-multi-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most research in Relation Extraction (RE) involves the English language, mainly due to the lack of multi-lingual resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-crossre-a-multi-lingual-multi-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QPGesture: Quantization-Based and Phase-Guided Motion Matching for Natural Speech-Driven Gesture Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qpgesture-quantization-based-and-phase-guided-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Levenshtein distance based on audio quantization as a similarity metric of corresponding speech of gestures helps match more appropriate gestures with speech, and solves the alignment problem of speech and gestures well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qpgesture-quantization-based-and-phase-guided-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-High Resolution Segmentation with Ultra-Rich Context: A Novel Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-high-resolution-segmentation-with-ultra-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increasing interest and rapid development of methods for Ultra-High Resolution (UHR) segmentation, a large-scale benchmark covering a wide range of scenes with full fine-grained dense annotations is urgently needed to facilitate the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-high-resolution-segmentation-with-ultra-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less Can Be More: Unsupervised Graph Pruning for Large-scale Dynamic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-can-be-more-unsupervised-graph-pruning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We approach the problem by our proposed STEP, a self-supervised temporal pruning framework that learns to remove potentially redundant edges from input dynamic graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-can-be-more-unsupervised-graph-pruning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackout Diffusion: Generative Diffusion Models in Discrete-State Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blackout-diffusion-generative-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalizing from specific (Gaussian) forward processes to discrete-state processes without a variational approximation sheds light on how to interpret diffusion models, which we discuss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blackout-diffusion-generative-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Pansharpening via Low-rank Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-pansharpening-via-low-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we assume that the HRMS image is decomposed into the product of two low-rank tensors, i. e., the base tensor and the coefficient matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-pansharpening-via-low-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Study on E-Branchformer vs Conformer in Speech Recognition, Translation, and Understanding Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-on-e-branchformer-vs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conformer, a convolution-augmented Transformer variant, has become the de facto encoder architecture for speech processing due to its superior performance in various tasks, including automatic speech recognition (ASR), speech translation (ST) and spoken language understanding (SLU).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-on-e-branchformer-vs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive State Augmentations for Reinforcement Learning-Based Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-state-augmentations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the second issue, we propose introducing contrastive signals between augmented states and the state randomly sampled from other sessions to improve the state representation learning further.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-state-augmentations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Graph Contrastive Learning for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-graph-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two generators are able to create adaptive contrastive views, addressing the problem of model collapse and achieving adaptive contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-graph-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMScore: Unveiling the Power of Large Language Models in Text-to-Image Synthesis Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmscore-unveiling-the-power-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing automatic evaluation on text-to-image synthesis can only provide an image-text matching score, without considering the object-level compositionality, which results in poor correlation with human judgments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmscore-unveiling-the-power-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silver Syntax Pre-training for Cross-Domain Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/silver-syntax-pre-training-for-cross-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the main reasons for this is the limited training size of current RE datasets: obtaining high-quality (manually annotated) data is extremely expensive and cannot realistically be repeated for each new domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/silver-syntax-pre-training-for-cross-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TrueTeacher: Learning Factual Consistency Evaluation with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trueteacher-learning-factual-consistency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using the the mFACE dataset, we also show that our method generalizes to multilingual scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trueteacher-learning-factual-consistency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BioAug: Conditional Generation based Data Augmentation for Low-Resource Biomedical NER</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bioaug-conditional-generation-based-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though data augmentation has shown to be highly effective for low-resource NER in general, existing data augmentation techniques fail to produce factual and diverse augmentations for BioNER.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bioaug-conditional-generation-based-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taxonomy Completion with Probabilistic Scorer via Box Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taxonomy-completion-with-probabilistic-scorer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, TaxBox consists of three components: (1) a graph aggregation module to leverage the structural information of the taxonomy and two lightweight decoders that map features to box embedding and capture complex relationships between concepts; (2) two probabilistic scorers that correspond to attachment and insertion operations and ensure the avoidance of pseudo-leaves; and (3) three learning objectives that assist the model in mapping concepts more granularly onto the box embedding space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taxonomy-completion-with-probabilistic-scorer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query Performance Prediction: From Ad-hoc to Conversational Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-performance-prediction-from-ad-hoc-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The QPP task is to predict the retrieval quality of a search system for a query without relevance judgments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-performance-prediction-from-ad-hoc-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making More of Little Data: Improving Low-Resource Automatic Speech Recognition Using Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-more-of-little-data-improving-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For Gronings, for which there was a pre-existing text-to-speech (TTS) system available, we also examined the use of TTS to generate ASR training data from text-only sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-more-of-little-data-improving-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpeechGPT: Empowering Large Language Models with Intrinsic Cross-Modal Conversational Abilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechgpt-empowering-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal large language models are regarded as a crucial step towards Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) and have garnered significant interest with the emergence of ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechgpt-empowering-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Time-Series Pre-Trained Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-time-series-pre-trained-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time-Series Mining (TSM) is an important research area since it shows great potential in practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-time-series-pre-trained-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual Event Extraction from Historical Newspaper Adverts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-event-extraction-from-historical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that: 1) even with scarce annotated data, it is possible to achieve surprisingly good results by formulating the problem as an extractive QA task and leveraging existing datasets and models for modern languages; and 2) cross-lingual low-resource learning for historical languages is highly challenging, and machine translation of the historical datasets to the considered target languages is, in practice, often the best-performing solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-event-extraction-from-historical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Adaptive Sim-to-Real Segmentation of Oropharyngeal Organs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-sim-to-real-segmentation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a domain adaptive Sim-to-Real framework called IoU-Ranking Blend-ArtFlow (IRB-AF) for image segmentation of oropharyngeal organs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-sim-to-real-segmentation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discourse Centric Evaluation of Machine Translation with a Densely Annotated Parallel Corpus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discourse-centric-evaluation-of-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several recent papers claim human parity at sentence-level Machine Translation (MT), especially in high-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discourse-centric-evaluation-of-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How does the task complexity of masked pretraining objectives affect downstream performance?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-does-the-task-complexity-of-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Masked language modeling (MLM) is a widely used self-supervised pretraining objective, where a model needs to predict an original token that is replaced with a mask given contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-does-the-task-complexity-of-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instruct2Act: Mapping Multi-modality Instructions to Robotic Actions with Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruct2act-mapping-multi-modality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents Instruct2Act, a framework that utilizes Large Language Models to map multi-modal instructions to sequential actions for robotic manipulation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruct2act-mapping-multi-modality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReGen: Zero-Shot Text Classification via Training Data Generation with Progressive Dense Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regen-zero-shot-text-classification-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the development of large language models (LLMs), zero-shot learning has attracted much attention for various NLP tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regen-zero-shot-text-classification-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A benchmark for computational analysis of animal behavior, using animal-borne tags</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-computational-analysis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Animal-borne sensors ('bio-loggers') can record a suite of kinematic and environmental data, which can elucidate animal ecophysiology and improve conservation efforts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-computational-analysis-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unbiased Gradient Boosting Decision Tree with Unbiased Feature Importance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-gradient-boosting-decision-tree-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we provide a fine-grained analysis of bias in GBDT and demonstrate that the bias originates from 1) the systematic bias in the gain estimation of each split and 2) the bias in the split finding algorithm resulting from the use of the same data to evaluate the split improvement and determine the best split.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-gradient-boosting-decision-tree-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-dimensional Asymptotics of Denoising Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-asymptotics-of-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the problem of denoising data from a Gaussian mixture using a two-layer non-linear autoencoder with tied weights and a skip connection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-asymptotics-of-denoising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE-PEACE: Exploring One General Representation Model Toward Unlimited Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-peace-exploring-one-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore a scalable way for building a general representation model toward unlimited modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-peace-exploring-one-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompting the Hidden Talent of Web-Scale Speech Models for Zero-Shot Task Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompting-the-hidden-talent-of-web-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the emergent abilities of the recently proposed web-scale speech model Whisper, by adapting it to unseen tasks with prompt engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompting-the-hidden-talent-of-web-scale</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
