<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:17:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>GLS: Geometry-aware 3D Language Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gls-geometry-aware-3d-language-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, 3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) has achieved significant performance on indoor surface reconstruction and open-vocabulary segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gls-geometry-aware-3d-language-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeneQuery: A General QA-based Framework for Spatial Gene Expression Predictions from Histology Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genequery-a-general-qa-based-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gene expression profiling provides profound insights into molecular mechanisms, but its time-consuming and costly nature often presents significant challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genequery-a-general-qa-based-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaVLN: Towards Visual Language Navigation in Continuous Indoor Environments with Moving Humans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adavln-towards-visual-language-navigation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Language Navigation is a task that challenges robots to navigate in realistic environments based on natural language instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adavln-towards-visual-language-navigation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isometry pursuit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isometry-pursuit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Isometry pursuit is a convex algorithm for identifying orthonormal column-submatrices of wide matrices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isometry-pursuit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoLLM Knows When to Speak: Enhancing Time-Sensitive Video Comprehension with Video-Text Duet Interaction Format</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videollm-knows-when-to-speak-enhancing-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We construct MMDuetIT, a video-text training dataset designed to adapt VideoLLMs to video-text duet interaction format.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videollm-knows-when-to-speak-enhancing-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Neural Networks Do Work with Pre-Defined Filters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-do-work-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel class of Convolutional Neural Networks called Pre-defined Filter Convolutional Neural Networks (PFCNNs), where all nxn convolution kernels with n>1 are pre-defined and constant during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-do-work-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Surface Priors for Editable Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-surface-priors-for-editable-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike other methods, our pipeline allows modifications applied to the extracted mesh to be propagated to the proxy representation, from which we recover the updated parameters of the Gaussians.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-surface-priors-for-editable-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUPE: Heuristic Underwater Perceptual Enhancement with Semantic Collaborative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hupe-heuristic-underwater-perceptual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To strike a balance between visual quality and application, we propose a heuristic invertible network for underwater perception enhancement, dubbed HUPE, which enhances visual quality and demonstrates flexibility in handling other downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hupe-heuristic-underwater-perceptual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Fourier-embedded Network for Bi-modal Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fourier-embedded-network-for-bi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of deep learning provides a significant improvement of salient object detection combining both RGB and thermal images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fourier-embedded-network-for-bi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Mamba Distillation for Low-resolution Fine-grained Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-mamba-distillation-for-low-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-resolution fine-grained image classification has recently made significant progress, largely thanks to the super-resolution techniques and knowledge distillation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-mamba-distillation-for-low-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RITA: Automatic Framework for Designing of Resilient IoT Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rita-automatic-framework-for-designing-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing resilient Internet of Things (IoT) systems requires i) identification of IoT Critical Objects (ICOs) such as services, devices, and resources, ii) threat analysis, and iii) mitigation strategy selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rita-automatic-framework-for-designing-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatRex: Taming Multimodal LLM for Joint Perception and Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatrex-taming-multimodal-llm-for-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From the data perspective, we build a fully automated data engine and construct the Rexverse-2M dataset which possesses multiple granularities to support the joint training of perception and understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatrex-taming-multimodal-llm-for-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Open Vocabulary to Open World: Teaching Vision Language Models to Detect Novel Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-open-vocabulary-to-open-world-teaching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address theses limitations, we propose a framework that enables OVD models to operate in open world settings, by identifying and incrementally learning novel objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-open-vocabulary-to-open-world-teaching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training and Evaluating Language Models with Template-based Data Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-evaluating-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we introduce Template-based Data Generation (TDG), a novel approach that leverages LLMs (GPT-4) to automatically generate parameterized meta-templates, which are then used to synthesize a vast array of high-quality problems and solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-evaluating-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing MMDiT-Based Text-to-Image Models for Similar Subject Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-mmdit-based-text-to-image-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant improvements, we observe that semantic ambiguity persists when generating multiple similar subjects, as the guidance provided by overlap loss is not explicit enough.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-mmdit-based-text-to-image-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveying the space of descriptions of a composite system with machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surveying-the-space-of-descriptions-of-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By integrating machine learning into a fine-grained information theoretic analysis of composite random variables, our framework opens a new avenues for probing the structure of real-world complex systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surveying-the-space-of-descriptions-of-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimeMarker: A Versatile Video-LLM for Long and Short Video Understanding with Superior Temporal Localization Ability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timemarker-a-versatile-video-llm-for-long-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rapid development of large language models (LLMs) has significantly advanced multimodal large language models (LMMs), particularly in vision-language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timemarker-a-versatile-video-llm-for-long-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Draft Model Knows When to Stop: A Self-Verification Length Policy for Speculative Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/draft-model-knows-when-to-stop-a-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speculative Decoding (SD) has become an important technique in accelerating the inference speed of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/draft-model-knows-when-to-stop-a-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectral-Spatial Transformer with Active Transfer Learning for Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-spatial-transformer-with-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a novel multi-stage active transfer learning (ATL) framework that integrates a Spatial-Spectral Transformer (SST) with an active learning process for efficient HSI classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-spatial-transformer-with-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SatVision-TOA: A Geospatial Foundation Model for Coarse-Resolution All-Sky Remote Sensing Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/satvision-toa-a-geospatial-foundation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work advances pre-trained vision modeling for multispectral RS by learning from a variety of atmospheric and aerosol conditions to improve cloud and land surface monitoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/satvision-toa-a-geospatial-foundation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PassionSR: Post-Training Quantization with Adaptive Scale in One-Step Diffusion based Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/passionsr-post-training-quantization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion-based image super-resolution (SR) models have shown superior performance at the cost of multiple denoising steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/passionsr-post-training-quantization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-MeshGraphNet: Scalable Multi-Scale Graph Neural Networks for Physics Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-meshgraphnet-scalable-multi-scale-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce X-MeshGraphNet, a scalable, multi-scale extension of MeshGraphNet designed to address these challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-meshgraphnet-scalable-multi-scale-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Hamiltonian neural networks without backpropagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-hamiltonian-neural-networks-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks that synergistically integrate data and physical laws offer great promise in modeling dynamical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-hamiltonian-neural-networks-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$H^3$Fusion: Helpful, Harmless, Honest Fusion of Aligned LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h-3-fusion-helpful-harmless-honest-fusion-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The former penalizes the selection errors of the expert-router, and the latter mediates the expert weights drifting during fine-tuning and dynamically adjusts the fusion behavior of the resulting model by canalizing the activations on the experts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h-3-fusion-helpful-harmless-honest-fusion-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P2DFlow: A Protein Ensemble Generative Model with SE(3) Flow Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p2dflow-a-protein-ensemble-generative-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Biological processes, functions, and properties are intricately linked to the ensemble of protein conformations, rather than being solely determined by a single stable conformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p2dflow-a-protein-ensemble-generative-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongKey: Keyphrase Extraction for Long Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longkey-keyphrase-extraction-for-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an era of information overload, manually annotating the vast and growing corpus of documents and scholarly papers is increasingly impractical.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longkey-keyphrase-extraction-for-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Imbalance Learning: A Novel Slack-Factor Fuzzy SVM Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-imbalance-learning-a-novel-slack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In real-world applications, class-imbalanced datasets pose significant challenges for machine learning algorithms, such as support vector machines (SVMs), particularly in effectively managing imbalance, noise, and outliers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-imbalance-learning-a-novel-slack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Networks Use Distance Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-use-distance-metrics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present empirical evidence that neural networks with ReLU and Absolute Value activations learn distance-based representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-use-distance-metrics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Different Bias Under Different Criteria: Assessing Bias in LLMs with a Fact-Based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/different-bias-under-different-criteria</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) often reflect real-world biases, leading to efforts to mitigate these effects and make the models unbiased.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/different-bias-under-different-criteria</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Large Language Models and Topic Modeling for Toxicity Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-large-language-models-and-topic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Content moderation and toxicity classification represent critical tasks with significant social implications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-large-language-models-and-topic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Efficiency of NLP-Inspired Methods for Tabular Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-efficiency-of-nlp-inspired-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in tabular deep learning (DL) have led to substantial performance improvements, surpassing the capabilities of traditional models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-efficiency-of-nlp-inspired-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linguistic Laws Meet Protein Sequences: A Comparative Analysis of Subword Tokenization Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linguistic-laws-meet-protein-sequences-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These findings highlight the limitations of applying traditional NLP tokenization methods to protein sequences and emphasize the need for developing specialized tokenization strategies that better account for the unique characteristics of proteins.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linguistic-laws-meet-protein-sequences-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Preserving Federated Unsupervised Domain Adaptation with Application to Age Prediction from DNA Methylation Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-federated-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our framework on the task of age prediction using DNA methylation data from multiple tissues, demonstrating that our approach performs comparably to existing centralized methods while maintaining data privacy, even in distributed environments where data is spread across multiple institutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-federated-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Extractive-Abstractive Spectrum: Uncovering Verifiability Trade-offs in LLM Generations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-extractive-abstractive-spectrum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLMs are abstractive because they address queries with answers that synthesize and logically transform relevant information from training and in-context sources without reliable citation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-extractive-abstractive-spectrum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relations, Negations, and Numbers: Looking for Logic in Generative Text-to-Image Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relations-negations-and-numbers-looking-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We asked human respondents (N=178 in total) to evaluate images generated by a state-of-the-art image-generating AI (DALL-E 3) prompted with these `logical probes', and find that none reliably produce human agreement scores greater than 50\%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relations-negations-and-numbers-looking-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Noisy Labels via Conditional Distributionally Robust Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-noisy-labels-via-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, to devise an efficient algorithm for CDRO, we derive a closed-form expression for the empirical robust risk and the optimal Lagrange multiplier of the dual problem, facilitating a principled balance between robustness and model fitting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-noisy-labels-via-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StableAnimator: High-Quality Identity-Preserving Human Image Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stableanimator-high-quality-identity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During inference, we propose a novel Hamilton-Jacobi-Bellman (HJB) equation-based optimization to further enhance the face quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stableanimator-high-quality-identity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isotropy Matters: Soft-ZCA Whitening of Embeddings for Semantic Code Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isotropy-matters-soft-zca-whitening-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low isotropy in an embedding space impairs performance on tasks involving semantic inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isotropy-matters-soft-zca-whitening-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training a neural netwok for data reduction and better generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-a-neural-netwok-for-data-reduction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The motivation for sparse learners is to compress the inputs (features) by selecting only the ones needed for good generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-a-neural-netwok-for-data-reduction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correlation-Aware Graph Convolutional Networks for Multi-Label Node Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-aware-graph-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-label node classification is an important yet under-explored domain in graph mining as many real-world nodes belong to multiple categories rather than just a single one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-aware-graph-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DreamMix: Decoupling Object Attributes for Enhanced Editability in Customized Image Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreammix-decoupling-object-attributes-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate that DreamMix effectively balances identity preservation and attribute editability across various application scenarios, including object insertion, attribute editing, and small object inpainting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreammix-decoupling-object-attributes-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WF-VAE: Enhancing Video VAE by Wavelet-Driven Energy Flow for Latent Video Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wf-vae-enhancing-video-vae-by-wavelet-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, as the resolution and duration of generated videos increase, the encoding cost of Video VAEs becomes a limiting bottleneck in training LVDMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wf-vae-enhancing-video-vae-by-wavelet-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Path-RAG: Knowledge-Guided Key Region Retrieval for Open-ended Pathology Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/path-rag-knowledge-guided-key-region</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Admitting the complexity of pathology image analysis, Path-RAG adopts a human-centered AI approach by retrieving domain knowledge using HistoCartography to select the relevant patches from pathology images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/path-rag-knowledge-guided-key-region</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GrokFormer: Graph Fourier Kolmogorov-Arnold Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grokformer-graph-fourier-kolmogorov-arnold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GrokFormer leverages learnable activation functions in order-$K$ graph spectrum through Fourier series modeling to i) learn eigenvalue-targeted filter functions producing learnable base that can capture a broad range of frequency signals flexibly, and ii) extract first- and higher-order graph spectral information adaptively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grokformer-graph-fourier-kolmogorov-arnold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2D Matryoshka Training for Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2d-matryoshka-training-for-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this reproducibility study, we implement and evaluate both versions of 2D Matryoshka Training on STS tasks and extend our analysis to retrieval tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2d-matryoshka-training-for-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-aware Evolutionary Graph Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-aware-evolutionary-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[According to the predicted metrics, non-dominated candidate transfer architectures are selected to warm-start the multi-objective evolutionary algorithm for optimizing the #Acc and #Params on a new dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-aware-evolutionary-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIGV-Assessor: Benchmarking and Evaluating the Perceptual Quality of Text-to-Video Generation with LMM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aigv-assessor-benchmarking-and-evaluating-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of large multimodal models (LMMs) has led to the rapid expansion of artificial intelligence generated videos (AIGVs), which highlights the pressing need for effective video quality assessment (VQA) models designed specifically for AIGVs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aigv-assessor-benchmarking-and-evaluating-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Explainable Treatment Policies with Clinician-Informed Representations: A Practical Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-explainable-treatment-policies-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our main contribution is to reveal the importance of clinical domain knowledge in developing state and action representations for effective, efficient, and interpretable targeting policies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-explainable-treatment-policies-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoA: Chain-of-Action for Generative Semantic Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coa-chain-of-action-for-generative-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These VLMs leverage a predefined set of categories to construct text prompts for zero-shot reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coa-chain-of-action-for-generative-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShowUI: One Vision-Language-Action Model for GUI Visual Agent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/showui-one-vision-language-action-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop a vision-language-action model in digital world, namely ShowUI, which features the following innovations: (i) UI-Guided Visual Token Selection to reduce computational costs by formulating screenshots as an UI connected graph, adaptively identifying their redundant relationship and serve as the criteria for token selection during self-attention blocks; (ii) Interleaved Vision-Language-Action Streaming that flexibly unifies diverse needs within GUI tasks, enabling effective management of visual-action history in navigation or pairing multi-turn query-action sequences per screenshot to enhance training efficiency; (iii) Small-scale High-quality GUI Instruction-following Datasets by careful data curation and employing a resampling strategy to address significant data type imbalances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/showui-one-vision-language-action-model-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
