<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 21:07:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Prediction Neural Network (UpNet): Embedding Artificial Neural Network in Bayesian Inversion Framework to Quantify the Uncertainty of Remote Sensing Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-prediction-neural-network-upnet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It has been widely used in the retrieval of biophysical variables (BV).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-prediction-neural-network-upnet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACCIO: Table Understanding Enhanced via Contrastive Learning with Aggregations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accio-table-understanding-enhanced-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With this idea, in this paper, we introduce ACCIO, tAble understanding enhanCed via Contrastive learnIng with aggregatiOns, a novel approach to enhancing table understanding by contrasting original tables with their pivot summaries through contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accio-table-understanding-enhanced-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Abnormal Stop Detection for Long Distance Coaches with Low-Frequency GPS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-abnormal-stop-detection-for-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an unsupervised method that helps transportation managers to efficiently discover the Abnormal Stop Detection (ASD) for long distance coaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-abnormal-stop-detection-for-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FASSILA: A Corpus for Algerian Dialect Fake News Detection and Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fassila-a-corpus-for-algerian-dialect-fake</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of low-resource languages, the Algerian dialect (AD) faces challenges due to the absence of annotated corpora, hindering its effective processing, notably in Machine Learning (ML) applications reliant on corpora for training and assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fassila-a-corpus-for-algerian-dialect-fake</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think Smart, Act SMARL! Analyzing Probabilistic Logic Driven Safety in Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/think-smart-act-smarl-analyzing-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An important challenge for enabling the deployment of reinforcement learning (RL) algorithms in the real world is safety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/think-smart-act-smarl-analyzing-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating the Influence of Sequentially Correlated Literary Properties in Textual Classification: A Data-Centric Hypothesis-Testing Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-the-influence-of-sequentially</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a hypothesis-testing approach to evaluate the influence of sequentially correlated literary properties on text classification, aiming to determine when these correlations drive classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-the-influence-of-sequentially</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Trust in Clinically Significant Prostate Cancer Prediction with Multiple Magnetic Resonance Imaging Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-trust-in-clinically-significant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their high performance, these models are not trusted by most clinical scientists as they are trained solely on a single modality whereas clinical scientists often use multiple magnetic resonance imaging modalities during their diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-trust-in-clinically-significant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TexLiverNet: Leveraging Medical Knowledge and Spatial-Frequency Perception for Enhanced Liver Tumor Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texlivernet-leveraging-medical-knowledge-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Integrating textual data with imaging in liver tumor segmentation is essential for enhancing diagnostic accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texlivernet-leveraging-medical-knowledge-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneProt: Towards Multi-Modal Protein Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oneprot-towards-multi-modal-protein</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent AI advances have enabled multi-modal systems to model and translate diverse information spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oneprot-towards-multi-modal-protein</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt-Guided Internal States for Hallucination Detection of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-guided-internal-states-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By utilizing appropriate prompts to guide changes in the structure related to text truthfulness within the LLM's internal states, we make this structure more salient and consistent across texts from different domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-guided-internal-states-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subspace-Constrained Quadratic Matrix Factorization: Algorithm and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subspace-constrained-quadratic-matrix</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Theoretical properties of the quadratic projection problem and convergence characteristics of the alternating strategy are also investigated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subspace-constrained-quadratic-matrix</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPGD: Steepest Perturbed Gradient Descent Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spgd-steepest-perturbed-gradient-descent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimization algorithms are pivotal in advancing various scientific and industrial fields but often encounter obstacles such as trapping in local minima, saddle points, and plateaus (flat regions), which makes the convergence to reasonable or near-optimal solutions particularly challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spgd-steepest-perturbed-gradient-descent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightning IR: Straightforward Fine-tuning and Inference of Transformer-based Language Models for Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightning-ir-straightforward-fine-tuning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A wide range of transformer-based language models have been proposed for information retrieval tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightning-ir-straightforward-fine-tuning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanos: Enhancing Conversational Agents with Skill-of-Mind-Infused Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thanos-enhancing-conversational-agents-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To increase social bonding with interlocutors, humans naturally acquire the ability to respond appropriately in a given situation by considering which conversational skill is most suitable for the response - a process we call skill-of-mind.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thanos-enhancing-conversational-agents-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DomainGallery: Few-shot Domain-driven Image Generation by Attribute-centric Finetuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domaingallery-few-shot-domain-driven-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent progress in text-to-image models pretrained on large-scale datasets has enabled us to generate various images as long as we provide a text prompt describing what we want.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domaingallery-few-shot-domain-driven-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Strong Lottery Ticket Networks with Genetic Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-strong-lottery-ticket-networks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[According to the Strong Lottery Ticket Hypothesis, every sufficiently large neural network with randomly initialized weights contains a sub-network which - still with its random weights - already performs as well for a given task as the trained super-network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-strong-lottery-ticket-networks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain Tumour Removing and Missing Modality Generation using 3D WDM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-tumour-removing-and-missing-modality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the inpainting task of BraTS 2024, the use of a large and variable number of healthy masks and the stability and efficiency of the 3D wavelet diffusion model resulted in 0. 007, 22. 61 and 0. 842 in the validation set and 0. 07 , 22. 8 and 0. 91 in the testing set (MSE, PSNR and SSIM respectively).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-tumour-removing-and-missing-modality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVDQunat: Absorbing Outliers by Low-Rank Components for 4-Bit Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svdqunat-absorbing-outliers-by-low-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we co-design an inference engine Nunchaku that fuses the kernels of the low-rank branch into those of the low-bit branch to cut off redundant memory access.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svdqunat-absorbing-outliers-by-low-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuroFly: A framework for whole-brain single neuron reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurofly-a-framework-for-whole-brain-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we introduce NeuroFly, a validated framework for large-scale automatic single neuron reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurofly-a-framework-for-whole-brain-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One fish, two fish, but not the whole sea: Alignment reduces language models' conceptual diversity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-fish-two-fish-but-not-the-whole-sea</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers in social science and psychology have recently proposed using large language models (LLMs) as replacements for humans in behavioral research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-fish-two-fish-but-not-the-whole-sea</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming Rectified Flow for Inversion and Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-rectified-flow-for-inversion-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rectified-flow-based diffusion transformers, such as FLUX and OpenSora, have demonstrated exceptional performance in the field of image and video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-rectified-flow-for-inversion-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Bradley-Terry Models in Preference-Based Reward Modeling: Foundations, Theory, and Alternatives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-bradley-terry-models-in-preference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Bradley-Terry (BT) model is a common and successful practice in reward modeling for Large Language Model (LLM) alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-bradley-terry-models-in-preference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZAHA: Introducing the Level of Facade Generalization and the Large-Scale Point Cloud Facade Semantic Segmentation Benchmark Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zaha-introducing-the-level-of-facade</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facade semantic segmentation is a long-standing challenge in photogrammetry and computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zaha-introducing-the-level-of-facade</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soft Hoeffding Tree: A Transparent and Differentiable Model on Data Streams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soft-hoeffding-tree-a-transparent-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose soft Hoeffding trees (SoHoT) as a new differentiable and transparent model for possibly infinite and changing data streams.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soft-hoeffding-tree-a-transparent-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Graph Attention Networks with Structural Motifs for Predicting Cell Line-Specific Synergistic Drug Combinations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-graph-attention-networks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, I believe that the proposed equivariant geometric deep learning framework serves as an effective tool for virtually screening anticancer drug combinations for further validation in a wet lab environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-graph-attention-networks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peri-midFormer: Periodic Pyramid Transformer for Time Series Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peri-midformer-periodic-pyramid-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to break through the limitations of the previous methods, we decouple the implied complex periodic variations into inclusion and overlap relationships among different level periodic components based on the observation of the multi-periodicity therein and its inclusion relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peri-midformer-periodic-pyramid-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centrality Graph Shift Operators for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centrality-graph-shift-operators-for-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Shift Operators (GSOs), such as the adjacency and graph Laplacian matrices, play a fundamental role in graph theory and graph representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centrality-graph-shift-operators-for-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Low-Rank Adaptation Using IVON</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-low-rank-adaptation-using-ivon</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We replace AdamW by the Improved Variational Online Newton (IVON) algorithm to finetune large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-low-rank-adaptation-using-ivon</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conjugate gradient methods for high-dimensional GLMMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conjugate-gradient-methods-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalized linear mixed models (GLMMs) are a widely used tool in statistical analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conjugate-gradient-methods-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust and Efficient Fine-tuning of LLMs with Bayesian Reparameterization of Low-Rank Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-and-efficient-fine-tuning-of-llms-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are highly resource-intensive to fine-tune due to their enormous size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-and-efficient-fine-tuning-of-llms-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Reasoning Improves Tool Use in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-reasoning-improves-tool-use-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Tool selECTion via meta-reasONing (TECTON), a two-phase system that first reasons over a task using a custom fine-tuned LM head and outputs candidate tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-reasoning-improves-tool-use-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>wav2sleep: A Unified Multi-Modal Approach to Sleep Stage Classification from Physiological Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wav2sleep-a-unified-multi-modal-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing approaches to this problem have typically used deep learning models designed and trained to operate on one or more specific input signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wav2sleep-a-unified-multi-modal-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELIFT: Data Efficient Language model Instruction Fine Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delift-data-efficient-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning large language models (LLMs) is essential for enhancing their performance on specific tasks but is often resource-intensive due to redundant or uninformative data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delift-data-efficient-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM2CLIP: Powerful Language Model Unlock Richer Visual Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm2clip-powerful-language-model-unlock</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose LLM2CLIP, a novel approach that embraces the power of LLMs to unlock CLIP's potential.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm2clip-powerful-language-model-unlock</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IGDrivSim: A Benchmark for the Imitation Gap in Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/igdrivsim-a-benchmark-for-the-imitation-gap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce \textbf{IGDrivSim}, a benchmark built on top of the Waymax simulator, designed to investigate the effects of the imitation gap in learning autonomous driving policy from human expert demonstrations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/igdrivsim-a-benchmark-for-the-imitation-gap</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noisy Zero-Shot Coordination: Breaking The Common Knowledge Assumption In Zero-Shot Coordination Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisy-zero-shot-coordination-breaking-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that with NZSC training, RL agents can be trained to coordinate well with novel partners even when the (exact) problem setting of the coordination is not common knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisy-zero-shot-coordination-breaking-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Semantic Hub Hypothesis: Language Models Share Semantic Representations Across Languages and Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-semantic-hub-hypothesis-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hypothesize that models acquire this capability through learning a shared representation space across heterogeneous data types (e. g., different languages and modalities), which places semantically similar inputs near one another, even if they are from different modalities/languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-semantic-hub-hypothesis-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring short-form factuality in large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-short-form-factuality-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SimpleQA, a benchmark that evaluates the ability of language models to answer short, fact-seeking questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-short-form-factuality-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Calibration of Win Rate Estimation with LLM Evaluators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-calibration-of-win-rate-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in large language models (LLMs) show the potential of using LLMs as evaluators for assessing the quality of text generations from LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-calibration-of-win-rate-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Euclidean Mixture Model for Social Network Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-euclidean-mixture-model-for-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We call this model Non-Euclidean Mixture Model, i. e., NMM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-euclidean-mixture-model-for-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVSplat360: Feed-Forward 360 Scene Synthesis from Sparse Views</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvsplat360-feed-forward-360-scene-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate MVSplat360's performance, we introduce a new benchmark using the challenging DL3DV-10K dataset, where MVSplat360 achieves superior visual quality compared to state-of-the-art methods on wide-sweeping or even 360{\deg} NVS tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvsplat360-feed-forward-360-scene-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Differentiable Logic Gate Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-differentiable-logic-gate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increasing inference cost of machine learning models, there is a growing interest in models with fast and efficient inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-differentiable-logic-gate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Trade-offs: Policy Summarization for Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-trade-offs-policy-summarization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the solution set is typically large and multi-dimensional, where each policy (e. g., a neural network) is represented by its objective values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-trade-offs-policy-summarization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Aware Resource Management for C-V2X Platooning via Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-resource-management-for-c-v2x</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed approach leverages the semantic information to optimize the allocation of communication resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-resource-management-for-c-v2x</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Higher-Order GNNs Meet Efficiency: Sparse Sobolev Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/higher-order-gnns-meet-efficiency-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This observation has significant implications for capturing higher-order information in GNNs for various tasks such as node classification and semi-supervised learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/higher-order-gnns-meet-efficiency-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Multi-Task Brain Tumour Segmentation with Synthetic Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-multi-task-brain-tumour-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The use of automated tools in clinical practice has increased due to the development of more and more sophisticated and reliable algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-multi-task-brain-tumour-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Unifying Interpretability and Control: Evaluation via Intervention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-unifying-interpretability-and-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce two new evaluation metrics: intervention success rate and the coherence-intervention tradeoff, designed to measure the accuracy of explanations and their utility in controlling model behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-unifying-interpretability-and-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social EgoMesh Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-egomesh-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurately estimating the 3D pose of the camera wearer in egocentric video sequences is crucial to modeling human behavior in virtual and augmented reality applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-egomesh-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Impact of Semi-Supervised Learning on Line Segment Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-impact-of-semi-supervised-learning-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present a method for line segment detection in images, based on a semi-supervised framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-impact-of-semi-supervised-learning-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention Masks Help Adversarial Attacks to Bypass Safety Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-masks-help-adversarial-attacks-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent research advancements in adversarial attack methods, current approaches against XAI monitors are still discoverable and slower.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-masks-help-adversarial-attacks-to</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
