<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 09:12:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Spectral Efficiency Analysis of Uplink-Downlink Decoupled Access in C-V2X Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-efficiency-analysis-of-uplink</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The uplink (UL)/downlink (DL) decoupled access has been emerging as a novel access architecture to improve the performance gains in cellular networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-efficiency-analysis-of-uplink</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointCaM: Cut-and-Mix for Open-Set Point Cloud Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointcam-cut-and-mix-for-open-set-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we use the Unknown-Point Simulator to simulate unknown data in the training stage by manipulating the geometric context of partial known data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointcam-cut-and-mix-for-open-set-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Stroke-Level Modifications for Scene Text Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-stroke-level-modifications-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, two new datasets (Tamper-Syn2k and Tamper-Scene) are proposed to fill the blank of public evaluation datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-stroke-level-modifications-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Observational and Interventional Causal Learning for Regret-Minimizing Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/observational-and-interventional-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A state-of-the-art observational causal discovery algorithm for time series capable of handling latent confounders and contemporaneous effects, called LPCMCI, is extended to profit from casual constraints found through randomized control trials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/observational-and-interventional-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TD3 with Reverse KL Regularizer for Offline Reinforcement Learning from Mixed Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/td3-with-reverse-kl-regularizer-for-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are two challenges for this setting: 1) The optimal trade-off between optimizing the RL signal and the behavior cloning (BC) signal changes on different states due to the variation of the action coverage induced by different behavior policies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/td3-with-reverse-kl-regularizer-for-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query Your Model with Definitions in FrameNet: An Effective Method for Frame Semantic Role Labeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-your-model-with-definitions-in-framenet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such methods usually model role classification as naive multi-class classification and treat arguments individually, which neglects label semantics and interactions between arguments and thus hindering performance and generalization of models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-your-model-with-definitions-in-framenet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Neural Topic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-neural-topic-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the last years, topic modeling has emerged as a powerful technique for organizing and summarizing big collections of documents or searching for particular patterns in them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-neural-topic-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Imbalanced Data with Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-imbalanced-data-with-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we systematically investigate the ViTs' performance in LTR and propose LiVT to train ViTs from scratch only with LT data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-imbalanced-data-with-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoding natural image stimuli from fMRI data with a surface-based convolutional network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-natural-image-stimuli-from-fmri-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel approach for this task, which we call Cortex2Image, to decode visual stimuli with high semantic fidelity and rich fine-grained detail.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-natural-image-stimuli-from-fmri-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An iterative unbiased geometric approach to identifying crystalline order and disorder via denoising score function model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-iterative-unbiased-geometric-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In atomistic simulations of solids, ability to classify crystal phases and lattice defects in the presence of thermal fluctuations is essential for gaining deeper insights into the simulated dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-iterative-unbiased-geometric-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L2SR: Learning to Sample and Reconstruct for Accelerated MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l2sr-learning-to-sample-and-reconstruct-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accelerated MRI aims to find a pair of samplers and reconstructors to reduce acquisition time while maintaining the reconstruction quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l2sr-learning-to-sample-and-reconstruct-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Images Speak in Images: A Generalist Painter for In-Context Visual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/images-speak-in-images-a-generalist-painter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Painter, a generalist model which addresses these obstacles with an "image"-centric solution, that is, to redefine the output of core vision tasks as images, and specify task prompts as also images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/images-speak-in-images-a-generalist-painter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissimilar Nodes Improve Graph Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dissimilar-nodes-improve-graph-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The existing Active Graph Embedding framework proposes to use centrality score, density score, and entropy score to evaluate the value of unlabeled nodes, and it has been shown to be capable of bringing some improvement to the node classification tasks of Graph Convolutional Networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dissimilar-nodes-improve-graph-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SASFormer: Transformers for Sparsely Annotated Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sasformer-transformers-for-sparsely-annotated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a simple yet effective sparse annotated semantic segmentation framework based on segformer, dubbed SASFormer, that achieves remarkable performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sasformer-transformers-for-sparsely-annotated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact of Domain-Adapted Multilingual Neural Machine Translation in the Medical Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-domain-adapted-multilingual-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multilingual Neural Machine Translation (MNMT) models leverage many language pairs during training to improve translation quality for low-resource languages by transferring knowledge from high-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-domain-adapted-multilingual-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Contrast for Unsupervised Skeleton-based Action Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-contrast-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper targets unsupervised skeleton-based action representation learning and proposes a new Hierarchical Contrast (HiCo) framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-contrast-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaceQAN: Face Image Quality Assessment Through Adversarial Noise Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faceqan-face-image-quality-assessment-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach to face image quality assessment, called FaceQAN, that is based on adversarial examples and relies on the analysis of adversarial noise which can be calculated with any FR model learned by using some form of gradient descent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faceqan-face-image-quality-assessment-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Location-Aware Self-Supervised Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/location-aware-self-supervised-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose to pretrain networks for semantic segmentation by predicting the relative location of image parts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/location-aware-self-supervised-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MapInWild: A Remote Sensing Dataset to Address the Question What Makes Nature Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapinwild-a-remote-sensing-dataset-to-address</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Antrophonegic pressure (i. e. human influence) on the environment is one of the largest causes of the loss of biological diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapinwild-a-remote-sensing-dataset-to-address</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certifying Fairness of Probabilistic Circuits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certifying-fairness-of-probabilistic-circuits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an algorithm to search for discrimination patterns in a general class of probabilistic models, namely probabilistic circuits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certifying-fairness-of-probabilistic-circuits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Momentum Decoding: Open-ended Text Generation As Graph Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/momentum-decoding-open-ended-text-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we formulate open-ended text generation from a new perspective, i. e., we view it as an exploration process within a directed graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/momentum-decoding-open-ended-text-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving the Weather4cast Challenge via Visual Transformers for 3D Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-the-weather4cast-challenge-via-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurately forecasting the weather is an important task, as many real-world processes and decisions depend on future meteorological conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-the-weather4cast-challenge-via-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Med-Query: Steerable Parsing of 9-DoF Medical Anatomies with Query Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/med-query-steerable-parsing-of-9-dof-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For rib parsing, CT scans have been annotated at the rib instance-level for quantitative evaluation, similarly for spine vertebrae and abdominal organs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/med-query-steerable-parsing-of-9-dof-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LE-UDA: Label-efficient unsupervised domain adaptation for medical image segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/le-uda-label-efficient-unsupervised-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To assess the effectiveness of our method, we conduct extensive experiments on two different tasks for cross-modality segmentation between MRI and CT images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/le-uda-label-efficient-unsupervised-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Window Normalization: Enhancing Point Cloud Understanding by Unifying Inconsistent Point Densities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/window-normalization-enhancing-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods are limited by the inconsistent point densities of different parts in the point cloud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/window-normalization-enhancing-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning Architectures for FSCV, a Comparison</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-architectures-for-fscv-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We examined multiple deep neural network (DNN) architectures for suitability in predicting neurotransmitter concentrations from labeled in vitro fast scan cyclic voltammetry (FSCV) data collected on carbon fiber electrodes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-architectures-for-fscv-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval as Attention: End-to-end Learning of Retrieval and Reading within a Single Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-as-attention-end-to-end-learning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Systems for knowledge-intensive tasks such as open-domain question answering (QA) usually consist of two stages: efficient retrieval of relevant documents from a large corpus and detailed reading of the selected documents to generate answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-as-attention-end-to-end-learning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNN-SL: Sequence Labeling Based on Nearest Examples via GNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnn-sl-sequence-labeling-based-on-nearest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better handle long-tail cases in the sequence labeling (SL) task, in this work, we introduce graph neural networks sequence labeling (GNN-SL), which augments the vanilla SL model output with similar tagging examples retrieved from the whole training set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnn-sl-sequence-labeling-based-on-nearest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RLogist: Fast Observation Strategy on Whole-slide Images with Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlogist-fast-observation-strategy-on-whole</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most of the existing methods rely on a multiple instance learning framework that requires densely sampling local patches at high magnification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlogist-fast-observation-strategy-on-whole</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pair-Based Joint Encoding with Relational Graph Convolutional Networks for Emotion-Cause Pair Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pair-based-joint-encoding-with-relational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Emotion-cause pair extraction (ECPE) aims to extract emotion clauses and corresponding cause clauses, which have recently received growing attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pair-based-joint-encoding-with-relational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-aware multi-head self-attentional neural network model for next location prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-multi-head-self-attentional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate activity location prediction is a crucial component of many mobility applications and is particularly required to develop personalized, sustainable transportation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-multi-head-self-attentional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain Tumor Synthetic Data Generation with Adaptive StyleGANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-tumor-synthetic-data-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the model can generate high-quality synthetic brain MRI with a tumor that can limit the small sample size issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-tumor-synthetic-data-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Lightweight Scene Regressor for Camera Relocalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-lightweight-scene-regressor-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed approach uses sparse descriptors to regress the scene coordinates, instead of a dense RGB image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-lightweight-scene-regressor-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melody transcription via generative pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melody-transcription-via-generative-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The combination of generative pre-training and a new dataset for this task results in $77$% stronger performance on melody transcription relative to the strongest available baseline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melody-transcription-via-generative-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint graph learning from Gaussian observations in the presence of hidden nodes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-graph-learning-from-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, we propose a joint graph learning method that takes into account the presence of hidden (latent) variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-graph-learning-from-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constructing Highly Inductive Contexts for Dialogue Safety through Controllable Reverse Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-highly-inductive-contexts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to detect such toxic generations, existing methods rely on templates, real-world data extraction, crowdsourcing workers, or automatic generation to construct adversarial contexts that are likely to induce toxic generations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-highly-inductive-contexts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphGDP: Generative Diffusion Processes for Permutation Invariant Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphgdp-generative-diffusion-processes-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph generative models have broad applications in biology, chemistry and social science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphgdp-generative-diffusion-processes-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automata Learning meets Shielding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automata-learning-meets-shielding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Iteratively, we use the collected data to learn new MDPs with higher accuracy, resulting in turn in shields able to prevent more safety violations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automata-learning-meets-shielding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label Encoding for Regression Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-encoding-for-regression-networks-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior work has shown that solving a regression problem with a set of binary classifiers can improve accuracy by utilizing well-studied binary classification algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-encoding-for-regression-networks-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-lingual Similarity of Multilingual Representations Revisited</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-similarity-of-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Related works used indexes like CKA and variants of CCA to measure the similarity of cross-lingual representations in multilingual language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-similarity-of-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iEnhancer-ELM: Improve Enhancer Identification by Extracting Multi-scale Contextual Information based on Enhancer Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ienhancer-elm-improve-enhancer-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results: In this paper, we propose a multi-scale enhancer identification method (iEnhancer-ELM) based on enhancer language models, which treat enhancer sequences as natural language sentences that are composed of k-mer nucleotides.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ienhancer-elm-improve-enhancer-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Stochastic Autoregressive Image Modeling for Visual Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-stochastic-autoregressive-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By introducing stochastic prediction and the parallel encoder-decoder, SAIM significantly improve the performance of autoregressive image modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-stochastic-autoregressive-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calibration and generalizability of probabilistic models on low-data chemical datasets with DIONYSUS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibration-and-generalizability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning models that leverage large datasets are often the state of the art for modelling molecular properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibration-and-generalizability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laplacian Convolutional Representation for Traffic Time Series Imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplacian-convolutional-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To make an accurate reconstruction on partially observed traffic data, we assert the importance of characterizing both global and local trends in traffic time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplacian-convolutional-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approximate Message Passing for Multi-Layer Estimation in Rotationally Invariant Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximate-message-passing-for-multi-layer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of reconstructing the signal and the hidden variables from observations coming from a multi-layer network with rotationally invariant weight matrices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximate-message-passing-for-multi-layer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoTMix: Contrastive Domain Adaptation for Time-Series via Temporal Mixup</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cotmix-contrastive-domain-adaptation-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a novel temporal mixup strategy to generate two intermediate augmented views for the source and target domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cotmix-contrastive-domain-adaptation-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-driven Mobile Apps: an Explorative Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-driven-mobile-apps-an-explorative-study</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we conduct the most extensive empirical study on 56, 682 published AI apps from three perspectives: dataset characteristics, development issues, and user feedback and privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-driven-mobile-apps-an-explorative-study</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Question Answering From Another Perspective: CLEVR Mental Rotation Tests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-question-answering-from-another-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different types of mental rotation tests have been used extensively in psychology to understand human visual reasoning and perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-question-answering-from-another-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Generalized Scalarization Method for Evolutionary Multi-objective Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generalized-scalarization-method-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze how GR can no longer avoid mismatches when $L_{\infty}$ is replaced by another $L_{p}$ with $p\in [1,\infty)$, and find that the $L_p$-based ($1\leq p<\infty$) subproblems having inconsistently large preference regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generalized-scalarization-method-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Euler Characteristic Curves and Profiles: a stable shape invariant for big data problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/euler-characteristic-curves-and-profiles-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While being a weaker invariant in one dimension, we show that Euler Characteristic based approaches do not possess some handicaps of persistent homology; we show efficient algorithms to compute them in a distributed way, their generalization to multifiltrations and practical applicability for big data problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/euler-characteristic-curves-and-profiles-a</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
