<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:06:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Semi-supervised Learning for Underwater Image Restoration via Reliable Bank</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-semi-supervised-learning-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the remarkable achievement of recent underwater image restoration techniques, the lack of labeled data has become a major hurdle for further progress.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-semi-supervised-learning-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Framework for Real-time Object Detection and Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-real-time-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, a two-stage framework for object detection and image restoration is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-real-time-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extracting the Brain-like Representation by an Improved Self-Organizing Map for Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extracting-the-brain-like-representation-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Backpropagation-based supervised learning has achieved great success in computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extracting-the-brain-like-representation-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebSHAP: Towards Explaining Any Machine Learning Models Anywhere</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webshap-towards-explaining-any-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As machine learning (ML) is increasingly integrated into our everyday Web experience, there is a call for transparent and explainable web-based ML.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webshap-towards-explaining-any-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EmotiEffNet Facial Features in Uni-task Emotion Recognition in Video at ABAW-5 competition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotieffnet-facial-features-in-uni-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, the results of our team for the fifth Affective Behavior Analysis in-the-wild (ABAW) competition are presented.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotieffnet-facial-features-in-uni-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-head Supervision for Crowd Counting with Noisy Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-head-supervision-for-crowd-counting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate the negative impact of noisy annotations, we propose a novel crowd counting model with one convolution head and one transformer head, in which these two heads can supervise each other in noisy areas, called Cross-Head Supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-head-supervision-for-crowd-counting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRE for Diffusion-Generated Image Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dire-for-diffusion-generated-image-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that existing detectors struggle to detect images generated by diffusion models, even if we include generated images from a specific diffusion model in their training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dire-for-diffusion-generated-image-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixTeacher: Mining Promising Labels with Mixed Scale Teacher for Semi-Supervised Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixteacher-mining-promising-labels-with-mixed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the remarkable progress made by modern detection models, this challenge is particularly evident in the semi-supervised case.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixteacher-mining-promising-labels-with-mixed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depth-Aware Image Compositing Model for Parallax Camera Motion Blur</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-aware-image-compositing-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The (forward) model produces realistic motion blur from a single image, depth map, and camera trajectory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-aware-image-compositing-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming Diffusion Models for Audio-Driven Co-Speech Gesture Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-diffusion-models-for-audio-driven-co</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel diffusion-based framework, named Diffusion Co-Speech Gesture (DiffGesture), to effectively capture the cross-modal audio-to-gesture associations and preserve temporal coherence for high-fidelity audio-driven co-speech gesture generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-diffusion-models-for-audio-driven-co</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Spectral Denoising Transformer with Learnable Query</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-spectral-denoising-transformer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Challenges in adapting transformer for HSI arise from the capabilities to tackle existing limitations of CNN-based methods in capturing the global and local spatial-spectral correlations while maintaining efficiency and flexibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-spectral-denoising-transformer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Intel Neuromorphic DNS Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-intel-neuromorphic-dns-challenge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A critical enabler for progress in neuromorphic computing research is the ability to transparently evaluate different neuromorphic solutions on important tasks and to compare them to state-of-the-art conventional solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-intel-neuromorphic-dns-challenge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurroundOcc: Multi-Camera 3D Occupancy Prediction for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surroundocc-multi-camera-3d-occupancy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Towards a more comprehensive perception of a 3D scene, in this paper, we propose a SurroundOcc method to predict the 3D occupancy with multi-camera images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surroundocc-multi-camera-3d-occupancy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-HPC: Generating Synthetic Images with Realistic Humans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-hpc-generating-synthetic-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent text-to-image generative models have exhibited remarkable abilities in generating high-fidelity and photo-realistic images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-hpc-generating-synthetic-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-modal Differentiable Unsupervised Feature Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-differentiable-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal high throughput biological data presents a great scientific opportunity and a significant computational challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-differentiable-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AU-aware graph convolutional network for Macro- and Micro-expression spotting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/au-aware-graph-convolutional-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic Micro-Expression (ME) spotting in long videos is a crucial step in ME analysis but also a challenging task due to the short duration and low intensity of MEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/au-aware-graph-convolutional-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Automated Hemorrhage Detection in Sparse-view Computed Tomography via Deep Convolutional Neural Network based Artifact Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-automated-hemorrhage-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate the hemorrhage detectability in the predicted CCTs with a hemorrhage classification convolutional neural network, trained on fully sampled CCTs to detect and classify different sub-types of hemorrhages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-automated-hemorrhage-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TemporalMaxer: Maximize Temporal Context with only Max Pooling for Temporal Action Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporalmaxer-maximize-temporal-context-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce TemporalMaxer, which minimizes long-term temporal context modeling while maximizing information from the extracted video clip features with a basic, parameter-free, and local region operating max-pooling block.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporalmaxer-maximize-temporal-context-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Classifiers Leak Sensitive Attributes About Their Classes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-classifiers-leak-sensitive-attributes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural network-based image classifiers are powerful tools for computer vision tasks, but they inadvertently reveal sensitive attribute information about their classes, raising concerns about their privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-classifiers-leak-sensitive-attributes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Enhancement for Remote Photoplethysmography in a Low-Light Environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-enhancement-for-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using collected dataset, we found 1) face detection algorithm cannot detect faces in video captured in low light conditions; 2) A decrease in the amplitude of the pulsatile signal will lead to the noise signal to be in the dominant position; and 3) the chrominance-based method suffers from the limitation in the assumption about skin-tone will not hold, and Green and ICA method receive less influence than POS in dark illuminance environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-enhancement-for-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning for Amalgamation: A Multi-Source Transfer Learning Framework For Sentiment Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-for-amalgamation-a-multi-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transfer learning plays an essential role in Deep Learning, which can remarkably improve the performance of the target domain, whose training data is not sufficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-for-amalgamation-a-multi-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Benchmark: On the Utility of Synthetic Data with Blender for Bare Supervised Learning and Downstream Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-benchmark-on-the-utility-of-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we use the simulation-to-reality adaptation as a downstream task for comparing the transferability between synthetic and real data when used for pre-training, which demonstrates that synthetic data pre-training is also promising to improve real test results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-benchmark-on-the-utility-of-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Selective Kernel Network for Remote Sensing Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-selective-kernel-network-for-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this is the first time that large and selective kernel mechanisms have been explored in the field of remote sensing object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-selective-kernel-network-for-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoLo-CAM: Class Activation Mapping for Object Co-Localization in Weakly-Labeled Unconstrained Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colo-cam-class-activation-mapping-for-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although results are promising, objects are assumed to have minimal movement leading to degradation in performance for relatively long-term dependencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colo-cam-class-activation-mapping-for-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Clutter in Radar Data -- Label Generation and Detection Using PointNet++</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-clutter-in-radar-data-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because there is no suitable public data set in which clutter is annotated, we design a method to automatically generate the respective labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-clutter-in-radar-data-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExoplANNET: A deep learning algorithm to detect and identify planetary signals in radial velocity data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exoplannet-a-deep-learning-algorithm-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, a neural network is proposed to replace the computation of the significance of the signal detected with the radial velocity method and to classify it as of planetary origin or not.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exoplannet-a-deep-learning-algorithm-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyVBMC: Efficient Bayesian inference in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyvbmc-efficient-bayesian-inference-in-python</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PyVBMC is a Python implementation of the Variational Bayesian Monte Carlo (VBMC) algorithm for posterior and model inference for black-box computational models (Acerbi, 2018, 2020).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyvbmc-efficient-bayesian-inference-in-python</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FindView: Precise Target View Localization Task for Look Around Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/findview-precise-target-view-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increase in demands for service robots and automated inspection, agents need to localize in its surrounding environment to achieve more natural communication with humans by shared contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/findview-precise-target-view-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hubs and Hyperspheres: Reducing Hubness and Improving Transductive Few-shot Learning with Hyperspherical Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hubs-and-hyperspheres-reducing-hubness-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Distance-based classification is frequently used in transductive few-shot learning (FSL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hubs-and-hyperspheres-reducing-hubness-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Metric Learning for Unsupervised Remote Sensing Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-metric-learning-for-unsupervised-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This loss is motivated by the principle of metric learning where we simultaneously maximize the distance between change pair-wise pixels while minimizing the distance between no-change pair-wise pixels in bi-temporal image domain and their deep feature domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-metric-learning-for-unsupervised-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieving a Better Stability-Plasticity Trade-off via Auxiliary Networks in Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-a-better-stability-plasticity-trade</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to the natural capabilities of humans to learn new tasks in a sequential fashion, neural networks are known to suffer from catastrophic forgetting, where the model's performances on old tasks drop dramatically after being optimized for a new task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-a-better-stability-plasticity-trade</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifiability Results for Multimodal Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifiability-results-for-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work generalizes previous identifiability results by redefining the generative process in terms of distinct mechanisms with modality-specific latent variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifiability-results-for-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining Distance to Class Centroids and Outlier Discounting for Improved Learning with Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-distance-to-class-centroids-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new approach for addressing the challenge of training machine learning models in the presence of noisy labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-distance-to-class-centroids-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effectively Modeling Time Series with Simple Discrete State Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effectively-modeling-time-series-with-simple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For expressivity, we propose a new SSM parameterization based on the companion matrix -- a canonical representation for discrete-time processes -- which enables SpaceTime's SSM layers to learn desirable autoregressive processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effectively-modeling-time-series-with-simple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Logic Specifications for Soft Policy Guidance in POMCP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-logic-specifications-for-soft-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we use inductive logic programming to learn logic specifications from traces of POMCP executions, i. e., sets of belief-action pairs generated by the planner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-logic-specifications-for-soft-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataflow graphs as complete causal graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataflow-graphs-as-complete-causal-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Component-based development is one of the core principles behind modern software engineering practices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataflow-graphs-as-complete-causal-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Bangla Complex Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-bangla-complex-named-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Named Entity Recognition (NER) is a fundamental task in natural language processing that involves identifying and classifying named entities in text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-bangla-complex-named-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FateZero: Fusing Attentions for Zero-shot Text-based Video Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fatezero-fusing-attentions-for-zero-shot-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also have a better zero-shot shape-aware editing ability based on the text-to-video model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fatezero-fusing-attentions-for-zero-shot-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Spatio-Temporal Aggregations for Large-Scale Capacity Expansion Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-spatio-temporal-aggregations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate aggregation outcomes over a range of hyperparameters governing the loss function and compare resulting upper bounds on the original problem with those obtained using benchmark methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-spatio-temporal-aggregations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lane Graph as Path: Continuity-preserving Path-wise Modeling for Online Lane Graph Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lane-graph-as-path-continuity-preserving-path</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a path-based online lane graph construction method, termed LaneGAP, which end-to-end learns the path and recovers the lane graph via a Path2Graph algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lane-graph-as-path-continuity-preserving-path</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical learning on measures: an application to persistence diagrams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-learning-on-measures-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider a binary supervised learning classification problem where instead of having data in a finite-dimensional Euclidean space, we observe measures on a compact space $\mathcal{X}$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-learning-on-measures-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cascading and Direct Approaches to Unsupervised Constituency Parsing on Spoken Sentences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascading-and-direct-approaches-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal is to determine the spoken sentences' hierarchical syntactic structure in the form of constituency parse trees, such that each node is a span of audio that corresponds to a constituent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascading-and-direct-approaches-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch or Listen: Robust Audio-Visual Speech Recognition with Visual Corruption Modeling and Reliability Scoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watch-or-listen-robust-audio-visual-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we firstly analyze that the previous AVSR models are not indeed robust to the corruption of multimodal input streams, the audio and the visual inputs, compared to uni-modal models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watch-or-listen-robust-audio-visual-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dually Enhanced Propensity Score Estimation in Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dually-enhanced-propensity-score-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[According to the graph, two complementary propensity scores are estimated from the views of item and user, respectively, based on the same set of user feedback data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dually-enhanced-propensity-score-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-less Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-less-collaborative-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by these limitations, we propose a simple and effective collaborative filtering model (SimRec) that marries the power of knowledge distillation and contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-less-collaborative-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning Weight Pruning with RMT-SVD: Increasing Accuracy and Reducing Overfitting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-weight-pruning-with-rmt-svd</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, random matrix theory (RMT) has been applied to the overfitting problem in deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-weight-pruning-with-rmt-svd</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Individualized Effects of Internet-Based Treatment for Genito-Pelvic Pain/Penetration Disorder: Development and Internal Validation of a Multivariable Decision Tree Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-individualized-effects-of-internet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we developed and internally validated a multivariable decision tree model that predicts effects of an internet-based treatment on a multidimensional composite score of GPPPD symptoms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-individualized-effects-of-internet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAtch, eXpand and Improve: Unsupervised Finetuning for Zero-Shot Action Recognition with Language Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/match-expand-and-improve-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We adapt a VL model for zero-shot and few-shot action recognition using a collection of unlabeled videos and an unpaired action dictionary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/match-expand-and-improve-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffusionAD: Denoising Diffusion for Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusionad-denoising-diffusion-for-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new pipeline, DiffusionAD, to anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusionad-denoising-diffusion-for-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic Segmentation with Conditional Categorical Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-segmentation-with-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation has made significant progress in recent years thanks to deep neural networks, but the common objective of generating a single segmentation output that accurately matches the image's content may not be suitable for safety-critical domains such as medical diagnostics and autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-segmentation-with-conditional</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
