<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 09:15:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Royal Game of Ur Using Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-royal-game-of-ur-using-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning has recently surfaced as a very powerful tool to solve complex problems in the domain of board games, wherein an agent is generally required to learn complex strategies and moves based on its own experiences and rewards received.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-royal-game-of-ur-using-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faint Features Tell: Automatic Vertebrae Fracture Screening Assisted by Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faint-features-tell-automatic-vertebrae</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method has a specificity of 99\% and a sensitivity of 85\% in binary classification, and a macio-F1 of 77\% in multi-classification, indicating that contrastive learning significantly improves the accuracy of vertebrae fracture screening, especially for the mild fractures and normal controls.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faint-features-tell-automatic-vertebrae</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchically Decomposed Graph Convolutional Networks for Skeleton-Based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchically-decomposed-graph-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph convolutional networks (GCNs) are the most commonly used method for skeleton-based action recognition and have achieved remarkable performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchically-decomposed-graph-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modal Representation Learning with SAT for Commodity Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-representation-learning-with-sat</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a method to identify identical commodities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-representation-learning-with-sat</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Constrained Deformable Convolutional Network for Efficient Single Image Dynamic Scene Blind Deblurring with Spatially-Variant Motion Blur Kernels Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-constrained-deformable-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing deep-learning-based single image dynamic scene blind deblurring (SIDSBD) methods usually design deep networks to directly remove the spatially-variant motion blurs from one inputted motion blurred image, without blur kernels estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-constrained-deformable-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Self-Supervision using Patch-based Contrastive Learning for Histopathology Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-self-supervision-using-patch-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive self-supervised learning provides a framework to learn meaningful representations using learned notions of similarity measures from simple pretext tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-self-supervision-using-patch-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural PCA for Flow-Based Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-pca-for-flow-based-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Without exploiting any label information, the principal components recovered store the most informative elements in their \emph{leading} dimensions and leave the negligible in the \emph{trailing} ones, allowing for clear performance improvements of $5\%$-$10\%$ in downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-pca-for-flow-based-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Question Answering via Answer Diversifying</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-question-answering-via-answer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous works usually make use of heuristic rules as well as pre-trained models to construct data and train QA models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-question-answering-via-answer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A flexible empirical Bayes approach to multiple linear regression and connections with penalized regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-flexible-empirical-bayes-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new empirical Bayes approach for large-scale multiple linear regression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-flexible-empirical-bayes-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-high-resolution unpaired stain transformation via Kernelized Instance Normalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-high-resolution-unpaired-stain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, we proposed a strategy for ultra-high-resolution unpaired image-to-image translation: Kernelized Instance Normalization (KIN), which preserves local information and successfully achieves seamless stain transformation with constant GPU memory usage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-high-resolution-unpaired-stain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAPER: Coarsen, Align, Project, Refine - A General Multilevel Framework for Network Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caper-coarsen-align-project-refine-a-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Network alignment, or the task of finding corresponding nodes in different networks, is an important problem formulation in many application domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caper-coarsen-align-project-refine-a-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retinal Structure Detection in OCTA Image via Voting-based Multi-task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retinal-structure-detection-in-octa-image-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated detection of retinal structures, such as retinal vessels (RV), the foveal avascular zone (FAZ), and retinal vascular junctions (RVJ), are of great importance for understanding diseases of the eye and clinical decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retinal-structure-detection-in-octa-image-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning an Efficient Multimodal Depth Completion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-an-efficient-multimodal-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the wide application of sparse ToF sensors in mobile devices, RGB image-guided sparse depth completion has attracted extensive attention recently, but still faces some problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-an-efficient-multimodal-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Privacy Enhancement and Quantization in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-privacy-enhancement-and-quantization-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The distributed operation of FL gives rise to challenges that are not encountered in centralized machine learning, including the need to preserve the privacy of the local datasets, and the communication load due to the repeated exchange of updated models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-privacy-enhancement-and-quantization-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CM-MLP: Cascade Multi-scale MLP with Axial Context Relation Encoder for Edge Segmentation of Medical Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cm-mlp-cascade-multi-scale-mlp-with-axial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, those methods have the following challenges when dealing with the edges of the medical images: (1) Previous convolutional-based methods do not focus on the boundary relationship between foreground and background around the segmentation edge, which leads to the degradation of segmentation performance when the edge changes complexly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cm-mlp-cascade-multi-scale-mlp-with-axial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrative conformal p-values for powerful out-of-distribution testing with labeled outliers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrative-conformal-p-values-for-powerful</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper develops novel conformal methods to test whether a new observation was sampled from the same distribution as a reference set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrative-conformal-p-values-for-powerful</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AniWho : A Quick and Accurate Way to Classify Anime Character Faces in Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aniwho-a-quick-and-accurate-way-to-classify</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper aims to dive more deeply into various models available, including; InceptionV3, InceptionResNetV2, MobileNetV2, and EfficientNetB7 using transfer learning, to classify Japanese animation-style character faces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aniwho-a-quick-and-accurate-way-to-classify</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ULISSE: A Tool for One-shot Sky Exploration and its Application to Active Galactic Nuclei Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ulisse-a-tool-for-one-shot-sky-exploration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we focus on applying our method to the detection of AGN candidates in a Sloan Digital Sky Survey galaxy sample, since the identification and classification of Active Galactic Nuclei (AGN) in the optical band still remains a challenging task in extragalactic astronomy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ulisse-a-tool-for-one-shot-sky-exploration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepInteraction: 3D Object Detection via Modality Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepinteraction-3d-object-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing top-performance 3D object detectors typically rely on the multi-modal fusion strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepinteraction-3d-object-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distance-Aware Occlusion Detection with Focused Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-aware-occlusion-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, (1) we propose a novel three-decoder architecture as the infrastructure for focused attention; 2) we use the generalized intersection box prediction task to effectively guide our model to focus on occlusion-specific regions; 3) our model achieves a new state-of-the-art performance on distance-aware relationship detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-aware-occlusion-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompting as Probing: Using Language Models for Knowledge Base Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompting-as-probing-using-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ProP implements a multi-step approach that combines a variety of prompting techniques to achieve this.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompting-as-probing-using-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistency Regularization for Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-regularization-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Collection of real world annotations for training semantic segmentation models is an expensive process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-regularization-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurvSHAP(t): Time-dependent explanations of machine learning survival models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survshap-t-time-dependent-explanations-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on synthetic and medical data confirm that SurvSHAP(t) can detect variables with a time-dependent effect, and its aggregation is a better determinant of the importance of variables for a prediction than SurvLIME.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survshap-t-time-dependent-explanations-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CitySim: A Drone-Based Vehicle Trajectory Dataset for Safety Oriented Research and Digital Twins</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citysim-a-drone-based-vehicle-trajectory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of safety-oriented research ideas and applications requires fine-grained vehicle trajectory data that not only has high accuracy but also captures a substantial number of critical safety events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citysim-a-drone-based-vehicle-trajectory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing User Behavior Sequence Modeling by Generative Tasks for Session Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-user-behavior-sequence-modeling-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To help the encoding of the current user behavior sequence, we propose to use a decoder and the information of future sequences and a supplemental query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-user-behavior-sequence-modeling-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Across Domains Gaze Target Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-across-domains-gaze-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the gaze target detection problem in single images captured from the third-person perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-across-domains-gaze-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Perceptual Noise Injection for Social Media Fingerprint Privacy Protection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-perceptual-noise-injection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The threat of fingerprint leakage from social media raises a strong desire for anonymizing shared images while maintaining image qualities, since fingerprints act as a lifelong individual biometric password.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-perceptual-noise-injection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMPaSh: A Novel Domain-shift Resistant Representation for Colorectal Cancer Tissue Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impash-a-novel-domain-shift-resistant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The appearance of histopathology images depends on tissue type, staining and digitization procedure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impash-a-novel-domain-shift-resistant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Feature Augmentation for Cross-domain Few-shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-feature-augmentation-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods based on meta-learning predict novel-class labels for (target domain) testing tasks via meta knowledge learned from (source domain) training tasks of base classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-feature-augmentation-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Computed Tomography (CT) Reconstruction via 3D Shape Induction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-computed-tomography-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chest computed tomography (CT) imaging adds valuable insight in the diagnosis and management of pulmonary infectious diseases, like tuberculosis (TB).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-computed-tomography-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pystacked: Stacking generalization and machine learning in Stata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pystacked-stacking-generalization-and-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[pystacked implements stacked generalization (Wolpert, 1992) for regression and binary classification via Python's scikit-lear}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pystacked-stacking-generalization-and-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Anomaly Localization with Structural Feature-Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-anomaly-localization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most commonly, the anomaly detection model generates a "normal" version of an input image, and the pixel-wise $l^p$-difference of the two is used to localize anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-anomaly-localization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure Regularized Attentive Network for Automatic Femoral Head Necrosis Diagnosis and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-regularized-attentive-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to the tissue overlap, X-ray images are difficult to provide fine-grained features for early diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-regularized-attentive-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survival Mixture Density Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survival-mixture-density-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Survival MDN applies an invertible positive function to the output of Mixture Density Networks (MDNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survival-mixture-density-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VILT: Video Instructions Linking for Complex Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vilt-video-instructions-linking-for-complex</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work addresses challenges in developing conversational assistants that support rich multimodal video interactions to accomplish real-world tasks interactively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vilt-video-instructions-linking-for-complex</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Visibility for Robust Dense Human Body Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-visibility-for-robust-dense-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An alternative approach is to estimate dense vertices of a predefined template body in the image space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-visibility-for-robust-dense-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIBAC: Towards Robust and Imperceptible Backdoor Attack against Compact DNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ribac-towards-robust-and-imperceptible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently backdoor attack has become an emerging threat to the security of deep neural network (DNN) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ribac-towards-robust-and-imperceptible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DP-Rewrite: Towards Reproducibility and Transparency in Differentially Private Text Rewriting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dp-rewrite-towards-reproducibility-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text rewriting with differential privacy (DP) provides concrete theoretical guarantees for protecting the privacy of individuals in textual documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dp-rewrite-towards-reproducibility-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locate Then Ask: Interpretable Stepwise Reasoning for Multi-hop Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locate-then-ask-interpretable-stepwise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an interpretable stepwise reasoning framework to incorporate both single-hop supporting sentence identification and single-hop question generation at each intermediate step, and utilize the inference of the current hop for the next until reasoning out the final result.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locate-then-ask-interpretable-stepwise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Knowledge-aware Recommendation with Multi-level Interactive Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-knowledge-aware-recommendation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we first construct local and non-local graphs for user/item in KG, exploring more KG facts for KGR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-knowledge-aware-recommendation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Multi-Task Learning Approach for Context-Sensitive Compound Type Identification in Sanskrit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-multi-task-learning-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The phenomenon of compounding is ubiquitous in Sanskrit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-multi-task-learning-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recent Advances in Text-to-SQL: A Survey of What We Have and What We Expect</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recent-advances-in-text-to-sql-a-survey-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-SQL has attracted attention from both the natural language processing and database communities because of its ability to convert the semantics in natural language into SQL queries and its practical application in building natural language interfaces to database systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recent-advances-in-text-to-sql-a-survey-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Individual Tree Detection in Large-Scale Urban Environments using High-Resolution Multispectral Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individual-tree-detection-in-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel deep learning method for detection of individual trees in urban environments using high-resolution multispectral aerial imagery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individual-tree-detection-in-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Knowledge Distillation via Cross-Entropy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-knowledge-distillation-via-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we smooth students' target output to treat it as the soft target for training without teachers and propose a teacher-free new KD loss (tf-NKD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-knowledge-distillation-via-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep 3D Vessel Segmentation based on Cross Transformer Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-3d-vessel-segmentation-based-on-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In CTN, a transformer module is constructed in parallel to a U-Net to learn long-distance dependencies between different anatomical regions; and these dependencies are communicated to the U-Net at multiple stages to endow it with global awareness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-3d-vessel-segmentation-based-on-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FairDisCo: Fairer AI in Dermatology via Disentanglement Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairdisco-fairer-ai-in-dermatology-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning models have achieved great success in automating skin lesion diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairdisco-fairer-ai-in-dermatology-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Temporal Structures of Cyclostationary Signals for Data-Driven Single-Channel Source Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-temporal-structures-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of single-channel source separation (SCSS), and focus on cyclostationary signals, which are particularly suitable in a variety of application domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-temporal-structures-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repurposing Knowledge Graph Embeddings for Triple Representation via Weak Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repurposing-knowledge-graph-embeddings-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The majority of knowledge graph embedding techniques treat entities and predicates as separate embedding matrices, using aggregation functions to build a representation of the input triple.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repurposing-knowledge-graph-embeddings-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LTE4G: Long-Tail Experts for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lte4g-long-tail-experts-for-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After having trained an expert for each balanced subset, we adopt knowledge distillation to obtain two class-wise students, i. e., Head class student and Tail class student, each of which is responsible for classifying nodes in the head classes and tail classes, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lte4g-long-tail-experts-for-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient-level Microsatellite Stability Assessment from Whole Slide Images By Combining Momentum Contrast Learning and Group Patch Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patient-level-microsatellite-stability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the high resolution of WSI practically prevent direct classification of the entire WSI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patient-level-microsatellite-stability</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
