<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 09:12:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>FashionSAP: Symbols and Attributes Prompt for Fine-grained Fashion Vision-Language Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fashionsap-symbols-and-attributes-prompt-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method for fine-grained fashion vision-language pre-training based on fashion Symbols and Attributes Prompt (FashionSAP) to model fine-grained multi-modalities fashion attributes and characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fashionsap-symbols-and-attributes-prompt-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survey on Leveraging Uncertainty Estimation Towards Trustworthy Deep Neural Networks: The Case of Reject Option and Post-training Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survey-on-leveraging-uncertainty-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a systematic review of the prediction with the reject option in the context of various neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survey-on-leveraging-uncertainty-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OccFormer: Dual-path Transformer for Vision-based 3D Semantic Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occformer-dual-path-transformer-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The vision-based perception for autonomous driving has undergone a transformation from the bird-eye-view (BEV) representations to the 3D semantic occupancy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occformer-dual-path-transformer-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Vertical View: A Hierarchical Network for Heterogeneous Trajectory Prediction via Spectrums</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/another-vertical-view-a-hierarchical-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we bring a new ``view'' for trajectory prediction to model and forecast trajectories hierarchically according to different frequency portions from the spectral domain to learn to forecast trajectories by considering their frequency responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/another-vertical-view-a-hierarchical-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topology Reasoning for Driving Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-reasoning-for-driving-scenes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the road genome is essential to realize autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-reasoning-for-driving-scenes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pointless Global Bundle Adjustment With Relative Motions Hessians</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointless-global-bundle-adjustment-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bundle adjustment (BA) is the standard way to optimise camera poses and to produce sparse representations of a scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointless-global-bundle-adjustment-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fracture Detection in Pediatric Wrist Trauma X-ray Images Using YOLOv8 Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fracture-detection-in-pediatric-wrist-trauma</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, YOLOv8 algorithm is used to train models on the GRAZPEDWRI-DX dataset, which includes X-ray images from 6, 091 pediatric patients with wrist trauma.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fracture-detection-in-pediatric-wrist-trauma</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeAT: Neural Artistic Tracing for Beautiful Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neat-neural-artistic-tracing-for-beautiful</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a component of curating this data, we present a novel model able to classify if an image is stylistic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neat-neural-artistic-tracing-for-beautiful</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Capacity and Robustness Trade-off: Revisiting the Channel Independent Strategy for Multivariate Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-capacity-and-robustness-trade-off</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results conclude that the CD approach has higher capacity but often lacks robustness to accurately predict distributionally drifted time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-capacity-and-robustness-trade-off</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The No Free Lunch Theorem, Kolmogorov Complexity, and the Role of Inductive Biases in Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-no-free-lunch-theorem-kolmogorov</link>
      <description><![CDATA[No free lunch theorems for supervised learning state that no learner can solve all problems or that all learners achieve exactly the same accuracy on average over a uniform distribution on learning problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-no-free-lunch-theorem-kolmogorov</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PP-MobileSeg: Explore the Fast and Accurate Semantic Segmentation Model on Mobile Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pp-mobileseg-explore-the-fast-and-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose PP-MobileSeg, a semantic segmentation model that achieves state-of-the-art performance on mobile devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pp-mobileseg-explore-the-fast-and-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinpointing Why Object Recognition Performance Degrades Across Income Levels and Geographies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pinpointing-why-object-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As an example, we show that mitigating a model's vulnerability to texture can improve performance on the lower income level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pinpointing-why-object-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel-wise Guidance for Utilizing Auxiliary Features in Monte Carlo Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixel-wise-guidance-for-utilizing-auxiliary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then we design our ensembling network to obtain per-pixel ensembling weight maps, which represent pixel-wise guidance for which auxiliary feature should be dominant at reconstructing each individual pixel and use them to ensemble the two denoised results of our denosiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixel-wise-guidance-for-utilizing-auxiliary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Optimization of Catalysts With In-context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-optimization-of-catalysts-with-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show a prompting system that enables regression with uncertainty for in-context learning with frozen LLM (GPT-3, GPT-3. 5, and GPT-4) models, allowing predictions without features or architecture tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-optimization-of-catalysts-with-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Neural Radiance Fields with Depth-aware Optimization for Novel View Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-neural-radiance-fields-with-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through these explicit constraints and the implicit constraint from NeRF, our method improves the view synthesis as well as the 3D-scene geometry performance of NeRF at the same time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-neural-radiance-fields-with-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Feature Description for Small Body Relative Navigation using Binary Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-feature-description-for-small-body</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We train and test our models on real images of small bodies from legacy and ongoing missions and demonstrate increased performance relative to traditional handcrafted methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-feature-description-for-small-body</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards preserving word order importance through Forced Invalidation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-preserving-word-order-importance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large pre-trained language models such as BERT have been widely used as a framework for natural language understanding (NLU) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-preserving-word-order-importance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model sparsification can simplify machine unlearning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-sparsification-can-simplify-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While exact unlearning is possible by conducting a model retraining with the remaining data from scratch, its computational cost has led to the development of approximate but efficient unlearning schemes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-sparsification-can-simplify-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooperative Coevolution for Non-Separable Large-Scale Black-Box Optimization: Convergence Analyses and Distributed Accelerations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-coevolution-for-non-separable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the ubiquity of non-separable optimization problems in real worlds, in this paper we analyze and extend the large-scale version of the well-known cooperative coevolution (CC), a divide-and-conquer optimization framework, on non-separable functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-coevolution-for-non-separable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Recommender Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-recommender-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In light of the impressive advantages of Diffusion Models (DMs) over traditional generative models in image synthesis, we propose a novel Diffusion Recommender Model (named DiffRec) to learn the generative process in a denoising manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-recommender-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Graph Neural Networks for Charged Particle Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-graph-neural-networks-for-charged</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) have gained traction in high-energy physics (HEP) for their potential to improve accuracy and scalability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-graph-neural-networks-for-charged</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Efficient Fine-tuning of Pre-trained Code Models: An Experimental Study and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-fine-tuning-of-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental study shows that (1) lexical, syntactic and structural properties of source code are encoded in the lower, intermediate, and higher layers, respectively, while the semantic property spans across the entire model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-fine-tuning-of-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automaton-Guided Curriculum Generation for Reinforcement Learning Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automaton-guided-curriculum-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments in gridworld and physics-based simulated robotics domains show that the curricula produced by AGCL achieve improved time-to-threshold performance on a complex sequential decision-making problem relative to state-of-the-art curriculum learning (e. g, teacher-student, self-play) and automaton-guided reinforcement learning baselines (e. g, Q-Learning for Reward Machines).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automaton-guided-curriculum-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TodyNet: Temporal Dynamic Graph Neural Network for Multivariate Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/todynet-temporal-dynamic-graph-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, the existing deep learning-based methods neglect the hidden dependencies in different dimensions and also rarely consider the unique dynamic features of time series, which lack sufficient feature extraction capability to obtain satisfactory classification accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/todynet-temporal-dynamic-graph-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task Difficulty Aware Parameter Allocation &amp; Regularization for Lifelong Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-difficulty-aware-parameter-allocation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the Parameter Allocation & Regularization (PAR), which adaptively select an appropriate strategy for each task from parameter allocation and regularization based on its learning difficulty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-difficulty-aware-parameter-allocation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did we personalize? Assessing personalization by an online reinforcement learning algorithm using resampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/did-we-personalize-assessing-personalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use a working definition of personalization and introduce a resampling-based methodology for investigating whether the personalization exhibited by the RL algorithm is an artifact of the RL algorithm stochasticity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/did-we-personalize-assessing-personalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRHF: Rank Responses to Align Language Models with Human Feedback without tears</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rrhf-rank-responses-to-align-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning from Human Feedback (RLHF) facilitates the alignment of large language models with human preferences, significantly enhancing the quality of interactions between humans and these models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rrhf-rank-responses-to-align-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Learning for News Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-learning-for-news-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some recent \textit{news recommendation} (NR) methods introduce a Pre-trained Language Model (PLM) to encode news representation by following the vanilla pre-train and fine-tune paradigm with carefully-designed recommendation-specific neural networks and objective functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-learning-for-news-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of Differentially Constrained Motion Models for Graph-Based Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-differentially-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research investigates the performance of various motion models in combination with numerical solvers for the prediction task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-differentially-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGXplain: Rule-Based Deep Neural Network Explanations Using Dual Linear Programs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cgxplain-rule-based-deep-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rule-based surrogate models are an effective and interpretable way to approximate a Deep Neural Network's (DNN) decision boundaries, allowing humans to easily understand deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cgxplain-rule-based-deep-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum-Based Imitation of Versatile Skills</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-based-imitation-of-versatile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning skills by imitation is a promising concept for the intuitive teaching of robots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-based-imitation-of-versatile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is ChatGPT a Good Sentiment Analyzer? A Preliminary Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-chatgpt-a-good-sentiment-analyzer-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, ChatGPT has drawn great attention from both the research community and the public.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-chatgpt-a-good-sentiment-analyzer-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Test Time Adaptation under Online Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-test-time-adaptation-under-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a more realistic evaluation protocol for TTA methods, where data is received in an online fashion from a constant-speed data stream, thereby accounting for the method's adaptation speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-test-time-adaptation-under-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVKG: An Interlinked and Interoperable Electric Vehicle Knowledge Graph for Smart Transportation System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evkg-an-interlinked-and-interoperable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the past decade, the electric vehicle industry has experienced unprecedented growth and diversification, resulting in a complex ecosystem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evkg-an-interlinked-and-interoperable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing Data Imputation with Graph Laplacian Pyramid Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/missing-data-imputation-with-graph-laplacian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data imputation is a prevalent and important task due to the ubiquitousness of missing data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/missing-data-imputation-with-graph-laplacian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Effective Factors for Improving Visual In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-effective-factors-for-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By doing this, the model can leverage the diverse knowledge stored in different parts of the model to improve its performance on new tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-effective-factors-for-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Active Alignment of Knowledge Graph Entities and Schemata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-active-alignment-of-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With deep learning, it learns the embeddings of entities, relations and classes, and jointly aligns them in a semi-supervised manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-active-alignment-of-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAGI: When LLM Meets Domain Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openagi-when-llm-meets-domain-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, the LLM is responsible for synthesizing various external models for solving complex tasks, while RLTF provides feedback to improve its task-solving ability, enabling a feedback loop for self-improving AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openagi-when-llm-meets-domain-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphMAE2: A Decoding-Enhanced Masked Self-Supervised Graph Learner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphmae2-a-decoding-enhanced-masked-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph self-supervised learning (SSL), including contrastive and generative approaches, offers great potential to address the fundamental challenge of label scarcity in real-world graph data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphmae2-a-decoding-enhanced-masked-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambiguous Medical Image Segmentation using Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambiguous-medical-image-segmentation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Collective insights from a group of experts have always proven to outperform an individual's best diagnostic for clinical tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambiguous-medical-image-segmentation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Point-based Algorithm for Multi-agent Control Using the Common Information Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-point-based-algorithm-for-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Common Information (CI) approach provides a systematic way to transform a multi-agent stochastic control problem to a single-agent partially observed Markov decision problem (POMDP) called the coordinator's POMDP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-point-based-algorithm-for-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention at SemEval-2023 Task 10: Explainable Detection of Online Sexism (EDOS)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-at-semeval-2023-task-10-explainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we have worked on interpretability, trust, and understanding of the decisions made by models in the form of classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-at-semeval-2023-task-10-explainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Network Predicts Ion Concentration Profiles under Nanoconfinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-predicts-ion-concentration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, our deep learning model is a fast, flexible, and accurate surrogate model to predict ion concentration profiles in nanoconfinement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-predicts-ion-concentration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monte Carlo Linear Clustering with Single-Point Supervision is Enough for Infrared Small Target Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-linear-clustering-with-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core idea of this work is to recover the per-pixel mask of each target from the given single point label by using clustering approaches, which looks simple but is indeed challenging since targets are always insalient and accompanied with background clutters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-linear-clustering-with-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H2RBox-v2: Boosting HBox-supervised Oriented Object Detection via Symmetric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h2rbox-v2-boosting-hbox-supervised-oriented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increasing demand for oriented object detection e. g. in autonomous driving and remote sensing, the oriented annotation has become a labor-intensive work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h2rbox-v2-boosting-hbox-supervised-oriented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Recipes for Better 3D Pseudo-GTs of 3D Human Mesh Estimation in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/three-recipes-for-better-3d-pseudo-gts-of-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recovering 3D human mesh in the wild is greatly challenging as in-the-wild (ITW) datasets provide only 2D pose ground truths (GTs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/three-recipes-for-better-3d-pseudo-gts-of-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebBrain: Learning to Generate Factually Correct Articles for Queries by Grounding on Large Web Corpus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webbrain-learning-to-generate-factually</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a new NLP task -- generating short factual articles with references for queries by mining supporting evidence from the Web.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webbrain-learning-to-generate-factually</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Image Matting: A Comprehensive Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-image-matting-a-comprehensive-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image matting refers to extracting precise alpha matte from natural images, and it plays a critical role in various downstream applications, such as image editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-image-matting-a-comprehensive-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulated Annealing in Early Layers Leads to Better Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulated-annealing-in-early-layers-leads-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our principal innovation in this work is to use Simulated annealing in EArly Layers (SEAL) of the network in place of re-initialization of later layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulated-annealing-in-early-layers-leads-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning from Passive Data via Latent Intentions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-from-passive-data-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Passive observational data, such as human videos, is abundant and rich in information, yet remains largely untapped by current RL methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-from-passive-data-via</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
