<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 21:06:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>EigenTrajectory: Low-Rank Descriptors for Multi-Modal Trajectory Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigentrajectory-low-rank-descriptors-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present EigenTrajectory ($\mathbb{ET}$), a trajectory prediction approach that uses a novel trajectory descriptor to form a compact space, known here as $\mathbb{ET}$ space, in place of Euclidean space, for representing pedestrian movements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigentrajectory-low-rank-descriptors-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Machine Learning for Extraction of Theorems and Proofs in the Scientific Literature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-machine-learning-for-extraction-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, a simple CRF-based approach uses the features of the multimodal model along with information on block sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-machine-learning-for-extraction-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedDefender: Client-Side Attack-Tolerant Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddefender-client-side-attack-tolerant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluations of real-world scenarios across multiple datasets show that the proposed method enhances the robustness of federated learning against model poisoning attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddefender-client-side-attack-tolerant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVA2023 Small Object Detection Challenge for Spotting Birds: Dataset, Methods, and Results</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mva2023-small-object-detection-challenge-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Small Object Detection (SOD) is an important machine vision topic because (i) a variety of real-world applications require object detection for distant objects and (ii) SOD is a challenging task due to the noisy, blurred, and less-informative image appearances of small objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mva2023-small-object-detection-challenge-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluate Fine-tuning Strategies for Fetal Head Ultrasound Image Segmentation with U-Net</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluate-fine-tuning-strategies-for-fetal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method addresses the challenges associated with training a CNN network from scratch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluate-fine-tuning-strategies-for-fetal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OnlineRefer: A Simple Online Baseline for Referring Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onlinerefer-a-simple-online-baseline-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Referring video object segmentation (RVOS) aims at segmenting an object in a video following human instruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onlinerefer-a-simple-online-baseline-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Llama 2: Open Foundation and Fine-Tuned Chat Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-2-open-foundation-and-fine-tuned-chat</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop and release Llama 2, a collection of pretrained and fine-tuned large language models (LLMs) ranging in scale from 7 billion to 70 billion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-2-open-foundation-and-fine-tuned-chat</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constraining Depth Map Geometry for Multi-View Stereo: A Dual-Depth Approach with Saddle-shaped Depth Cells</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constraining-depth-map-geometry-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning-based multi-view stereo (MVS) methods deal with predicting accurate depth maps to achieve an accurate and complete 3D representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constraining-depth-map-geometry-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overthinking the Truth: Understanding how Language Models Process False Demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overthinking-the-truth-understanding-how</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first phenomenon, overthinking, appears when we decode predictions from intermediate layers, given correct vs. incorrect few-shot demonstrations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overthinking-the-truth-understanding-how</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel-wise Graph Attention Networks for Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixel-wise-graph-attention-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on these two modules, we consulted the ResNet and design a pixel-wise graph attention network (PGANet).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixel-wise-graph-attention-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTK-approximating MLP Fusion for Efficient Language Model Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntk-approximating-mlp-fusion-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning a pre-trained language model (PLM) emerges as the predominant strategy in many natural language processing applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntk-approximating-mlp-fusion-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OxfordVGG Submission to the EGO4D AV Transcription Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oxfordvgg-submission-to-the-ego4d-av</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report presents the technical details of our submission on the EGO4D Audio-Visual (AV) Automatic Speech Recognition Challenge 2023 from the OxfordVGG team.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oxfordvgg-submission-to-the-ego4d-av</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smooth Attention for Deep Multiple Instance Learning: Application to CT Intracranial Hemorrhage Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smooth-attention-for-deep-multiple-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiple Instance Learning (MIL) has been widely applied to medical imaging diagnosis, where bag labels are known and instance labels inside bags are unknown.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smooth-attention-for-deep-multiple-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Region-Aware Neural Radiance Fields for High-Fidelity Talking Portrait Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-region-aware-neural-radiance-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents ER-NeRF, a novel conditional Neural Radiance Fields (NeRF) based architecture for talking portrait synthesis that can concurrently achieve fast convergence, real-time rendering, and state-of-the-art performance with small model size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-region-aware-neural-radiance-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modal Discussion Transformer: Integrating Text, Images and Graph Transformers to Detect Hate Speech on Social Media</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-discussion-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Multi-Modal Discussion Transformer (mDT), a novel multi-modal graph-based transformer model for detecting hate speech in online social networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-discussion-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using the IBM Analog In-Memory Hardware Acceleration Kit for Neural Network Training and Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-the-ibm-analog-in-memory-hardware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analog In-Memory Computing (AIMC) is a promising approach to reduce the latency and energy consumption of Deep Neural Network (DNN) inference and training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-the-ibm-analog-in-memory-hardware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alioth: A Machine Learning Based Interference-Aware Performance Monitor for Multi-Tenancy Applications in Public Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alioth-a-machine-learning-based-interference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-tenancy in public clouds may lead to co-location interference on shared resources, which possibly results in performance degradation of cloud applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alioth-a-machine-learning-based-interference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>qecGPT: decoding Quantum Error-correcting Codes with Generative Pre-trained Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qecgpt-decoding-quantum-error-correcting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our framework is general and can be applied to any error model and quantum codes with different topologies such as surface codes and quantum LDPC codes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qecgpt-decoding-quantum-error-correcting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application of BERT in Wind Power Forecasting-Teletraan's Solution in Baidu KDD Cup 2022</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-bert-in-wind-power-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nowadays, wind energy has drawn increasing attention as its important role in carbon neutrality and sustainable development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-bert-in-wind-power-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RepViT: Revisiting Mobile CNN From ViT Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repvit-revisiting-mobile-cnn-from-vit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On ImageNet, RepViT achieves over 80\% top-1 accuracy with nearly 1ms latency on an iPhone 12, which is the first time for a lightweight model, to the best of our knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repvit-revisiting-mobile-cnn-from-vit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Neural Network Training for Hyperbox-Based Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-neural-network-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperbox-based classification has been seen as a promising technique in which decisions on the data are represented as a series of orthogonal, multidimensional boxes (i. e., hyperboxes) that are often interpretable and human-readable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-neural-network-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-shot Query Reformulation for Conversational Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-query-reformulation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nevertheless, existing zero-shot methods face three primary limitations: they are not universally applicable to all retrievers, their effectiveness lacks sufficient explainability, and they struggle to resolve common conversational ambiguities caused by omission.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-query-reformulation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Learning with Costly Features in Non-stationary Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-learning-with-costly-features-in-non</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Maximizing long-term rewards is the primary goal in sequential decision-making problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-learning-with-costly-features-in-non</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Self-Supervised Thermal Water Segmentation for Aerial Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-self-supervised-thermal-water</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new method to adapt an RGB-trained water segmentation network to target-domain aerial thermal imagery using online self-supervision by leveraging texture and motion cues as supervisory signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-self-supervised-thermal-water</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How is ChatGPT's behavior changing over time?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-is-chatgpt-s-behavior-changing-over-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the performance and behavior of both GPT-3. 5 and GPT-4 can vary greatly over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-is-chatgpt-s-behavior-changing-over-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency-mixed Single-source Domain Generalization for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-mixed-single-source-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consequently, domain generalization (DG) is developed to boost the performance of segmentation models on unseen domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-mixed-single-source-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Can Simple Arithmetic Operations Do for Temporal Modeling?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-can-simple-arithmetic-operations-do-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct comprehensive ablation studies on the instantiation of ATMs and demonstrate that this module provides powerful temporal modeling capability at a low computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-can-simple-arithmetic-operations-do-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a performance analysis on pre-trained Visual Question Answering models for autonomous driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-performance-analysis-on-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This short paper presents a preliminary analysis of three popular Visual Question Answering (VQA) models, namely ViLBERT, ViLT, and LXMERT, in the context of answering questions relating to driving scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-performance-analysis-on-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptMagician: Interactive Prompt Engineering for Text-to-Image Creation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptmagician-interactive-prompt-engineering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative text-to-image models have gained great popularity among the public for their powerful capability to generate high-quality images based on natural language prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptmagician-interactive-prompt-engineering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PatchCT: Aligning Patch Set and Label Set with Conditional Transport for Multi-Label Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchct-aligning-patch-set-and-label-set-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that by formulating the multi-label classification as a CT problem, we can exploit the interactions between the image and label efficiently by minimizing the bidirectional CT cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchct-aligning-patch-set-and-label-set-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Snake Convolution based on Topological Geometric Constraints for Tubular Structure Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-snake-convolution-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we note the specificity of tubular structures and use this knowledge to guide our DSCNet to simultaneously enhance perception in three stages: feature extraction, feature fusion, and loss constraint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-snake-convolution-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOPE: High-order Polynomial Expansion of Black-box Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hope-high-order-polynomial-expansion-of-black</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their remarkable performance, deep neural networks remain mostly ``black boxes'', suggesting inexplicability and hindering their wide applications in fields requiring making rational decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hope-high-order-polynomial-expansion-of-black</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEAR: Augmenting Language Models with Generalizable and Efficient Tool Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gear-augmenting-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GEAR achieves better efficiency by delegating tool grounding and execution to small language models (SLM) and LLM, respectively; while leveraging semantic and pattern-based evaluation at both question and answer levels for generalizable tool grounding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gear-augmenting-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast model inference and training on-board of Satellites</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-model-inference-and-training-on-board-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we demonstrate the reliable use of RaVAEn onboard a satellite, achieving an encoding time of 0. 110s for tiles of a 4. 8x4. 8 km$^2$ area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-model-inference-and-training-on-board-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scale-Aware Modulation Meet Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-aware-modulation-meet-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, SMT with 11. 5M / 2. 4GFLOPs and 32M / 7. 7GFLOPs can achieve 82. 2% and 84. 3% top-1 accuracy on ImageNet-1K, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-aware-modulation-meet-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Did the President Visit Last Week? Detecting Celebrity Trips from News Articles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/where-did-the-president-visit-last-week</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although news articles contain travel information of celebrities, it is not possible to perform large-scale and network-wise analysis due to the lack of automatic itinerary detection tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/where-did-the-president-visit-last-week</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVDFormer: Complementing Point Cloud via Self-view Augmentation and Self-structure Dual-generator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svdformer-complementing-point-cloud-via-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel network, SVDFormer, to tackle two specific challenges in point cloud completion: understanding faithful global shapes from incomplete point clouds and generating high-accuracy local structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svdformer-complementing-point-cloud-via-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A mixed policy to improve performance of language models on math problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mixed-policy-to-improve-performance-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering math problems are deterministic, we propose a mixed policy exploration approach to solve math problems with reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mixed-policy-to-improve-performance-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retentive Network: A Successor to Transformer for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retentive-network-a-successor-to-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose Retentive Network (RetNet) as a foundation architecture for large language models, simultaneously achieving training parallelism, low-cost inference, and good performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retentive-network-a-successor-to-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Objective Optimization of Performance and Interpretability of Tabular Supervised Machine Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-optimization-of-performance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficient optimization is achieved via augmentation of the search space of the learning algorithm by incorporating feature selection, interaction and monotonicity constraints into the hyperparameter search space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-optimization-of-performance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBMLtoODEjax: efficient simulation and optimization of ODE SBML models in JAX</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sbmltoodejax-efficient-simulation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Developing methods to explore, predict and control the dynamic behavior of biological systems, from protein pathways to complex cellular processes, is an essential frontier of research for bioengineering and biomedicine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sbmltoodejax-efficient-simulation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Item Global Residual Value for Fair Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-item-global-residual-value-for-fair</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we call for a shift of attention from modeling user preferences to developing fair exposure mechanisms for items.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-item-global-residual-value-for-fair</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deficiency-Aware Masked Transformer for Video Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deficiency-aware-masked-transformer-for-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we pretrain a image inpainting model DMT_img serve as a prior for distilling the video model DMT_vid, thereby benefiting the hallucination of deficiency cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deficiency-aware-masked-transformer-for-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not All Steps are Created Equal: Selective Diffusion Distillation for Image Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-steps-are-created-equal-selective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conditional diffusion models have demonstrated impressive performance in image manipulation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-steps-are-created-equal-selective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Video Depth Stabilizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-video-depth-stabilizer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video depth estimation aims to infer temporally consistent depth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-video-depth-stabilizer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Box-DETR: Understanding and Boxing Conditional Spatial Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/box-detr-understanding-and-boxing-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In DAB-DETR, such queries are modulated by the so-called conditional linear projection at each decoder stage, aiming to search for positions of interest such as the four extremities of the box.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/box-detr-understanding-and-boxing-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Local Basis Functions for Shape Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-local-basis-functions-for-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantitative and qualitative experiments demonstrate that our method outperforms the state-of-the-art methods in shape completion, detail preservation, generalization to unseen geometries, and computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-local-basis-functions-for-shape</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Counting from Self-Collages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-counting-from-self-collages</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While recent supervised methods for reference-based object counting continue to improve the performance on benchmark datasets, they have to rely on small datasets due to the cost associated with manually annotating dozens of objects in images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-counting-from-self-collages</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classification with Incoherent Kernel Dictionary Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classification-with-incoherent-kernel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present a new classification method based on Dictionary Learning (DL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classification-with-incoherent-kernel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Image Harmonization with Generative Model Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-image-harmonization-with-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, in the harmonization process, a human mainly utilizes his long-term prior on harmonious images and makes a composite image close to that prior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-image-harmonization-with-generative</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
