<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 21:06:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CASE: Commonsense-Augmented Score with an Expanded Answer Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/case-commonsense-augmented-score-with-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the major limitations of the basic score is that it treats all words as equally important.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/case-commonsense-augmented-score-with-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calibrate and Boost Logical Expressiveness of GNN Over Multi-Relational and Temporal Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrate-and-boost-logical-expressiveness-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we extend our analysis of expressiveness and graph transformation to temporal graphs, exploring several temporal GNN architectures and providing an expressiveness hierarchy for them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrate-and-boost-logical-expressiveness-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>inkn'hue: Enhancing Manga Colorization from Multiple Priors with Alignment Multi-Encoder VAE</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inkn-hue-enhancing-manga-colorization-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, the desire to experience manga in vibrant colors has sparked the pursuit of manga colorization, a task of paramount significance for artists.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inkn-hue-enhancing-manga-colorization-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flow-Based Feature Fusion for Vehicle-Infrastructure Cooperative 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-based-feature-fusion-for-vehicle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues in vehicle-infrastructure cooperative 3D (VIC3D) object detection, we propose the Feature Flow Net (FFNet), a novel cooperative detection framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-based-feature-fusion-for-vehicle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FETV: A Benchmark for Fine-Grained Evaluation of Open-Domain Text-to-Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fetv-a-benchmark-for-fine-grained-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The multi-aspect categorization of FETV enables fine-grained analysis of the metrics' reliability in different scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fetv-a-benchmark-for-fine-grained-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$R^3$-NL2GQL: A Hybrid Models Approach for for Accuracy Enhancing and Hallucinations Mitigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-3-nl2gql-a-hybrid-models-approach-for-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While current NL2SQL tasks constructed using Foundation Models have achieved commendable results, their direct application to Natural Language to Graph Query Language (NL2GQL) tasks poses challenges due to the significant differences between GQL and SQL expressions, as well as the numerous types of GQL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-3-nl2gql-a-hybrid-models-approach-for-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PPTC Benchmark: Evaluating Large Language Models for PowerPoint Task Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pptc-benchmark-evaluating-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent evaluations of Large Language Models (LLMs) have centered around testing their zero-shot/few-shot capabilities for basic natural language tasks and their ability to translate instructions into tool APIs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pptc-benchmark-evaluating-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForecastPFN: Synthetically-Trained Zero-Shot Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecastpfn-synthetically-trained-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The vast majority of time-series forecasting approaches require a substantial training dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecastpfn-synthetically-trained-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flexible Error Mitigation of Quantum Processes with Data Augmentation Empowered Neural Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-error-mitigation-of-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks have shown their effectiveness in various tasks in the realm of quantum computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-error-mitigation-of-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EmojiLM: Modeling the New Emoji Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emojilm-modeling-the-new-emoji-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid development of the internet, online social media welcomes people with different backgrounds through its diverse content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emojilm-modeling-the-new-emoji-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indicative Summarization of Long Discussions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indicative-summarization-of-long-discussions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online forums encourage the exchange and discussion of different stances on many topics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indicative-summarization-of-long-discussions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Image Segmentation with Domain Adaptation: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-image-segmentation-with-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our goal was to provide researchers with up-to-date references on the applications of domain adaptation in medical image segmentation studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-image-segmentation-with-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constructing Temporal Dynamic Knowledge Graphs from Interactive Text-based Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-temporal-dynamic-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to address DGU's weaknesses while preserving its high interpretability, we propose the Temporal Discrete Graph Updater (TDGU), a novel neural network model that represents dynamic knowledge graphs as a sequence of timestamped graph events and models them using a temporal point based graph neural network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-temporal-dynamic-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RiskQ: Risk-sensitive Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning Value Factorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/riskq-risk-sensitive-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-agent systems are characterized by environmental uncertainty, varying policies of agents, and partial observability, which result in significant risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/riskq-risk-sensitive-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Korean Text Classification Benchmark for Recognizing the Political Intents in Online Newspapers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-korean-text-classification-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we focus on automatically recognizing the political intents of a given online newspaper by understanding the context of the text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-korean-text-classification-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixCon3D: Synergizing Multi-View and Cross-Modal Contrastive Learning for Enhancing 3D Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixcon3d-synergizing-multi-view-and-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive learning has emerged as a promising paradigm for 3D open-world understanding, jointly with text, image, and point cloud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixcon3d-synergizing-multi-view-and-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Transformer Blocks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-transformer-blocks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A simple design recipe for deep Transformers is to compose identical building blocks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-transformer-blocks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Learning-Based Species Range Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-based-species-range</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results demonstrate that our method outperforms alternative active learning methods and approaches the performance of end-to-end trained models, even when only using a fraction of the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-based-species-range</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AFPQ: Asymmetric Floating Point Quantization for LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/afpq-asymmetric-floating-point-quantization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) show great performance in various tasks, but face deployment challenges from limited memory capacity and bandwidth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/afpq-asymmetric-floating-point-quantization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXIM: A Hybrid Explicit-Implicit Representation for Text-Guided 3D Shape Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exim-a-hybrid-explicit-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new text-guided technique for generating 3D shapes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exim-a-hybrid-explicit-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum circuit synthesis with diffusion models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-circuit-synthesis-with-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model excels at generating new circuits and supports typical DM extensions such as masking and editing to, for instance, align the circuit generation to the constraints of the targeted quantum device.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-circuit-synthesis-with-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models Illuminate a Progressive Pathway to Artificial Healthcare Assistant: A Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-illuminate-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This has sparked significant interest in applying LLMs to enhance various aspects of healthcare, ranging from medical education to clinical decision support.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-illuminate-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Generalization Properties of Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-generalization-properties-of-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This precisely elucidates the adverse effect of "modes shift" in ground truths on the model generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-generalization-properties-of-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous federated collaborative filtering using FAIR: Federated Averaging in Random Subspaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-federated-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To include data from all devices in federated learning, we must enable collective training of embedding tables on devices with heterogeneous memory capacities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-federated-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grounded Intuition of GPT-Vision's Abilities with Scientific Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounded-intuition-of-gpt-vision-s-abilities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GPT-Vision has impressed us on a range of vision-language tasks, but it comes with the familiar new challenge: we have little idea of its capabilities and limitations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounded-intuition-of-gpt-vision-s-abilities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaboration and Transition: Distilling Item Transitions into Multi-Query Self-Attention for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaboration-and-transition-distilling-item</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we develop a transition-aware embedding distillation module that distills global item-to-item transition patterns into item embeddings, which enables the model to memorize and leverage transitional signals and serves as a calibrator for collaborative signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaboration-and-transition-distilling-item</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Multimodal Information Bottleneck for Multimodality Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-multimodal-information-bottleneck-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our information bottleneck module serves to filter out the task-irrelevant information and noises in the fused feature, and we further introduce a sufficiency loss to prevent dropping of task-relevant information, thus explicitly preserving the sufficiency of prediction information in the distilled feature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-multimodal-information-bottleneck-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sim2Real Bilevel Adaptation for Object Surface Classification using Vision-Based Tactile Sensors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim2real-bilevel-adaptation-for-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our evaluation is conducted on a dataset of tactile images obtained from a set of ten 3D printed YCB objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim2real-bilevel-adaptation-for-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision-Language Interpreter for Robot Task Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-language-interpreter-for-robot-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The aim is to generate a problem description (PD), a machine-readable file used by the planners to find a plan.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-language-interpreter-for-robot-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Models for Reinforcement Learning: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-for-reinforcement-learning-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have emerged as a prominent class of generative models, surpassing previous methods regarding sample quality and training stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-for-reinforcement-learning-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Relation Learning for Cross-domain Few-shot Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-relation-learning-for-cross-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, it adopts a transformer based cross-attention learning module to learn the set-level sample relations and acquire the attentions from query samples to support samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-relation-learning-for-cross-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InsPLAD: A Dataset and Benchmark for Power Line Asset Inspection in UAV Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insplad-a-dataset-and-benchmark-for-power</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, InsPLAD is the first large real-world dataset and benchmark for power line asset inspection with multiple components and defects for various computer vision tasks, with a potential impact to improve state-of-the-art methods in the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insplad-a-dataset-and-benchmark-for-power</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RTP: Rethinking Tensor Parallelism with Memory Deduplication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rtp-rethinking-tensor-parallelism-with-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the evolving landscape of neural network models, one prominent challenge stand out: the significant memory overheads associated with training expansive models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rtp-rethinking-tensor-parallelism-with-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AeroPath: An airway segmentation benchmark dataset with challenging pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aeropath-an-airway-segmentation-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce a new public benchmark dataset (AeroPath), consisting of 27 CT images from patients with pathologies ranging from emphysema to large tumors, with corresponding trachea and bronchi annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aeropath-an-airway-segmentation-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invariant-Feature Subspace Recovery: A New Class of Provable Domain Generalization Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-feature-subspace-recovery-a-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, in the binary classification setup of Rosenfeld et al. (2021), we show that our first algorithm, ISR-Mean, can identify the subspace spanned by invariant features from the first-order moments of the class-conditional distributions, and achieve provable domain generalization with $d_s+1$ training environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-feature-subspace-recovery-a-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning A Multi-Task Transformer Via Unified And Customized Instruction Tuning For Chest Radiograph Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-multi-task-transformer-via-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first compose a multi-task training dataset comprising 13. 4 million instruction and ground-truth pairs (with approximately one million radiographs) for the customized tuning, involving both image- and pixel-level tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-multi-task-transformer-via-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Information-Guided Network using Contrastive Learning for Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-information-guided-network-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we first incorporate the projected images from the point clouds and fuse the cross-modal features using the attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-information-guided-network-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating QM1B with PySCF$_{\text{IPU}}$</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-qm1b-with-pyscf-text-ipu</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Similar benefits are yet to be unlocked for quantum chemistry, where the potential of deep learning is constrained by comparatively small datasets with 100k to 20M training examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-qm1b-with-pyscf-text-ipu</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention based Dual-Branch Complex Feature Fusion Network for Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-based-dual-branch-complex-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental evidence show that SE block improves the models overall accuracy by almost 1\%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-based-dual-branch-complex-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling Out-of-Distribution Robustness from Vision-Language Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-out-of-distribution-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a conceptually simple and lightweight framework for improving the robustness of vision models through the combination of knowledge distillation and data augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-out-of-distribution-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distance-Based Propagation for Efficient Knowledge Graph Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-based-propagation-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A new class of methods have been proposed to tackle this problem by aggregating path information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-based-propagation-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Robustness via Tilted Exponential Layer: A Communication-Theoretic Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-robustness-via-tilted-exponential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art techniques for enhancing robustness of deep networks mostly rely on empirical risk minimization with suitable data augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-robustness-via-tilted-exponential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Chain of Thought Reasoning via Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-chain-of-thought-reasoning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore an alternative reasoning approach: instead of explicitly producing the chain of thought reasoning steps, we use the language model's internal hidden states to perform implicit reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-chain-of-thought-reasoning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Series Anomaly Detection using Diffusion-based Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-anomaly-detection-using-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our models outperform the baselines on synthetic datasets and are competitive on real-world datasets, illustrating the potential of diffusion-based methods for AD in multivariate time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-anomaly-detection-using-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task-Agnostic Low-Rank Adapters for Unseen English Dialects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-agnostic-low-rank-adapters-for-unseen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are trained on corpora disproportionally weighted in favor of Standard American English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-agnostic-low-rank-adapters-for-unseen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TopicGPT: A Prompt-based Topic Modeling Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topicgpt-a-prompt-based-topic-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topic modeling is a well-established technique for exploring text corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topicgpt-a-prompt-based-topic-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combating Bilateral Edge Noise for Robust Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combating-bilateral-edge-noise-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this dilemma, we propose an information-theory-guided principle, Robust Graph Information Bottleneck (RGIB), to extract reliable supervision signals and avoid representation collapse.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combating-bilateral-edge-noise-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invariant Causal Imitation Learning for Generalizable Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-causal-imitation-learning-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By leveraging data from multiple environments, we propose Invariant Causal Imitation Learning (ICIL), a novel technique in which we learn a feature representation that is invariant across domains, on the basis of which we learn an imitation policy that matches expert behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-causal-imitation-learning-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resilient Multiple Choice Learning: A learned scoring scheme with application to audio scene analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resilient-multiple-choice-learning-a-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiple Choice Learning is a simple framework to tackle multimodal density estimation, using the Winner-Takes-All (WTA) loss for a set of hypotheses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resilient-multiple-choice-learning-a-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Act As You Wish: Fine-Grained Control of Motion Diffusion Model with Hierarchical Semantic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/act-as-you-wish-fine-grained-control-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these compact text representations may overemphasize the action names at the expense of other important properties and lack fine-grained details to guide the synthesis of subtly distinct motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/act-as-you-wish-fine-grained-control-of</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
