<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 21:06:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Affective Faces for Goal-Driven Dyadic Communication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affective-faces-for-goal-driven-dyadic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a video framework for modeling the association between verbal and non-verbal communication during dyadic conversation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affective-faces-for-goal-driven-dyadic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A benchmark for toxic comment classification on Civil Comments dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-toxic-comment-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BiLSTM remains a good compromise between performance and inference time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-toxic-comment-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which Experiences Are Influential for Your Agent? Policy Iteration with Turn-over Dropout</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/which-experiences-are-influential-for-your</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In reinforcement learning (RL) with experience replay, experiences stored in a replay buffer influence the RL agent's performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/which-experiences-are-influential-for-your</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Problems in Applied Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-problems-in-applied-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work formulates the machine learning mechanism as a bi-level optimization problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-problems-in-applied-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trajectory-Aware Eligibility Traces for Off-Policy Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajectory-aware-eligibility-traces-for-off</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Off-policy learning from multistep returns is crucial for sample-efficient reinforcement learning, but counteracting off-policy bias without exacerbating variance is challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajectory-aware-eligibility-traces-for-off</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftMatch: Addressing the Quantity-Quality Trade-off in Semi-supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softmatch-addressing-the-quantity-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The critical challenge of Semi-Supervised Learning (SSL) is how to effectively leverage the limited labeled data and massive unlabeled data to improve the model's generalization performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softmatch-addressing-the-quantity-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-based Recommendation for Sparse and Heterogeneous User Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-recommendation-for-sparse-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a graph-based recommender model which utilizes heterogeneous interactions between users and content of different types and is able to operate well on small-scale datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-recommendation-for-sparse-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoRaLay: A Multilingual and Multimodal Dataset for Long Range and Layout-Aware Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loralay-a-multilingual-and-multimodal-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text Summarization is a popular task and an active area of research for the Natural Language Processing community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loralay-a-multilingual-and-multimodal-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Regions of Counterfactual Explanations via Robust Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-regions-of-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, our method provides a whole region of CEs allowing the user to choose a suitable recourse to obtain a desired outcome.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-regions-of-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Molecular Language Model as Multi-task Generator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-language-model-as-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further propose multi-task molecular prefix tuning across several molecular generation tasks and different molecular domains (synthetic & natural products) with a self-feedback mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-language-model-as-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Temporal Modeling for CLIP-based Image-to-Video Knowledge Transferring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-temporal-modeling-for-clip-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, based on the CLIP model, we revisit temporal modeling in the context of image-to-video knowledge transferring, which is the key point for extending image-text pretrained models to the video domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-temporal-modeling-for-clip-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WL meet VC</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wl-meet-vc</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, when an upper bound on the graphs' order is known, we show a tight connection between the number of graphs distinguishable by the $1\text{-}\mathsf{WL}$ and GNNs' VC dimension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wl-meet-vc</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-step interpretable modeling of Intensive Care Acquired Infections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-step-interpretable-modeling-of-intensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel methodology for integrating high resolution longitudinal data with the dynamic prediction capabilities of survival models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-step-interpretable-modeling-of-intensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Systematic Review of Green AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-review-of-green-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a conclusion, the Green AI research field results to have reached a considerable level of maturity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-review-of-green-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Train Hard, Fight Easy: Robust Meta Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/train-hard-fight-easy-robust-meta</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that the former disappears in MRL, and address the latter via the novel Robust Meta RL algorithm (RoML).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/train-hard-fight-easy-robust-meta</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Planning as Heuristic Search: A new planning search-space that leverages pointers over objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-planning-as-heuristic-search-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, the paper introduces a new pointer-based solution space for GP that is independent of the number of classical planning instances in a GP problem and the size of those instances (i. e. the number of objects, state variables and their domain sizes).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-planning-as-heuristic-search-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Reasoning of Entities and Events in Procedural Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-reasoning-of-entities-and-events-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entities and events have long been regarded as the crux of machine reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-reasoning-of-entities-and-events-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemSup-XC: Semantic Supervision for Zero and Few-shot Extreme Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semsup-xc-semantic-supervision-for-zero-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we develop SemSup-XC, a model that achieves state-of-the-art zero-shot and few-shot performance on three XC datasets derived from legal, e-commerce, and Wikipedia data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semsup-xc-semantic-supervision-for-zero-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling Cognitive Backdoor Patterns within an Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-cognitive-backdoor-patterns-within</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct extensive experiments to show that CD can robustly detect a wide range of advanced backdoor attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-cognitive-backdoor-patterns-within</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compact Transformer Tracker with Correlative Masked Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-transformer-tracker-with-correlative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer framework has been showing superior performances in visual object tracking for its great strength in information aggregation across the template and search image with the well-known attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-transformer-tracker-with-correlative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cut and Learn for Unsupervised Object Detection and Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cut-and-learn-for-unsupervised-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Cut-and-LEaRn (CutLER), a simple approach for training unsupervised object detection and segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cut-and-learn-for-unsupervised-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Box$^2$EL: Concept and Role Box Embeddings for the Description Logic EL++</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/box-2-el-concept-and-role-box-embeddings-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representation learning in the form of semantic embeddings has been successfully applied to a variety of tasks in natural language processing and knowledge graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/box-2-el-concept-and-role-box-embeddings-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Building Changes with Off-Nadir Aerial Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-building-changes-with-off-nadir</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The tilted viewing nature of the off-nadir aerial images brings severe challenges to the building change detection (BCD) problem: the mismatch of the nearby buildings and the semantic ambiguity of the building facades.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-building-changes-with-off-nadir</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Contrastive Learning for Skeleton-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-contrastive-learning-for-skeleton-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a graph contrastive learning framework for skeleton-based action recognition (\textit{SkeletonGCL}) to explore the \textit{global} context across all sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-contrastive-learning-for-skeleton-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Multiple Independent Advisors in Multi-agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-multiple-independent-advisors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper considers the problem of simultaneously learning from multiple independent advisors in multi-agent reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-multiple-independent-advisors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Projection-Enhancement Network (PEN)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-projection-enhancement-network-pen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contemporary approaches to instance segmentation in cell science use 2D or 3D convolutional networks depending on the experiment and data structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-projection-enhancement-network-pen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Medical Image Segmentation with TransCeption: A Multi-Scale Feature Fusion Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-medical-image-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(3) In contrast to a bridge that only contains token-wise self-attention, we propose a Dual Transformer Bridge that also includes channel-wise self-attention to exploit correlations between scales at different stages from a dual perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-medical-image-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce CausalAI Library: A Fast and Scalable Framework for Causal Analysis of Time Series and Tabular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salesforce-causalai-library-a-fast-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Salesforce CausalAI Library, an open-source library for causal analysis using observational data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salesforce-causalai-library-a-fast-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEJA VU: Continual Model Generalization For Unseen Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deja-vu-continual-model-generalization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations of DA and DG in handling the Unfamiliar Period during continual domain shift, we propose RaTP, a framework that focuses on improving models' target domain generalization (TDG) capability, while also achieving effective target domain adaptation (TDA) capability right after training on certain domains and forgetting alleviation (FA) capability on past domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deja-vu-continual-model-generalization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Clinical Trials Puzzle: How Network Effects Limit Drug Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-clinical-trials-puzzle-how-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The depth of knowledge offered by post-genomic medicine has carried the promise of new drugs, and cures for multiple diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-clinical-trials-puzzle-how-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Model for All Domains: Collaborative Domain-Prefix Tuning for Cross-Domain NER</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-model-for-all-domains-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous typical solutions mainly obtain a NER model by pre-trained language models (PLMs) with data from a rich-resource domain and adapt it to the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-model-for-all-domains-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Editing Language Model-based Knowledge Graph Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editing-language-model-based-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We build four new datasets: E-FB15k237, A-FB15k237, E-WN18RR, and A-WN18RR, and evaluate several knowledge editing baselines demonstrating the limited ability of previous models to handle the proposed challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editing-language-model-based-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Selection: Key to Enhance Node Classification with Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-selection-key-to-enhance-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graphs help to define the relationships between entities in the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-selection-key-to-enhance-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExaRanker: Explanation-Augmented Neural Ranker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exaranker-explanation-augmented-neural-ranker</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work has shown that inducing a large language model (LLM) to generate explanations prior to outputting an answer is an effective strategy to improve performance on a wide range of reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exaranker-explanation-augmented-neural-ranker</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Learning in Deep Learning Models for Building Load Forecasting: Case of Limited Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-in-deep-learning-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to adapt Deep Learning models for buildings with limited and scarce data, this paper proposes a Building-to-Building Transfer Learning framework to overcome the problem and enhance the performance of Deep Learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-in-deep-learning-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Tooth Mesh Segmentation with Simplified Mesh Cell Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-tooth-mesh-segmentation-with-simplified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Summarizing of the mesh cell/triangle in this manner imposes an implicit structural constraint and makes it difficult to work with multiple resolutions which is done in many point cloud based deep learning algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-tooth-mesh-segmentation-with-simplified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWING: Balancing Coverage and Faithfulness for Dialogue Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swing-balancing-coverage-and-faithfulness-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing information is a common issue of dialogue summarization where some information in the reference summaries is not covered in the generated summaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swing-balancing-coverage-and-faithfulness-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Consistent Deep Rigid MRI Motion Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-consistent-deep-rigid-mri-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motion artifacts are a pervasive problem in MRI, leading to misdiagnosis or mischaracterization in population-level imaging studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-consistent-deep-rigid-mri-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Graph Generation by Restricting Graph Bandwidth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-graph-generation-by-restricting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, one of the main limitations of existing methods is their large output space, which limits generation scalability and hinders accurate modeling of the underlying distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-graph-generation-by-restricting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Efficient Approximate Method for Online Convolutional Dictionary Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-approximate-method-for-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing convolutional dictionary learning (CDL) algorithms are based on batch learning, where the dictionary filters and the convolutional sparse representations are optimized in an alternating manner using a training dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-approximate-method-for-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated multilingual detection of Pro-Kremlin propaganda in newspapers and Telegram posts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-multilingual-detection-of-pro</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The full-scale conflict between the Russian Federation and Ukraine generated an unprecedented amount of news articles and social media data reflecting opposing ideologies and narratives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-multilingual-detection-of-pro</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLPGradientFlow: going with the flow of multilayer perceptrons (and finding minima fast and accurately)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlpgradientflow-going-with-the-flow-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MLPGradientFlow is a software package to solve numerically the gradient flow differential equation $\dot \theta = -\nabla \mathcal L(\theta; \mathcal D)$, where $\theta$ are the parameters of a multi-layer perceptron, $\mathcal D$ is some data set, and $\nabla \mathcal L$ is the gradient of a loss function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlpgradientflow-going-with-the-flow-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exact and rapid linear clustering of networks with dynamic programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-and-rapid-linear-clustering-of-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of clustering networks whose nodes have imputed or physical positions in a single dimension, such as prestige hierarchies or the similarity dimension of hyperbolic embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-and-rapid-linear-clustering-of-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Layers Play the Lottery, all Tickets Win at Initialization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-layers-play-the-lottery-all-tickets-win</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate LTH and pruning at initialization from the lens of layer pruning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-layers-play-the-lottery-all-tickets-win</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal decision making in robotic assembly and other trial-and-error tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-decision-making-in-robotic-assembly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Uncertainty in perception, actuation, and the environment often require multiple attempts for a robotic task to be successful.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-decision-making-in-robotic-assembly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Tenant Optimization For Few-Shot Task-Oriented FAQ Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-tenant-optimization-for-few-shot-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Business-specific Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ) retrieval in task-oriented dialog systems poses unique challenges vis-\`a-vis community based FAQs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-tenant-optimization-for-few-shot-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster DAN: Multi-target Queries with Document Positional Encoding for End-to-end Handwritten Document Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-dan-multi-target-queries-with-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in handwritten text recognition enabled to recognize whole documents in an end-to-end way: the Document Attention Network (DAN) recognizes the characters one after the other through an attention-based prediction process until reaching the end of the document.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-dan-multi-target-queries-with-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViDeBERTa: A powerful pre-trained language model for Vietnamese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videberta-a-powerful-pre-trained-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents ViDeBERTa, a new pre-trained monolingual language model for Vietnamese, with three versions - ViDeBERTa_xsmall, ViDeBERTa_base, and ViDeBERTa_large, which are pre-trained on a large-scale corpus of high-quality and diverse Vietnamese texts using DeBERTa architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videberta-a-powerful-pre-trained-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E(n)-equivariant Graph Neural Cellular Automata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-n-equivariant-graph-neural-cellular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cellular automata (CAs) are computational models exhibiting rich dynamics emerging from the local interaction of cells arranged in a regular lattice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-n-equivariant-graph-neural-cellular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recursive deep learning framework for forecasting the decadal world economic outlook</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recursive-deep-learning-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the diversity and complexity of the world economy, a wide range of models have been used, but there are challenges in making decadal GDP forecasts given unexpected changes such as pandemics and wars.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recursive-deep-learning-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
