<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 09:12:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Goal-oriented Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goal-oriented-autonomous-driving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern autonomous driving system is characterized as modular tasks in sequential order, i. e., perception, prediction and planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goal-oriented-autonomous-driving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interleaving Retrieval with Chain-of-Thought Reasoning for Knowledge-Intensive Multi-Step Questions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interleaving-retrieval-with-chain-of-thought</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is insufficient, however, when the necessary knowledge is not available or up-to-date within a model's parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interleaving-retrieval-with-chain-of-thought</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BMX: Boosting Machine Translation Metrics with Explainability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bmx-boosting-machine-translation-metrics-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, recent works consider their explainability with the goals of better understandability for humans and better metric analysis, including failure cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bmx-boosting-machine-translation-metrics-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which Pixel to Annotate: a Label-Efficient Nuclei Segmentation Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/which-pixel-to-annotate-a-label-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently deep neural networks, which require a large amount of annotated samples, have been widely applied in nuclei instance segmentation of H\&E stained pathology images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/which-pixel-to-annotate-a-label-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precise Zero-Shot Dense Retrieval without Relevance Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precise-zero-shot-dense-retrieval-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a query, HyDE first zero-shot instructs an instruction-following language model (e. g. InstructGPT) to generate a hypothetical document.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precise-zero-shot-dense-retrieval-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Improving Summarization Factual Consistency from Natural Language Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-improving-summarization-factual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study whether informational feedback in natural language can be leveraged to improve generation quality and user preference alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-improving-summarization-factual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperBO+: Pre-training a universal prior for Bayesian optimization with hierarchical Gaussian processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbo-pre-training-a-universal-prior-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, those prior learning methods typically assume that the input domains are the same for all tasks, weakening their ability to use observations on functions with different domains or generalize the learned priors to BO on different search spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbo-pre-training-a-universal-prior-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReCode: Robustness Evaluation of Code Generation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recode-robustness-evaluation-of-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing works on robustness in text or code tasks have focused on classification, while robustness in generation tasks is an uncharted area and to date there is no comprehensive benchmark for robustness in code generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recode-robustness-evaluation-of-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Image Classification using Hierarchical Data Learning with Weighted Sampling and Label Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galaxy-image-classification-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the development of a series of Galaxy sky surveys in recent years, the observations increased rapidly, which makes the research of machine learning methods for galaxy image recognition a hot topic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galaxy-image-classification-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Federated Learning Meets Pre-trained Language Models' Parameter-Efficient Tuning Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-federated-learning-meets-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate the research of PETuning in FL, we also develop a federated tuning framework FedPETuning, which allows practitioners to exploit different PETuning methods under the FL training paradigm conveniently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-federated-learning-meets-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insights into undergraduate pathways using course load analytics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insights-into-undergraduate-pathways-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Course load analytics (CLA) inferred from LMS and enrollment features can offer a more accurate representation of course workload to students than credit hours and potentially aid in their course selection decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insights-into-undergraduate-pathways-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Reasoning in Large Language Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-reasoning-in-large-language-models-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reasoning is a fundamental aspect of human intelligence that plays a crucial role in activities such as problem solving, decision making, and critical thinking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-reasoning-in-large-language-models-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robustness of Text-to-SQL Models Against Natural and Realistic Adversarial Table Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robustness-of-text-to-sql-models-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The robustness of Text-to-SQL parsers against adversarial perturbations plays a crucial role in delivering highly reliable applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robustness-of-text-to-sql-models-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Machine Learning to Determine Morphologies of $z&lt;1$ AGN Host Galaxies in the Hyper Suprime-Cam Wide Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-machine-learning-to-determine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The classification precision of our models has a noticeable dependency on host galaxy radius and magnitude.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-machine-learning-to-determine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DimonGen: Diversified Generative Commonsense Reasoning for Explaining Concept Relationships</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dimongen-diversified-generative-commonsense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose DimonGen, which aims to generate diverse sentences describing concept relationships in various everyday scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dimongen-diversified-generative-commonsense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Inference for Knowledge Graph based Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-inference-for-knowledge-graph-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Graph (KG), as a side-information, tends to be utilized to supplement the collaborative filtering (CF) based recommendation model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-inference-for-knowledge-graph-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Not to Trust Language Models: Investigating Effectiveness and Limitations of Parametric and Non-Parametric Memories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-not-to-trust-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their impressive performance on diverse tasks, large language models (LMs) still struggle with tasks requiring rich world knowledge, implying the limitations of relying solely on their parameters to encode a wealth of world knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-not-to-trust-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking person re-identification datasets and approaches for practical real-world implementations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-person-re-identification-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, Person Re-Identification (Re-ID) has received a lot of attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-person-re-identification-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-trained Language Models for Keyphrase Generation: A Thorough Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-trained-language-models-for-keyphrase</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, there lacks a systematic study of how the two types of approaches compare and how different design choices can affect the performance of PLM-based models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-trained-language-models-for-keyphrase</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Instruct: Aligning Language Model with Self Generated Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-instruct-aligning-language-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applying our method to vanilla GPT3, we demonstrate a 33% absolute improvement over the original model on Super-NaturalInstructions, on par with the performance of InstructGPT_001, which is trained with private user data and human annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-instruct-aligning-language-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>True Detective: A Challenging Benchmark for Deep Abductive Reasoning \\in Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/true-detective-a-challenging-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work provides a challenging benchmark for future studies on reasoning in language models and contributes to a better understanding of the limits of LLMs' abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/true-detective-a-challenging-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Understanding Chain-of-Thought Prompting: An Empirical Study of What Matters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-understanding-chain-of-thought</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chain-of-Thought (CoT) prompting can dramatically improve the multi-step reasoning abilities of large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-understanding-chain-of-thought</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparison Between Tsetlin Machines and Deep Neural Networks in the Context of Recommendation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-between-tsetlin-machines-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These comparisons are based on model performance, interpretability/explainability, and scalability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-between-tsetlin-machines-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOC: Improving Long Story Coherence With Detailed Outline Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doc-improving-long-story-coherence-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In human evaluations of automatically generated stories, DOC substantially outperforms a strong Re3 baseline (Yang et al., 2022) on plot coherence (22. 5% absolute gain), outline relevance (28. 2%), and interestingness (20. 7%).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doc-improving-long-story-coherence-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing the Power of Visual Prompting At the Pixel Level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-power-of-visual-prompting-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a simple and effective visual prompting method for adapting pre-trained models to downstream recognition tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-power-of-visual-prompting-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Pair: Synthesizing Changes from Single Source for Object Change Detection in Remote Sensing Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-pair-synthesizing-changes-from-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For change detection in remote sensing, constructing a training dataset for deep learning models is difficult due to the requirements of bi-temporal supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-pair-synthesizing-changes-from-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Human Eye Movements with Neural Networks in a Maze-Solving Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-human-eye-movements-with-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This not only provides a generative model of eye movements in this task but also suggests a computational theory for how humans solve the task, namely that humans use mental simulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-human-eye-movements-with-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Factorization Machines for Preference Elicitation in Large-Scale Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-factorization-machines-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Factorization machines (FMs) are a powerful tool for regression and classification in the context of sparse observations, that has been successfully applied to collaborative filtering, especially when side information over users or items is available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-factorization-machines-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward a Unified Framework for Unsupervised Complex Tabular Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-a-unified-framework-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge the gap between the programs and natural language sentences, we design a powerful "NL-Generator" module to generate natural language sentences with complex logic from these programs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-a-unified-framework-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models Are Reasoning Teachers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-reasoning-teachers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Fine-tune-CoT, a method that leverages the capabilities of very large LMs to generate reasoning samples and teach smaller models via fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-reasoning-teachers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-adaptive In-context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-adaptive-in-context-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the surprising few-shot performance of in-context learning (ICL), it is still a common practice to randomly sample examples to serve as context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-adaptive-in-context-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks in Computer Vision -- Architectures, Datasets and Common Approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-in-computer-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we investigate the architectures of Graph Neural Networks and their derivatives used in this area to provide accurate and explainable recommendations for the ensuing investigations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-in-computer-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Challenges of Open Domain Multi-Document Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-challenges-of-open-domain-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-document summarization (MDS) has traditionally been studied assuming a set of ground-truth topic-related input documents is provided.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-challenges-of-open-domain-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADAS: A Simple Active-and-Adaptive Baseline for Cross-Domain 3D Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adas-a-simple-active-and-adaptive-baseline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art 3D semantic segmentation models are trained on the off-the-shelf public benchmarks, but they often face the major challenge when these well-trained models are deployed to a new domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adas-a-simple-active-and-adaptive-baseline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Decades Progress on Code-Switching Research in NLP: A Systematic Survey on Trends and Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-decades-progress-on-code-switching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Code-Switching, a common phenomenon in written text and conversation, has been studied over decades by the natural language processing (NLP) research community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-decades-progress-on-code-switching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Label Smoothing on Multi-hop Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-label-smoothing-on-multi-hop</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Label smoothing is a regularization technique widely used in supervised learning to improve the generalization of models on various tasks, such as image classification and machine translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-label-smoothing-on-multi-hop</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning with Language Model Prompting: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-with-language-model-prompting-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reasoning, as an essential ability for complex problem-solving, can provide back-end support for various real-world applications, such as medical diagnosis, negotiation, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-with-language-model-prompting-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Sparse Network for Time Series Classification: Learning What to "see''</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-sparse-network-for-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The receptive field (RF), which determines the region of time series to be ``seen'' and used, is critical to improve the performance for time series classification (TSC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-sparse-network-for-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Object-level Point Augmentor for Semi-supervised 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-object-level-point-augmentor-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose an object-level point augmentor (OPA) that performs local transformations for semi-supervised 3D object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-object-level-point-augmentor-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visconde: Multi-document QA with GPT-3 and Neural Reranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visconde-multi-document-qa-with-gpt-3-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a question-answering system that can answer questions whose supporting evidence is spread over multiple (potentially long) documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visconde-multi-document-qa-with-gpt-3-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Prompts for Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-prompts-for-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of laborious human engineering, we propose prompt adaptation, a general framework that automatically adapts original user input to model-preferred prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-prompts-for-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photo-Realistic Out-of-domain GAN inversion via Invertibility Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/photo-realistic-out-of-domain-gan-inversion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel framework that enhances the fidelity of human face inversion by designing a new module to decompose the input images to ID and OOD partitions with invertibility masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/photo-realistic-out-of-domain-gan-inversion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Low Rank column-wise Compressive Sensing for Accelerated Dynamic MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-low-rank-column-wise-compressive-sensing-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This claim is based on comparisons on 8 different retrospectively under sampled multi-coil dynamic MRI applications, sampled using either 1D Cartesian or 2D pseudo radial under sampling, at multiple sampling rates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-low-rank-column-wise-compressive-sensing-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flowstorm: Open-Source Platform with Hybrid Dialogue Architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowstorm-open-source-platform-with-hybrid-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the essential features of the platform is the possibility to reuse the created assets across applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowstorm-open-source-platform-with-hybrid-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Human-Language Model Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-human-language-model-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many real-world applications of language models (LMs), such as code autocomplete and writing assistance, involve human-LM interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-human-language-model-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NusaCrowd: Open Source Initiative for Indonesian NLP Resources</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nusacrowd-open-source-initiative-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present NusaCrowd, a collaborative initiative to collect and unite existing resources for Indonesian languages, including opening access to previously non-public resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nusacrowd-open-source-initiative-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XEngine: Optimal Tensor Rematerialization for Neural Networks in Heterogeneous Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xengine-optimal-tensor-rematerialization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this, we formulate a mixed-integer quadratic program (MIQP) to schedule operators of deep learning networks on heterogeneous systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xengine-optimal-tensor-rematerialization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Training Dynamics: Identifying Mislabeled Data Beyond Manually Designed Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-training-dynamics-identifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While mislabeled or ambiguously-labeled samples in the training set could negatively affect the performance of deep models, diagnosing the dataset and identifying mislabeled samples helps to improve the generalization power.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-training-dynamics-identifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models are reasoners with Self-Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-reasoners-with-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new method called self-verification that uses the conclusion of the CoT as a condition to build a new sample and asks the LLM to re-predict the original conditions which be masked.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-reasoners-with-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Randomized Quantization for Data Agnostic Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randomized-quantization-for-data-agnostic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Towards this end, masking has emerged as a generic and powerful tool where content is withheld along the sequential dimension, e. g., spatial in images, temporal in audio, and syntactic in language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randomized-quantization-for-data-agnostic</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
