<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:06:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SFOD: Spiking Fusion Object Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfod-spiking-fusion-object-detector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thereby, we establish state-of-the-art classification results based on SNNs, achieving 93. 7\% accuracy on the NCAR dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfod-spiking-fusion-object-detector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IUST at ClimateActivism 2024: Towards Optimal Stance Detection: A Systematic Study of Architectural Choices and Data Cleaning Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iust-at-climateactivism-2024-towards-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents a systematic search of various model architecture configurations and data cleaning methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iust-at-climateactivism-2024-towards-optimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow Generation for Composite Image Using Diffusion model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadow-generation-for-composite-image-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of image composition, generating realistic shadow for the inserted foreground remains a formidable challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadow-generation-for-composite-image-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Model Ensemble Approach with LLM for Chinese Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-model-ensemble-approach-with-llm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic medical text categorization can assist doctors in efficiently managing patient information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-model-ensemble-approach-with-llm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniTraj: A Unified Framework for Scalable Vehicle Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitraj-a-unified-framework-for-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vehicle trajectory prediction has increasingly relied on data-driven solutions, but their ability to scale to different data domains and the impact of larger dataset sizes on their generalization remain under-explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitraj-a-unified-framework-for-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imagination Augmented Generation: Learning to Imagine Richer Context for Question Answering over Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagination-augmented-generation-learning-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-Augmented-Generation and Gener-ation-Augmented-Generation have been proposed to enhance the knowledge required for question answering over Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagination-augmented-generation-learning-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient-based Sampling for Class Imbalanced Semi-supervised Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-based-sampling-for-class-imbalanced-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle the confirmation bias from incorrect pseudo labels of minority classes, the class-rebalancing sampling module resamples unlabeled data following the guidance of the gradient-based reweighting module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-based-sampling-for-class-imbalanced-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternVideo2: Scaling Video Foundation Models for Multimodal Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internvideo2-scaling-video-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce InternVideo2, a new video foundation model (ViFM) that achieves the state-of-the-art performance in action recognition, video-text tasks, and video-centric dialogue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internvideo2-scaling-video-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOv5-6D: Advancing 6-DoF Instrument Pose Estimation in Variable X-Ray Imaging Geometries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov5-6d-advancing-6-dof-instrument-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a general-purpose approach of data acquisition for 6-DoF pose estimation tasks in X-ray systems, a novel and general purpose YOLOv5-6D pose architecture for accurate and fast object pose estimation and a complete method for surgical screw pose estimation under acquisition geometry consideration from a monocular cone-beam X-ray image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov5-6d-advancing-6-dof-instrument-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DomainLab: A modular Python package for domain generalization in deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domainlab-a-modular-python-package-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DomainLab is a modular Python package for training user specified neural networks with composable regularization loss terms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domainlab-a-modular-python-package-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View-decoupled Transformer for Person Re-identification under Aerial-ground Camera Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/view-decoupled-transformer-for-person-re</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on two datasets show that VDT is a feasible and effective solution for AGPReID, surpassing the previous method on mAP/Rank1 by up to 5. 0%/2. 7% on CARGO and 3. 7%/5. 2% on AG-ReID, keeping the same magnitude of computational complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/view-decoupled-transformer-for-person-re</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChainLM: Empowering Large Language Models with Improved Chain-of-Thought Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chainlm-empowering-large-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response to this challenge, we present an empirical investigation of CoT prompting and introduce CoTGenius, a novel framework designed for the automatic generation of superior CoT prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chainlm-empowering-large-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAC: Hash-grid Assisted Context for 3D Gaussian Splatting Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hac-hash-grid-assisted-context-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) has emerged as a promising framework for novel view synthesis, boasting rapid rendering speed with high fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hac-hash-grid-assisted-context-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSALM: Pixelwise SegmentAtion with Large Multi-Modal Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psalm-pixelwise-segmentation-with-large-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PSALM is a powerful extension of the Large Multi-modal Model (LMM) to address the segmentation task challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psalm-pixelwise-segmentation-with-large-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CombiNeRF: A Combination of Regularization Techniques for Few-Shot Neural Radiance Field View Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combinerf-a-combination-of-regularization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When dealing with few-shot settings, i. e. with a small set of input views, the training could overfit those views, leading to artifacts and geometric and chromatic inconsistencies in the resulting rendering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combinerf-a-combination-of-regularization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Vocabulary Attention Maps with Token Optimization for Semantic Segmentation in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-attention-maps-with-token</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach limits the generation of segmentation masks derived from word tokens not contained in the text prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-attention-maps-with-token</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising Diffusion Models for 3D Healthy Brain Tissue Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-models-for-3d-healthy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monitoring diseases that affect the brain's structural integrity requires automated analysis of magnetic resonance (MR) images, e. g., for the evaluation of volumetric changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-models-for-3d-healthy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Image Classification Accuracy through Complementary Intra-Class and Inter-Class Mixup</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-image-classification-accuracy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, our integrated solution seamlessly combines our intra-class mixup method with an existing mixup approach such as MixUp or Manifold MixUp.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-image-classification-accuracy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleCineGAN: Landscape Cinemagraph Generation using a Pre-trained StyleGAN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylecinegan-landscape-cinemagraph-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method that can generate cinemagraphs automatically from a still landscape image using a pre-trained StyleGAN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylecinegan-landscape-cinemagraph-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A reinforcement learning guided hybrid evolutionary algorithm for the latency location routing problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reinforcement-learning-guided-hybrid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The latency location routing problem integrates the facility location problem and the multi-depot cumulative capacitated vehicle routing problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reinforcement-learning-guided-hybrid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less but Better: Enabling Generalized Zero-shot Learning Towards Unseen Domains by Intrinsic Learning from Redundant LLM Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-but-better-enabling-generalized-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from existing GZSL methods which alleviate DSP by generating features of unseen classes with semantics, CDGZSL needs to construct a common feature space across domains and acquire the corresponding intrinsic semantics shared among domains to transfer from seen to unseen domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-but-better-enabling-generalized-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaIR: Adaptive All-in-One Image Restoration via Frequency Mining and Modulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adair-adaptive-all-in-one-image-restoration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach is motivated by the observation that different degradation types impact the image content on different frequency subbands, thereby requiring different treatments for each restoration task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adair-adaptive-all-in-one-image-restoration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Enhanced Data-free Approach for Federated Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-enhanced-data-free-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this field, Data-Free Knowledge Transfer (DFKT) plays a crucial role in addressing catastrophic forgetting and data privacy problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-enhanced-data-free-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training point-based deep learning networks for forest segmentation with synthetic data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-point-based-deep-learning-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, a question arises whether it is possible to use synthetic data to train deep learning networks without the need to rely on large volumes of real forest data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-point-based-deep-learning-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>covSTATIS: a multi-table technique for network neuroscience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covstatis-a-multi-table-technique-for-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Similarity analyses between multiple correlation or covariance tables constitute the cornerstone of network neuroscience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covstatis-a-multi-table-technique-for-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftPatch: Unsupervised Anomaly Detection with Noisy Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softpatch-unsupervised-anomaly-detection-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Noise discriminators are utilized to generate outlier scores for patch-level noise elimination before coreset construction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softpatch-unsupervised-anomaly-detection-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning for Trajectory Data Management and Mining: A Survey and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-trajectory-data-management</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a comprehensive review of the development and recent advances in deep learning for trajectory computing (DL4Traj).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-trajectory-data-management</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Agent VQA: Exploring Multi-Agent Foundation Models in Zero-Shot Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-vqa-exploring-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work explores the zero-shot capabilities of foundation models in Visual Question Answering (VQA) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-vqa-exploring-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVSplat: Efficient 3D Gaussian Splatting from Sparse Multi-View Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvsplat-efficient-3d-gaussian-splatting-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose MVSplat, an efficient feed-forward 3D Gaussian Splatting model learned from sparse multi-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvsplat-efficient-3d-gaussian-splatting-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetic Programming for Explainable Manifold Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genetic-programming-for-explainable-manifold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental analysis demonstrates that GP-EMaL is able to match the performance of the existing approach in most cases, while using simpler, smaller, and more interpretable tree structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genetic-programming-for-explainable-manifold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can ChatGPT Detect DeepFakes? A Study of Using Multimodal Large Language Models for Media Forensics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-chatgpt-detect-deepfakes-a-study-of-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DeepFakes, which refer to AI-generated media content, have become an increasing concern due to their use as a means for disinformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-chatgpt-detect-deepfakes-a-study-of-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StreamingT2V: Consistent, Dynamic, and Extendable Long Video Generation from Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streamingt2v-consistent-dynamic-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, we introduce StreamingT2V, an autoregressive approach for long video generation of 80, 240, 600, 1200 or more frames with smooth transitions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streamingt2v-consistent-dynamic-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine-learning invariant foliations in forced systems for reduced order modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-invariant-foliations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We identify reduced order models (ROM) of forced systems from data using invariant foliations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-invariant-foliations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S2LIC: Learned Image Compression with the SwinV2 Block, Adaptive Channel-wise and Global-inter Attention Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s2lic-learned-image-compression-with-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an Adaptive Channel-wise and Global-inter attention Context (ACGC) entropy model, which can efficiently achieve dual feature aggregation in both inter-slice and intraslice contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s2lic-learned-image-compression-with-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Framework for Model Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-framework-for-model-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With EMMET, we present a closed form solution for the equality-constrained version of the preservation-memorization objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-framework-for-model-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Chinese Commonsense Reasoning of LLMs: From Chinese-Specifics to Reasoning-Memorization Correlations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-chinese-commonsense-reasoning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce CHARM, the first benchmark for comprehensively and in-depth evaluating the commonsense reasoning ability of large language models (LLMs) in Chinese, which covers both globally known and Chinese-specific commonsense.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-chinese-commonsense-reasoning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Text-to-Vision Self Supervised Alignment for Improved Histopathology Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-text-to-vision-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised representation learning has been highly promising for histopathology image analysis with numerous approaches leveraging their patient-slide-patch hierarchy to learn better representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-text-to-vision-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLC++: Source-Free Universal Domain Adaptation through Global-Local Clustering and Contrastive Affinity Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glc-source-free-universal-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GLC++ enhances the novel category clustering accuracy of GLC by 4. 3% in open-set scenarios on Office-Home.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glc-source-free-universal-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing Unlabeled Data: A Paradigm for Cross-View Geo-Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-unlabeled-data-a-paradigm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the effective utilization of unlabeled data for large-area cross-view geo-localization (CVGL), encompassing both unsupervised and semi-supervised settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-unlabeled-data-a-paradigm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Models with Ensembled Structure-Based Anomaly Scoring for Unsupervised Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-with-ensembled-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that this ensembling strategy can enhance the performance of DMs and mitigate the sensitivity to different kernel sizes across varying pathologies, highlighting its promise for brain MRI anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-with-ensembled-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Concept Trustworthiness in Concept Bottleneck Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-concept-trustworthiness-in-concept</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concept Bottleneck Models (CBMs), which break down the reasoning process into the input-to-concept mapping and the concept-to-label prediction, have garnered significant attention due to their remarkable interpretability achieved by the interpretable concept bottleneck.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-concept-trustworthiness-in-concept</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detoxifying Large Language Models via Knowledge Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detoxifying-large-language-models-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates using knowledge editing techniques to detoxify Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detoxifying-large-language-models-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Ranking Loss for Recommendation with Sparse User Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-ranking-loss-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we uncover a new challenge associated with BCE loss in scenarios with sparse positive feedback, such as CTR prediction: the gradient vanishing for negative samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-ranking-loss-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Learning for Cross-dataset Isolated Sign Language Recognition in Under-Resourced Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-cross-dataset-isolated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sign language recognition (SLR) has recently achieved a breakthrough in performance thanks to deep neural networks trained on large annotated sign datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-cross-dataset-isolated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Repository for Long Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-repository-for-long-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a Language Repository (LangRepo) for LLMs, that maintains concise and structured information as an interpretable (i. e., all-textual) representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-repository-for-long-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Elements of Differentiable Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-elements-of-differentiable-programming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence has recently experienced remarkable advances, fueled by large models, vast datasets, accelerated hardware, and, last but not least, the transformative power of differentiable programming.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-elements-of-differentiable-programming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAmBLA: A Framework for Evaluating the Reliability of LLMs as Assistants in the Biomedical Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rambla-a-framework-for-evaluating-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) increasingly support applications in a wide range of domains, some with potential high societal impact such as biomedicine, yet their reliability in realistic use cases is under-researched.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rambla-a-framework-for-evaluating-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowdsourced Multilingual Speech Intelligibility Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crowdsourced-multilingual-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advent of generative audio features, there is an increasing need for rapid evaluation of their impact on speech intelligibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crowdsourced-multilingual-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curvature Augmented Manifold Embedding and Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvature-augmented-manifold-embedding-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A new dimensional reduction (DR) and data visualization method, Curvature-Augmented Manifold Embedding and Learning (CAMEL), is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvature-augmented-manifold-embedding-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpikingResformer: Bridging ResNet and Vision Transformer in Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spikingresformer-bridging-resnet-and-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on DSSA, we propose a novel spiking Vision Transformer architecture called SpikingResformer, which combines the ResNet-based multi-stage architecture with our proposed DSSA to improve both performance and energy efficiency while reducing parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spikingresformer-bridging-resnet-and-vision</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
