<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 09:18:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CART-ELC: Oblique Decision Tree Induction via Exhaustive Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cart-elc-oblique-decision-tree-induction-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Oblique decision trees have attracted attention due to their potential for improved classification performance over traditional axis-aligned decision trees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cart-elc-oblique-decision-tree-induction-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVAD: From Single Image to 3D Avatar via Synthetic Data Generation with Video Diffusion and Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svad-from-single-image-to-3d-avatar-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method generates synthetic training data through video diffusion, enhances it with identity preservation and image restoration modules, and utilizes this refined data to train 3DGS avatars.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svad-from-single-image-to-3d-avatar-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chain-of-Thought Tokens are Computer Program Variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chain-of-thought-tokens-are-computer-program</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chain-of-thoughts (CoT) requires large language models (LLMs) to generate intermediate steps before reaching the final answer, and has been proven effective to help LLMs solve complex reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chain-of-thought-tokens-are-computer-program</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenworldAUC: Towards Unified Evaluation and Optimization for Open-world Prompt Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openworldauc-towards-unified-evaluation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This practical challenge has spurred the development of open-world prompt tuning, which demands a unified evaluation of two stages: 1) detecting whether an input belongs to the base or new domain (P1), and 2) classifying the sample into its correct class (P2).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openworldauc-towards-unified-evaluation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StabStitch++: Unsupervised Online Video Stitching with Spatiotemporal Bidirectional Warps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stabstitch-unsupervised-online-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose StabStitch++, a novel video stitching framework to realize spatial stitching and temporal stabilization with unsupervised learning simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stabstitch-unsupervised-online-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foam-Agent: Towards Automated Intelligent CFD Workflows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foam-agent-towards-automated-intelligent-cfd</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computational Fluid Dynamics (CFD) is an essential simulation tool in various engineering disciplines, but it often requires substantial domain expertise and manual configuration, creating barriers to entry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foam-agent-towards-automated-intelligent-cfd</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LSRP: A Leader-Subordinate Retrieval Framework for Privacy-Preserving Cloud-Device Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lsrp-a-leader-subordinate-retrieval-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This leads to two interconnected issues: 1) Limited utilization of the problem-solving capabilities of on-cloud LLMs, which fail to align with personalized user-task needs, and 2) Inadequate integration of user data into on-device SLM responses, resulting in mismatches in contextual user information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lsrp-a-leader-subordinate-retrieval-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt-Based LLMs for Position Bias-Aware Reranking in Personalized Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-based-llms-for-position-bias-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate the effects of user history reordering and instructional prompts for mitigating position bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-based-llms-for-position-bias-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Scene Generation: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-scene-generation-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in deep generative models (e. g., GANs, diffusion models) and 3D representations (e. g., NeRF, 3D Gaussians) have enabled the learning of real-world scene distributions, improving fidelity, diversity, and view consistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-scene-generation-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-Assisted and Topology-Informed Deep Learning for Weather Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-assisted-and-topology-informed-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although deep learning models have demonstrated remarkable potential in weather prediction, most of them overlook either the \textbf{physics} of the underlying weather evolution or the \textbf{topology} of the Earth's surface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-assisted-and-topology-informed-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearing and Seeing Through CLIP: A Framework for Self-Supervised Sound Source Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hearing-and-seeing-through-clip-a-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a framework that maps audios into tokens compatible with CLIP's text encoder, producing audio-driven embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hearing-and-seeing-through-clip-a-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring Reason to Vision: Understanding Perception and Reasoning through Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bring-reason-to-vision-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-Language Models (VLMs) combine visual perception with the general capabilities, such as reasoning, of Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bring-reason-to-vision-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Multi-Stage Influence Function for Large Language Models via Eigenvalue-Corrected Kronecker-Factored Parameterization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-multi-stage-influence-function-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirical results validate the superior scalability of EK-FAC approximation and the effectiveness of our multi-stage influence function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-multi-stage-influence-function-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WaterDrum: Watermarking for Data-centric Unlearning Metric</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/waterdrum-watermarking-for-data-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language model (LLM) unlearning is critical in real-world applications where it is necessary to efficiently remove the influence of private, copyrighted, or harmful data from some users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/waterdrum-watermarking-for-data-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving with Context: Online Map Matching for Complex Roads Using Lane Markings and Scenario Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/driving-with-context-online-map-matching-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed method can achieve accurate map matching even in complex road networks by carefully leveraging lane markings and scenario recognition in the designing of the probability factors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/driving-with-context-online-map-matching-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DispBench: Benchmarking Disparity Estimation to Synthetic Corruptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dispbench-benchmarking-disparity-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, DL-based disparity estimation methods are highly susceptible to distribution shifts and adversarial attacks, raising concerns about their reliability and generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dispbench-benchmarking-disparity-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOAP: Style-Omniscient Animatable Portraits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soap-style-omniscient-animatable-portraits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Creating animatable 3D avatars from a single image remains challenging due to style limitations (realistic, cartoon, anime) and difficulties in handling accessories or hairstyles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soap-style-omniscient-animatable-portraits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threshold Modulation for Online Test-Time Adaptation of Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/threshold-modulation-for-online-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method offers a practical solution for online test-time adaptation of SNNs, providing inspiration for the design of future neuromorphic chips.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/threshold-modulation-for-online-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flow-GRPO: Training Flow Matching Models via Online RL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-grpo-training-flow-matching-models-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Flow-GRPO, the first method integrating online reinforcement learning (RL) into flow matching models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-grpo-training-flow-matching-models-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmented Deep Contexts for Spatially Embedded Video Coding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmented-deep-contexts-for-spatially</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To relieve the limitations, we propose a Spatially Embedded Video Codec (SEVC), in which the low-resolution video is compressed for spatial references.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmented-deep-contexts-for-spatially</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPSO: A Unified Optimization View for Learning-Augmented Power System Operations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lapso-a-unified-optimization-view-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adopting a native optimization perspective, LAPSO is centered on the operation stage and aims to break the boundary between temporally siloed power system tasks, such as forecast, operation and control, while unifying the objectives of machine learning and model-based optimizations at both training and inference stages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lapso-a-unified-optimization-view-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeCLIP: Decoupled Learning for Open-Vocabulary Dense Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/declip-decoupled-learning-for-open-vocabulary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose DeCLIP, a novel framework that enhances CLIP by decoupling the self-attention module to obtain ``content'' and ``context'' features respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/declip-decoupled-learning-for-open-vocabulary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Synthetic Corruptions A Reliable Proxy For Real-World Corruptions?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-synthetic-corruptions-a-reliable-proxy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results reveal a strong correlation in mean performance, supporting the use of synthetic corruptions for robustness evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-synthetic-corruptions-a-reliable-proxy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HDiffTG: A Lightweight Hybrid Diffusion-Transformer-GCN Architecture for 3D Human Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hdifftg-a-lightweight-hybrid-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose HDiffTG, a novel 3D Human Pose Estimation (3DHPE) method that integrates Transformer, Graph Convolutional Network (GCN), and diffusion model into a unified framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hdifftg-a-lightweight-hybrid-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TS-Diff: Two-Stage Diffusion Model for Low-Light RAW Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ts-diff-two-stage-diffusion-model-for-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During the aligning stage, CFIs are averaged to create a target-specific CFI$^T$, which is fine-tuned using a small amount of real RAW data to adapt to the noise characteristics of specific cameras.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ts-diff-two-stage-diffusion-model-for-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAPrompt: Geometry-Aware Point Cloud Prompt for 3D Vision Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaprompt-geometry-aware-point-cloud-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we introduce a Point Prompt that serves as an auxiliary input alongside the original point cloud, explicitly guiding the model to capture fine-grained geometric details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaprompt-geometry-aware-point-cloud-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Graph Prompting via Semantic Low-Rank Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-graph-prompting-via-semantic-low-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision GNN (ViG) demonstrates superior performance by representing images as graph structures, providing a more natural way to capture irregular semantic patterns beyond traditional grid or sequence-based representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-graph-prompting-via-semantic-low-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WDMamba: When Wavelet Degradation Prior Meets Vision Mamba for Image Dehazing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wdmamba-when-wavelet-degradation-prior-meets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we reveal a novel haze-specific wavelet degradation prior observed through wavelet transform analysis, which shows that haze-related information predominantly resides in low-frequency components.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wdmamba-when-wavelet-degradation-prior-meets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TetWeave: Isosurface Extraction using On-The-Fly Delaunay Tetrahedral Grids for Gradient-Based Mesh Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tetweave-isosurface-extraction-using-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce TetWeave, a novel isosurface representation for gradient-based mesh optimization that jointly optimizes the placement of a tetrahedral grid used for Marching Tetrahedra and a novel directional signed distance at each point.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tetweave-isosurface-extraction-using-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced SCanNet with CBAM and Dice Loss for Semantic Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-scannet-with-cbam-and-dice-loss-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These findings highlight the effectiveness of attention mechanisms and Dice loss in improving feature representation and addressing class imbalance in semantic change detection tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-scannet-with-cbam-and-dice-loss-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EchoInk-R1: Exploring Audio-Visual Reasoning in Multimodal LLMs via Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/echoink-r1-exploring-audio-visual-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce EchoInk-R1, a reinforcement learning framework that enhances such reasoning in MLLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/echoink-r1-exploring-audio-visual-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFVO: Learning Darkness-free Visible and Infrared Image Disentanglement and Fusion All at Once</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfvo-learning-darkness-free-visible-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visible and infrared image fusion is one of the most crucial tasks in the field of image fusion, aiming to generate fused images with clear structural information and high-quality texture features for high-level vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfvo-learning-darkness-free-visible-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-stationary Diffusion For Probabilistic Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-stationary-diffusion-for-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A diffusion-based probabilistic forecasting framework, termed Non-stationary Diffusion (NsDiff), is designed based on LSNM that is capable of modeling the changing pattern of uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-stationary-diffusion-for-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consensus-Aware AV Behavior: Trade-offs Between Safety, Interaction, and Performance in Mixed Urban Traffic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consensus-aware-av-behavior-trade-offs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transportation systems have long been shaped by complexity and heterogeneity, driven by the interdependency of agent actions and traffic outcomes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consensus-aware-av-behavior-trade-offs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoPath-LLaVA: Pathology Diagnostic Reasoning Through Video Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videopath-llava-pathology-diagnostic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present VideoPath-LLaVA, the first large multimodal model (LMM) in computational pathology that integrates three distinct image scenarios, single patch images, automatically keyframe-extracted clips, and manually segmented video pathology images, to mimic the natural diagnostic process of pathologists.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videopath-llava-pathology-diagnostic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABKD: Pursuing a Proper Allocation of the Probability Mass in Knowledge Distillation via $α$-$β$-Divergence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abkd-pursuing-a-proper-allocation-of-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, both are too strong in RKLD, causing the student to overly emphasize the target class while ignoring the broader distributional information from the teacher.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abkd-pursuing-a-proper-allocation-of-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Manifold Reconstruction and Representation with Topological and Geometrical Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-manifold-reconstruction-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Manifold learning aims to discover and represent low-dimensional structures underlying high-dimensional data while preserving critical topological and geometric properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-manifold-reconstruction-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Componential Prompt-Knowledge Alignment for Domain Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/componential-prompt-knowledge-alignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain Incremental Learning (DIL) aims to learn from non-stationary data streams across domains while retaining and utilizing past knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/componential-prompt-knowledge-alignment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S3D: Sketch-Driven 3D Model Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s3d-sketch-driven-3d-model-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This streamlined framework demonstrates the effectiveness of S3D in generating high-quality 3D models from sketch inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s3d-sketch-driven-3d-model-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LHT: Statistically-Driven Oblique Decision Trees for Interpretable Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lht-statistically-driven-oblique-decision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The explicit feature weighting at each split provides inherent interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lht-statistically-driven-oblique-decision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking LLMs' Swarm intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-llms-swarm-intelligence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) show potential for complex reasoning, yet their capacity for emergent coordination in Multi-Agent Systems (MAS) when operating under strict constraints-such as limited local perception and communication, characteristic of natural swarms-remains largely unexplored, particularly concerning the nuances of swarm intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-llms-swarm-intelligence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing and Benchmarking Personalized Tool Invocation for LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-and-benchmarking-personalized-tool</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tool invocation is a crucial mechanism for extending the capabilities of Large Language Models (LLMs) and has recently garnered significant attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-and-benchmarking-personalized-tool</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Sampling for MRI-based Sequential Decision Making</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-sampling-for-mri-based-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach paves the way for the future of MRI as a comprehensive and affordable PoC device.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-sampling-for-mri-based-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Registration of 3D Point Sets Using Exponential-based Similarity Matrix</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/registration-of-3d-point-sets-using-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, state-of-the-art registration techniques often struggle when large rotational differences exist between point sets or when the data is significantly corrupted by sensor noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/registration-of-3d-point-sets-using-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VITA-Audio: Fast Interleaved Cross-Modal Token Generation for Efficient Large Speech-Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vita-audio-fast-interleaved-cross-modal-token</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce a lightweight Multiple Cross-modal Token Prediction (MCTP) module that efficiently generates multiple audio tokens within a single model forward pass, which not only accelerates the inference but also significantly reduces the latency for generating the first audio in streaming scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vita-audio-fast-interleaved-cross-modal-token</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAIL: Region-Aware Instructive Learning for Semi-Supervised Tooth Segmentation in CBCT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rail-region-aware-instructive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing methods still face two persistent challenges: limited corrective supervision in structurally ambiguous or mislabeled regions during supervised training and performance degradation caused by unreliable pseudo-labels on unlabeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rail-region-aware-instructive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bounding Box-Guided Diffusion for Synthesizing Industrial Images and Segmentation Map</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bounding-box-guided-diffusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthetic dataset generation in Computer Vision, particularly for industrial applications, is still underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bounding-box-guided-diffusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matching Distance and Geometric Distribution Aided Learning Multiview Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matching-distance-and-geometric-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper concentrates on pose graph construction and motion synchronization within multiview registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matching-distance-and-geometric-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Active Inference Model of Covert and Overt Visual Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-active-inference-model-of-covert-and-overt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to selectively attend to relevant stimuli while filtering out distractions is essential for agents that process complex, high-dimensional sensory input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-active-inference-model-of-covert-and-overt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototype-Based Information Compensation Network for Multi-Source Remote Sensing Data Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-based-information-compensation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Afterward, we design a prototype-based information compensation module to model the global multi-source complementary information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-based-information-compensation</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
