<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 21:07:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ArzEn-LLM: Code-Switched Egyptian Arabic-English Translation and Speech Recognition Using LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arzen-llm-code-switched-egyptian-arabic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our models and code are available as open-source resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arzen-llm-code-switched-egyptian-arabic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Surprising Effectiveness of Multimodal Large Language Models for Video Moment Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-surprising-effectiveness-of-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We achieve a new state-of-the-art in moment retrieval on the widely used benchmarks Charades-STA, QVHighlights, and ActivityNet Captions and illustrate our method's versatility with a new state-of-the-art in temporal action localization on ActivityNet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-surprising-effectiveness-of-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Soft Q-Learning by Bounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-soft-q-learning-by-bounding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An agent's ability to leverage past experience is critical for efficiently solving new tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-soft-q-learning-by-bounding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Compositionality in Concept Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-compositionality-in-concept-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To automatically discover compositional concept representations, we identify two salient properties of such representations, and propose Compositional Concept Extraction (CCE) for finding concepts which obey these properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-compositionality-in-concept-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective Prompting Tuning for Personalized Conversations with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-prompting-tuning-for-personalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate those issues, we propose \textbf{S}elective \textbf{P}rompt \textbf{T}uning (SPT), which softly prompts LLMs for personalized conversations in a selective way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-prompting-tuning-for-personalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming Data and Transformers for Audio Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-data-and-transformers-for-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating ambient sounds and effects is a challenging problem due to data scarcity and often insufficient caption quality, making it difficult to employ large-scale generative models for the task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-data-and-transformers-for-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look into Mixture-of-Experts in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-into-mixture-of-experts-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mixture-of-experts (MoE) is gaining increasing attention due to its unique properties and remarkable performance, especially for language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-into-mixture-of-experts-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiTrack: Bidirectional Offline 3D Multi-Object Tracking Using Camera-LiDAR Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitrack-bidirectional-offline-3d-multi-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared with real-time multi-object tracking (MOT), offline multi-object tracking (OMOT) has the advantages to perform 2D-3D detection fusion, erroneous link correction, and full track optimization but has to deal with the challenges from bounding box misalignment and track evaluation, editing, and refinement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitrack-bidirectional-offline-3d-multi-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChronoMagic-Bench: A Benchmark for Metamorphic Evaluation of Text-to-Time-lapse Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chronomagic-bench-a-benchmark-for-metamorphic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel text-to-video (T2V) generation benchmark, ChronoMagic-Bench, to evaluate the temporal and metamorphic capabilities of the T2V models (e. g. Sora and Lumiere) in time-lapse video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chronomagic-bench-a-benchmark-for-metamorphic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expressive Keypoints for Skeleton-based Action Recognition via Skeleton Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressive-keypoints-for-skeleton-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of skeleton-based action recognition, the traditional methods which rely on coarse body keypoints fall short of capturing subtle human actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressive-keypoints-for-skeleton-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Context Pruning: Optimizing Real-World Code Completion with Repository-Level Pretrained Code LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-context-pruning-optimizing-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We applied the HCP strategy in experiments with six Repo-Code LLMs, and the results demonstrate that our proposed method can significantly enhance completion accuracy while substantially reducing the length of input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-context-pruning-optimizing-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy spectroscopy without spectra: Galaxy properties from photometric images with conditional diffusion models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galaxy-spectroscopy-without-spectra-galaxy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we report the development of a generative AI method capable of predicting optical galaxy spectra from photometric broad-band images alone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galaxy-spectroscopy-without-spectra-galaxy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Diffusion Segmentation for Biomedical Images with Single-step Reverse Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-diffusion-segmentation-for-biomedical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have demonstrated their effectiveness across various generative tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-diffusion-segmentation-for-biomedical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniRec: A Dual Enhancement of Uniformity and Frequency in Sequential Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unirec-a-dual-enhancement-of-uniformity-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[UniRec leverages sequence uniformity and item frequency to enhance performance, particularly improving the representation of non-uniform sequences and less-frequent items.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unirec-a-dual-enhancement-of-uniformity-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Scaling Up 3D Gaussian Splatting Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-scaling-up-3d-gaussian-splatting-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluations using large-scale, high-resolution scenes show that Grendel enhances rendering quality by scaling up 3DGS parameters across multiple GPUs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-scaling-up-3d-gaussian-splatting-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Unknown: Conditional Evidence Decoupling for Unknown Rejection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-unknown-conditional-evidence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate this issue, we develop a novel open-set object detection framework, which delves into conditional evidence decoupling for the unknown rejection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-unknown-conditional-evidence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial-temporal Hierarchical Reinforcement Learning for Interpretable Pathology Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-temporal-hierarchical-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the higher-level spatial manager is proposed to pick out the most corrupted patch for the lower-level patch worker.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-temporal-hierarchical-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BADGE: BADminton report Generation and Evaluation with LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badge-badminton-report-generation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Following report generation, the LLM evaluates and scores the reports to assess their quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badge-badminton-report-generation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaZeta: Adaptive Zeroth-Order Tensor-Train Adaption for Memory-Efficient Large Language Models Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adazeta-adaptive-zeroth-order-tensor-train</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the Adaptive Zeroth-order Tensor-Train Adaption (AdaZeta) framework, specifically designed to improve the performance and convergence of the ZO methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adazeta-adaptive-zeroth-order-tensor-train</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symbolic Learning Enables Self-Evolving Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-learning-enables-self-evolving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce agent symbolic learning, a systematic framework that enables language agents to optimize themselves on their own in a data-centric way using symbolic optimizers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-learning-enables-self-evolving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Barrier: Enhanced Utility and Robustness in Smoothed DRL Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-barrier-enhanced-utility-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, a notable gap exists in the performance of current smoothed DRL agents, often characterized by significantly low clean rewards and weak robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-barrier-enhanced-utility-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Brittle Decisions for Free: Leveraging Margin Consistency in Deep Robust Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-brittle-decisions-for-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we establish that margin consistency is a necessary and sufficient condition to use a model's logit margin as a score for identifying non-robust samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-brittle-decisions-for-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start from Zero: Triple Set Prediction for Automatic Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/start-from-zero-triple-set-prediction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel graph-level automatic KG completion task called Triple Set Prediction (TSP) which assumes none of the elements in the missing triples is given.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/start-from-zero-triple-set-prediction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Human-Level 3D Relative Pose Estimation: Generalizable, Training-Free, with Single Reference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-human-level-3d-relative-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, we propose a novel 3D generalizable relative pose estimation method by elaborating (i) with a 2. 5D shape from an RGB-D reference, (ii) with an off-the-shelf differentiable renderer, and (iii) with semantic cues from a pretrained model like DINOv2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-human-level-3d-relative-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising as Adaptation: Noise-Space Domain Adaptation for Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-as-adaptation-noise-space-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results on three classical image restoration tasks, namely denoising, deblurring, and deraining, demonstrate the effectiveness of the proposed method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-as-adaptation-noise-space-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidirectional-Reachable Hierarchical Reinforcement Learning with Mutually Responsive Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-reachable-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hierarchical reinforcement learning (HRL) addresses complex long-horizon tasks by skillfully decomposing them into subgoals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-reachable-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S3: A Simple Strong Sample-effective Multimodal Dialog System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s3-a-simple-strong-sample-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a conceptually simple yet powerful baseline for the multimodal dialog task, an S3 model, that achieves near state-of-the-art results on two compelling leaderboards: MMMU and AI Journey Contest 2023.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s3-a-simple-strong-sample-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining Automated Optimisation of Hyperparameters and Reward Shape</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-automated-optimisation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then propose a methodology for the combined optimisation of hyperparameters and the reward function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-automated-optimisation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Training with Pseudo-Label Scorer for Aspect Sentiment Quad Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-training-with-pseudo-label-scorer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aspect Sentiment Quad Prediction (ASQP) aims to predict all quads (aspect term, aspect category, opinion term, sentiment polarity) for a given review, which is the most representative and challenging task in aspect-based sentiment analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-training-with-pseudo-label-scorer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Classification of Time Series: Taxonomy and Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-classification-of-time-series-taxonomy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many situations, the measurements of a studied phenomenon are provided sequentially, and the prediction of its class needs to be made as early as possible so as not to incur too high a time penalty, but not too early and risk paying the cost of misclassification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-classification-of-time-series-taxonomy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weak Reward Model Transforms Generative Models into Robust Causal Event Extraction Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weak-reward-model-transforms-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The inherent ambiguity of cause and effect boundaries poses a challenge in evaluating causal event extraction tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weak-reward-model-transforms-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EmT: A Novel Transformer for Generalized Cross-subject EEG Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emt-a-novel-transformer-for-generalized-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we design a temporal contextual transformer module (TCT) with two types of token mixers to learn the temporal contextual information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emt-a-novel-transformer-for-generalized-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Space Knowledge Distillation for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-space-knowledge-distillation-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, this discrepancy also hinders the KD process between models with different vocabularies, which is common for current LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-space-knowledge-distillation-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director3D: Real-world Camera Trajectory and 3D Scene Generation from Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/director3d-real-world-camera-trajectory-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this, (1) we first utilize a Trajectory Diffusion Transformer, acting as the Cinematographer, to model the distribution of camera trajectories based on textual descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/director3d-real-world-camera-trajectory-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-SAM: Promptable 3D Segmentation Model for Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-sam-promptable-3d-segmentation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of 2D foundation models for image segmentation has been significantly advanced by the Segment Anything Model (SAM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-sam-promptable-3d-segmentation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic speech recognition for the Nepali language using CNN, bidirectional LSTM and ResNet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-speech-recognition-for-the-nepali</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an end-to-end deep learning model for Automatic Speech Recognition (ASR) that transcribes Nepali speech to text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-speech-recognition-for-the-nepali</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XAMI -- A Benchmark Dataset for Artefact Detection in XMM-Newton Optical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xami-a-benchmark-dataset-for-artefact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hand-annotated a sample of 1000 images with artefacts which we use to train automated ML methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xami-a-benchmark-dataset-for-artefact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DARG: Dynamic Evaluation of Large Language Models via Adaptive Reasoning Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/darg-dynamic-evaluation-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Dynamic Evaluation of LLMs via Adaptive Reasoning Graph Evolvement (DARG) to dynamically extend current benchmarks with controlled complexity and diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/darg-dynamic-evaluation-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Arithmetic Reasoning Ability of Large Language Models through Relation Tuples, Verification and Dynamic Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-arithmetic-reasoning-ability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we use relation tuples, which are not only human-readable but also machine-friendly and easier to verify than natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-arithmetic-reasoning-ability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Prototype-Aware Learning for Active Voltage Control on Power Distribution Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-prototype-aware-learning-for-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel temporal prototype-aware learning method, abbreviated as TPA, to learn time-adaptive AVC under short-term training trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-prototype-aware-learning-for-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALPBench: A Benchmark for Active Learning Pipelines on Tabular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpbench-a-benchmark-for-active-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This particularly holds for the combination of query strategies with different learning algorithms into active learning pipelines and examining the impact of the learning algorithm choice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpbench-a-benchmark-for-active-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TopoGCL: Topological Graph Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topogcl-topological-graph-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph contrastive learning (GCL) has recently emerged as a new concept which allows for capitalizing on the strengths of graph neural networks (GNNs) to learn rich representations in a wide variety of applications which involve abundant unlabeled information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topogcl-topological-graph-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DocParseNet: Advanced Semantic Segmentation and OCR Embeddings for Efficient Scanned Document Annotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docparsenet-advanced-semantic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automating the annotation of scanned documents is challenging, requiring a balance between computational efficiency and accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docparsenet-advanced-semantic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Continual Learning Abilities in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-continual-learning-abilities-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we introduce $\textbf{MIGU}$ ($\textbf{M}$agn$\textbf{I}$tude-based $\textbf{G}$radient $\textbf{U}$pdating for continual learning), a rehearsal-free and task-label-free method that only updates the model parameters with large magnitudes of output in LMs' linear layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-continual-learning-abilities-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANQAS: Kolmogorov Arnold Network for Quantum Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kanqas-kolmogorov-arnold-network-for-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a noiseless scenario, the probability of success and the number of optimal quantum circuit configurations to generate the multi-qubit maximally entangled states are significantly higher than MLPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kanqas-kolmogorov-arnold-network-for-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal-Channel Modeling in Multi-head Self-Attention for Synthetic Speech Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-channel-modeling-in-multi-head-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent synthetic speech detectors leveraging the Transformer model have superior performance compared to the convolutional neural network counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-channel-modeling-in-multi-head-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled Motion Modeling for Video Frame Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-motion-modeling-for-video-frame</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, they require complex training and large computational cost for modeling on the pixel space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-motion-modeling-for-video-frame</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGIC: Meta-Ability Guided Interactive Chain-of-Distillation for Effective-and-Efficient Vision-and-Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magic-meta-ability-guided-interactive-chain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the remarkable developments of recent large models in Embodied Artificial Intelligence (E-AI), their integration into robotics is hampered by their excessive parameter sizes and computational demands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magic-meta-ability-guided-interactive-chain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leave No Document Behind: Benchmarking Long-Context LLMs with Extended Multi-Doc QA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leave-no-document-behind-benchmarking-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long-context modeling capabilities have garnered widespread attention, leading to the emergence of Large Language Models (LLMs) with ultra-context windows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leave-no-document-behind-benchmarking-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-centered In-building Embodied Delivery Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-centered-in-building-embodied-delivery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This environment also includes autonomous human characters and robots with grasping and mobility capabilities, as well as a large number of interactive items.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-centered-in-building-embodied-delivery</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
