<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:13:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MasterWeaver: Taming Editability and Identity for Personalized Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masterweaver-taming-editability-and-identity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present MasterWeaver, a test-time tuning-free method designed to generate personalized images with both faithful identity fidelity and flexible editability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masterweaver-taming-editability-and-identity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probing Multimodal LLMs as World Models for Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-multimodal-llms-as-world-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide a sober look at the application of Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) within the domain of autonomous driving and challenge/verify some common assumptions, focusing on their ability to reason and interpret dynamic driving scenarios through sequences of images/frames in a closed-loop control environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-multimodal-llms-as-world-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Hierarchical Graph Alignment Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-hierarchical-graph-alignment-kernels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Typical R-convolution graph kernels invoke the kernel functions that decompose graphs into non-isomorphic substructures and compare them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-hierarchical-graph-alignment-kernels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Stream Keypoint Attention Network for Sign Language Recognition and Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stream-keypoint-attention-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The resulting framework is denoted as MSKA-SLR, which is expanded into a sign language translation (SLT) model through the straightforward addition of an extra translation network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stream-keypoint-attention-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Statements in Text: A Domain-Agnostic Few-Shot Solution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-statements-in-text-a-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In light of this, we propose and release a qualitative and versatile few-shot learning methodology as a common paradigm for any claim-based textual classification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-statements-in-text-a-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rectified Gaussian kernel multi-view k-means clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rectified-gaussian-kernel-multi-view-k-means</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show two new variants of multi-view k-means (MVKM) algorithms to address multi-view data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rectified-gaussian-kernel-multi-view-k-means</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenFactCheck: A Unified Framework for Factuality Evaluation of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openfactcheck-a-unified-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increased use of large language models (LLMs) across a variety of real-world applications calls for mechanisms to verify the factual accuracy of their outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openfactcheck-a-unified-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Multimodal Large Language Models with Visual Tokens Withdrawal for Rapid Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-multimodal-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach is inspired by two intriguing phenomena we have observed: (1) the attention sink phenomenon that is prevalent in LLMs also persists in MLLMs, suggesting that initial tokens and nearest tokens receive the majority of attention, while middle vision tokens garner minimal attention in deep layers; (2) the presence of information migration, which implies that visual information is transferred to subsequent text tokens within the first few layers of MLLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-multimodal-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous max-flow augmentation of self-supervised few-shot learning on SPECT left ventricles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-max-flow-augmentation-of-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Single-Photon Emission Computed Tomography (SPECT) left ventricular assessment protocols are important for detecting ischemia in high-risk patients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-max-flow-augmentation-of-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characteristic Learning for Provable One Step Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characteristic-learning-for-provable-one-step</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the characteristic generator, a novel one-step generative model that combines the efficiency of sampling in Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) with the stable performance of flow-based models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characteristic-learning-for-provable-one-step</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lumina-T2X: Transforming Text into Any Modality, Resolution, and Duration via Flow-based Large Diffusion Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lumina-t2x-transforming-text-into-any</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sora unveils the potential of scaling Diffusion Transformer for generating photorealistic images and videos at arbitrary resolutions, aspect ratios, and durations, yet it still lacks sufficient implementation details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lumina-t2x-transforming-text-into-any</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-trained Text-to-Image Diffusion Models Are Versatile Representation Learners for Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-trained-text-to-image-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This has led to the emergence of pre-trained vision-language models as a tool for transferring representations learned from internet-scale data to downstream tasks and new domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-trained-text-to-image-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LayerPlexRank: Exploring Node Centrality and Layer Influence through Algebraic Connectivity in Multiplex Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layerplexrank-exploring-node-centrality-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the calculation of centrality in complex networks becomes increasingly vital across technological, biological, and social systems, precise and scalable ranking methods are essential for understanding these networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layerplexrank-exploring-node-centrality-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Learning of Time Series Representation via Diffusion Process and Imputation-Interpolation-Forecasting Mask</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-of-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time Series Representation Learning (TSRL) focuses on generating informative representations for various Time Series (TS) modeling tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-of-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Link Stealing Attacks Against Inductive Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-stealing-attacks-against-inductive-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper fills the gap by conducting a systematic privacy analysis of inductive GNNs through the lens of link stealing attacks, one of the most popular attacks that are specifically designed for GNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-stealing-attacks-against-inductive-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selecting the Most Conflicting Pair of Candidates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-the-most-conflicting-pair-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study committee elections from a perspective of finding the most conflicting candidates, that is, candidates that imply the largest amount of conflict, as per voter preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-the-most-conflicting-pair-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Level Superoptimizer for Tensor Programs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-level-superoptimizer-for-tensor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Mirage, the first multi-level superoptimizer for tensor programs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-level-superoptimizer-for-tensor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CuMo: Scaling Multimodal LLM with Co-Upcycled Mixture-of-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cumo-scaling-multimodal-llm-with-co-upcycled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in Multimodal Large Language Models (LLMs) have focused primarily on scaling by increasing text-image pair data and enhancing LLMs to improve performance on multimodal tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cumo-scaling-multimodal-llm-with-co-upcycled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving Edge Federated Learning for Intelligent Mobile-Health Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-edge-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, enabling learning from distributed data over such edge Internet of Things (IoT) systems (e. g., mobile-health and wearable technologies, involving sensitive personal/medical data) in a privacy-preserving fashion presents a major challenge mainly due to their stringent resource constraints, i. e., limited computing capacity, communication bandwidth, memory storage, and battery lifetime.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-edge-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenBA-V2: Reaching 77.3% High Compression Ratio with Fast Multi-Stage Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openba-v2-reaching-77-3-high-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have played an important role in many fields due to their powerful capabilities. However, their massive number of parameters leads to high deployment requirements and incurs significant inference costs, which impedes their practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openba-v2-reaching-77-3-high-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Care: Assessing the Healthcare Implications of Pre-training Data on Language Model Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-care-assessing-the-healthcare</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are increasingly essential in processing natural languages, yet their application is frequently compromised by biases and inaccuracies originating in their training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-care-assessing-the-healthcare</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outlier-robust Kalman Filtering through Generalised Bayes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-robust-kalman-filtering-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We derive a novel, provably robust, and closed-form Bayesian update rule for online filtering in state-space models in the presence of outliers and misspecified measurement models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-robust-kalman-filtering-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Motion Detection Using Dynamic Mode Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-motion-detection-using-dynamic-mode</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic Mode Decomposition (DMD) is a numerical method that seeks to fit timeseries data to a linear dynamical system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-motion-detection-using-dynamic-mode</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVA-X: A Foundation Model for General Chest X-ray Analysis with Self-supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eva-x-a-foundation-model-for-general-chest-x</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The diagnosis and treatment of chest diseases play a crucial role in maintaining human health.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eva-x-a-foundation-model-for-general-chest-x</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communication-Efficient Collaborative Perception via Information Filling with Codebook</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communication-efficient-collaborative-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It inherently results in a fundamental trade-off between perception ability and communication cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communication-efficient-collaborative-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Anomaly Detection for Complex Industrial Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-anomaly-detection-for-complex</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Acknowledging that traditional AD methods struggle with this dataset, we introduce (2) Segmentation-based Anomaly Detector (SegAD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-anomaly-detection-for-complex</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisionGraph: Leveraging Large Multimodal Models for Graph Theory Problems in Visual Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visiongraph-leveraging-large-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Multimodal Models (LMMs) have achieved impressive success in visual understanding and reasoning, remarkably improving the performance of mathematical reasoning in a visual context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visiongraph-leveraging-large-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offline Model-Based Optimization via Policy-Guided Gradient Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-model-based-optimization-via-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Offline optimization is an emerging problem in many experimental engineering domains including protein, drug or aircraft design, where online experimentation to collect evaluation data is too expensive or dangerous.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-model-based-optimization-via-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer Architecture for NetsDB</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-architecture-for-netsdb</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers models have become the backbone of the current state-of-the-art models in language, vision, and multimodal domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-architecture-for-netsdb</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Efficient Training and Evaluation of Robust Models against $l_0$ Bounded Adversarial Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-training-and-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we combine sparse-PGD with a black-box attack to comprehensively and more reliably evaluate the models' robustness against $l_0$ bounded adversarial perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-training-and-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting and Refining HiRISE Image Patches Obscured by Atmospheric Dust</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-and-refining-hirise-image-patches</link>
      <description><![CDATA[HiRISE (High-Resolution Imaging Science Experiment) is a camera onboard the Mars Reconnaissance orbiter responsible for photographing vast areas of the Martian surface in unprecedented detail.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-and-refining-hirise-image-patches</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Entropy Enigma: Success and Failure of Entropy Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-entropy-enigma-success-and-failure-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After many steps of optimization, EM makes the model embed test images far away from the embeddings of training images, which results in a degradation of accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-entropy-enigma-success-and-failure-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINBAD: Saliency-informed detection of breakage caused by ad blocking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sinbad-saliency-informed-detection-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Privacy-enhancing blocking tools based on filter-list rules tend to break legitimate functionality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sinbad-saliency-informed-detection-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Language Models Can Provide Feedback: Evaluating LLMs' Ability to Help Students Using GPT-4-As-A-Judge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-language-models-can-provide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by recent work that has utilised very powerful LLMs, such as GPT-4, to evaluate the outputs produced by less powerful models, we conduct an automated analysis of the quality of the feedback produced by several open source models using a dataset from an introductory programming course.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-language-models-can-provide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVDD Challenge 2024: A Singing Voice Deepfake Detection Challenge Evaluation Plan</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svdd-challenge-2024-a-singing-voice-deepfake</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of AI-generated singing voices, which now closely mimic natural human singing and align seamlessly with musical scores, has led to heightened concerns for artists and the music industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svdd-challenge-2024-a-singing-voice-deepfake</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HMANet: Hybrid Multi-Axis Aggregation Network for Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hmanet-hybrid-multi-axis-aggregation-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the super-resolution task in the training phase, a novel pre-training method is designed to enhance the model representation capabilities further and validate the proposed model's effectiveness through many experiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hmanet-hybrid-multi-axis-aggregation-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Social Graph for Inactive User Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-social-graph-for-inactive-user</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel social recommendation method called LSIR (\textbf{L}earning \textbf{S}ocial Graph for \textbf{I}nactive User \textbf{R}ecommendation) that learns an optimal social graph structure for social recommendation, especially for inactive users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-social-graph-for-inactive-user</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DALK: Dynamic Co-Augmentation of LLMs and KG to answer Alzheimer's Disease Questions with Scientific Literature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dalk-dynamic-co-augmentation-of-llms-and-kg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a synergized framework of LLM and KG mutually enhancing each other, we first leverage LLM to construct an evolving AD-specific knowledge graph (KG) sourced from AD-related scientific literature, and then we utilize a coarse-to-fine sampling method with a novel self-aware knowledge retrieval approach to select appropriate knowledge from the KG to augment LLM inference capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dalk-dynamic-co-augmentation-of-llms-and-kg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-scale Bottleneck Transformer for Weakly Supervised Multimodal Violence Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-bottleneck-transformer-for-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the pursuit of effective multimodal violence detection (MVD), information redundancy, modality imbalance, and modality asynchrony are identified as three key challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-bottleneck-transformer-for-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffMatch: Visual-Language Guidance Makes Better Semi-supervised Change Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffmatch-visual-language-guidance-makes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, we first propose a VLM-based mixed change event generation (CEG) strategy to yield pseudo labels for unlabeled CD data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffmatch-visual-language-guidance-makes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Effect of Model Size on LLM Post-hoc Explainability via LIME</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-model-size-on-llm-post-hoc</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are becoming bigger to boost performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-model-size-on-llm-post-hoc</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Assisted Dynamical Classification of Trans-Neptunian Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-assisted-dynamical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comparisons between the different dynamical classes of modeled and observed TNOs can help constrain the history of the outer solar system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-assisted-dynamical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Searching for Programmatic Policies in Semantic Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/searching-for-programmatic-policies-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hypothesized that searching in semantic spaces is more sample-efficient compared to syntax-based spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/searching-for-programmatic-policies-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>myAURA: Personalized health library for epilepsy management via knowledge graph sparsification and visualization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/myaura-personalized-health-library-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Objective: We report the development of the patient-centered myAURA application and suite of methods designed to aid epilepsy patients, caregivers, and researchers in making decisions about care and self-management.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/myaura-personalized-health-library-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Geometric Ontology Embeddings for $\mathcal{EL}^{++}$ with Negative Sampling and Deductive Closure Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-geometric-ontology-embeddings-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ontology embeddings map classes, relations, and individuals in ontologies into $\mathbb{R}^n$, and within $\mathbb{R}^n$ similarity between entities can be computed or new axioms inferred.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-geometric-ontology-embeddings-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fishing for Magikarp: Automatically Detecting Under-trained Tokens in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fishing-for-magikarp-automatically-detecting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The disconnect between tokenizer creation and model training in language models has been known to allow for certain inputs, such as the infamous SolidGoldMagikarp token, to induce unwanted behaviour.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fishing-for-magikarp-automatically-detecting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fault Identification Enhancement with Reinforcement Learning (FIERL)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fault-identification-enhancement-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This letter presents a novel approach in the field of Active Fault Detection (AFD), by explicitly separating the task into two parts: Passive Fault Detection (PFD) and control input design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fault-identification-enhancement-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Posterior Sampling for Revenue Management under Time-varying Demand</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-posterior-sampling-for-revenue</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose a heuristic modification of the proposed algorithm, which further efficiently learns the pricing policy in the experiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-posterior-sampling-for-revenue</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Molecule-Space: Free Lunch in Unified Multimodal Space via Knowledge Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecule-space-free-lunch-in-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unified multi-model representation spaces are the foundation of multimodal understanding and generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecule-space-free-lunch-in-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Place Recognition Survey: Towards Real-World Autonomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-place-recognition-survey-towards-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conclude with a discussion on PR's future directions, accompanied by a summary of the literature covered and access to our open-source library, available to the robotics community at: https://github. com/MetaSLAM/GPRS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-place-recognition-survey-towards-real</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
