<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 21:07:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Invariant Collaborative Filtering to Popularity Distribution Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-collaborative-filtering-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Collaborative Filtering (CF) models, despite their great success, suffer from severe performance drops due to popularity distribution shifts, where these changes are ubiquitous and inevitable in real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-collaborative-filtering-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The out-of-sample $R^2$: estimation and inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-out-of-sample-r-2-estimation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-sample prediction is the acid test of predictive models, yet an independent test dataset is often not available for assessment of the prediction error.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-out-of-sample-r-2-estimation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of Data Augmentation and Loss Functions in Semantic Image Segmentation for Drilling Tool Wear Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-data-augmentation-and-loss</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, models are trained on image tiles of different sizes, and augmentation techniques of varying intensities are deployed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-data-augmentation-and-loss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Tailed Partial Label Learning via Dynamic Rebalancing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-partial-label-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The straightforward combination of LT and PLL, i. e., LT-PLL, suffers from a fundamental dilemma: LT methods build upon a given class distribution that is unavailable in PLL, and the performance of PLL is severely influenced in long-tailed context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-partial-label-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIOSA: An approach to the automatic identification of obstructive sleep apnea events based on deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aiosa-an-approach-to-the-automatic-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Obstructive Sleep Apnea Syndrome (OSAS) is the most common sleep-related breathing disorder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aiosa-an-approach-to-the-automatic-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Bias in the Dice Similarity Coefficient: Introducing nDSC for White Matter Lesion Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-bias-in-the-dice-similarity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work describes a detailed analysis of the recently proposed normalised Dice Similarity Coefficient (nDSC) for binary segmentation tasks as an adaptation of DSC which scales the precision at a fixed recall rate to tackle this bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-bias-in-the-dice-similarity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllability-Aware Unsupervised Skill Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllability-aware-unsupervised-skill</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the key capabilities of intelligent agents is the ability to discover useful skills without external supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllability-aware-unsupervised-skill</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Span-based Named Entity Recognition by Generating and Compressing Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/span-based-named-entity-recognition-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For one type of IB model, we incorporate two unsupervised generative components, span reconstruction and synonym generation, into a span-based NER system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/span-based-named-entity-recognition-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unbinned Profiled Unfolding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbinned-profiled-unfolding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new machine learning-based unfolding method that results in an unbinned differential cross section and can profile nuisance parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbinned-profiled-unfolding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Penalty-based Bilevel Gradient Descent Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-penalty-based-bilevel-gradient-descent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bilevel optimization enjoys a wide range of applications in hyper-parameter optimization, meta-learning and reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-penalty-based-bilevel-gradient-descent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short-Term Aggregated Residential Load Forecasting using BiLSTM and CNN-BiLSTM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/short-term-aggregated-residential-load</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using a publicly available dataset consisting of 38 homes, the BiLSTM and CNN-BiLSTM models are trained to forecast the aggregated active power demand for each hour within a 24 hr.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/short-term-aggregated-residential-load</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVC: Towards Real-Time Neural Image Compression with Mask Decay</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evc-towards-real-time-neural-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Both mask decay and residual representation learning greatly improve the RD performance of our scalable encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evc-towards-real-time-neural-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A deep convolutional neural network for salt-and-pepper noise removal using selective convolutional blocks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-convolutional-neural-network-for-salt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we proposed a deep CNN model, namely SeConvNet, to suppress SAP noise in gray-scale and color images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-convolutional-neural-network-for-salt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Degree Bias in Embedding-Based Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-degree-bias-in-embedding-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It aims to predict unseen edges by learning representations for all the entities and relations in a KG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-degree-bias-in-embedding-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGA-PoseNet: Camera Pose Regression via a 1D-Up Approach to Conformal Geometric Algebra</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cga-posenet-camera-pose-regression-via-a-1d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This 1D-Up approach to CGA can be employed to overcome the dichotomy between translational and orientational components in camera pose regression in a compact and elegant way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cga-posenet-camera-pose-regression-via-a-1d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEN-HDR: Computationally Efficient neural Network for real-time High Dynamic Range imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cen-hdr-computationally-efficient-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High dynamic range (HDR) imaging is still a challenging task in modern digital photography.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cen-hdr-computationally-efficient-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the cardinality of a reduced Gröbner basis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-cardinality-of-a-reduced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use ansatz neural network models to predict key metrics of complexity for Gr\"obner bases of binomial ideals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-cardinality-of-a-reduced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensor Generalized Canonical Correlation Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensor-generalized-canonical-correlation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Regularized Generalized Canonical Correlation Analysis (RGCCA) is a general statistical framework for multi-block data analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensor-generalized-canonical-correlation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A SWAT-based Reinforcement Learning Framework for Crop Management</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-swat-based-reinforcement-learning-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Crop management involves a series of critical, interdependent decisions or actions in a complex and highly uncertain environment, which exhibit distinct spatial and temporal variations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-swat-based-reinforcement-learning-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Substitute Models More Bayesian Can Enhance Transferability of Adversarial Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-substitute-models-more-bayesian-can</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, by contrast, we opt for the diversity in substitute models and advocate to attack a Bayesian model for achieving desirable transferability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-substitute-models-more-bayesian-can</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adjacent-level Feature Cross-Fusion with 3D CNN for Remote Sensing Image Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjacent-level-feature-cross-fusion-with-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, through the inner fusion property of 3D convolution, we design a new feature fusion way that can simultaneously extract and fuse the feature information from bi-temporal images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjacent-level-feature-cross-fusion-with-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan-then-Seam: Towards Efficient Table-to-Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plan-then-seam-towards-efficient-table-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Table-to-text generation aims at automatically generating text to help people conveniently obtain salient information in tables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plan-then-seam-towards-efficient-table-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Memory Units with Uncertainty Regulation for Weakly Supervised Video Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-memory-units-with-uncertainty-regulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose an Uncertainty Regulated Dual Memory Units (UR-DMU) model to learn both the representations of normal data and discriminative features of abnormal data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-memory-units-with-uncertainty-regulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOMINO: Domain-aware Loss for Deep Learning Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domino-domain-aware-loss-for-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning has achieved the state-of-the-art performance across medical imaging tasks; however, model calibration is often not considered.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domino-domain-aware-loss-for-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Video Anomaly Event Detection: Systematic Taxonomy and Comparison of Deep Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-video-anomaly-event-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video Anomaly Event Detection (VAED) is the core technology of intelligent surveillance systems aiming to temporally or spatially locate anomalous events in videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-video-anomaly-event-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Functional Hashing in Automatic Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-functional-hashing-in-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show that large efficiency gains can be obtained by employing a fast unified functional hash, especially through the functional equivalence caching technique, which we also present.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-functional-hashing-in-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XFL: A High Performace, Lightweighted Federated Learning Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xfl-a-high-performace-lightweighted-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces XFL, an industrial-grade federated learning project.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xfl-a-high-performace-lightweighted-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Synesthesia: A Sound and Emotion Guided AI Painter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robot-synesthesia-a-sound-and-emotion-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For speech, we decouple speech into its transcribed text and the tone of the speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robot-synesthesia-a-sound-and-emotion-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Diffusion Models Further Improve Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-diffusion-models-further-improve</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It has been recognized that the data generated by the denoising diffusion probabilistic model (DDPM) improves adversarial training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-diffusion-models-further-improve</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Principled and Efficient Motif Finding for Structure Learning in Lifted Graphical Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/principled-and-efficient-motif-finding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the first principled approach for mining structural motifs in lifted graphical models, languages that blend first-order logic with probabilistic models, which uses a stochastic process to measure the similarity of entities in the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/principled-and-efficient-motif-finding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Contextomized Quotes in News Headlines by Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-contextomized-quotes-in-news</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quotes are critical for establishing credibility in news articles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-contextomized-quotes-in-news</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Question Answering against Distribution Shifts with Test-Time Adaptation: An Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-question-answering-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To answer this question, we evaluate test-time adaptation (TTA) to improve a model after deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-question-answering-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reversible Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reversible-vision-transformers-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reversible Vision Transformers achieve a reduced memory footprint of up to 15. 5x at roughly identical model complexity, parameters and accuracy, demonstrating the promise of reversible vision transformers as an efficient backbone for hardware resource limited training regimes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reversible-vision-transformers-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Transformer-based Response Evaluator for Open-Domain Spoken Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transformer-based-response-evaluator-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we collect a corpus of Athena conversations with live human traffic, where potential responses from all enabled response generators are logged and subsequently annotated for response quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transformer-based-response-evaluator-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RayNet: A Simulation Platform for Developing Reinforcement Learning-Driven Network Protocols</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raynet-a-simulation-platform-for-developing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce RayNet, a scalable and adaptable simulation framework for the development of learning-based network protocols.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raynet-a-simulation-platform-for-developing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Generative Adversarial Imitation Learning with Mid-level Input Generation for Autonomous Driving on Urban Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-generative-adversarial-imitation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed hGAIL consists of an hierarchical Adversarial Imitation Learning architecture composed of two main modules: the GAN (Generative Adversarial Nets) which generates the Bird's-Eye View (BEV) representation mainly from the images of three frontal cameras of the vehicle, and the GAIL which learns to control the vehicle based mainly on the BEV predictions from the GAN as input. Our experiments have shown that GAIL exclusively from cameras (without BEV) fails to even learn the task, while hGAIL, after training, was able to autonomously navigate successfully in all intersections of the city.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-generative-adversarial-imitation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massively Multilingual Language Models for Cross Lingual Fact Extraction from Low Resource Indian Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/massively-multilingual-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross Lingual Information Extraction aims at extracting factual information in the form of English triples from low resource Indian Language text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/massively-multilingual-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ManiSkill2: A Unified Benchmark for Generalizable Manipulation Skills</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maniskill2-a-unified-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalizable manipulation skills, which can be composed to tackle long-horizon and complex daily chores, are one of the cornerstones of Embodied AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maniskill2-a-unified-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating a Structured Summary of Numerous Academic Papers: Dataset and Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-a-structured-summary-of-numerous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing MDS datasets usually focus on producing the structureless summary covering a few input documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-a-structured-summary-of-numerous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Learning for Requirements Classification: An Exploratory Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-learning-for-requirements</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Principal ideas-results: To address this challenge, this paper proposes an approach that employs the embedding-based unsupervised Zero-Shot Learning (ZSL) technique to perform requirements classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-learning-for-requirements</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Anomaly Detection: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-anomaly-detection-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Anomaly detection (AD) is a crucial task in machine learning with various applications, such as detecting emerging diseases, identifying financial frauds, and detecting fake news.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-anomaly-detection-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Select Pivotal Samples for Meta Re-weighting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-select-pivotal-samples-for-meta</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study how to learn to identify such a meta sample set from a large, imperfect training set, that is subsequently cleaned and used to optimize performance in the meta re-weighting setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-select-pivotal-samples-for-meta</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Constraints with Prompting for Zero-Shot Event Argument Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-constraints-with-prompting-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose to use global constraints with prompting to effectively tackles event argument classification without any annotation and task-specific training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-constraints-with-prompting-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GCI: A (G)raph (C)oncept (I)nterpretation Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gci-a-g-raph-c-oncept-i-nterpretation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Explainable AI (XAI) underwent a recent surge in research on concept extraction, focusing on extracting human-interpretable concepts from Deep Neural Networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gci-a-g-raph-c-oncept-i-nterpretation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gentlest ascent dynamics on manifolds defined by adaptively sampled point-clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gentlest-ascent-dynamics-on-manifolds-defined</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finding saddle points of dynamical systems is an important problem in practical applications such as the study of rare events of molecular systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gentlest-ascent-dynamics-on-manifolds-defined</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Visual Feedback to Guide Benchmark Creation: A Human-and-Metric-in-the-Loop Workflow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-visual-feedback-to-guide-benchmark-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In pursuit of creating better benchmarks, we propose VAIDA, a novel benchmark creation paradigm for NLP, that focuses on guiding crowdworkers, an under-explored facet of addressing benchmark idiosyncrasies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-visual-feedback-to-guide-benchmark-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>rMultiNet: An R Package For Multilayer Networks Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmultinet-an-r-package-for-multilayer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper develops an R package rMultiNet to analyze multilayer network data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmultinet-an-r-package-for-multilayer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperparameter Search Is All You Need For Training-Agnostic Backdoor Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameter-search-is-all-you-need-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate how to use our metric to estimate the robustness of models to backdoor attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameter-search-is-all-you-need-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Context Learning with Many Demonstration Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-learning-with-many-demonstration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on EVALM, we scale up the size of examples efficiently in both instruction tuning and in-context learning to explore the boundary of the benefits from more annotated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-learning-with-many-demonstration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaussian Process-Gated Hierarchical Mixtures of Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-process-gated-hierarchical-mixtures</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, the experts are also built with Gaussian processes and provide predictions that depend on test data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-process-gated-hierarchical-mixtures</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
