<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 21:06:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patent image retrieval using transformer-based deep metric learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patent-image-retrieval-using-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intellectual property work covers a wide range of areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patent-image-retrieval-using-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Deployment Adaptation with Access to Source Data via Federated Learning and Source-Target Remote Gradient Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-deployment-adaptation-with-access-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper challenges this assumption and introduces FedPDA, a novel adaptation framework that brings the utility of learning from remote data from Federated Learning into PDA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-deployment-adaptation-with-access-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficacy of Neural Prediction-Based NAS for Zero-Shot NAS Paradigm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficacy-of-neural-prediction-based-nas-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, handcrafted performance indicators (zero-shot NAS), which use the same architecture with random initialization, can generalize across multiple search spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficacy-of-neural-prediction-based-nas-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpreting Sentiment Composition with Latent Semantic Tree</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-sentiment-composition-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the key to sentiment analysis, sentiment composition considers the classification of a constituent via classifications of its contained sub-constituents and rules operated on them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-sentiment-composition-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-evolving Vector Quantization for ID-based Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-evolving-vector-quantization-for-id-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Category information plays a crucial role in enhancing the quality and personalization of recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-evolving-vector-quantization-for-id-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curvature-based Pooling within Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvature-based-pooling-within-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CurvPool exploits the notion of curvature of a graph to adaptively identify structures responsible for both over-smoothing and over-squashing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvature-based-pooling-within-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointLLM: Empowering Large Language Models to Understand Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointllm-empowering-large-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The unprecedented advancements in Large Language Models (LLMs) have created a profound impact on natural language processing but are yet to fully embrace the realm of 3D understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointllm-empowering-large-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Programming Languages Boost Each Other via Instruction Tuning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-programming-languages-boost-each-other</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results demonstrate that programming languages can significantly improve each other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-programming-languages-boost-each-other</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointOcc: Cylindrical Tri-Perspective View for Point-based 3D Semantic Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointocc-cylindrical-tri-perspective-view-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose a cylindrical tri-perspective view to represent point clouds effectively and comprehensively and a PointOcc model to process them efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointocc-cylindrical-tri-perspective-view-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleInV: A Temporal Style Modulated Inversion Network for Unconditional Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styleinv-a-temporal-style-modulated-inversion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel motion generator design that uses a learning-based inversion network for GAN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styleinv-a-temporal-style-modulated-inversion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BioCoder: A Benchmark for Bioinformatics Code Generation with Contextual Pragmatic Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biocoder-a-benchmark-for-bioinformatics-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BioCoder incorporates a fuzz-testing framework for evaluation, and we have applied it to evaluate many models including InCoder, CodeGen, CodeGen2, SantaCoder, StarCoder, StarCoder+, InstructCodeT5+, and ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biocoder-a-benchmark-for-bioinformatics-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained Cross-View Geo-Localization Using a Correlation-Aware Homography Estimator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-cross-view-geo-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel approach to fine-grained cross-view geo-localization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-cross-view-geo-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BenchTemp: A General Benchmark for Evaluating Temporal Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchtemp-a-general-benchmark-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To handle graphs in which features or connectivities are evolving over time, a series of temporal graph neural networks (TGNNs) have been proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchtemp-a-general-benchmark-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-pruning Graph Neural Network for Predicting Inflammatory Disease Activity in Multiple Sclerosis from Brain MR Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-pruning-graph-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a two-stage MS inflammatory disease activity prediction approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-pruning-graph-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything, Everywhere All in One Evaluation: Using Multiverse Analysis to Evaluate the Influence of Model Design Decisions on Algorithmic Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/everything-everywhere-all-in-one-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is therefore important to make explicit the decisions made during the design of ADM systems and understand how these decisions affect the fairness of the resulting system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/everything-everywhere-all-in-one-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple LLM Prompting is State-of-the-Art for Robust and Multilingual Dialogue Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-llm-prompting-is-state-of-the-art-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant research effort in the development of automatic dialogue evaluation metrics, little thought is given to evaluating dialogues other than in English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-llm-prompting-is-state-of-the-art-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Incomplete Multi-View Clustering with Structure Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-incomplete-multi-view-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although several anchor-based IMVC methods have been proposed to process the large-scale incomplete data, they still suffer from the following drawbacks: i) Most existing approaches neglect the inter-view discrepancy and enforce cross-view representation to be consistent, which would corrupt the representation capability of the model; ii) Due to the samples disparity between different views, the learned anchor might be misaligned, which we referred as the Anchor-Unaligned Problem for Incomplete data (AUP-ID).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-incomplete-multi-view-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Njobvu-AI: An open-source tool for collaborative image labeling and implementation of computer vision models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/njobvu-ai-an-open-source-tool-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This step is often not compatible with many cloud-based services for marking or labeling image and video data due to limited internet bandwidth in many regions of the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/njobvu-ai-an-open-source-tool-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-adaptive Message Passing Graph Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-message-passing-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-network node classification (CNNC), which aims to classify nodes in a label-deficient target network by transferring the knowledge from a source network with abundant labels, draws increasing attention recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-message-passing-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CktGNN: Circuit Graph Neural Network for Electronic Design Automation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cktgnn-circuit-graph-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The electronic design automation of analog circuits has been a longstanding challenge in the integrated circuit field due to the huge design space and complex design trade-offs among circuit specifications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cktgnn-circuit-graph-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RGB-T Tracking via Multi-Modal Mutual Prompt Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgb-t-tracking-via-multi-modal-mutual-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object tracking based on the fusion of visible and thermal im-ages, known as RGB-T tracking, has gained increasing atten-tion from researchers in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgb-t-tracking-via-multi-modal-mutual-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InterDiff: Generating 3D Human-Object Interactions with Physics-Informed Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interdiff-generating-3d-human-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses a novel task of anticipating 3D human-object interactions (HOIs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interdiff-generating-3d-human-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate Your Own Scotland: Satellite Image Generation Conditioned on Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generate-your-own-scotland-satellite-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advancements in image generation, diffusion models still remain largely underexplored in Earth Observation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generate-your-own-scotland-satellite-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoMA: Momentum Contrastive Learning with Multi-head Attention-based Knowledge Distillation for Histopathology Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moma-momentum-contrastive-learning-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we employ a student-teacher framework to learn a target model from a pre-trained, teacher model without direct access to source data and distill relevant knowledge via momentum contrastive learning with multi-head attention mechanism, which provides consistent and context-aware feature representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moma-momentum-contrastive-learning-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScrollNet: Dynamic Weight Importance for Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scrollnet-dynamic-weight-importance-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The importance of weights for each task can be determined either explicitly through learning a task-specific mask during training (e. g., parameter isolation-based approaches) or implicitly by introducing a regularization term (e. g., regularization-based approaches).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scrollnet-dynamic-weight-importance-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised CT Metal Artifact Reduction by Plugging Diffusion Priors in Dual Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-ct-metal-artifact-reduction-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an unsupervised MAR method based on the diffusion model, a generative model with a high capacity to represent data distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-ct-metal-artifact-reduction-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Lens Flare Removal with General Purpose Pipeline and Multiple Light Sources Recovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-lens-flare-removal-with-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a solution to improve the performance of lens flare removal by revisiting the ISP and remodeling the principle of automatic exposure in the synthesis pipeline and design a more reliable light sources recovery strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-lens-flare-removal-with-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Optimal Patch Size in Vision Transformers for Tumor Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-optimal-patch-size-in-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although transformers can capture long-range features, their segmentation performance decreases with various tumor sizes due to the model sensitivity to the input patch size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-optimal-patch-size-in-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Gradient Regularizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-gradient-regularizer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NGR is applicable to various image types and different image processing tasks, functioning in a zero-shot learning fashion, making it a versatile and plug-and-play regularizer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-gradient-regularizer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D-STMN: Dependency-Driven Superpoint-Text Matching Network for End-to-End 3D Referring Expression Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-stmn-dependency-driven-superpoint-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In 3D Referring Expression Segmentation (3D-RES), the earlier approach adopts a two-stage paradigm, extracting segmentation proposals and then matching them with referring expressions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-stmn-dependency-driven-superpoint-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illumination Distillation Framework for Nighttime Person Re-Identification and A New Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illumination-distillation-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The illumination enhancement branch first estimates an enhanced image from the nighttime image using a nonlinear curve mapping method and then extracts the enhanced features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illumination-distillation-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Recognition of Unknown Objects for Open-World Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-recognition-of-unknown-objects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-World Object Detection (OWOD) extends object detection problem to a realistic and dynamic scenario, where a detection model is required to be capable of detecting both known and unknown objects and incrementally learning newly introduced knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-recognition-of-unknown-objects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Power of MEME: Adversarial Malware Creation with Model-Based Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-power-of-meme-adversarial-malware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, machine learning models are susceptible to adversarial attacks, requiring the testing of model and product robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-power-of-meme-adversarial-malware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNFactor: Multi-Task Real Robot Learning with Generalizable Neural Feature Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnfactor-multi-task-real-robot-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To incorporate semantics in 3D, the reconstruction module utilizes a vision-language foundation model ($\textit{e. g.}$, Stable Diffusion) to distill rich semantic information into the deep 3D voxel.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnfactor-multi-task-real-robot-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMDB: The Electromagnetic Database of Global 3D Human Pose and Shape in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emdb-the-electromagnetic-database-of-global</link>
      <description><![CDATA[EMDB is a novel dataset that contains high-quality 3D SMPL pose and shape parameters with global body and camera trajectories for in-the-wild videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emdb-the-electromagnetic-database-of-global</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Few-shot Image Generation by Structural Discrimination and Textural Modulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-few-shot-image-generation-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the frequency awareness of the model is reinforced by encouraging the model to distinguish frequency signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-few-shot-image-generation-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deontic Paradoxes in ASP with Weak Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deontic-paradoxes-in-asp-with-weak</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise of powerful AI technology for a range of applications that are sensitive to legal, social, and ethical norms demands decision-making support in presence of norms and regulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deontic-paradoxes-in-asp-with-weak</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpSAT-TD in Model Counting Competitions 2021-2023</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharpsat-td-in-model-counting-competitions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe SharpSAT-TD, our submission to the unweighted and weighted tracks of the Model Counting Competition in 2021-2023, which has won in total $6$ first places in different tracks of the competition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharpsat-td-in-model-counting-competitions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explanations for Answer Set Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanations-for-answer-set-programming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from xASP, the new system, xASP2, supports different clingo constructs like the choice rules, the constraints, and the aggregates such as #sum, #min.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanations-for-answer-set-programming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Reward Shaping using Human Feedback for Correcting Reward Misspecification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-reward-shaping-using-human-feedback</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach allows the user to provide trajectory-level feedback on agent's behavior during training, which can be integrated as a reward shaping signal in the following training iteration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-reward-shaping-using-human-feedback</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaSM: Large Language and Speech Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llasm-large-language-and-speech-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose Large Language and Speech Model (LLaSM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llasm-large-language-and-speech-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Deep Learning for Full-disk Solar Flare Prediction with Empirical Insights from Guided Grad-CAM Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-deep-learning-for-full-disk-solar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study progresses solar flare prediction research by presenting a full-disk deep-learning model to forecast $\geq$M-class solar flares and evaluating its efficacy on both central (within $\pm$70$^\circ$) and near-limb (beyond $\pm$70$^\circ$) events, showcasing qualitative assessment of post hoc explanations for the model's predictions, and providing empirical findings from human-centered quantitative assessments of these explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-deep-learning-for-full-disk-solar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards One-Shot Learning for Text Classification using Inductive Logic Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-one-shot-learning-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the ever-increasing potential of AI to perform personalised tasks, it is becoming essential to develop new machine learning techniques which are data-efficient and do not require hundreds or thousands of training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-one-shot-learning-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-Rank Multitask Learning based on Tensorized SVMs and LSSVMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-rank-multitask-learning-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to previous MTL frameworks, our decision function in the dual induces a weighted kernel function with a task-coupling term characterized by the similarities of the task-specific factors, better revealing the explicit relations across tasks in MTL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-rank-multitask-learning-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Multilabel Topic Classification in the Kyrgyz Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-multilabel-topic-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Kyrgyz is a very underrepresented language in terms of modern natural language processing resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-multilabel-topic-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Response: Emergent analogical reasoning in large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/response-emergent-analogical-reasoning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In their recent Nature Human Behaviour paper, "Emergent analogical reasoning in large language models," (Webb, Holyoak, and Lu, 2023) the authors argue that "large language models such as GPT-3 have acquired an emergent ability to find zero-shot solutions to a broad range of analogy problems."]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/response-emergent-analogical-reasoning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Underwater Visual Tracking With a Large Scale Dataset and Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-underwater-visual-tracking-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The method has resulted in a significant performance improvement, of up to 5. 0% AUC, of state-of-the-art (SOTA) visual trackers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-underwater-visual-tracking-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Multi-Modalities Fusion in Sequential Recommendation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-multi-modalities-fusion-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a graph-based approach (named MMSR) to fuse modality features in an adaptive order, enabling each modality to prioritize either its inherent sequential nature or its interplay with other modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-multi-modalities-fusion-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHARP Challenge 2023: Solving CAD History and pArameters Recovery from Point clouds and 3D scans. Overview, Datasets, Metrics, and Baselines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharp-challenge-2023-solving-cad-history-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we define the proposed SHARP 2023 tracks, describe the provided datasets, and propose a set of baseline methods along with suitable evaluation metrics to assess the performance of the track solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharp-challenge-2023-solving-cad-history-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calibrated Explanations for Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrated-explanations-for-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces an extension of a feature importance explanation method, Calibrated Explanations (CE), previously only supporting classification, with support for standard regression and probabilistic regression, i. e., the probability that the target is above an arbitrary threshold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrated-explanations-for-regression</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
