<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 21:08:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CLOUDSPAM: Contrastive Learning On Unlabeled Data for Segmentation and Pre-Training Using Aggregated Point Clouds and MoCo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cloudspam-contrastive-learning-on-unlabeled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this merging is not a straightforward procedure due to the variety of size and number of points in the point clouds of these datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cloudspam-contrastive-learning-on-unlabeled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing Reasoning Capability of LLMs via Scalable Question Synthesis from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-reasoning-capability-of-llms-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The availability of high-quality data is one of the most important factors in improving the reasoning capability of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-reasoning-capability-of-llms-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DreamClear: High-Capacity Real-World Image Restoration with Privacy-Safe Dataset Curation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamclear-high-capacity-real-world-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our second contribution, DreamClear, is a DiT-based image restoration model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamclear-high-capacity-real-world-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMITE: Segment Me In TimE</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smite-segment-me-in-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segmenting an object in a video presents significant challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smite-segment-me-in-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Better Open-Ended Text Generation: A Multicriteria Evaluation Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-open-ended-text-generation-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-ended text generation has become a prominent task in natural language processing due to the rise of powerful (large) language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-open-ended-text-generation-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Class Abnormality Classification in Video Capsule Endoscopy Using Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-class-abnormality-classification-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report outlines Team Seq2Cure's deep learning approach for the Capsule Vision 2024 Challenge, leveraging an ensemble of convolutional neural networks (CNNs) and transformer-based architectures for multi-class abnormality classification in video capsule endoscopy frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-class-abnormality-classification-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-Augmented Diffusion Models for Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-diffusion-models-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, this reference-guided mechanism also compensates for the deficiencies of existing time series diffusion models in terms of guidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-diffusion-models-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distill Visual Chart Reasoning Ability from LLMs to MLLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distill-visual-chart-reasoning-ability-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we employ text-based synthesizing techniques to construct chart-plotting code and produce ReachQA, a dataset containing 3k reasoning-intensive charts and 20k Q&A pairs to enhance both recognition and reasoning abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distill-visual-chart-reasoning-ability-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Self-Tuning LLMs for Enhanced Jailbreaking Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-self-tuning-llms-for-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research has shown that Large Language Models (LLMs) are vulnerable to automated jailbreak attacks, where adversarial suffixes crafted by algorithms appended to harmful queries bypass safety alignment and trigger unintended responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-self-tuning-llms-for-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Irregular Tensor Low-Rank Representation for Hyperspectral Image Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irregular-tensor-low-rank-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the spatial distribution of the HSI is always irregular, while the previous tensor low-rank representation methods can only be applied to the regular data cubes, which limits the performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irregular-tensor-low-rank-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIKeD: Self-guided Iterative Knowledge Distillation for mathematical reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siked-self-guided-iterative-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While LLMs can accurately solve reasoning tasks through a variety of strategies, even without fine-tuning, smaller models are not expressive enough to fit the LLMs distribution on all strategies when distilled and tend to prioritize one strategy over the others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siked-self-guided-iterative-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Language-Image Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-language-image-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language models (VLMs) embed aligned image-text pairs into a joint space but often rely on deterministic embeddings, assuming a one-to-one correspondence between images and texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-language-image-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Link, Synthesize, Retrieve: Universal Document Linking for Zero-Shot Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-synthesize-retrieve-universal-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the recent advancements in information retrieval (IR), zero-shot IR remains a significant challenge, especially when dealing with new domains, languages, and newly-released use cases that lack historical query traffic from existing users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-synthesize-retrieve-universal-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Interpretable Capabilities with Concept-Enhanced Diffusion and Prototype Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-interpretable-capabilities-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concept-based machine learning methods have increasingly gained importance due to the growing interest in making neural networks interpretable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-interpretable-capabilities-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models Reflect the Ideology of their Creators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-reflect-the-ideology-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By identifying and analyzing moral assessments reflected in the generated descriptions, we find consistent normative differences between how the same LLM responds in Chinese compared to English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-reflect-the-ideology-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Vocabulary Pruning in Early-Exit LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-vocabulary-pruning-in-early-exit-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Increasing the size of large language models (LLMs) has been shown to lead to better performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-vocabulary-pruning-in-early-exit-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-Latency Video Anonymization for Crowd Anomaly Detection: Privacy vs. Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-latency-video-anonymization-for-crowd</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluated the approaches on publicly available privacy and VAD data sets to examine the strengths and weaknesses of the different anonymization techniques and highlight the promising efficacy of our approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-latency-video-anonymization-for-crowd</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-end Training for Recommendation with Language-based User Profiles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-training-for-recommendation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While existing work has shown that language-based profiles from standard LLMs can be effective, such generalist LLMs are unlikely to be optimal for this task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-training-for-recommendation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRISM: A Methodology for Auditing Biases in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prism-a-methodology-for-auditing-biases-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Auditing Large Language Models (LLMs) to discover their biases and preferences is an emerging challenge in creating Responsible Artificial Intelligence (AI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prism-a-methodology-for-auditing-biases-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAFFLE: Multi-Modal Model for Automated Front-End Development</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/waffle-multi-modal-model-for-automated-front</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Web development involves turning UI designs into functional webpages, which can be difficult for both beginners and experienced developers due to the complexity of HTML's hierarchical structures and styles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/waffle-multi-modal-model-for-automated-front</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving Object Segmentation in Point Cloud Data using Hidden Markov Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moving-object-segmentation-in-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous agents require the capability to identify dynamic objects in their environment for safe planning and navigation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moving-object-segmentation-in-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Explaining with Attention Matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-explaining-with-attention-matrices</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce and effectively compute efficient attention, which isolates the effective components of attention matrices in tasks and models in which AW play an explanatory role.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-explaining-with-attention-matrices</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should We Really Edit Language Models? On the Evaluation of Edited Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/should-we-really-edit-language-models-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings indicate that current editing methods are only suitable for small-scale knowledge updates within language models, which motivates further research on more practical and reliable editing methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/should-we-really-edit-language-models-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Watermarking Using Generative Priors Against Image Editing: From Benchmarking to Advances</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-watermarking-using-generative-priors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current image watermarking methods are vulnerable to advanced image editing techniques enabled by large-scale text-to-image models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-watermarking-using-generative-priors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeCoRe: Decoding by Contrasting Retrieval Heads to Mitigate Hallucinations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decore-decoding-by-contrasting-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) often hallucinate, producing unfaithful or factually incorrect outputs by misrepresenting the provided context or incorrectly recalling internal knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decore-decoding-by-contrasting-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D-Adapter: Geometry-Consistent Multi-View Diffusion for High-Quality 3D Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-adapter-geometry-consistent-multi-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-view image diffusion models have significantly advanced open-domain 3D object generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-adapter-geometry-consistent-multi-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wavetable Synthesis Using CVAE for Timbre Control Based on Semantic Label</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavetable-synthesis-using-cvae-for-timbre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research introduces a method of timbre control in wavetable synthesis that is intuitive and sensible and utilizes semantic labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavetable-synthesis-using-cvae-for-timbre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bilinear Sequence Regression: A Model for Learning from Long Sequences of High-dimensional Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilinear-sequence-regression-a-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Statistical physics provides powerful tools to study the functioning of learning with neural networks and has played a recognized role in the development of modern machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilinear-sequence-regression-a-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Imitation to Introspection: Probing Self-Consciousness in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-imitation-to-introspection-probing-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-consciousness, the introspection of one's existence and thoughts, represents a high-level cognitive process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-imitation-to-introspection-probing-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thermal Chameleon: Task-Adaptive Tone-mapping for Radiometric Thermal-Infrared images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermal-chameleon-task-adaptive-tone-mapping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thermal Infrared (TIR) imaging provides robust perception for navigating in challenging outdoor environments but faces issues with poor texture and low image contrast due to its 14/16-bit format.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermal-chameleon-task-adaptive-tone-mapping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MissNODAG: Differentiable Cyclic Causal Graph Learning from Incomplete Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/missnodag-differentiable-cyclic-causal-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal discovery in real-world systems, such as biological networks, is often complicated by feedback loops and incomplete data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/missnodag-differentiable-cyclic-causal-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KVSharer: Efficient Inference via Layer-Wise Dissimilar KV Cache Sharing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kvsharer-efficient-inference-via-layer-wise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we verify that \textit{KVSharer} is compatible with existing intra-layer KV cache compression methods, and combining both can further save memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kvsharer-efficient-inference-via-layer-wise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difficult for Whom? A Study of Japanese Lexical Complexity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difficult-for-whom-a-study-of-japanese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The tasks of lexical complexity prediction (LCP) and complex word identification (CWI) commonly presuppose that difficult to understand words are shared by the target population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difficult-for-whom-a-study-of-japanese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart ETL and LLM-based contents classification: the European Smart Tourism Tools Observatory experience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-etl-and-llm-based-contents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results: The Smart ETL process to import STTs to the observatory combines PDF-scraping techniques with LLMs for text content-based classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-etl-and-llm-based-contents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Consistency Tuning: Understanding and Improving Consistency Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-consistency-tuning-understanding-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models achieve superior generation quality but suffer from slow generation speed due to the iterative nature of denoising.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-consistency-tuning-understanding-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classifier Clustering and Feature Alignment for Federated Learning under Distributed Concept Drift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classifier-clustering-and-feature-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, to address data heterogeneity, we study the feature alignment under distributed concept drift, and find two factors that are crucial for feature alignment: the conditional distribution $P(Y|X)$ and the degree of data heterogeneity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classifier-clustering-and-feature-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context is Key: A Benchmark for Forecasting with Essential Textual Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-is-key-a-benchmark-for-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce "Context is Key" (CiK), a time series forecasting benchmark that pairs numerical data with diverse types of carefully crafted textual context, requiring models to integrate both modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-is-key-a-benchmark-for-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying Large Language Models for Medicine: A Primer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-large-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then review the strategies, such as prompt engineering and fine-tuning, to adapt standard LLMs to specialized medical tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-large-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling up Masked Diffusion Models on Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-masked-diffusion-models-on-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Masked diffusion models (MDMs) have shown promise in language modeling, yet their scalability and effectiveness in core language tasks, such as text generation and language understanding, remain underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-masked-diffusion-models-on-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homomorphism Counts as Structural Encodings for Graph Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/homomorphism-counts-as-structural-encodings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Transformers are popular neural networks that extend the well-known Transformer architecture to the graph domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/homomorphism-counts-as-structural-encodings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Joint Representation Using Continuous and Discrete Features for Cardiovascular Diseases Risk Prediction on Chest CT Scans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-joint-representation-using-continuous-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we proposed a novel joint representation that integrates discrete quantitative biomarkers and continuous deep features extracted from chest CT scans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-joint-representation-using-continuous-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully Stochastic Primal-dual Gradient Algorithm for Non-convex Optimization on Random Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-stochastic-primal-dual-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stochastic decentralized optimization algorithms often suffer from issues such as synchronization overhead and intermittent communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-stochastic-primal-dual-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOGO -- Long cOntext aliGnment via efficient preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logo-long-context-alignment-via-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome the GPU memory-bound issue caused by the long sequence, LOGO employs a reference-free preference optimization strategy and adopts a position synthesis method to construct the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logo-long-context-alignment-via-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing pretraining efficiency for medical image segmentation via transferability metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-pretraining-efficiency-for-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By examining over 300 combinations of models, datasets, and training methods, we find that shorter pretraining often leads to better results on the downstream task, providing additional proof to the well-known fact that the accuracy of the model on ImageNet is a poor indicator for downstream performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-pretraining-efficiency-for-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tuning-free coreset Markov chain Monte Carlo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tuning-free-coreset-markov-chain-monte-carlo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A Bayesian coreset is a small, weighted subset of a data set that replaces the full data during inference to reduce computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tuning-free-coreset-markov-chain-monte-carlo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time 3D-aware Portrait Video Relighting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-3d-aware-portrait-video-relighting-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the effectiveness and interactivity of our method on various portrait videos with diverse lighting and viewing conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-3d-aware-portrait-video-relighting-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What If the Input is Expanded in OOD Detection?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-if-the-input-is-expanded-in-ood</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on that, we formalize a new scoring method, namely, Confidence aVerage (CoVer), which can capture the dynamic differences by simply averaging the scores obtained from different corrupted inputs and the original ones, making the OOD and ID distributions more separable in detection tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-if-the-input-is-expanded-in-ood</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMAN: An Adaptive Network for Robust NPC Mortality Prediction with Missing Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iman-an-adaptive-network-for-robust-npc</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate prediction of mortality in nasopharyngeal carcinoma (NPC), a complex malignancy particularly challenging in advanced stages, is crucial for optimizing treatment strategies and improving patient outcomes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iman-an-adaptive-network-for-robust-npc</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreCaS: Efficient Higher-Resolution Image Generation via Frequency-aware Cascaded Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frecas-efficient-higher-resolution-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While image generation with diffusion models has achieved a great success, generating images of higher resolution than the training size remains a challenging task due to the high computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frecas-efficient-higher-resolution-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMEL-Bench: A Comprehensive Arabic LMM Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camel-bench-a-comprehensive-arabic-lmm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop a comprehensive LMM evaluation benchmark for the Arabic language to represent a large population of over 400 million speakers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camel-bench-a-comprehensive-arabic-lmm</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
