<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:11:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of the Evolution of Advanced Transformer-Based Language Models: Experiments on Opinion Mining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-the-evolution-of-advanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Opinion mining, also known as sentiment analysis, is a subfield of natural language processing (NLP) that focuses on identifying and extracting subjective information in textual material.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-the-evolution-of-advanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Randomized algorithms for precise measurement of differentially-private, personalized recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randomized-algorithms-for-precise-measurement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized recommendations form an important part of today's internet ecosystem, helping artists and creators to reach interested users, and helping users to discover new and engaging content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randomized-algorithms-for-precise-measurement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PURL: Safe and Effective Sanitization of Link Decoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/purl-safe-and-effective-sanitization-of-link</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since trackers need to exfiltrate information from the client- to server-side through link decoration regardless of the tracking technique they employ, a promising orthogonal approach is to detect and sanitize tracking information in decorated links.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/purl-safe-and-effective-sanitization-of-link</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do You Remember? Overcoming Catastrophic Forgetting for Fake Audio Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-you-remember-overcoming-catastrophic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The orthogonal weight modification to overcome catastrophic forgetting does not consider the similarity of genuine audio across different datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-you-remember-overcoming-catastrophic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Adversarial Detection without Extra Model: Training Loss Should Change</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-adversarial-detection-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial robustness poses a critical challenge in the deployment of deep learning models for real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-adversarial-detection-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Aggregation Transformer for Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-aggregation-transformer-for-image-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the above idea, we propose a novel Transformer model, Dual Aggregation Transformer (DAT), for image SR. Our DAT aggregates features across spatial and channel dimensions, in the inter-block and intra-block dual manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-aggregation-transformer-for-image-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-View Graph Convolutional Network for Multimedia Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-graph-convolutional-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, a behavior-aware fuser is designed to comprehensively model user preferences by adaptively learning the relative importance of different modality features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-graph-convolutional-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotionally Numb or Empathetic? Evaluating How LLMs Feel Using EmotionBench</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotionally-numb-or-empathetic-evaluating-how</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aspire to contribute to the advancement of LLMs regarding better alignment with the emotional behaviors of human beings, thereby enhancing their utility and applicability as intelligent assistants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotionally-numb-or-empathetic-evaluating-how</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Model in Causal Inference with Unmeasured Confounders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-model-in-causal-inference-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study how to extend the use of the diffusion model to answer the causal question from the observational data under the existence of unmeasured confounders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-model-in-causal-inference-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubly Robust Estimator for Off-Policy Evaluation with Large Action Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doubly-robust-estimator-for-off-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, Marginalized Inverse Propensity Scoring (MIPS) was proposed to mitigate the estimator's variance via embeddings of an action.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doubly-robust-estimator-for-off-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AFN: Adaptive Fusion Normalization via Encoder-Decoder Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/afn-adaptive-fusion-normalization-via-encoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of deep learning is inseparable from normalization layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/afn-adaptive-fusion-normalization-via-encoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SciGraphQA: A Large-Scale Synthetic Multi-Turn Question-Answering Dataset for Scientific Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scigraphqa-a-large-scale-synthetic-multi-turn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We asked GPT-4 to assess the matching quality of our question-answer turns given the paper's context, obtaining an average rating of 8. 7/10 on our 3K test set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scigraphqa-a-large-scale-synthetic-multi-turn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmark for Chinese-English Scene Text Image Super-resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-chinese-english-scene-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scene Text Image Super-resolution (STISR) aims to recover high-resolution (HR) scene text images with visually pleasant and readable text content from the given low-resolution (LR) input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-chinese-english-scene-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurvBeX: An explanation method of the machine learning survival models based on the Beran estimator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survbex-an-explanation-method-of-the-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For every generated example, the survival function of the black-box model is computed, and the survival function of the surrogate model (the Beran estimator) is constructed as a function of the explanation coefficients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survbex-an-explanation-method-of-the-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PaniniQA: Enhancing Patient Education Through Interactive Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paniniqa-enhancing-patient-education-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Patient portal allows discharged patients to access their personalized discharge instructions in electronic health records (EHRs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paniniqa-enhancing-patient-education-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiT: Efficient Vision Transformers with Dynamic Token Routing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dit-efficient-vision-transformers-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed framework generates a data-dependent path per token, adapting to the object scales and visual discrimination of tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dit-efficient-vision-transformers-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bilevel Generative Learning for Low-Light Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilevel-generative-learning-for-low-light</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a generic low-light vision solution by introducing a generative block to convert data from the RAW to the RGB domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilevel-generative-learning-for-low-light</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dimensionality Reduction for Improving Out-of-Distribution Detection in Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dimensionality-reduction-for-improving-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clinically deployed segmentation models are known to fail on data outside of their training distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dimensionality-reduction-for-improving-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APBench: A Unified Benchmark for Availability Poisoning Attacks and Defenses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apbench-a-unified-benchmark-for-availability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further evaluate the attack and defense capabilities of these poisoning methods, we have developed a benchmark -- APBench for assessing the efficacy of adversarial poisoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apbench-a-unified-benchmark-for-availability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lighting Every Darkness in Two Pairs: A Calibration-Free Pipeline for RAW Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lighting-every-darkness-in-two-pairs-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Calibration-based methods have dominated RAW image denoising under extremely low-light environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lighting-every-darkness-in-two-pairs-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning a Graph Neural Network with Cross Modality Interaction for Image Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-graph-neural-network-with-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we merge all graph features to get the fusion result.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-graph-neural-network-with-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaptiveSAM: Towards Efficient Tuning of SAM for Surgical Scene Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptivesam-towards-efficient-tuning-of-sam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, SAM does not generalize well to the medical domain as is without utilizing a large amount of compute resources for fine-tuning and using task-specific prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptivesam-towards-efficient-tuning-of-sam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biomedical Knowledge Graph Embeddings with Negative Statements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomedical-knowledge-graph-embeddings-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Explicitly considering negative statements has been shown to improve performance on tasks such as entity summarization and question answering or domain-specific tasks such as protein function prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomedical-knowledge-graph-embeddings-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentBench: Evaluating LLMs as Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentbench-evaluating-llms-as-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are becoming increasingly smart and autonomous, targeting real-world pragmatic missions beyond traditional NLP tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentbench-evaluating-llms-as-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling may be all you need for achieving human-level object recognition capacity with human-like visual experience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-may-be-all-you-need-for-achieving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that it is feasible to reach human-level object recognition capacity at sub-human scales of model size, data size, and image size, if these factors are scaled up simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-may-be-all-you-need-for-achieving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynJax: Structured Probability Distributions for JAX</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synjax-structured-probability-distributions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The models that explicitly account for structured objects, such as trees and segmentations, did not benefit equally because they require custom algorithms that are difficult to implement in a vectorized form.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synjax-structured-probability-distributions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny LVLM-eHub: Early Multimodal Experiments with Bard</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiny-lvlm-ehub-early-multimodal-experiments</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, it conducts an in-depth analysis of LVLMs' predictions using the ChatGPT Ensemble Evaluation (CEE), which leads to a robust and accurate evaluation and exhibits improved alignment with human evaluation compared to the word matching approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiny-lvlm-ehub-early-multimodal-experiments</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Forgetting Compensation for Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-forgetting-compensation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To surmount the above challenges, we develop a novel Heterogeneous Forgetting Compensation (HFC) model, which can resolve heterogeneous forgetting of easy-to-forget and hard-to-forget old categories from both representation and gradient aspects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-forgetting-compensation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FSD V2: Improving Fully Sparse 3D Object Detection with Virtual Voxels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fsd-v2-improving-fully-sparse-3d-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consequently, we develop a suite of components to complement the virtual voxel concept, including a virtual voxel encoder, a virtual voxel mixer, and a virtual voxel assignment strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fsd-v2-improving-fully-sparse-3d-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cal-SFDA: Source-Free Domain-adaptive Semantic Segmentation with Differentiable Expected Calibration Error</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cal-sfda-source-free-domain-adaptive-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prevalence of domain adaptive semantic segmentation has prompted concerns regarding source domain data leakage, where private information from the source domain could inadvertently be exposed in the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cal-sfda-source-free-domain-adaptive-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focus the Discrepancy: Intra- and Inter-Correlation Learning for Image Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focus-the-discrepancy-intra-and-inter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Humans recognize anomalies through two aspects: larger patch-wise representation discrepancies and weaker patch-to-normal-patch correlations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focus-the-discrepancy-intra-and-inter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FireFly A Synthetic Dataset for Ember Detection in Wildfire</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/firefly-a-synthetic-dataset-for-ember</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents "FireFly", a synthetic dataset for ember detection created using Unreal Engine 4 (UE4), designed to overcome the current lack of ember-specific training resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/firefly-a-synthetic-dataset-for-ember</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precise Benchmarking of Explainable AI Attribution Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precise-benchmarking-of-explainable-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental results provide novel insights into the performance of Guided-Backprop and Smoothgrad XAI methods that are widely in use.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precise-benchmarking-of-explainable-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGBA: Curvature-aware Geometric Black-box Attack</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cgba-curvature-aware-geometric-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the proposed CGBA attack can work effectively for an arbitrary decision boundary, it is particularly efficient in exploiting the low curvature to craft high-quality adversarial examples, which is widely seen and experimentally verified in commonly used classifiers under non-targeted attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cgba-curvature-aware-geometric-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NNVISR: Bring Neural Network Video Interpolation and Super Resolution into Video Processing Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nnvisr-bring-neural-network-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present NNVISR - an open-source filter plugin for the VapourSynth video processing framework, which facilitates the application of neural networks for various kinds of video enhancing tasks, including denoising, super resolution, interpolation, and spatio-temporal super-resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nnvisr-bring-neural-network-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Fine-Grained Features for Pixel-wise Video Correspondences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-fine-grained-features-for-pixel-wise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the problem of learning features for establishing pixel-wise correspondences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-fine-grained-features-for-pixel-wise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FourLLIE: Boosting Low-Light Image Enhancement by Fourier Frequency Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fourllie-boosting-low-light-image-enhancement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first stage, we improve the lightness of low-light images by estimating the amplitude transform map in the Fourier space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fourllie-boosting-low-light-image-enhancement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECT: Fine-grained Edge Detection with Learned Cause Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ect-fine-grained-edge-detection-with-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these three issues, we propose a two-stage transformer-based network sequentially predicting generic edges and fine-grained edges, which has a global receptive field thanks to the attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ect-fine-grained-edge-detection-with-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOPIQ: A Top-down Approach from Semantics to Distortions for Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topiq-a-top-down-approach-from-semantics-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach to IQA involves the design of a heuristic coarse-to-fine network (CFANet) that leverages multi-scale features and progressively propagates multi-level semantic information to low-level representations in a top-down manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topiq-a-top-down-approach-from-semantics-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lightweight Method for Modeling Confidence in Recommendations with Learned Beta Distributions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-method-for-modeling-confidence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most Recommender Systems (RecSys) do not provide an indication of confidence in their decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-method-for-modeling-confidence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCTformer+: Multi-Class Token Transformer for Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mctformer-multi-class-token-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon the observation that the attended regions of the one-class token in the standard vision transformer can contribute to a class-agnostic localization map, we explore the potential of the transformer model to capture class-specific attention for class-discriminative object localization by learning multiple class tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mctformer-multi-class-token-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine learning methods for the search for L&amp;T brown dwarfs in the data of modern sky surveys</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-methods-for-the-search-for-l</link>
      <description><![CDATA[According to various estimates, brown dwarfs (BD) should account for up to 25 percent of all objects in the Galaxy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-methods-for-the-search-for-l</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleEDL: Style-Guided High-order Attention Network for Image Emotion Distribution Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styleedl-style-guided-high-order-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Emotion distribution learning has gained increasing attention with the tendency to express emotions through images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styleedl-style-guided-high-order-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Sides of Miscalibration: Identifying Over and Under-Confidence Prediction for Network Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-sides-of-miscalibration-identifying-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then we utilize the class-wise miscalibration score as a proxy to design a calibration technique that can tackle both over and under-confidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-sides-of-miscalibration-identifying-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Detection and Localization of Pancreatic Cancer by Label-Free Tumor Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-detection-and-localization-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further investigate the per-voxel segmentation performance of pancreatic tumors if AI is trained on a combination of CT scans with synthetic tumors and CT scans with annotated large tumors at an advanced stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-detection-and-localization-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Few-shot 3D Point Cloud Segmentation via Query-Guided Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-few-shot-3d-point-cloud-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although extensive research has been conducted on 3D point cloud segmentation, effectively adapting generic models to novel categories remains a formidable challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-few-shot-3d-point-cloud-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spanish Pre-trained BERT Model and Evaluation Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spanish-pre-trained-bert-model-and-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Spanish language is one of the top 5 spoken languages in the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spanish-pre-trained-bert-model-and-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARCH: Large Language Model-based Automatic Readme Creation with Heuristics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/larch-large-language-model-based-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Writing a readme is a crucial aspect of software development as it plays a vital role in managing and reusing program code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/larch-large-language-model-based-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Guided Feature Distillation for Multimodal Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-guided-feature-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The teacher model first extracts rich modality features from the generic modality feature by considering both the semantic information of items and the complementary information of multiple modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-guided-feature-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recurrent Spike-based Image Restoration under General Illumination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrent-spike-based-image-restoration-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spike camera is a new type of bio-inspired vision sensor that records light intensity in the form of a spike array with high temporal resolution (20, 000 Hz).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrent-spike-based-image-restoration-under</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
