<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 21:07:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Style Your Hair: Latent Optimization for Pose-Invariant Hairstyle Transfer via Local-Style-Aware Hair Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/style-your-hair-latent-optimization-for-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Editing hairstyle is unique and challenging due to the complexity and delicacy of hairstyle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/style-your-hair-latent-optimization-for-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating Appearance Models for Image Segmentation via Tensor Factorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-appearance-models-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image Segmentation is one of the core tasks in Computer Vision and solving it often depends on modeling the image appearance data via the color distributions of each it its constituent regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-appearance-models-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object Discovery via Contrastive Learning for Weakly Supervised Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-discovery-via-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly Supervised Object Detection (WSOD) is a task that detects objects in an image using a model trained only on image-level annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-discovery-via-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HVS-Inspired Signal Degradation Network for Just Noticeable Difference Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hvs-inspired-signal-degradation-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, they have a major drawback that the generated JND is assessed in the real-world signal domain instead of in the perceptual domain in the human brain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hvs-inspired-signal-degradation-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Supervision-based Information Bottleneck for Out-of-Distribution Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-supervision-based-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Along this line, a recent study (Arjovsky et al., 2019) has made a first step and proposes a learning principle of information bottleneck based invariant risk minimization (IB-IRM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-supervision-based-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-guided Source-free Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-guided-source-free-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Source-free domain adaptation (SFDA) aims to adapt a classifier to an unlabelled target data set by only using a pre-trained source model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-guided-source-free-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-Aware Streaming Perception in Dynamic Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-streaming-perception-in-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These works evaluate accuracy offline, one image at a time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-streaming-perception-in-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-Injected Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-injected-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is an emerging technique for training models from decentralized data sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-injected-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novel algorithm to generate shortest edit script using Levenshtein distance algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-algorithm-to-generate-shortest-edit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[String similarity, longest common subsequence and shortest edit scripts are the triplets of problem that related to each other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-algorithm-to-generate-shortest-edit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-dimensional topological loss for cortical plate segmentation in fetal brain MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dimensional-topological-loss-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, CP growth and folding patterns are key indicator in the assessment of the brain development and maturation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dimensional-topological-loss-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask and Reason: Pre-Training Knowledge Graph Transformers for Complex Logical Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-and-reason-pre-training-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present the Knowledge Graph Transformer (kgTransformer) with masked pre-training and fine-tuning strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-and-reason-pre-training-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-guided Semantic Style Transfer of 3D Indoor Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-guided-semantic-style-transfer-of-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the new problem of language-guided semantic style transfer of 3D indoor scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-guided-semantic-style-transfer-of-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning-Based Test Smell Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-based-test-smell-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Objective: We propose the design and experimentation of a novel test smell detection approach based on machine learning to detect four test smells.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-based-test-smell-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A unifying partially-interpretable framework for neural network-based extreme quantile regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unifying-partially-interpretable-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new methodological framework for performing extreme quantile regression using artificial neutral networks, which are able to capture complex non-linear relationships and scale well to high-dimensional data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unifying-partially-interpretable-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleFaceV: Face Video Generation via Decomposing and Recomposing Pretrained StyleGAN3</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylefacev-face-video-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, StyleFaceV is capable of generating realistic $1024\times1024$ face videos even without high-resolution training videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylefacev-face-video-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON: Decentralized Fault Tolerance in Edge Federations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dragon-decentralized-fault-tolerance-in-edge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Edge Federation is a new computing paradigm that seamlessly interconnects the resources of multiple edge service providers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dragon-decentralized-fault-tolerance-in-edge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Latent Variable Models with Auto-encoding Variational Bayes: A Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-latent-variable-models-with-auto</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Auto-encoding Variational Bayes (AEVB) is a powerful and general algorithm for fitting latent variable models (a promising direction for unsupervised learning), and is well-known for training the Variational Auto-Encoder (VAE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-latent-variable-models-with-auto</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CorpusBrain: Pre-train a Generative Retrieval Model for Knowledge-Intensive Language Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/corpusbrain-pre-train-a-generative-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that a strong generative retrieval model can be learned with a set of adequately designed pre-training tasks, and be adopted to improve a variety of downstream KILT tasks with further fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/corpusbrain-pre-train-a-generative-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised domain adaptation semantic segmentation of high-resolution remote sensing imagery with invariant domain-level context memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study proposes a novel unsupervised domain adaptation semantic segmentation network (MemoryAdaptNet) for the semantic segmentation of HRS imagery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConTextual Mask Auto-Encoder for Dense Passage Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-mask-auto-encoder-for-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dense passage retrieval aims to retrieve the relevant passages of a query from a large corpus based on dense representations (i. e., vectors) of the query and the passages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-mask-auto-encoder-for-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man-in-the-Middle Attack against Object Detection Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/man-in-the-middle-attack-against-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Is deep learning secure for robots?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/man-in-the-middle-attack-against-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InvisibiliTee: Angle-agnostic Cloaking from Person-Tracking Systems with a Tee</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invisibilitee-angle-agnostic-cloaking-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After a survey for person-tracking system-induced privacy concerns, we propose a black-box adversarial attack method on state-of-the-art human detection models called InvisibiliTee.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invisibilitee-angle-agnostic-cloaking-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Vision Transformers for Malware Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-vision-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Malware detection plays a crucial role in cyber-security with the increase in malware growth and advancements in cyber-attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-vision-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-efficiency trade-off of Unsupervised Keyword Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-efficiency-trade-off-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficiently identifying keyphrases that represent a given document is a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-efficiency-trade-off-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SYN-MAD 2022: Competition on Face Morphing Attack Detection Based on Privacy-aware Synthetic Training Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syn-mad-2022-competition-on-face-morphing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The competition attracted a total of 12 participating teams, both from academia and industry and present in 11 different countries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syn-mad-2022-competition-on-face-morphing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Interpretable Sleep Stage Classification Using Cross-Modal Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-interpretable-sleep-stage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we propose Cross-Modal Transformers, which is a transformer-based method for sleep stage classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-interpretable-sleep-stage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computational Empathy Counteracts the Negative Effects of Anger on Creative Problem Solving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-empathy-counteracts-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an online experiment with 1, 006 participants randomly assigned to an emotion elicitation intervention (with a control elicitation condition and anger elicitation condition) and a computational empathy intervention (with a control virtual agent and an empathic virtual agent), we examine how anger and empathy influence participants' performance in solving a word game based on Wordle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-empathy-counteracts-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Deep Learning-based 3-lead ECG Classification with Heartbeat Counting and Demographic Data Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-deep-learning-based-3-lead-ecg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nowadays, an increasing number of people are being diagnosed with cardiovascular diseases (CVDs), the leading cause of death globally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-deep-learning-based-3-lead-ecg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WiFi Based Distance Estimation Using Supervised Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wifi-based-distance-estimation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, measuring the spatial distance between given set of WiFi fingerprints is heavily affected by the selection of the signal distance function used to model signal space as geospatial distance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wifi-based-distance-estimation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hypergraphs with Edge-Dependent Vertex Weights: p-Laplacians and Spectral Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypergraphs-with-edge-dependent-vertex</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study p-Laplacians and spectral clustering for a recently proposed hypergraph model that incorporates edge-dependent vertex weights (EDVWs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypergraphs-with-edge-dependent-vertex</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELEVANT: A Fully Automatic Fine-Grained Entity Linking Evaluation and Analysis Tool</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elevant-a-fully-automatic-fine-grained-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Elevant, a tool for the fully automatic fine-grained evaluation of a set of entity linkers on a set of benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elevant-a-fully-automatic-fine-grained-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reward Design For An Online Reinforcement Learning Algorithm Supporting Oral Self-Care</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reward-design-for-an-online-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dental disease is one of the most common chronic diseases despite being largely preventable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reward-design-for-an-online-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of impact of emotions on target speech extraction and speech separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-impact-of-emotions-on-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the factors causing such degradation may be intrinsic speaker variability, such as emotions, occurring commonly in realistic speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-impact-of-emotions-on-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Z-BERT-A: a zero-shot Pipeline for Unknown Intent detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/z-bert-a-a-zero-shot-pipeline-for-unknown</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main challenge resides in the need to identify from input utterances novel unseen in-tents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/z-bert-a-a-zero-shot-pipeline-for-unknown</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Task Software Caching-assisted Computation Offloading for Multi-Access Edge Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-task-software-caching-assisted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, this work considers dynamic task software caching at the MEC server to assist users' task execution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-task-software-caching-assisted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining Predictions under Uncertainty: The Case of Random Decision Trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-predictions-under-uncertainty-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A common approach to aggregate classification estimates in an ensemble of decision trees is to either use voting or to average the probabilities for each class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-predictions-under-uncertainty-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLAND: Graph Learning Framework for Dynamic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roland-graph-learning-framework-for-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we propose a scalable and efficient training approach for dynamic GNNs via incremental training and meta-learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roland-graph-learning-framework-for-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DM-NeRF: 3D Scene Geometry Decomposition and Manipulation from 2D Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dm-nerf-3d-scene-geometry-decomposition-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the problem of 3D scene geometry decomposition and manipulation from 2D views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dm-nerf-3d-scene-geometry-decomposition-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Pole Segmentation on Range Images for Long-term LiDAR Localization in Urban Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-pole-segmentation-on-range-images-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further use the extracted poles as pseudo labels to train a deep neural network for online range image-based pole segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-pole-segmentation-on-range-images-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynKB: Semantic Search for Synthetic Procedures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synkb-semantic-search-for-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present SynKB, an open-source, automatically extracted knowledge base of chemical synthesis protocols.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synkb-semantic-search-for-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Video Domain Adaptation: A Disentanglement Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-video-domain-adaptation-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we consider the generation of cross-domain videos from two sets of latent factors, one encoding the static domain-related information and another encoding the temporal and semantic-related information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-video-domain-adaptation-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining Gradients and Probabilities for Heterogeneous Approximation of Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-gradients-and-probabilities-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further demonstrate that our error model can predict the parameters of an approximate multiplier in the context of the commonly used additive Gaussian noise (AGN) model with high accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-gradients-and-probabilities-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HoW-3D: Holistic 3D Wireframe Perception from a Single Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-3d-holistic-3d-wireframe-perception-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the problem of holistic 3D wireframe perception (HoW-3D), a new task of perceiving both the visible 3D wireframes and the invisible ones from single-view 2D images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-3d-holistic-3d-wireframe-perception-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Does Data Freshness Affect Real-time Supervised Learning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-does-data-freshness-affect-real-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To minimize the inference error in real-time, we propose a new "selection-from-buffer" model for sending the features, which is more general than the "generate-at-will" model used in earlier studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-does-data-freshness-affect-real-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applying Regularized Schrödinger-Bridge-Based Stochastic Process in Generative Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applying-regularized-schrodinger-bridge-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, this study tried to reduce the number of timesteps and training time required and proposed regularization terms to the existing SB models to make the bidirectional stochastic processes consistent and stable with a reduced number of timesteps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applying-regularized-schrodinger-bridge-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Causal View of Domain Invariant Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-causal-view-of-domain-invariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning methods can be unreliable when deployed in domains that differ from the domains on which they were trained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-causal-view-of-domain-invariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pyramidal Predictive Network: A Model for Visual-frame Prediction Based on Predictive Coding Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyramidal-predictive-network-a-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main innovation of our model is that the update frequency of neural units on each of the layer decreases with the increasing of network levels, which results in the model appears like a pyramid from the perspective of time dimension, so we call it the Pyramid Predictive Network (PPNet).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyramidal-predictive-network-a-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Task-Oriented Dialogue Systems with Response Selection as an Auxiliary Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-task-oriented-dialogue-systems-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The adoption of pre-trained language models in task-oriented dialogue systems has resulted in significant enhancements of their text generation abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-task-oriented-dialogue-systems-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM.int8(): 8-bit Matrix Multiplication for Transformers at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-int8-8-bit-matrix-multiplication-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a procedure for Int8 matrix multiplication for feed-forward and attention projection layers in transformers, which cut the memory needed for inference by half while retaining full precision performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-int8-8-bit-matrix-multiplication-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Attention Network for Few-Shot Object Detection via Meta-Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-attention-network-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a hierarchical attention network with sequentially large receptive fields to fully exploit the query and support images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-attention-network-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
