<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 09:20:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dual‑detector Re‑optimization for Federated Weakly Supervised Video Anomaly Detection Via Adaptive Dynamic Recursive Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-detector-re-optimization-for-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated weakly supervised video anomaly detection represents a significant advancement in privacy-preserving collaborative learning, enabling distributed clients to train anomaly detectors using only video-level annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-detector-re-optimization-for-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring Decomposition Attacks in LLMs with Lightweight Sequential Monitors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monitoring-decomposition-attacks-in-llms-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that a carefully prompt engineered lightweight monitor achieves a 93% defense success rate, beating reasoning models like o3 mini as a monitor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monitoring-decomposition-attacks-in-llms-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constructing and Evaluating Declarative RAG Pipelines in PyTerrier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-and-evaluating-declarative-rag</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Search engines often follow a pipeline architecture, where complex but effective reranking components are used to refine the results of an initial retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-and-evaluating-declarative-rag</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Protoform Reconstruction through Parsimonious Rule-guided Heuristics and Evolutionary Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-protoform-reconstruction-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an unsupervised method for the reconstruction of protoforms i. e., ancestral word forms from which modern language forms are derived.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-protoform-reconstruction-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precise Zero-Shot Pointwise Ranking with LLMs through Post-Aggregated Global Context Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precise-zero-shot-pointwise-ranking-with-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to improve the effectiveness of pointwise methods while preserving their efficiency through two key innovations: (1) We propose a novel Global-Consistent Comparative Pointwise Ranking (GCCP) strategy that incorporates global reference comparisons between each candidate and an anchor document to generate contrastive relevance scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precise-zero-shot-pointwise-ranking-with-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWE-Factory: Your Automated Factory for Issue Resolution Training Data and Evaluation Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swe-factory-your-automated-factory-for-issue</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Constructing large-scale datasets for the GitHub issue resolution task is crucial for both training and evaluating the software engineering capabilities of Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swe-factory-your-automated-factory-for-issue</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Multimodal Emotion Recognition under Missing Modalities and Distribution Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-multimodal-emotion-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose a novel robust MER framework, Causal Inference Distiller (CIDer), and introduce a new task, Random Modality Feature Missing (RMFM), to generalize the definition of modality missing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-multimodal-emotion-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ming-Omni: A Unified Multimodal Model for Perception and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ming-omni-a-unified-multimodal-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Ming-Omni, a unified multimodal model capable of processing images, text, audio, and video, while demonstrating strong proficiency in both speech and image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ming-omni-a-unified-multimodal-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Gap Between Open-Source and Proprietary LLMs in Table QA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-open-source-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a system developed for SemEval 2025 Task 8: Question Answering (QA) over tabular data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-open-source-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Large Language Models are Reliable for Judging Empathic Communication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-large-language-models-are-reliable-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) excel at generating empathic responses in text-based conversations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-large-language-models-are-reliable-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoRT: Code-integrated Reasoning within Thinking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cort-code-integrated-reasoning-within</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Reasoning Models (LRMs) like o1 and DeepSeek-R1 have shown remarkable progress in natural language reasoning with long chain-of-thought (CoT), yet they remain inefficient or inaccurate when handling complex mathematical operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cort-code-integrated-reasoning-within</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Call for Collaborative Intelligence: Why Human-Agent Systems Should Precede AI Autonomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-call-for-collaborative-intelligence-why</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper argues that progress in AI should not be measured by how independent systems become, but by how well they can work with humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-call-for-collaborative-intelligence-why</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise Conditional Variational Score Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-conditional-variational-score</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Noise Conditional Variational Score Distillation (NCVSD), a novel method for distilling pretrained diffusion models into generative denoisers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-conditional-variational-score</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urban1960SatSeg: Unsupervised Semantic Segmentation of Mid-20$^{th}$ century Urban Landscapes with Satellite Imageries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/urban1960satseg-unsupervised-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, $\textbf{Urban1960SatBench}$ serves as a novel, expertly annotated semantic segmentation dataset built on mid-20$^{th}$ century Keyhole imagery, covering 1, 240 km$^2$ and key urban classes (buildings, roads, farmland, water).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/urban1960satseg-unsupervised-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exposure-slot: Exposure-centric representations learning with Slot-in-Slot Attention for Region-aware Exposure Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposure-slot-exposure-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image exposure correction enhances images captured under diverse real-world conditions by addressing issues of under- and over-exposure, which can result in the loss of critical details and hinder content recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposure-slot-exposure-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Driven Modeling of IRCU Patient Flow in the COVID-19 Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-modeling-of-ircu-patient-flow-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study evaluated clinical outcomes and operational dynamics of a new Spanish IRCU with specialized staffing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-modeling-of-ircu-patient-flow-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisit What You See: Disclose Language Prior in Vision Tokens for Efficient Guided Decoding of LVLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisit-what-you-see-disclose-language-prior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach leverages the semantic information embedded within vision tokens by projecting them into the text token distribution space, and dynamically selecting the most relevant vision token at each decoding step through constrained divergence minimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisit-what-you-see-disclose-language-prior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Depth and Language for Open-Vocabulary Domain-Generalized Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-depth-and-language-for-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-Vocabulary semantic segmentation (OVSS) and domain generalization in semantic segmentation (DGSS) highlight a subtle complementarity that motivates Open-Vocabulary Domain-Generalized Semantic Segmentation (OV-DGSS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-depth-and-language-for-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SRPL-SFDA: SAM-Guided Reliable Pseudo-Labels for Source-Free Domain Adaptation in Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srpl-sfda-sam-guided-reliable-pseudo-labels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain Adaptation (DA) is crucial for robust deployment of medical image segmentation models when applied to new clinical centers with significant domain shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srpl-sfda-sam-guided-reliable-pseudo-labels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sampling Theory for Super-Resolution with Implicit Neural Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampling-theory-for-super-resolution-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implicit neural representations (INRs) have emerged as a powerful tool for solving inverse problems in computer vision and computational imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampling-theory-for-super-resolution-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Meaning Stays the Same, but Models Drift: Evaluating Quality of Service under Token-Level Behavioral Instability in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-meaning-stays-the-same-but-models-drift</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate how large language models respond to prompts that differ only in their token-level realization but preserve the same semantic intent, a phenomenon we call prompt variance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-meaning-stays-the-same-but-models-drift</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V-JEPA 2: Self-Supervised Video Models Enable Understanding, Prediction and Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v-jepa-2-self-supervised-video-models-enable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we show how self-supervised learning can be applied to robotic planning tasks by post-training a latent action-conditioned world model, V-JEPA 2-AC, using less than 62 hours of unlabeled robot videos from the Droid dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v-jepa-2-self-supervised-video-models-enable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Communication Quality of Interest Rate Announcements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-communication-quality-of-interest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use text-mining techniques to measure the accessibility and quality of information within the texts of interest rate announcements published by the Bank of Israel over the past decade.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-communication-quality-of-interest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Part-level 3D Object Generation via Dual Volume Packing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-part-level-3d-object-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in 3D object generation has greatly improved both the quality and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-part-level-3d-object-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Graph Compression for Quantum Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guided-graph-compression-for-quantum-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The compression is guided to enhance the performance of a downstream classification task, which can be applied either with a quantum or a classical classifier.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guided-graph-compression-for-quantum-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMail-Inject: A Dataset from a Realistic Adaptive Prompt Injection Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmail-inject-a-dataset-from-a-realistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Indirect Prompt Injection attacks exploit the inherent limitation of Large Language Models (LLMs) to distinguish between instructions and data in their inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmail-inject-a-dataset-from-a-realistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding simple structure at inference improves Vision-Language Compositionality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adding-simple-structure-at-inference-improves</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dual encoder Vision-Language Models (VLM) such as CLIP are widely used for image-text retrieval tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adding-simple-structure-at-inference-improves</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apollo: A Posteriori Label-Only Membership Inference Attack Towards Machine Unlearning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apollo-a-posteriori-label-only-membership</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine Unlearning (MU) aims to update Machine Learning (ML) models following requests to remove training samples and their influences on a trained model efficiently without retraining the original ML model from scratch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apollo-a-posteriori-label-only-membership</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Four Color Theorem for Cell Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-four-color-theorem-for-cell-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel cell instance segmentation method inspired by the four-color theorem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-four-color-theorem-for-cell-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evasion Attacks Against Bayesian Predictive Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evasion-attacks-against-bayesian-predictive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is an increasing interest in analyzing the behavior of machine learning systems against adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evasion-attacks-against-bayesian-predictive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VerIF: Verification Engineering for Reinforcement Learning in Instruction Following</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verif-verification-engineering-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore the verification challenge in RL for instruction following and propose VerIF, a verification method that combines rule-based code verification with LLM-based verification from a large reasoning model (e. g., QwQ-32B).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verif-verification-engineering-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AtmosMJ: Revisiting Gating Mechanism for AI Weather Forecasting Beyond the Year Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atmosmj-revisiting-gating-mechanism-for-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This has led to the prevailing assumption that such representations are necessary to enforce physical consistency and long-term stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atmosmj-revisiting-gating-mechanism-for-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query-Focused Retrieval Heads Improve Long-Context Reasoning and Re-ranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-focused-retrieval-heads-improve-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce QRHEAD (Query-Focused Retrieval Head), an improved set of attention heads that enhance retrieval from long context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-focused-retrieval-heads-improve-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Diffusion Models: From Generative Pre-training to One-Step Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-diffusion-models-from-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion distillation is a widely used technique to reduce the sampling cost of diffusion models, yet it often requires extensive training, and the student performance tends to be degraded.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-diffusion-models-from-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-step Instructions and a Simple Tabular Output Format Improve the Dependency Parsing Accuracy of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/step-by-step-instructions-and-a-simple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in large language models (LLMs) have enabled impressive performance in various tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/step-by-step-instructions-and-a-simple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PersonaLens: A Benchmark for Personalization Evaluation in Conversational AI Assistants</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalens-a-benchmark-for-personalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have advanced conversational AI assistants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalens-a-benchmark-for-personalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OmniDRCA: Parallel Speech-Text Foundation Model via Dual-Resolution Speech Representations and Contrastive Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnidrca-parallel-speech-text-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents OmniDRCA, a parallel speech-text foundation model based on joint autoregressive modeling, featuring dual-resolution speech representations and contrastive cross-modal alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnidrca-parallel-speech-text-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the Cost of Differential Privacy for Deep Learning-Based Trajectory Generation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-is-the-cost-of-differential-privacy-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In conclusion, DP trajectory generation remains a challenging task, and formal guarantees are currently only feasible with large datasets and in constrained use cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-is-the-cost-of-differential-privacy-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inverting Black-Box Face Recognition Systems via Zero-Order Optimization in Eigenface Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverting-black-box-face-recognition-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstructing facial images from black-box recognition models poses a significant privacy threat.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverting-black-box-face-recognition-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EquiCaps: Predictor-Free Pose-Aware Pre-Trained Capsule Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equicaps-predictor-free-pose-aware-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning self-supervised representations that are invariant and equivariant to transformations is crucial for advancing beyond traditional visual classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equicaps-predictor-free-pose-aware-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScaleLSD: Scalable Deep Line Segment Detection Streamlined</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalelsd-scalable-deep-line-segment-detection-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the problem of Line Segment Detection (LSD) for the characterization of line geometry in images, with the aim of learning a domain-agnostic robust LSD model that works well for any natural images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalelsd-scalable-deep-line-segment-detection-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inv-Entropy: A Fully Probabilistic Framework for Uncertainty Quantification in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inv-entropy-a-fully-probabilistic-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on this, we propose a fully probabilistic framework based on an inverse model, which quantifies uncertainty by evaluating the diversity of the input space conditioned on a given output through systematic perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inv-entropy-a-fully-probabilistic-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Practical Alzheimer's Disease Diagnosis: A Lightweight and Interpretable Spiking Neural Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-practical-alzheimer-s-disease</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Early diagnosis of Alzheimer's Disease (AD), especially at the mild cognitive impairment (MCI) stage, is vital yet hindered by subjective assessments and the high cost of multimodal imaging modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-practical-alzheimer-s-disease</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Similarities of Embeddings in Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-similarities-of-embeddings-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive learning (CL) operates on a simple yet effective principle: embeddings of positive pairs are pulled together, while those of negative pairs are pushed apart.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-similarities-of-embeddings-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gender Bias in English-to-Greek Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gender-bias-in-english-to-greek-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the demand for inclusive language increases, concern has grown over the susceptibility of machine translation (MT) systems to reinforce gender stereotypes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gender-bias-in-english-to-greek-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECAM: A Contrastive Learning Approach to Avoid Environmental Collision in Trajectory Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecam-a-contrastive-learning-approach-to-avoid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces ECAM (Environmental Collision Avoidance Module), a contrastive learning-based module to enhance collision avoidance ability with the environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecam-a-contrastive-learning-approach-to-avoid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CausalVQA: A Physically Grounded Causal Reasoning Benchmark for Video Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalvqa-a-physically-grounded-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce CausalVQA, a benchmark dataset for video question answering (VQA) composed of question-answer pairs that probe models' understanding of causality in the physical world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalvqa-a-physically-grounded-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D-Aware Vision-Language Models Fine-Tuning with Geometric Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-aware-vision-language-models-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-Language Models (VLMs) have shown remarkable performance on diverse visual and linguistic tasks, yet they remain fundamentally limited in their understanding of 3D spatial structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-aware-vision-language-models-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CINeMA: Conditional Implicit Neural Multi-Modal Atlas for a Spatio-Temporal Representation of the Perinatal Brain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cinema-conditional-implicit-neural-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Magnetic resonance imaging of fetal and neonatal brains reveals rapid neurodevelopment marked by substantial anatomical changes unfolding within days.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cinema-conditional-implicit-neural-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outside Knowledge Conversational Video (OKCV) Dataset -- Dialoguing over Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outside-knowledge-conversational-video-okcv</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To explore this task, we introduce a dataset comprised of $2, 017$ videos with $5, 986$ human-annotated dialogues consisting of $40, 954$ interleaved dialogue turns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outside-knowledge-conversational-video-okcv</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
