<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 21:06:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>BiFormer: Learning Bilateral Motion Estimation via Bilateral Transformer for 4K Video Frame Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biformer-learning-bilateral-motion-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, in global motion estimation, we predict symmetric bilateral motion fields at a coarse scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biformer-learning-bilateral-motion-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Quantigraphic Image Enhancement via Comparametric Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-quantigraphic-image-enhancement-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most recent methods of deep image enhancement can be generally classified into two types: decompose-and-enhance and illumination estimation-centric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-quantigraphic-image-enhancement-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Anomaly Detection with Domain Shift: A Real-world Dataset and Masked Multi-scale Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/industrial-anomaly-detection-with-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, to bridge this gap, we propose the Aero-engine Blade Anomaly Detection (AeBAD) dataset, consisting of two sub-datasets: the single-blade dataset and the video anomaly detection dataset of blades.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/industrial-anomaly-detection-with-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TM2D: Bimodality Driven 3D Dance Generation via Music-Text Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tm2d-bimodality-driven-3d-dance-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel task for generating 3D dance movements that simultaneously incorporate both text and music modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tm2d-bimodality-driven-3d-dance-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Impact of Voice Anonymization on Speech-Based COVID-19 Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-impact-of-voice-anonymization-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With advances seen in deep learning, voice-based applications are burgeoning, ranging from personal assistants, affective computing, to remote disease diagnostics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-impact-of-voice-anonymization-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A dynamic Bayesian optimized active recommender system for curiosity-driven Human-in-the-loop automated experiments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamic-bayesian-optimized-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimization of experimental materials synthesis and characterization through active learning methods has been growing over the last decade, with examples ranging from measurements of diffraction on combinatorial alloys at synchrotrons, to searches through chemical space with automated synthesis robots for perovskites.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamic-bayesian-optimized-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Validation in Structure from Motion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-validation-in-structure-from-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, semantic labels on input images are used for the removal of objects associated with motion in the output SfM models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-validation-in-structure-from-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selecting Features by their Resilience to the Curse of Dimensionality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-features-by-their-resilience-to-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-world datasets are often of high dimension and effected by the curse of dimensionality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-features-by-their-resilience-to-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to choose your best allies for a transferable attack?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-choose-your-best-allies-for-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The transferability of adversarial examples is a key issue in the security of deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-choose-your-best-allies-for-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HNeRV: A Hybrid Neural Representation for Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hnerv-a-hybrid-neural-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such embedding largely limits the regression capacity and internal generalization for video interpolation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hnerv-a-hybrid-neural-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoocRadar: A Fine-grained and Multi-aspect Knowledge Repository for Improving Cognitive Student Modeling in MOOCs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moocradar-a-fine-grained-and-multi-aspect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Student modeling, the task of inferring a student's learning characteristics through their interactions with coursework, is a fundamental issue in intelligent education.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moocradar-a-fine-grained-and-multi-aspect</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MS3D: Leveraging Multiple Detectors for Unsupervised Domain Adaptation in 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ms3d-leveraging-multiple-detectors-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed Kernel-Density Estimation (KDE) Box Fusion method fuses box proposals from multiple domains to obtain pseudo-labels that surpass the performance of the best source domain detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ms3d-leveraging-multiple-detectors-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segment Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Segment Anything (SA) project: a new task, model, and dataset for image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-annotator Deep Learning: A Probabilistic Framework for Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-annotator-deep-learning-a-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training standard deep neural networks leads to subpar performances in such multi-annotator supervised learning settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-annotator-deep-learning-a-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ParroT: Translating During Chat Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parrot-translating-during-chat-using-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose the $\mathbf{ParroT}$ framework to enhance and regulate the translation abilities during chat based on open-sourced LLMs (i. e., LLaMA-7b) and human written translation and evaluation data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parrot-translating-during-chat-using-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Distillation for Gaussian Process Regression and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-distillation-for-gaussian-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose two approaches to extend the notion of knowledge distillation to Gaussian Process Regression (GPR) and Gaussian Process Classification (GPC); data-centric and distribution-centric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-distillation-for-gaussian-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying the Roles of Visual, Linguistic, and Visual-Linguistic Complexity in Verb Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-the-roles-of-visual-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on these results, we conclude that verb acquisition is influenced by all three sources of complexity, but that the variability of visual structure poses the most significant challenge for verb learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-the-roles-of-visual-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EigenFold: Generative Protein Structure Prediction with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigenfold-generative-protein-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Protein structure prediction has reached revolutionary levels of accuracy on single structures, yet distributional modeling paradigms are needed to capture the conformational ensembles and flexibility that underlie biological function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigenfold-generative-protein-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiGA: Distil to Generalize and then Adapt for Domain Adaptive Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diga-distil-to-generalize-and-then-adapt-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain adaptive semantic segmentation methods commonly utilize stage-wise training, consisting of a warm-up and a self-training stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diga-distil-to-generalize-and-then-adapt-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Deduplication and Leakage Detection in Large Scale Image Datasets with a focus on the CrowdAI Mapping Challenge Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-deduplication-and-leakage-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The CrowdAI Mapping Challenge Dataset is one of these datasets that has been used extensively in recent years to train deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-deduplication-and-leakage-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Compare Longitudinal Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-compare-longitudinal-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, normalizing for nuisance variation might be hard in settings where there are a lot of idiosyncratic changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-compare-longitudinal-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCB-dataset: A Dataset for Detecting Student Classroom Behavior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scb-dataset-a-dataset-for-detecting-student</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The use of deep learning methods for automatic detection of students' classroom behavior is a promising approach to analyze their class performance and enhance teaching effectiveness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scb-dataset-a-dataset-for-detecting-student</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMPConv: Self-moving Point Representations for Continuous Convolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smpconv-self-moving-point-representations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper suggests an alternative approach to building a continuous convolution without neural networks, resulting in more computationally efficient and improved performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smpconv-self-moving-point-representations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of ChatGPT Family of Models for Biomedical Reasoning and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-chatgpt-family-of-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first task is classifying whether statements of clinical and policy recommendations in scientific literature constitute health advice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-chatgpt-family-of-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting and Grounding Multi-Modal Media Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-and-grounding-multi-modal-media</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we highlight a new research problem for multi-modal fake media, namely Detecting and Grounding Multi-Modal Media Manipulation (DGM^4).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-and-grounding-multi-modal-media</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AToMiC: An Image/Text Retrieval Test Collection to Support Multimedia Content Creation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomic-an-image-text-retrieval-test</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the AToMiC (Authoring Tools for Multimedia Content) dataset, designed to advance research in image/text cross-modal retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomic-an-image-text-retrieval-test</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Vision-Language Models for Imbalanced Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-vision-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, their performance on imbalanced dataset is relatively poor, where the distribution of classes in the training dataset is skewed, leading to poor performance in predicting minority classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-vision-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-BSN: Self-Supervised Image Denoising for Real-World with Multi-Mask based on Blind-Spot Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-bsn-self-supervised-image-denoising-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our MM-BSN can be used to address the problem of large-noise denoising, which cannot be efficiently handled by other BSN methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-bsn-self-supervised-image-denoising-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learned Tree Search for Long-Horizon Social Robot Navigation in Shared Airspace</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learned-tree-search-for-long-horizon-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose Social Robot Tree Search (SoRTS), an algorithm for the safe navigation of mobile robots in social domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learned-tree-search-for-long-horizon-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully Convolutional Networks for Dense Water Flow Intensity Prediction in Swedish Catchment Areas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-convolutional-networks-for-dense-water</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, we are the first to tackle the task of dense water flow intensity prediction; earlier works have considered predicting flow intensities at a sparse set of locations at a time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-convolutional-networks-for-dense-water</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time-space-frequency feature Fusion for 3-channel motor imagery classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-space-frequency-feature-fusion-for-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TSFF-Net comprises four main components: time-frequency representation, time-frequency feature extraction, time-space feature extraction, and feature fusion and classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-space-frequency-feature-fusion-for-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handling Concept Drift in Global Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handling-concept-drift-in-global-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Handling concept drift in forecasting is essential for many ML methods in use nowadays, however, the prior work only proposes methods to handle concept drift in the classification domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handling-concept-drift-in-global-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Outlier Rejection for 3D Registration with Variational Bayes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-outlier-rejection-for-3d-registration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Embedded with the inlier/outlier label, the posterior feature distribution is label-dependent and discriminative.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-outlier-rejection-for-3d-registration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Form-NLU: Dataset for the Form Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/form-nlu-dataset-for-the-form-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to general document analysis tasks, form document structure understanding and retrieval are challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/form-nlu-dataset-for-the-form-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneShotSTL: One-Shot Seasonal-Trend Decomposition For Online Time Series Anomaly Detection And Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oneshotstl-one-shot-seasonal-trend</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on real-world benchmark datasets for downstream time series anomaly detection and forecasting tasks demonstrate that OneShotSTL is from 10 to over 1, 000 times faster than the state-of-the-art methods, while still providing comparable or even better accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oneshotstl-one-shot-seasonal-trend</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SportsPose -- A Dynamic 3D sports pose dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sportspose-a-dynamic-3d-sports-pose-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate 3D human pose estimation is essential for sports analytics, coaching, and injury prevention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sportspose-a-dynamic-3d-sports-pose-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Blind Denoising Using Dual Convolutional Neural Network with Skip Connection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-blind-denoising-using-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed DCBDNet consists of a noise estimation network and a dual convolutional neural network (CNN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-blind-denoising-using-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>naplib-python: Neural Acoustic Data Processing and Analysis Tools in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naplib-python-neural-acoustic-data-processing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, the computational neuroscience community has pushed for more transparent and reproducible methods across the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naplib-python-neural-acoustic-data-processing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Domain Image Captioning with Discriminative Finetuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-image-captioning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, when the model is used without further tuning to generate captions for out-of-domain datasets, our discriminatively-finetuned captioner generates descriptions that resemble human references more than those produced by the same captioner without finetuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-image-captioning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Recover Spectral Reflectance from RGB Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-recover-spectral-reflectance-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of relying on naive end-to-end training, we also propose a novel architecture that integrates the physical relationship between the spectral reflectance and the corresponding RGB images into the network based on our mathematical analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-recover-spectral-reflectance-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EDeR: A Dataset for Exploring Dependency Relations Between Events</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eder-a-dataset-for-exploring-dependency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that an important type of relation not explored in NLP or IR research to date is that of an event being an argument - required or optional - of another event.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eder-a-dataset-for-exploring-dependency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resources and Few-shot Learners for In-context Learning in Slavic Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resources-and-few-shot-learners-for-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the rapid recent progress in creating accurate and compact in-context learners, most recent work focuses on in-context learning (ICL) for tasks in English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resources-and-few-shot-learners-for-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Networks for Porous Crystalline Materials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-networks-for-porous-crystalline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we develop a model which incorporates the symmetries of the unit cell of a crystal in its architecture and explicitly models the porous structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-networks-for-porous-crystalline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Improvement of Factual Knowledge in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-improvement-of-factual-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose an approach for influencing MLM pretraining in a way that can improve language model performance on a variety of knowledge-intensive tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-improvement-of-factual-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Avatar Stream: a cost-down approach to the Metaverse experience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virtual-avatar-stream-a-cost-down-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Metaverse through VR headsets is a rapidly growing concept, but the high cost of entry currently limits access for many users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virtual-avatar-stream-a-cost-down-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De-novo Identification of Small Molecules from Their GC-EI-MS Spectra</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/de-novo-identification-of-small-molecules</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identification of experimentally acquired mass spectra of unknown compounds presents a~particular challenge because reliable spectral databases do not cover the potential chemical space with sufficient density.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/de-novo-identification-of-small-molecules</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The expressive power of pooling in Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-expressive-power-of-pooling-in-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Graph Neural Networks (GNNs), hierarchical pooling operators generate a coarser representation of the input data by creating local summaries of the graph structure and its vertex features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-expressive-power-of-pooling-in-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FakET: Simulating Cryo-Electron Tomograms with Neural Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faket-simulating-cryo-electron-tomograms-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key shortcoming of these supervised learning methods is their need for large training data sets, typically generated from particle models in conjunction with complex numerical forward models simulating the physics of transmission electron microscopes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faket-simulating-cryo-electron-tomograms-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Comprehension: Language Models with Compiled Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-comprehension-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models have achieved impressive results in natural language processing tasks, but their ability to perform symbolic operations and arithmetic operations, remains limited, which attribute to their learn the rules implicitly from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-comprehension-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Torch-Choice: A PyTorch Package for Large-Scale Choice Modelling with Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torch-choice-a-pytorch-package-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[$\texttt{torch-choice}$ provides a $\texttt{ChoiceDataset}$ data structure to manage databases flexibly and memory-efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torch-choice-a-pytorch-package-for-large</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
