<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 21:06:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Study of Knowledge Editing for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-study-of-knowledge-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we first define the knowledge editing problem and then provide a comprehensive review of cutting-edge approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-study-of-knowledge-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JMA: a General Algorithm to Craft Nearly Optimal Targeted Adversarial Example</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jma-a-general-algorithm-to-craft-nearly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most of the approaches proposed so far to craft targeted adversarial examples against Deep Learning classifiers are highly suboptimal and typically rely on increasing the likelihood of the target class, thus implicitly focusing on one-hot encoding settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jma-a-general-algorithm-to-craft-nearly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auffusion: Leveraging the Power of Diffusion and Large Language Models for Text-to-Audio Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auffusion-leveraging-the-power-of-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Drawing inspiration from state-of-the-art Text-to-Image (T2I) diffusion models, we introduce Auffusion, a TTA system adapting T2I model frameworks to TTA task, by effectively leveraging their inherent generative strengths and precise cross-modal alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auffusion-leveraging-the-power-of-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable manifold learning by uniform landmark sampling and constrained locally linear embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-manifold-learning-by-uniform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a pivotal approach in machine learning and data science, manifold learning aims to uncover the intrinsic low-dimensional structure within complex nonlinear manifolds in high-dimensional space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-manifold-learning-by-uniform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DTBS: Dual-Teacher Bi-directional Self-training for Domain Adaptation in Nighttime Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dtbs-dual-teacher-bi-directional-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because the one-directional knowledge transfer from a single teacher is insufficient to adapt to a large domain shift.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dtbs-dual-teacher-bi-directional-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quokka: An Open-source Large Language Model ChatBot for Material Science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quokka-an-open-source-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the development of a specialized chatbot for materials science, leveraging the Llama-2 language model, and continuing pre-training on the expansive research articles in the materials science domain from the S2ORC dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quokka-an-open-source-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holistic Autonomous Driving Understanding by Bird's-Eye-View Injected Multi-Modal Large Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holistic-autonomous-driving-understanding-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BEV-InMLLM integrates multi-view, spatial awareness, and temporal semantics to enhance MLLMs' capabilities on NuInstruct tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holistic-autonomous-driving-understanding-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motif-aware Riemannian Graph Neural Network with Generative-Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motif-aware-riemannian-graph-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In light of the issues above, we propose the problem of \emph{Motif-aware Riemannian Graph Representation Learning}, seeking a numerically stable encoder to capture motif regularity in a diverse-curvature manifold without labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motif-aware-riemannian-graph-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Continual Anomaly Detection with Contrastively-learned Prompt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-continual-anomaly-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised Anomaly Detection (UAD) with incremental training is crucial in industrial manufacturing, as unpredictable defects make obtaining sufficient labeled data infeasible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-continual-anomaly-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$f$-Divergence Based Classification: Beyond the Use of Cross-Entropy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/f-divergence-based-classification-beyond-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, driven by the challenge of improving the state-of-the-art approach, we propose a bottom-up method that leads us to the formulation of a new objective function (and posterior probability estimator) corresponding to a novel $f$-divergence referred to as shifted log (SL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/f-divergence-based-classification-beyond-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IdentiFace : A VGG Based Multimodal Facial Biometric System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identiface-a-vgg-based-multimodal-facial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce "IdentiFace" which is a multimodal facial biometric system that combines the core of facial recognition with some of the most important soft biometric traits such as gender, face shape, and emotion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identiface-a-vgg-based-multimodal-facial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Structured Data as Graph for Data-to-Text Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-structured-data-as-graph-for-data-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we unify different types of structured data (i. e., table, key-value data, knowledge graph) into the graph format and cast different data-to-text generation tasks as graph-to-text generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-structured-data-as-graph-for-data-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Translation Testing via Syntactic Tree Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-translation-testing-via-syntactic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results show that STP can accurately find 5, 073 unique erroneous translations in Google Translate and 5, 100 unique erroneous translations in Bing Microsoft Translator (400% more than state-of-the-art techniques), with 64. 5% and 65. 4% precision, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-translation-testing-via-syntactic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAU-Net++: U-Shaped Hybrid CNN-Transformer Network for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brau-net-u-shaped-hybrid-cnn-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, BRAU-Net++ uses bi-level routing attention as the core building block to design our u-shaped encoder-decoder structure, in which both encoder and decoder are hierarchically constructed, so as to learn global semantic information while reducing computational complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brau-net-u-shaped-hybrid-cnn-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Large Language Models on Controllable Generation under Diversified Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-language-models-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While large language models (LLMs) have exhibited impressive instruction-following capabilities, it is still unclear whether and to what extent they can respond to explicit constraints that might be entailed in various instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-language-models-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An attempt to generate new bridge types from latent space of generative adversarial network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attempt-to-generate-new-bridge-types-from-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative adversarial network can create new bridge types by organically combining different structural components on the basis of human original bridge types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attempt-to-generate-new-bridge-types-from-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking RAFT for Efficient Optical Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-raft-for-efficient-optical-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these problems, this paper proposes a novel approach based on the RAFT framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-raft-for-efficient-optical-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring community structure in attributed hypergraphs using stochastic block models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-community-structure-in-attributed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hypergraphs are a representation of complex systems involving interactions among more than two entities and allow to investigation of higher-order structure and dynamics in real-world complex systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-community-structure-in-attributed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Families of costs with zero and nonnegative MTW tensor in optimal transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/families-of-costs-with-zero-and-nonnegative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compute explicitly the MTW tensor (or cross curvature) for the optimal transport problem on $\mathbb{R}^n$ with a cost function of form $\mathsf{c}(x, y) = \mathsf{u}(x^{\mathfrak{t}}y)$, where $\mathsf{u}$ is a scalar function with inverse $\mathsf{s}$, $x^{\ft}y$ is a nondegenerate bilinear pairing of vectors $x, y$ belonging to an open subset of $\mathbb{R}^n$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/families-of-costs-with-zero-and-nonnegative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Improved Proxy-based Deep Metric Learning via Data-Augmented Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-improved-proxy-based-deep-metric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments on benchmarks, including the popular CUB-200-2011, CARS196, Stanford Online Products, and In-Shop Clothes Retrieval, show that our learning algorithm significantly improves the existing proxy losses and achieves superior results compared to the existing methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-improved-proxy-based-deep-metric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astraios: Parameter-Efficient Instruction Tuning Code Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/astraios-parameter-efficient-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through investigations across 5 tasks and 8 different datasets encompassing both code comprehension and code generation tasks, we find that FFT generally leads to the best downstream performance across all scales, and PEFT methods differ significantly in their efficacy based on the model scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/astraios-parameter-efficient-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Computational Framework for Behavioral Assessment of LLM Therapists</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-computational-framework-for-behavioral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, we compare the behavior of LLM therapists against that of high- and low-quality human therapy, and study how their behavior can be modulated to better reflect behaviors observed in high-quality therapy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-computational-framework-for-behavioral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recent Advances in Text Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recent-advances-in-text-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we propose a new statistical model for ranking the citation impacts of $11$ topics, and we also build a cross-topic citation graph to illustrate how research results on different topics spread to one another.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recent-advances-in-text-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ToolEyes: Fine-Grained Evaluation for Tool Learning Capabilities of Large Language Models in Real-world Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tooleyes-fine-grained-evaluation-for-tool</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, a sole emphasis on outcomes disregards the intricate capabilities essential for LLMs to effectively utilize tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tooleyes-fine-grained-evaluation-for-tool</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharp-NeRF: Grid-based Fast Deblurring Neural Radiance Fields Using Sharpness Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharp-nerf-grid-based-fast-deblurring-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Especially, defocus blur is quite common in the images when they are normally captured using cameras.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharp-nerf-grid-based-fast-deblurring-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skeleton2vec: A Self-supervised Learning Framework with Contextualized Target Representations for Skeleton Sequence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton2vec-a-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show that using high-level contextualized features as prediction targets can achieve superior performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton2vec-a-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1st Place Solution for 5th LSVOS Challenge: Referring Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1st-place-solution-for-5th-lsvos-challenge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent transformer-based models have dominated the Referring Video Object Segmentation (RVOS) task due to the superior performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1st-place-solution-for-5th-lsvos-challenge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Leukocyte Detection Based on Deformable-DETR and Multi-Level Feature Fusion for Aiding Diagnosis of Blood Diseases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-leukocyte-detection-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, this paper proposes an innovative method of leukocyte detection: the Multi-level Feature Fusion and Deformable Self-attention DETR (MFDS-DETR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-leukocyte-detection-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bracketing is All You Need: Unifying Image Restoration and Enhancement Tasks with Multi-Exposure Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bracketing-is-all-you-need-unifying-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is challenging but highly desired to acquire high-quality photos with clear content in low-light environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bracketing-is-all-you-need-unifying-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Outlier Detection using Random Subspace and Subsampling Ensembles of Dirichlet Process Mixtures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-outlier-detection-using-random</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Probabilistic mixture models are acknowledged as a valuable tool for unsupervised outlier detection owing to their interpretability and intuitive grounding in statistical principles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-outlier-detection-using-random</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Symbolic Music Alignment with Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-symbolic-music-alignment-with-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, in its capacity to identify correct score positions for sampled test contexts; second, as the core technique of a complete algorithm for symbolic online note-wise alignment; and finally, as a real-time symbolic score follower.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-symbolic-music-alignment-with-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Generalist FaceX via Learning Unified Facial Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generalist-facex-via-learning-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents FaceX framework, a novel facial generalist model capable of handling diverse facial tasks simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generalist-facex-via-learning-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Granularity Representation Learning for Sketch-based Dynamic Face Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-representation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In specific scenarios, face sketch can be used to identify a person.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-representation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain-Conditional Multimodal Synthesis: A Survey and Taxonomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-conditional-multimodal-synthesis-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This survey comprehensively examines the emerging field of AIGC-based Brain-conditional Multimodal Synthesis, termed AIGC-Brain, to delineate the current landscape and future directions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-conditional-multimodal-synthesis-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of What Art? A Call for Multi-Prompt LLM Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/state-of-what-art-a-call-for-multi-prompt-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in large language models (LLMs) have led to the development of various evaluation benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/state-of-what-art-a-call-for-multi-prompt-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynCDR : Training Cross Domain Retrieval Models with Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syncdr-training-cross-domain-retrieval-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In cross-domain retrieval, a model is required to identify images from the same semantic category across two visual domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syncdr-training-cross-domain-retrieval-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effect of Optimizer, Initializer, and Architecture of Hypernetworks on Continual Learning from Demonstration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-optimizer-initializer-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we perform an exploratory study of the effects of different optimizers, initializers, and network architectures on the continual learning performance of hypernetworks for CLfD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-optimizer-initializer-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-GroundingDINO: Towards Open-Vocabulary Spatio-Temporal Video Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-groundingdino-towards-open-vocabulary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our contributions include a novel spatio-temporal video grounding model, surpassing state-of-the-art results in closed-set evaluations on multiple datasets and demonstrating superior performance in open-vocabulary scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-groundingdino-towards-open-vocabulary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Networks Against (and For) Self-Training: Classification with Small Labeled and Large Unlabeled Sets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-against-and-for-self-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this challenge, we propose a hybrid metric to replace the plain confidence measurement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-against-and-for-self-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVFAP: Self-supervised Video Facial Affect Perceiver</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svfap-self-supervised-video-facial-affect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video-based facial affect analysis has recently attracted increasing attention owing to its critical role in human-computer interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svfap-self-supervised-video-facial-affect</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSGAN: An Optical-to-SAR Dual Conditional GAN for Optical based SAR Temporal Shifting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsgan-an-optical-to-sar-dual-conditional-gan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel approach, termed SAR Temporal Shifting, which inputs an optical data from the desired timestamp along with a SAR data from a different temporal point but with a consistent viewing geometry as the expected SAR data, both complemented with a change map of optical data during the intervening period.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsgan-an-optical-to-sar-dual-conditional-gan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoGalactica: A Scientific Large Language Model in Geoscience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geogalactica-a-scientific-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our best knowledge, it is the largest language model for the geoscience domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geogalactica-a-scientific-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Modeling for Self-supervised Representation Learning on Vision and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-modeling-for-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the deep learning revolution marches on, self-supervised learning has garnered increasing attention in recent years thanks to its remarkable representation learning ability and the low dependence on labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-modeling-for-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Compact Representation for Bayesian Neural Networks By Removing Permutation Symmetry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-compact-representation-for-bayesian-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian neural networks (BNNs) are a principled approach to modeling predictive uncertainties in deep learning, which are important in safety-critical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-compact-representation-for-bayesian-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Fairness of the MIMIC-IV Dataset and a Baseline Algorithm: Application to the ICU Length of Stay Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-fairness-of-the-mimic-iv</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper uses the MIMIC-IV dataset to examine the fairness and bias in an XGBoost binary classification model predicting the Intensive Care Unit (ICU) length of stay (LOS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-fairness-of-the-mimic-iv</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain Tumor Segmentation Based on Deep Learning, Attention Mechanisms, and Energy-Based Uncertainty Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-tumor-segmentation-based-on-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Brain tumors are one of the deadliest forms of cancer with a mortality rate of over 80%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-tumor-segmentation-based-on-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDIF-DA: A Shallow-to-Deep Interaction Framework with Data Augmentation for Multi-modal Intent Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdif-da-a-shallow-to-deep-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The two core challenges for multi-modal intent detection are (1) how to effectively align and fuse different features of modalities and (2) the limited labeled multi-modal intent training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdif-da-a-shallow-to-deep-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balanced Graph Structure Information for Brain Disease Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balanced-graph-structure-information-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we proposed Bargrain (balanced graph structure for brains), which models two graph structures: filtered correlation matrix and optimal sample graph using graph convolution networks (GCNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balanced-graph-structure-information-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMMA: Co-Articulated Multi-Modal Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comma-co-articulated-multi-modal-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, the prompts of the vision and language branches in these methods are usually separated or uni-directionally correlated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comma-co-articulated-multi-modal-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CamPro: Camera-based Anti-Facial Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/campro-camera-based-anti-facial-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proliferation of images captured from millions of cameras and the advancement of facial recognition (FR) technology have made the abuse of FR a severe privacy threat.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/campro-camera-based-anti-facial-recognition</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
