<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:09:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Versatile Skills with Curriculum Masking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-versatile-skills-with-curriculum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by how humans learn by organizing knowledge in a curriculum, CurrMask adjusts its masking scheme during pretraining for learning versatile skills.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-versatile-skills-with-curriculum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DREB-Net: Dual-stream Restoration Embedding Blur-feature Fusion Network for High-mobility UAV Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreb-net-dual-stream-restoration-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, DREB-Net addresses the particularities of blurry image object detection problem by incorporating a Blurry image Restoration Auxiliary Branch (BRAB) during the training phase.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreb-net-dual-stream-restoration-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-model Control: Improving Multiple Large Language Models in One-time Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-model-control-improving-multiple-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this insight, we incorporate a tiny language model with a minimal number of parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-model-control-improving-multiple-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEADS: Lightweight Embedded Assisted Driving System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leads-lightweight-embedded-assisted-driving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid development of electric vehicles, formula races that face high school and university students have become more popular than ever as the threshold for design and manufacturing has been lowered.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leads-lightweight-embedded-assisted-driving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIA-DPO: Multi-Image Augmented Direct Preference Optimization For Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mia-dpo-multi-image-augmented-direct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing visual alignment methods, primarily designed for single-image scenarios, struggle to effectively handle the complexity of multi-image tasks due to the scarcity of diverse training data and the high cost of annotating chosen/rejected pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mia-dpo-multi-image-augmented-direct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Att2CPC: Attention-Guided Lossy Attribute Compression of Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/att2cpc-attention-guided-lossy-attribute</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on the task of learned lossy point cloud attribute compression (PCAC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/att2cpc-attention-guided-lossy-attribute</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADEM-VL: Adaptive and Embedded Fusion for Efficient Vision-Language Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adem-vl-adaptive-and-embedded-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we propose ADEM-VL, an efficient vision-language method that tunes VL models based on pretrained large language models (LLMs) by adopting a parameter-free cross-attention mechanism for similarity measurements in multimodal fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adem-vl-adaptive-and-embedded-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Transformer: Multi-Party Vertical Federated Learning on Practical Fuzzily Linked Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-transformer-multi-party-vertical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, we introduce the Federated Transformer (FeT), a novel framework that supports multi-party VFL with fuzzy identifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-transformer-multi-party-vertical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESpeW: Robust Copyright Protection for LLM-based EaaS via Embedding-Specific Watermark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/espew-robust-copyright-protection-for-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Embeddings as a Service (EaaS) is emerging as a crucial role in AI applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/espew-robust-copyright-protection-for-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DisenGCD: A Meta Multigraph-assisted Disentangled Graph Learning Framework for Cognitive Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disengcd-a-meta-multigraph-assisted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle the issues, this paper suggests a meta multigraph-assisted disentangled graph learning framework for CD (DisenGCD), which learns three types of representations on three disentangled graphs: student-exercise-concept interaction, exercise-concept relation, and concept dependency graphs, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disengcd-a-meta-multigraph-assisted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Two-View Geometry Estimation with Implicit Differentiation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-two-view-geometry-estimation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel two-view geometry estimation framework which is based on a differentiable robust loss function fitting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-two-view-geometry-estimation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding When Tree of Thoughts Succeeds: Larger Models Excel in Generation, Not Discrimination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-when-tree-of-thoughts-succeeds</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we analyze the roles of the generator and discriminator separately to better understand the conditions when ToT is beneficial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-when-tree-of-thoughts-succeeds</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blendify -- Python rendering framework for Blender</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blendify-python-rendering-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid growth of the volume of research fields like computer vision and computer graphics, researchers require effective and user-friendly rendering tools to visualize results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blendify-python-rendering-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Gaps: Utilizing Unlabeled Face Recognition Datasets to Boost Semi-Supervised Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gaps-utilizing-unlabeled-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, to further alleviate the scarcity of labeled and diverse images, we propose a Mixup-based data augmentation strategy tailored for facial images, and the loss weights of real and virtual images are determined according to the intersection-over-union (IoU) of the faces in the two images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gaps-utilizing-unlabeled-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Priors for Variational Likelihood Estimation and Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-priors-for-variational-likelihood</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we build upon diffusion priors and propose adaptive likelihood estimation and MAP inference during the reverse diffusion process to tackle real-world noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-priors-for-variational-likelihood</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HCDN: A Change Detection Network for Construction Housekeeping Using Feature Fusion and Large Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hcdn-a-change-detection-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite poor housekeeping is a significant contributor to construction accidents, there remains a significant lack of technological research focused on improving housekeeping practices in construction sites.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hcdn-a-change-detection-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Diffusion Language Models via Adaptation from Autoregressive Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-diffusion-language-models-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion Language Models (DLMs) have emerged as a promising new paradigm for text generative modeling, potentially addressing limitations of autoregressive (AR) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-diffusion-language-models-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Adaptive Framework for Generating Systematic Explanatory Answer in Online Q&amp;A Platforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-framework-for-generating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The naive RAG models, although effective in information retrieval, struggle with complex questions that require comprehensive and in-depth answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-framework-for-generating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FairDgcl: Fairness-aware Recommendation with Dynamic Graph Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairdgcl-fairness-aware-recommendation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose FairDgcl, a dynamic graph adversarial contrastive learning framework aiming at improving fairness in recommender system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairdgcl-fairness-aware-recommendation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphTeam: Facilitating Large Language Model-based Graph Analysis via Multi-Agent Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphteam-facilitating-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graphs are widely used for modeling relational data in real-world scenarios, such as social networks and urban computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphteam-facilitating-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenUDC: High Quality 3D Mesh Generation with Unsigned Dual Contouring Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genudc-high-quality-3d-mesh-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating high-quality meshes with complex structures and realistic surfaces is the primary goal of 3D generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genudc-high-quality-3d-mesh-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Foundation Models on Exceptional Cases: Dataset Creation and Validation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-foundation-models-on-exceptional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foundation models (FMs) have achieved significant success across various tasks, leading to research on benchmarks for reasoning abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-foundation-models-on-exceptional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALTA: Compiler-Based Analysis of Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alta-compiler-based-analysis-of-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new programming language called ALTA and a compiler that can map ALTA programs to Transformer weights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alta-compiler-based-analysis-of-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Random Feature Latent Variable Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-random-feature-latent-variable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we introduce a stick-breaking construction for DP to obtain an explicit PDF and a novel VBI algorithm called ``block coordinate descent variational inference" (BCD-VI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-random-feature-latent-variable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Effective Data-Free Knowledge Distillation via Diverse Diffusion Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-effective-data-free-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data-free knowledge distillation (DFKD) has emerged as a pivotal technique in the domain of model compression, substantially reducing the dependency on the original training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-effective-data-free-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mapping the Media Landscape: Predicting Factual Reporting and Political Bias Through Web Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-the-media-landscape-predicting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments, targeting two challenging bias descriptors, factual reporting and political bias, showed a significant performance improvement at the source media level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-the-media-landscape-predicting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Domain Adaptation for Action Recognition via Self-Ensembling and Conditional Embedding Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-for-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose $\mu$DAR, a novel joint optimization architecture comprised of three functions: (i) consistency regularizer between augmented samples to improve model classification generalizability, (ii) temporal ensemble for robust pseudo-label generation and (iii) conditional distribution alignment to improve domain generalizability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-for-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bilateral Hippocampi Segmentation in Low Field MRIs Using Mutual Feature Learning via Dual-Views</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilateral-hippocampi-segmentation-in-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate hippocampus segmentation in brain MRI is critical for studying cognitive and memory functions and diagnosing neurodevelopmental disorders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilateral-hippocampi-segmentation-in-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Deep Learning for Time Series Extrinsic Regression in predicting photometric metallicity of Fundamental-mode RR Lyrae Stars</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-deep-learning-for-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work underscores the importance of deep learning in astronomical research, particularly with large datasets from missions like Gaia.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-deep-learning-for-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Backpropagation: Optimization with Multi-Tangent Forward Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-backpropagation-optimization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Forward gradients are an approach to approximate the gradients from directional derivatives along random tangents computed by forward-mode automatic differentiation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-backpropagation-optimization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R-CoT: Reverse Chain-of-Thought Problem Generation for Geometric Reasoning in Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-cot-reverse-chain-of-thought-problem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current geometric data generation approaches, which apply preset templates to generate geometric data or use Large Language Models (LLMs) to rephrase questions and answers (Q&A), unavoidably limit data accuracy and diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-cot-reverse-chain-of-thought-problem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVT-B: A New Large-Scale Benchmark for Open-Vocabulary Multi-Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ovt-b-a-new-large-scale-benchmark-for-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, open-vocabulary object tracking (OVT) from a video has been studied less, and one reason is the shortage of benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ovt-b-a-new-large-scale-benchmark-for-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongRAG: A Dual-Perspective Retrieval-Augmented Generation Paradigm for Long-Context Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longrag-a-dual-perspective-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose LongRAG, a general, dual-perspective, and robust LLM-based RAG system paradigm for LCQA to enhance RAG's understanding of complex long-context knowledge (i. e., global information and factual details).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longrag-a-dual-perspective-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlantCamo: Plant Camouflage Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plantcamo-plant-camouflage-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the unique characteristics of plant camouflage, including holes and irregular borders, we developed a new framework, named PCNet, dedicated to PCD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plantcamo-plant-camouflage-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IdenBAT: Disentangled Representation Learning for Identity-Preserved Brain Age Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idenbat-disentangled-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Brain age transformation aims to convert reference brain images into synthesized images that accurately reflect the age-specific features of a target age group.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idenbat-disentangled-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Possibilities of AI-Powered Legal Assistance in Bangladesh through Large Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-possibilities-of-ai-powered-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research seeks to develop a specialized Large Language Model (LLM) to assist in the Bangladeshi legal system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-possibilities-of-ai-powered-legal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Point Cloud Upsampling and Cleaning with Octree-based CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-point-cloud-upsampling-and-cleaning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recovering dense and uniformly distributed point clouds from sparse or noisy data remains a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-point-cloud-upsampling-and-cleaning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISImed: A Framework for Self-Supervised Learning using Intrinsic Spatial Information in Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isimed-a-framework-for-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper demonstrates that spatial information can be used to learn interpretable representations in medical images using Self-Supervised Learning (SSL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isimed-a-framework-for-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correct after Answer: Enhancing Multi-Span Question Answering with Post-Processing Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correct-after-answer-enhancing-multi-span</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-Span Question Answering (MSQA) requires models to extract one or multiple answer spans from a given context to answer a question.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correct-after-answer-enhancing-multi-span</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SELA: Tree-Search Enhanced LLM Agents for Automated Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sela-tree-search-enhanced-llm-agents-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated Machine Learning (AutoML) approaches encompass traditional methods that optimize fixed pipelines for model selection and ensembling, as well as newer LLM-based frameworks that autonomously build pipelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sela-tree-search-enhanced-llm-agents-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMUSD: Asynchronous Multi-Device Speculative Decoding for LLM Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amusd-asynchronous-multi-device-speculative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce AMUSD (Asynchronous Multi-device Speculative Decoding), a system that further accelerates generation by decoupling the draft and verify phases into a continuous, asynchronous approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amusd-asynchronous-multi-device-speculative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Generative AI for De Novo Design of Co-Crystals with Enhanced Tabletability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-generative-ai-for-de-novo-design-of-co</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Co-crystallization is an accessible way to control physicochemical characteristics of organic crystals, which finds many biomedical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-generative-ai-for-de-novo-design-of-co</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-driven Coreference-based Ontology Building</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-coreference-based-ontology</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While coreference resolution is traditionally used as a component in individual document understanding, in this work we take a more global view and explore what can we learn about a domain from the set of all document-level coreference relations that are present in a large corpus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-coreference-based-ontology</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMScan: Causal Scan for LLM Misbehavior Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmscan-causal-scan-for-llm-misbehavior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the success of Large Language Models (LLMs) across various fields, their potential to generate untruthful, biased and harmful responses poses significant risks, particularly in critical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmscan-causal-scan-for-llm-misbehavior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Vanishing Activations in Deep CapsNets Using Channel Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-vanishing-activations-in-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, the backbone network and capsule layers are pruned with different pruning ratios to reduce the number of inactive capsules and achieve better model accuracy than the unpruned models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-vanishing-activations-in-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dhoroni: Exploring Bengali Climate Change and Environmental Views with a Multi-Perspective News Dataset and Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dhoroni-exploring-bengali-climate-change-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Climate change poses critical challenges globally, disproportionately affecting low-income countries that often lack resources and linguistic representation on the international stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dhoroni-exploring-bengali-climate-change-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing and improving reliability of neighbor embedding methods: a map-continuity perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-and-improving-reliability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LOO-map extends the embedding over a discrete set of input points to the entire input space, enabling a systematic assessment of map continuity, and thus the reliability of the visualizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-and-improving-reliability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoPS: Empowering LLM Agents with Provable Cross-Task Experience Sharing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cops-empowering-llm-agents-with-provable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In detail, CoPS leverages agents' experiences on previous tasks, selecting distribution-matched experiences via a provable pessimism-based strategy to maximize utility while minimizing risks from distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cops-empowering-llm-agents-with-provable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiniPLM: Knowledge Distillation for Pre-Training Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miniplm-knowledge-distillation-for-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For effectiveness, MiniPLM leverages the differences between large and small LMs to enhance the difficulty and diversity of the training data, helping student LMs acquire versatile and sophisticated knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miniplm-knowledge-distillation-for-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Science Out of Its Ivory Tower: Improving Accessibility with Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/science-out-of-its-ivory-tower-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A vast amount of scholarly work is published daily, yet much of it remains inaccessible to the general public due to dense jargon and complex language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/science-out-of-its-ivory-tower-improving</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
