<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 09:11:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>HARE: Explainable Hate Speech Detection with Step-by-Step Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hare-explainable-hate-speech-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the proliferation of social media, accurate detection of hate speech has become critical to ensure safety online.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hare-explainable-hate-speech-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caseformer: Pre-training for Legal Case Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caseformer-pre-training-for-legal-case</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Legal case retrieval aims to help legal workers find relevant cases related to their cases at hand, which is important for the guarantee of fairness and justice in legal judgments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caseformer-pre-training-for-legal-case</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMRec: Large Language Models with Graph Augmentation for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmrec-large-language-models-with-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By employing these strategies, we address the challenges posed by sparse implicit feedback and low-quality side information in recommenders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmrec-large-language-models-with-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing the Creative Mind: Language Model As Hierarchical Policy For Improved Exploration on Challenging Problem Solving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-creative-mind-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have achieved tremendous progress, yet they still often struggle with challenging reasoning problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-creative-mind-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noisy Exemplars Make Large Language Models More Robust: A Domain-Agnostic Behavioral Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisy-exemplars-make-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in prompt engineering enable large language models (LLMs) to solve multi-hop logical reasoning problems with impressive accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisy-exemplars-make-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFN: Dual-Encoder Fourier Group Harmonics Network for Three-Dimensional Macular Hole Reconstruction with Stochastic Retinal Defect Augmentation and Dynamic Weight Composition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defn-dual-encoder-fourier-group-harmonics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Macular hole diagnosis and treatment rely heavily on spatial and quantitative data, yet the scarcity of such data has impeded the progress of deep learning techniques for effective segmentation and real-time 3D reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defn-dual-encoder-fourier-group-harmonics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoulChat: Improving LLMs' Empathy, Listening, and Comfort Abilities through Fine-tuning with Multi-turn Empathy Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soulchat-improving-llms-empathy-listening-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have been widely applied in various fields due to their excellent capability for memorizing knowledge and chain of thought (CoT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soulchat-improving-llms-empathy-listening-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intriguing Properties of Data Attribution on Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intriguing-properties-of-data-attribution-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data attribution seeks to trace model outputs back to training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intriguing-properties-of-data-attribution-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CROMA: Remote Sensing Representations with Contrastive Radar-Optical Masked Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/croma-remote-sensing-representations-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that these objectives are complementary when leveraged on spatially aligned multimodal data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/croma-remote-sensing-representations-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature-oriented Deep Learning Framework for Pulmonary Cone-beam CT (CBCT) Enhancement with Multi-task Customized Perceptual Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-oriented-deep-learning-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel feature-oriented deep learning framework that translates low-quality CBCT images into high-quality CT-like imaging via a multi-task customized feature-to-feature perceptual loss function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-oriented-deep-learning-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaSent: Efficient Domain-Adapted Sentence Embeddings for Few-Shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adasent-efficient-domain-adapted-sentence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a solution, we propose AdaSent, which decouples SEPT from DAPT by training a SEPT adapter on the base PLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adasent-efficient-domain-adapted-sentence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Interpersonal Communication by Simulating Audiences with Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-interpersonal-communication-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How do we communicate with others to achieve our goals?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-interpersonal-communication-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Variational Inference for Probabilistic Programs with Stochastic Support</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-variational-inference-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Support Decomposition Variational Inference (SDVI), a new variational inference (VI) approach for probabilistic programs with stochastic support.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-variational-inference-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robustness Tests for Automatic Machine Translation Metrics with Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-tests-for-automatic-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate MT evaluation metric performance on adversarially-synthesized texts, to shed light on metric robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-tests-for-automatic-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MNN: Mixed Nearest-Neighbors for Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mnn-mixed-nearest-neighbors-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrastive self-supervised learning, positive samples are typically drawn from the same image but in different augmented views, resulting in a relatively limited source of positive samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mnn-mixed-nearest-neighbors-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event-based Background-Oriented Schlieren</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-based-background-oriented-schlieren</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Schlieren imaging is an optical technique to observe the flow of transparent media, such as air or water, without any particle seeding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-based-background-oriented-schlieren</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient LLM Inference on CPUs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-llm-inference-on-cpus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable performance and tremendous potential across a wide range of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-llm-inference-on-cpus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Instruction Tuning: Improving Cross-Task Generalization by Training on Prompt Sensitive Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-instruction-tuning-improving-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instruction tuning (IT) achieves impressive zero-shot generalization results by training large language models (LLMs) on a massive amount of diverse tasks with instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-instruction-tuning-improving-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Summarization with Normalizing Flows and Aggressive Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-summarization-with-normalizing-flows</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents FlowSUM, a normalizing flows-based variational encoder-decoder framework for Transformer-based summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-summarization-with-normalizing-flows</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Graph Clustering via Meta Weighting for Noisy Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-graph-clustering-via-meta-weighting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We add a learnable weight to each node pair, and MetaGC adaptively adjusts the weights of node pairs using meta-weighting so that the weights of meaningful node pairs increase and the weights of less-meaningful ones (e. g., noise edges) decrease.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-graph-clustering-via-meta-weighting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenForest: A data catalogue for machine learning in forest monitoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openforest-a-data-catalogue-for-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These datasets are grouped in OpenForest, a dynamic catalogue open to contributions that strives to reference all available open access forest datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openforest-a-data-catalogue-for-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuralGF: Unsupervised Point Normal Estimation by Learning Neural Gradient Function</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralgf-unsupervised-point-normal-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce loss functions to facilitate query points to iteratively reach the moving targets and aggregate onto the approximated surface, thereby learning a global surface representation of the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralgf-unsupervised-point-normal-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT-Powered Hierarchical Comparisons for Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-powered-hierarchical-comparisons-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The zero-shot open-vocabulary challenge in image classification is tackled by pretrained vision-language models like CLIP, which benefit from incorporating class-specific knowledge from large language models (LLMs) like ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-powered-hierarchical-comparisons-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Single-Channel Speaker-Turn Aware Conversational Speech Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-single-channel-speaker-turn-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional speech-to-text translation (ST) systems are trained on single-speaker utterances, and they may not generalize to real-life scenarios where the audio contains conversations by multiple speakers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-single-channel-speaker-turn-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Embedded Diachronic Sense Change Model with a Case Study from Ancient Greek</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-embedded-diachronic-sense-change-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These models represent the senses of a given target word such as "kosmos" (meaning decoration, order or world) as distributions over context words, and sense prevalence as a distribution over senses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-embedded-diachronic-sense-change-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Syllable-Level Pronunciation Stress with A Self-Attention Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-syllable-level-pronunciation-stress</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, knowing the stress level is important for English speakers and learners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-syllable-level-pronunciation-stress</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Cooperative Trajectory Representations for Motion Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-cooperative-trajectory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we present V2X-Graph, the first interpretable and end-to-end learning framework for cooperative motion forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-cooperative-trajectory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAUNE-Net: A Residual and Attention-Driven Underwater Image Enhancement Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raune-net-a-residual-and-attention-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Underwater image enhancement (UIE) poses challenges due to distinctive properties of the underwater environment, including low contrast, high turbidity, visual blurriness, and color distortion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raune-net-a-residual-and-attention-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TPSeNCE: Towards Artifact-Free Realistic Rain Generation for Deraining and Object Detection in Rain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tpsence-towards-artifact-free-realistic-rain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first introduce a Triangular Probability Similarity (TPS) constraint to guide the generated images toward clear and rainy images in the discriminator manifold, thereby minimizing artifacts and distortions during rain generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tpsence-towards-artifact-free-realistic-rain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Space Translation via Semantic Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-space-translation-via-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While different neural models often exhibit latent spaces that are alike when exposed to semantically related data, this intrinsic similarity is not always immediately discernible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-space-translation-via-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Latent Diffusion Model for 3D Medical Image to Image Translation: Multi-modal Magnetic Resonance Imaging Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-latent-diffusion-model-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model exhibited successful image synthesis across different source-target modality scenarios and surpassed other models in quantitative evaluations tested on multi-modal brain magnetic resonance imaging datasets of four different modalities and an independent IXI dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-latent-diffusion-model-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt-based Logical Semantics Enhancement for Implicit Discourse Relation Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-based-logical-semantics-enhancement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Essentially, our method seamlessly injects knowledge relevant to discourse relation into pre-trained language models through prompt-based connective prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-based-logical-semantics-enhancement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual atlas-based segmentation of prostate MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-atlas-based-segmentation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual learning (CL) methods designed for natural image classification often fail to reach basic quality standards for medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-atlas-based-segmentation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HWD: A Novel Evaluation Score for Styled Handwritten Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hwd-a-novel-evaluation-score-for-styled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through extensive experimental evaluation on different word-level and line-level datasets of handwritten text images, we demonstrate the suitability of the proposed HWD as a score for Styled HTG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hwd-a-novel-evaluation-score-for-styled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing the Impact of Companies on AI Research Based on Publications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-impact-of-companies-on-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI) is one of the most momentous technologies of our time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-impact-of-companies-on-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GACE: Geometry Aware Confidence Enhancement for Black-Box 3D Object Detectors on LiDAR-Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gace-geometry-aware-confidence-enhancement-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Widely-used LiDAR-based 3D object detectors often neglect fundamental geometric information readily available from the object proposals in their confidence estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gace-geometry-aware-confidence-enhancement-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate What You Prefer: Reshaping Sequential Recommendation via Guided Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generate-what-you-prefer-reshaping-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scrutinizing previous studies, we can summarize a common learning-to-classify paradigm -- given a positive item, a recommender model performs negative sampling to add negative items and learns to classify whether the user prefers them or not, based on his/her historical interaction sequence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generate-what-you-prefer-reshaping-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ling-CL: Understanding NLP Models through Linguistic Curricula</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ling-cl-understanding-nlp-models-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We employ a characterization of linguistic complexity from psycholinguistic and language acquisition research to develop data-driven curricula to understand the underlying linguistic knowledge that models learn to address NLP tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ling-cl-understanding-nlp-models-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linked Papers With Code: The Latest in Machine Learning as an RDF Knowledge Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linked-papers-with-code-the-latest-in-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Linked Papers With Code (LPWC), an RDF knowledge graph that provides comprehensive, current information about almost 400, 000 machine learning publications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linked-papers-with-code-the-latest-in-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utilitarian Algorithm Configuration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilitarian-algorithm-configuration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove upper bounds on the runtime of these procedures that are similar to theoretical lower bounds, while also demonstrating their performance empirically.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilitarian-algorithm-configuration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Transformer-Based Model With Self-Distillation for Multimodal Emotion Recognition in Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transformer-based-model-with-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Emotion recognition in conversations (ERC), the task of recognizing the emotion of each utterance in a conversation, is crucial for building empathetic machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transformer-based-model-with-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-Helpful Multimodal Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-helpful-multimodal-machine-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to the extensive training set, EVA contains a video-helpful evaluation set in which subtitles are ambiguous, and videos are guaranteed helpful for disambiguation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-helpful-multimodal-machine-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mathematical Introduction to Deep Learning: Methods, Implementations, and Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathematical-introduction-to-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This book aims to provide an introduction to the topic of deep learning algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathematical-introduction-to-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Histopathological Image Analysis with Style-Augmented Feature Domain Mixing for Improved Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histopathological-image-analysis-with-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Style transfer-based data augmentation is an emerging technique that can be used to improve the generalizability of machine learning models for histopathological images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histopathological-image-analysis-with-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BasisFormer: Attention-based Time Series Forecasting with Learnable and Interpretable Basis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/basisformer-attention-based-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bases have become an integral part of modern deep learning-based models for time series forecasting due to their ability to act as feature extractors or future references.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/basisformer-attention-based-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsyCoT: Psychological Questionnaire as Powerful Chain-of-Thought for Personality Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psycot-psychological-questionnaire-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Drawing inspiration from Psychological Questionnaires, which are carefully designed by psychologists to evaluate individual personality traits through a series of targeted items, we argue that these items can be regarded as a collection of well-structured chain-of-thought (CoT) processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psycot-psychological-questionnaire-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Guided Visual Question Answering: Elevate Your Multimodal Language Model Using Knowledge-Enriched Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-guided-visual-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual question answering (VQA) is the task of answering questions about an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-guided-visual-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decodable and Sample Invariant Continuous Object Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decodable-and-sample-invariant-continuous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, the encoding is decodable, which enables neural networks to regress continuous objects by regressing their encodings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decodable-and-sample-invariant-continuous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Compositionality in Sentiment: New Data and Analyses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-compositionality-in-sentiment-new-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When natural language phrases are combined, their meaning is often more than the sum of their parts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-compositionality-in-sentiment-new-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEDNet: A Hierarchical Encoder-Decoder Network for 3D Object Detection in Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hednet-a-hierarchical-encoder-decoder-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reduce computational costs, these methods resort to submanifold sparse convolutions, which prevent the information exchange among spatially disconnected features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hednet-a-hierarchical-encoder-decoder-network</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
