<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 21:08:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring GLU Expansion Ratios: A Study of Structured Pruning in LLaMA-3.2 Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-glu-expansion-ratios-a-study-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models with GLU architectures are typically designed with significant expansion ratios in their MLP layers, where output dimensions are several times larger than input dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-glu-expansion-ratios-a-study-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapter Merging with Centroid Prototype Mapping for Scalable Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapter-merging-with-centroid-prototype</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Adapter Merging with Centroid Prototype Mapping (ACMap), an exemplar-free framework for class-incremental learning (CIL) that addresses both catastrophic forgetting and scalability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapter-merging-with-centroid-prototype</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Thousand Brains Project: A New Paradigm for Sensorimotor Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-thousand-brains-project-a-new-paradigm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Each learning module operates as a semi-independent unit that can model entire objects, represents information through spatially structured reference frames, and both estimates and is able to effect movement in the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-thousand-brains-project-a-new-paradigm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChaI-TeA: A Benchmark for Evaluating Autocompletion of Interactions with LLM-based Chatbots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chai-tea-a-benchmark-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present ChaI-TeA: CHat InTEraction Autocomplete; An autcomplete evaluation framework for LLM-based chatbot interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chai-tea-a-benchmark-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICM-Assistant: Instruction-tuning Multimodal Large Language Models for Rule-based Explainable Image Content Moderation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icm-assistant-instruction-tuning-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Controversial contents largely inundate the Internet, infringing various cultural norms and child protection standards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icm-assistant-instruction-tuning-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERVD: An Efficient and Robust ViT-Based Distillation Framework for Remote Sensing Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ervd-an-efficient-and-robust-vit-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ERVD: An Efficient and Robust ViT-Based Distillation Framework for Remote Sensing Image Retrieval]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ervd-an-efficient-and-robust-vit-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiTCtrl: Exploring Attention Control in Multi-Modal Diffusion Transformer for Tuning-Free Multi-Prompt Longer Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ditctrl-exploring-attention-control-in-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our careful design, the video generated by DiTCtrl achieves smooth transitions and consistent object motion given multiple sequential prompts without additional training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ditctrl-exploring-attention-control-in-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HNCI: High-Dimensional Network Causal Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hnci-high-dimensional-network-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we suggest the new method of high-dimensional network causal inference (HNCI) that provides both valid confidence interval on the average direct treatment effect on the treated (ADET) and valid confidence set for the neighborhood size for interference effect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hnci-high-dimensional-network-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIMS: Image Matching System Based on Adaptive Graph Construction and Graph Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gims-image-matching-system-based-on-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Feature-based image matching has extensive applications in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gims-image-matching-system-based-on-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Property Enhanced Instruction Tuning for Multi-task Molecule Generation with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/property-enhanced-instruction-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first step, we use textual descriptions, SMILES, and biochemical properties as multimodal inputs to pre-train a model called PEIT-GEN, by aligning multi-modal representations to synthesize instruction data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/property-enhanced-instruction-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG-MoE: Bypass Isolated Gating MoE for Generalized Multimodal Face Anti-Spoofing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/big-moe-bypass-isolated-gating-moe-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the domain of facial recognition security, multimodal Face Anti-Spoofing (FAS) is essential for countering presentation attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/big-moe-bypass-isolated-gating-moe-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Threat of Fraud Gangs to Graph Neural Networks: Multi-Target Graph Injection Attacks against GNN-Based Fraud Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-threat-of-fraud-gangs-to-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on these scenarios, we study adversarial attacks against GNN-based fraud detectors by simulating attacks of fraud gangs in three real-world fraud cases: spam reviews, fake news, and medical insurance frauds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-threat-of-fraud-gangs-to-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-DeepONet: A Deep Operator Network Integrating PointNet for Nonlinear Analysis of Non-Parametric 3D Geometries and Load Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-deeponet-a-deep-operator-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nonlinear structural analyses in engineering often require extensive finite element simulations, limiting their applicability in design optimization, uncertainty quantification, and real-time control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-deeponet-a-deep-operator-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Representation for Interactive Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-representation-for-interactive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, we propose Contrastive Representation for Interactive Recommendation (CRIR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-representation-for-interactive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating event descriptions under syntactic and semantic constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-event-descriptions-under-syntactic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the goal of supporting scalable lexical semantic annotation, analysis, and theorizing, we conduct a comprehensive evaluation of different methods for generating event descriptions under both syntactic constraints -- e. g. desired clause structure -- and semantic constraints -- e. g. desired verb sense.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-event-descriptions-under-syntactic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expand VSR Benchmark for VLLM to Expertize in Spatial Rules</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expand-vsr-benchmark-for-vllm-to-expertize-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We found current VLLMs to exhibit a contradiction of over-sensitivity to language instructions and under-sensitivity to visual positional information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expand-vsr-benchmark-for-vllm-to-expertize-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Key of Understanding Vision Tasks: Explanatory Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-key-of-understanding-vision-tasks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore the idea that CV adopts discrete and terminological task definitions (\eg, ``image segmentation''), which may be a key barrier to zero-shot task generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-key-of-understanding-vision-tasks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MotifGPL: Motif-Enhanced Graph Prototype Learning for Deciphering Urban Social Segregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motifgpl-motif-enhanced-graph-prototype</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we propose a framework named Motif-Enhanced Graph Prototype Learning (MotifGPL), which consists of three key modules: prototype-based graph structure extraction, motif distribution discovery, and urban graph structure reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motifgpl-motif-enhanced-graph-prototype</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Tuning for Item Cold-start Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-tuning-for-item-cold-start</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing methods typically rely on content-based properties or text descriptions for prompting, which we argue may be suboptimal for cold-start recommendations due to 1) semantic gaps with recommender tasks, 2) model bias caused by warm-up items contribute most of the positive feedback to the model, which is the core of the cold-start problem that hinders the recommender quality on cold-start items.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-tuning-for-item-cold-start</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Intelligence in GameFi: Embodied AI Agents and the Convergence of DeFi and Virtual Ecosystems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-intelligence-in-gamefi-embodied</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the rapidly evolving landscape of GameFi, a fusion of gaming and decentralized finance (DeFi), there exists a critical need to enhance player engagement and economic interaction within gaming ecosystems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-intelligence-in-gamefi-embodied</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MinsStudio: A Streamlined Package for Minecraft AI Agent Development</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minsstudio-a-streamlined-package-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Minecraft has emerged as a valuable testbed for embodied intelligence and sequential decision-making research, yet the development and validation of novel agents remains hindered by significant engineering challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minsstudio-a-streamlined-package-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisionGRU: A Linear-Complexity RNN Model for Efficient Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visiongru-a-linear-complexity-rnn-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While CNNs excel at extracting multi-scale features and ViTs effectively capture global dependencies, both suffer from high computational costs, particularly when processing high-resolution images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visiongru-a-linear-complexity-rnn-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Token-Budget-Aware LLM Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-budget-aware-llm-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reasoning is critical for large language models (LLMs) to excel in a wide range of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-budget-aware-llm-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixMAS: A Framework for Sampling-Based Mixer Architecture Search for Multimodal Fusion and Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixmas-a-framework-for-sampling-based-mixer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Choosing a suitable deep learning architecture for multimodal data fusion is a challenging task, as it requires the effective integration and processing of diverse data types, each with distinct structures and characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixmas-a-framework-for-sampling-based-mixer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underwater Image Restoration via Polymorphic Large Kernel CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/underwater-image-restoration-via-polymorphic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work provides new insights into the potential of CNN-based approaches for challenging image restoration tasks in underwater environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/underwater-image-restoration-via-polymorphic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-supervised Credit Card Fraud Detection via Attribute-Driven Graph Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-credit-card-fraud-detection-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then we pass messages among the nodes through a Gated Temporal Attention Network (GTAN) to learn the transaction representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-credit-card-fraud-detection-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parallel Neural Computing for Scene Understanding from LiDAR Perception in Autonomous Racing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-neural-computing-for-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional sequential network approaches may struggle to meet the real-time knowledge and decision-making demands of an autonomous agent covering large displacements in a short time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-neural-computing-for-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Label Noise using Prompt-Based Hyperbolic Meta-Learning in Open-Set Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-label-noise-using-prompt-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-Set Domain Generalization (OSDG) is a challenging task requiring models to accurately predict familiar categories while minimizing confidence for unknown categories to effectively reject them in unseen domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-label-noise-using-prompt-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReducedLUT: Table Decomposition with "Don't Care" Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducedlut-table-decomposition-with-don-t</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then demonstrate a particular application to machine learning; by replacing unobserved patterns within the training data of neural network models with don't cares, we enable greater compression with minimal model accuracy degradation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducedlut-table-decomposition-with-don-t</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NoiseHGNN: Synthesized Similarity Graph-Based Neural Network For Noised Heterogeneous Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisehgnn-synthesized-similarity-graph-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For homogeneous graphs, the latest works use original node features to synthesize a similarity graph that can correct the structure of the noised graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisehgnn-synthesized-similarity-graph-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Driven Self-Supervised Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-self-supervised-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach is general that it can be applied to homogeneous and heterogeneous graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-self-supervised-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongDocURL: a Comprehensive Multimodal Long Document Benchmark Integrating Understanding, Reasoning, and Locating</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longdocurl-a-comprehensive-multimodal-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large vision language models (LVLMs) have improved the document understanding capabilities remarkably, enabling the handling of complex document elements, longer contexts, and a wider range of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longdocurl-a-comprehensive-multimodal-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3DGraphLLM: Combining Semantic Graphs and Large Language Models for 3D Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dgraphllm-combining-semantic-graphs-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a method 3DGraphLLM for constructing a learnable representation of a 3D scene graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dgraphllm-combining-semantic-graphs-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual Mathematical Reasoning: Advancing Open-Source LLMs in Hindi and English</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-mathematical-reasoning-advancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adopting a bilingual approach that combines English and Hindi samples achieves results comparable to individual language models, demonstrating the capability to learn mathematical reasoning in both languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-mathematical-reasoning-advancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Well Do LLMs Generate Code for Different Application Domains? Benchmark and Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-well-do-llms-generate-code-for-different</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing code generation benchmarks primarily focus on general-purpose scenarios, leaving the code generation performance of LLMs for specific application domains largely unknown.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-well-do-llms-generate-code-for-different</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClassifyViStA:WCE Classification with Visual understanding through Segmentation and Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classifyvista-wce-classification-with-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gastrointestinal (GI) bleeding is a serious medical condition that presents significant diagnostic challenges, particularly in settings with limited access to healthcare resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classifyvista-wce-classification-with-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segment-Based Attention Masking for GPTs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-based-attention-masking-for-gpts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Each of these is treated as a unit for the purpose of masking, such that the first tokens in each block can access the subsequent tokens in a non-causal manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-based-attention-masking-for-gpts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Traffic Scenarios via In-Context Learning to Learn Better Motion Planner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-traffic-scenarios-via-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we represent traffic scenarios as scripts, which are then used by the simulator to generate traffic scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-traffic-scenarios-via-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Hidden Treasures: Enhancing Recommendations with Unlabeled Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-hidden-treasures-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implementing the PNN paradigm is, however, technically challenging because: (1) it is difficult to classify unlabeled data into neutral or negative in the absence of supervised signals; (2) there does not exist any loss function that can handle set-level triple-wise ranking relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-hidden-treasures-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mulberry: Empowering MLLM with o1-like Reasoning and Reflection via Collective Monte Carlo Tree Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mulberry-empowering-mllm-with-o1-like</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using CoMCTS, we construct Mulberry-260k, a multimodal dataset with a tree of rich, explicit and well-defined reasoning nodes for each question.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mulberry-empowering-mllm-with-o1-like</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDM-Car: A Dataset for Small and Dim Moving Vehicles Detection in Satellite Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdm-car-a-dataset-for-small-and-dim-moving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vehicle detection and tracking in satellite video is essential in remote sensing (RS) applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdm-car-a-dataset-for-small-and-dim-moving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Optimization of Portfolio Allocation Using Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-optimization-of-portfolio-allocation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence is fundamentally transforming financial investment decision-making paradigms, with deep reinforcement learning (DRL) demonstrating significant application potential in domains such as robo-advisory services.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-optimization-of-portfolio-allocation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quo Vadis, Anomaly Detection? LLMs and VLMs in the Spotlight</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quo-vadis-anomaly-detection-llms-and-vlms-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video anomaly detection (VAD) has witnessed significant advancements through the integration of large language models (LLMs) and vision-language models (VLMs), addressing critical challenges such as interpretability, temporal reasoning, and generalization in dynamic, open-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quo-vadis-anomaly-detection-llms-and-vlms-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Form Speech Generation with Spoken Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-form-speech-generation-with-spoken</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the generative modeling of speech over multiple minutes, a requirement for long-form multimedia generation and audio-native voice assistants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-form-speech-generation-with-spoken</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-Panda: Parameter-efficient Alignment for Encoder-free Video-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-panda-parameter-efficient-alignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The fine-grained video question-answering evaluation demonstrates our model's effectiveness, outperforming the encoder-based approaches Video-ChatGPT and Video-LLaVA in key aspects like correctness and temporal understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-panda-parameter-efficient-alignment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the Known: Enhancing Open Set Domain Adaptation with Unknown Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-the-known-enhancing-open-set-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a new approach to improve OSDA techniques by extracting a set of high-confidence unknown instances and using it as a hard constraint to tighten the classification boundaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-the-known-enhancing-open-set-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Modality Generalization: A Benchmark and Prospective Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-modality-generalization-a-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal learning has achieved remarkable success by integrating information from various modalities, achieving superior performance in tasks like recognition and retrieval compared to uni-modal approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-modality-generalization-a-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crystal ball: From innovative attacks to attack effectiveness classifier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crystal-ball-from-innovative-attacks-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study presents a set of innovative problem-based evasion attacks against well-known Android malware detection systems, which decrease their detection rate by up to 97%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crystal-ball-from-innovative-attacks-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating AIGC Services with Latent Action Diffusion Scheduling in Edge Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-aigc-services-with-latent-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The LAD-TS generates a near-optimal offloading decision by leveraging the diffusion model's conditional generation capability and the reinforcement learning's environment interaction ability, thereby minimizing the service delays under multiple resource constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-aigc-services-with-latent-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Structure Learning for Spatial-Temporal Imputation: Adapting to Node and Feature Scales</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-structure-learning-for-spatial-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatial-temporal data collected across different geographic locations often suffer from missing values, posing challenges to data analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-structure-learning-for-spatial-temporal</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
