<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:09:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ChunkFormer: Masked Chunking Conformer For Long-Form Speech Transcription</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chunkformer-masked-chunking-conformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By eliminating the need for padding in standard batching, ChunkFormer's masked batching technique reduces execution time and memory usage by more than 3x in batch processing, substantially reducing costs for a wide range of ASR systems, particularly regarding GPU resources for models serving in real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chunkformer-masked-chunking-conformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Backdoor Samples in Contrastive Language Image Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-backdoor-samples-in-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive language-image pretraining (CLIP) has been found to be vulnerable to poisoning backdoor attacks where the adversary can achieve an almost perfect attack success rate on CLIP models by poisoning only 0. 01\% of the training dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-backdoor-samples-in-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Gradient Boosting Decision Tree: In-Place Updates for Efficient Adding/Deleting Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-gradient-boosting-decision-tree-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The backdoor attack results show that our framework can successfully inject and remove backdoor in a well-trained model using incremental and decremental learning, and the empirical results on public datasets confirm the effectiveness and efficiency of our proposed online learning framework and optimizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-gradient-boosting-decision-tree-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Tuning Discrete Diffusion Models with Policy Gradient Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-discrete-diffusion-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Discrete diffusion models have recently gained significant attention due to their ability to process complex discrete structures for language modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-discrete-diffusion-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partial Channel Network: Compute Fewer, Perform Better</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-channel-network-compute-fewer-perform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this assumption, we introduce a novel partial attention convolution (PATConv) that can efficiently combine convolution with visual attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-channel-network-compute-fewer-perform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly Lossless Adaptive Bit Switching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nearly-lossless-adaptive-bit-switching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model quantization is widely applied for compressing and accelerating deep neural networks (DNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nearly-lossless-adaptive-bit-switching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Position: More Rigorous Software Engineering Would Improve Reproducibility in Machine Learning Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-more-rigorous-software-engineering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental verification and falsification of scholarly work are part of the scientific method's core.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-more-rigorous-software-engineering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CycleGuardian: A Framework for Automatic RespiratorySound classification Based on Improved Deep clustering and Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cycleguardian-a-framework-for-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Auscultation plays a pivotal role in early respiratory and pulmonary disease diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cycleguardian-a-framework-for-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avoiding $\mathbf{exp(R_{max})}$ scaling in RLHF through Preference-based Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avoiding-mathbf-exp-r-max-scaling-in-rlhf</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning from Human Feedback (RLHF) has emerged as a pivotal technique for large language model (LLM) alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avoiding-mathbf-exp-r-max-scaling-in-rlhf</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complex Wavelet Mutual Information Loss: A Multi-Scale Loss Function for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-wavelet-mutual-information-loss-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose complex wavelet mutual information (CWMI) loss, a novel loss function that leverages mutual information from subband images decomposed by a complex steerable pyramid.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-wavelet-mutual-information-loss-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Converting Transformers into DGNNs Form</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/converting-transformers-into-dgnns-form</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in deep learning have established Transformer architectures as the predominant modeling paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/converting-transformers-into-dgnns-form</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-Inspired Distributed Radio Map Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-inspired-distributed-radio-map</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While existing deep learning based methods conduct RME given spectrum measurements gathered from dispersed sensors in the region of interest, they rely on centralized data at a fusion center, which however raises critical concerns on data privacy leakages and high communication overloads.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-inspired-distributed-radio-map</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAAT-EHR: Cross-Attentional Autoregressive Transformer for Multimodal Electronic Health Record Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caat-ehr-cross-attentional-autoregressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Electronic health records (EHRs) provide a comprehensive source of longitudinal patient data, encompassing structured modalities such as laboratory results, imaging data, and vital signs, and unstructured clinical notes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caat-ehr-cross-attentional-autoregressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Robustness of Representation Misdirection for Large Language Model Unlearning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-robustness-of-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representation Misdirection (RM) and variants are established large language model (LLM) unlearning methods with state-of-the-art performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-robustness-of-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Reasoning with Hidden Thinking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-reasoning-with-hidden-thinking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, we design corresponding Heima Decoder with traditional Large Language Models (LLMs) to adaptively interpret the hidden representations into variable-length textual sequence, reconstructing reasoning processes that closely resemble the original CoTs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-reasoning-with-hidden-thinking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Learning for Nonparametric Contextual Dynamic Pricing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-nonparametric-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel Transfer Learning for Dynamic Pricing (TLDP) algorithm that can effectively leverage pre-collected data from a source domain to enhance pricing decisions in the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-nonparametric-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Surprising Agreement Between Convex Optimization Theory and Learning-Rate Scheduling for Large Model Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-surprising-agreement-between-convex</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that learning-rate schedules for large model training behave surprisingly similar to a performance bound from non-smooth convex optimization theory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-surprising-agreement-between-convex</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Inverse Problem for Multi-armed Bandits via Convex Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-inverse-problem-for-multi-armed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the inverse problem of multi-armed bandits (IMAB) that are widely used in neuroscience and psychology research for behavior modelling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-inverse-problem-for-multi-armed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Diffusion Posterior Sampling: From Conditional Score Estimator to Maximizing a Posterior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-diffusion-posterior-sampling-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in diffusion models have been leveraged to address inverse problems without additional training, and Diffusion Posterior Sampling (DPS) (Chung et al., 2022a) is among the most popular approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-diffusion-posterior-sampling-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneBatchPAM: A Fast and Frugal K-Medoids Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onebatchpam-a-fast-and-frugal-k-medoids</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel k-medoids approximation algorithm to handle large-scale datasets with reasonable computational time and memory complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onebatchpam-a-fast-and-frugal-k-medoids</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mFollowIR: a Multilingual Benchmark for Instruction Following in Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mfollowir-a-multilingual-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We see strong cross-lingual performance with English-based retrievers that trained using instructions, but find a notable drop in performance in the multilingual setting, indicating that more work is needed in developing data for instruction-based multilingual retrievers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mfollowir-a-multilingual-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PathE: Leveraging Entity-Agnostic Paths for Parameter-Efficient Knowledge Graph Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathe-leveraging-entity-agnostic-paths-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is often done by allocating and learning embedding tables for all or a subset of the entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathe-leveraging-entity-agnostic-paths-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMDet: Learning Strong Open-Vocabulary Object Detectors under the Supervision of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmdet-learning-strong-open-vocabulary-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show that an open-vocabulary detector co-training with a large language model by generating image-level detailed captions for each image can further improve performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmdet-learning-strong-open-vocabulary-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DINAMO: Dynamic and INterpretable Anomaly MOnitoring for Large-Scale Particle Physics Experiments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dinamo-dynamic-and-interpretable-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ensuring reliable data collection in large-scale particle physics experiments demands Data Quality Monitoring (DQM) procedures to detect possible detector malfunctions and preserve data integrity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dinamo-dynamic-and-interpretable-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full-scale Representation Guided Network for Retinal Vessel Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/full-scale-representation-guided-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Passing full-scale information to the attention block allows for the generation of improved attention maps, which are then passed to the attention-guided filter, resulting in performance enhancement of the segmentation network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/full-scale-representation-guided-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VKFPos: A Learning-Based Monocular Positioning with Variational Bayesian Extended Kalman Filter Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vkfpos-a-learning-based-monocular-positioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the challenges in learning-based monocular positioning by proposing VKFPos, a novel approach that integrates Absolute Pose Regression (APR) and Relative Pose Regression (RPR) via an Extended Kalman Filter (EKF) within a variational Bayesian inference framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vkfpos-a-learning-based-monocular-positioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do LLMs Strategically Reveal, Conceal, and Infer Information? A Theoretical and Empirical Analysis in The Chameleon Game</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-llms-strategically-reveal-conceal-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The empirical results show that while non-chameleon LLM agents identify the chameleon, they fail to conceal the secret from the chameleon, and their winning probability is far from the levels of even trivial strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-llms-strategically-reveal-conceal-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Adversarial Approach to Register Extreme Resolution Tissue Cleared 3D Brain Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adversarial-approach-to-register-extreme</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compared our method both with traditional and deep-learning based registration methods. Two different versions of CUBIC dataset are used, representing two different resolutions 25% and 100% respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adversarial-approach-to-register-extreme</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vintix: Action Model via In-Context Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vintix-action-model-via-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In-Context Reinforcement Learning (ICRL) represents a promising paradigm for developing generalist agents that learn at inference time through trial-and-error interactions, analogous to how large language models adapt contextually, but with a focus on reward maximization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vintix-action-model-via-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Early Stopping: Refine, Then Calibrate</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-early-stopping-refine-then</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning classifiers often produce probabilistic predictions that are critical for accurate and interpretable decision-making in various domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-early-stopping-refine-then</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoding-based Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-based-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models have recently been shown capable of performing regression tasks wherein numeric predictions are represented as decoded strings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-based-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>s1: Simple test-time scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s1-simple-test-time-scaling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After supervised finetuning the Qwen2. 5-32B-Instruct language model on s1K and equipping it with budget forcing, our model s1-32B exceeds o1-preview on competition math questions by up to 27% (MATH and AIME24).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s1-simple-test-time-scaling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantastic Targets for Concept Erasure in Diffusion Models and Where To Find Them</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fantastic-targets-for-concept-erasure-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we model the concept space as a graph and empirically analyze the effects of erasing one concept on the remaining concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fantastic-targets-for-concept-erasure-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KBQA-o1: Agentic Knowledge Base Question Answering with Monte Carlo Tree Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kbqa-o1-agentic-knowledge-base-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, it employs MCTS, a heuristic search method driven by policy and reward models, to balance agentic exploration's performance and search space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kbqa-o1-agentic-knowledge-base-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Reasoning Gap: Small LLMs Can Plan with Generalised Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-reasoning-gap-small-llms-can</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our empirical results from planning and mathematical reasoning tasks demonstrate that these methods improve the performance of less resource-intensive LLMs to levels comparable with their more resource-intensive counterparts, at a fraction of the cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-reasoning-gap-small-llms-can</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$\infty$-Video: A Training-Free Approach to Long Video Understanding via Continuous-Time Memory Consolidation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infty-video-a-training-free-approach-to-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current video-language models struggle with long-video understanding due to limited context lengths and reliance on sparse frame subsampling, often leading to information loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infty-video-a-training-free-approach-to-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context Matters: Query-aware Dynamic Long Sequence Modeling of Gigapixel Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-matters-query-aware-dynamic-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Whole slide image (WSI) analysis presents significant computational challenges due to the massive number of patches in gigapixel images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-matters-query-aware-dynamic-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distorting Embedding Space for Safety: A Defense Mechanism for Adversarially Robust Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distorting-embedding-space-for-safety-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DES transforms unsafe embeddings, extracted from a text encoder using unsafe prompts, toward carefully calculated safe embedding regions to prevent unsafe contents generation, while reproducing the original safe embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distorting-embedding-space-for-safety-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIGNO: A Graph-based framework for robust and accurate operator learning for PDEs on arbitrary domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rigno-a-graph-based-framework-for-robust-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model, termed RIGNO, is tested on a challenging suite of benchmarks, composed of various time-dependent and steady PDEs defined on a diverse set of domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rigno-a-graph-based-framework-for-robust-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond checkmate: exploring the creative chokepoints in AI text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-checkmate-exploring-the-creative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have revolutionized Natural Language Processing (NLP) and Artificial Intelligence (AI), unlocking unprecedented capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-checkmate-exploring-the-creative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabFSBench: Tabular Benchmark for Feature Shifts in Open Environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabfsbench-tabular-benchmark-for-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TabFSBench evaluates impacts of four distinct feature-shift scenarios on four tabular model categories across various datasets and assesses the performance of large language models (LLMs) and tabular LLMs in the tabular benchmark for the first time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabfsbench-tabular-benchmark-for-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Impact of Noise in Differentially Private Text Rewriting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-impact-of-noise-in-differentially</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of text privatization often leverages the notion of $\textit{Differential Privacy}$ (DP) to provide formal guarantees in the rewriting or obfuscation of sensitive textual data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-impact-of-noise-in-differentially</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Quadratic Feature Analysis: An Information Geometry Approach to Dimensionality Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-quadratic-feature-analysis-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we present Supervised Quadratic Feature Analysis (SQFA), a dimensionality reduction method for learning linear features that maximize the differences between class-conditional first- and second-order statistics, which allow for quadratic discrimination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-quadratic-feature-analysis-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transcoders Beat Sparse Autoencoders for Interpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transcoders-beat-sparse-autoencoders-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse autoencoders (SAEs) extract human-interpretable features from deep neural networks by transforming their activations into a sparse, higher dimensional latent space, and then reconstructing the activations from these latents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transcoders-beat-sparse-autoencoders-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPO-VAE: Modeling Explainable Gene Perturbation Responses utilizing GRN-Aligned Parameter Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpo-vae-modeling-explainable-gene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the most effective ways to achieve explainability is incorporating the concept of gene regulatory networks (GRNs) in designing deep learning models such as VAEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpo-vae-modeling-explainable-gene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partially Rewriting a Transformer in Natural Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partially-rewriting-a-transformer-in-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first approximate one of the feedforward networks in the LLM with a wider MLP with sparsely activating neurons - a transcoder - and use an automated interpretability pipeline to generate explanations for these neurons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partially-rewriting-a-transformer-in-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GestureLSM: Latent Shortcut based Co-Speech Gesture Generation with Spatial-Temporal Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gesturelsm-latent-shortcut-based-co-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive quantitative and qualitative experiments demonstrate the effectiveness of GestureLSM, showcasing its potential for various applications in the development of digital humans and embodied agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gesturelsm-latent-shortcut-based-co-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiDAR Loop Closure Detection using Semantic Graphs with Graph Attention Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidar-loop-closure-detection-using-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel loop closure detection algorithm that uses graph attention neural networks to encode semantic graphs to perform place recognition and then use semantic registration to estimate the 6 DoF relative pose constraint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidar-loop-closure-detection-using-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concept Steerers: Leveraging K-Sparse Autoencoders for Controllable Generations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-steerers-leveraging-k-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the remarkable progress in text-to-image generative models, they are prone to adversarial attacks and inadvertently generate unsafe, unethical content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-steerers-leveraging-k-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XRF V2: A Dataset for Action Summarization with Wi-Fi Signals, and IMUs in Phones, Watches, Earbuds, and Glasses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xrf-v2-a-dataset-for-action-summarization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human Action Recognition (HAR) plays a crucial role in applications such as health monitoring, smart home automation, and human-computer interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xrf-v2-a-dataset-for-action-summarization</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
