<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 09:15:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Generative AI for Banks: Benchmarks and Algorithms for Synthetic Financial Transaction Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-ai-for-banks-benchmarks-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The banking sector faces challenges in using deep learning due to data sensitivity and regulatory constraints, but generative AI may offer a solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-ai-for-banks-benchmarks-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stack Trace Deduplication: Faster, More Accurately, and in More Realistic Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stack-trace-deduplication-faster-more</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model consists of two parts - (1) an embedding model with byte-pair encoding and approximate nearest neighbor search to quickly find the most relevant stack traces to the incoming one, and (2) a reranker that re-ranks the most fitting stack traces, taking into account the repeated frames between them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stack-trace-deduplication-faster-more</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffSim: Taming Diffusion Models for Evaluating Visual Similarity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffsim-taming-diffusion-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have fundamentally transformed the field of generative models, making the assessment of similarity between customized model outputs and reference inputs critically important.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffsim-taming-diffusion-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOMG-Bench: Evaluating LLMs on Text-based Open Molecule Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tomg-bench-evaluating-llms-on-text-based-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Text-based Open Molecule Generation Benchmark (TOMG-Bench), the first benchmark to evaluate the open-domain molecule generation capability of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tomg-bench-evaluating-llms-on-text-based-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlowAR: Scale-wise Autoregressive Image Generation Meets Flow Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowar-scale-wise-autoregressive-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, in image generation, VAR proposes scale-wise autoregressive modeling, which extends the next token prediction to the next scale prediction, preserving the 2D structure of images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowar-scale-wise-autoregressive-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReMoE: Fully Differentiable Mixture-of-Experts with ReLU Routing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remoe-fully-differentiable-mixture-of-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparsely activated Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) models are widely adopted to scale up model capacity without increasing the computation budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remoe-fully-differentiable-mixture-of-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Downscaling Precipitation with Bias-informed Conditional Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/downscaling-precipitation-with-bias-informed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a bias-informed conditional diffusion model for statistical downscaling of precipitation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/downscaling-precipitation-with-bias-informed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistent Human Image and Video Generation with Spatially Conditioned Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistent-human-image-and-video-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By fine-tuning existing base diffusion models on human video data, our method demonstrates strong generalization to unseen human identities and poses without requiring additional per-instance fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistent-human-image-and-video-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Spectral Calibration of Hyperspectral Images:Method, Dataset and Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-spectral-calibration-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Usually, HSI needs to be calibrated to minimize the impact of various illumination conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-spectral-calibration-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Constraint Models in Constraint Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-constraint-models-in-constraint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we address this limitation by proposing GenCon, a novel approach to learn parameterized constraint models capable of modeling varying instances of the same problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-constraint-models-in-constraint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preventing Local Pitfalls in Vector Quantization via Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preventing-local-pitfalls-in-vector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vector-quantized networks (VQNs) have exhibited remarkable performance across various tasks, yet they are prone to training instability, which complicates the training process due to the necessity for techniques such as subtle initialization and model distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preventing-local-pitfalls-in-vector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PC-BEV: An Efficient Polar-Cartesian BEV Fusion Framework for LiDAR Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pc-bev-an-efficient-polar-cartesian-bev</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive evaluation on the SemanticKITTI and nuScenes datasets provides compelling evidence that our method outperforms previous multiview fusion approaches in terms of both performance and inference speed, highlighting the potential of BEV-based fusion for LiDAR segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pc-bev-an-efficient-polar-cartesian-bev</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DS$^2$-ABSA: Dual-Stream Data Synthesis with Label Refinement for Few-Shot Aspect-Based Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ds-2-absa-dual-stream-data-synthesis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In few-shot aspect-based sentiment analysis (ABSA), previous efforts have explored data augmentation techniques, which prompt LLMs to generate new samples by modifying existing ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ds-2-absa-dual-stream-data-synthesis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling Uncertainty: A Deep Dive into Calibration and Performance of Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-uncertainty-a-deep-dive-into</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates representative MLLMs, focusing on their calibration across various scenarios, including before and after visual fine-tuning, as well as before and after multimodal training of the base LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-uncertainty-a-deep-dive-into</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head and Neck Tumor Segmentation of MRI from Pre- and Mid-radiotherapy with Pre-training, Data Augmentation and Dual Flow UNet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/head-and-neck-tumor-segmentation-of-mri-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Head and neck tumors and metastatic lymph nodes are crucial for treatment planning and prognostic analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/head-and-neck-tumor-segmentation-of-mri-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Associative memory inspires improvements for in-context learning using a novel attention residual stream architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/associative-memory-inspires-improvements-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) demonstrate an impressive ability to utilise information within the context of their input sequences to appropriately respond to data unseen by the LLM during its training procedure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/associative-memory-inspires-improvements-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORBIT: Cost-Effective Dataset Curation for Large Language Model Domain Adaptation with an Astronomy Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orbit-cost-effective-dataset-curation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in language modeling demonstrate the need for high-quality domain-specific training data, especially for tasks that require specialized knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orbit-cost-effective-dataset-curation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RobustFT: Robust Supervised Fine-tuning for Large Language Models under Noisy Response</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustft-robust-supervised-fine-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Supervised fine-tuning (SFT) plays a crucial role in adapting large language models (LLMs) to specific domains or tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustft-robust-supervised-fine-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-Structured Topic Modeling for Documents with Spatial or Covariate Dependencies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-structured-topic-modeling-for-documents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the challenge of incorporating document-level metadata into topic modeling to improve topic mixture estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-structured-topic-modeling-for-documents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent-SafetyBench: Evaluating the Safety of LLM Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-safetybench-evaluating-the-safety-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the absence of comprehensive benchmarks for evaluating agent safety presents a significant barrier to effective assessment and further improvement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-safetybench-evaluating-the-safety-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cal-DPO: Calibrated Direct Preference Optimization for Language Model Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cal-dpo-calibrated-direct-preference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive preference optimization has shown promising results in aligning LLMs with available preference data by optimizing the implicit reward associated with the policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cal-dpo-calibrated-direct-preference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sliding Windows Are Not the End: Exploring Full Ranking with Long-Context Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliding-windows-are-not-the-end-exploring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we identify two limitations of fine-tuning the full ranking model based on existing methods: (1) sliding window strategy fails to produce a full ranking list as a training label, and (2) the language modeling loss cannot emphasize top-ranked passage IDs in the label.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliding-windows-are-not-the-end-exploring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PA-RAG: RAG Alignment via Multi-Perspective Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pa-rag-rag-alignment-via-multi-perspective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emergence of Retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) has alleviated the issues of outdated and hallucinatory content in the generation of large language models (LLMs), yet it still reveals numerous limitations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pa-rag-rag-alignment-via-multi-perspective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLDG: Contrastive Learning on Dynamic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cldg-contrastive-learning-on-dynamic-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The graph with complex annotations is the most potent data type, whose constantly evolving motivates further exploration of the unsupervised dynamic graph representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cldg-contrastive-learning-on-dynamic-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsyDraw: A Multi-Agent Multimodal System for Mental Health Screening in Left-Behind Children</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psydraw-a-multi-agent-multimodal-system-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Left-behind children (LBCs), numbering over 66 million in China, face severe mental health challenges due to parental migration for work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psydraw-a-multi-agent-multimodal-system-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pitfalls of topology-aware image segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pitfalls-of-topology-aware-image-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topological correctness, i. e., the preservation of structural integrity and specific characteristics of shape, is a fundamental requirement for medical imaging tasks, such as neuron or vessel segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pitfalls-of-topology-aware-image-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FROC: Building Fair ROC from a Trained Classifier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/froc-building-fair-roc-from-a-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the proposed query model, we provide a rigorous theoretical analysis of the minimal AUC loss to achieve $\varepsilon_1$-Equalized ROC.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/froc-building-fair-roc-from-a-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entropy Regularized Task Representation Learning for Offline Meta-Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropy-regularized-task-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Context-based approaches utilize a history of state-action-reward transitions -- referred to as the context -- to infer representations of the current task, and then condition the agent, i. e., the policy and value function, on the task representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropy-regularized-task-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototypical Calibrating Ambiguous Samples for Micro-Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-calibrating-ambiguous-samples</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we propose a new prototypical diversity amplification loss to strengthen the model's capacity by amplifying the differences between different prototypes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-calibrating-ambiguous-samples</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promptable Representation Distribution Learning and Data Augmentation for Gigapixel Histopathology WSI Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptable-representation-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gigapixel image analysis, particularly for whole slide images (WSIs), often relies on multiple instance learning (MIL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptable-representation-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Self-Supervised Video Hashing with Selective State Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-self-supervised-video-hashing-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce S5VH, a Mamba-based video hashing model with an improved self-supervised learning paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-self-supervised-video-hashing-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alignment-Free RGB-T Salient Object Detection: A Large-scale Dataset and Progressive Correlation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignment-free-rgb-t-salient-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Alignment-free RGB-Thermal (RGB-T) salient object detection (SOD) aims to achieve robust performance in complex scenes by directly leveraging the complementary information from unaligned visible-thermal image pairs, without requiring manual alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignment-free-rgb-t-salient-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affordance-Aware Object Insertion via Mask-Aware Dual Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affordance-aware-object-insertion-via-mask</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a common image editing operation, image composition involves integrating foreground objects into background scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affordance-aware-object-insertion-via-mask</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Sensor Object Anomaly Detection: Unifying Appearance, Geometry, and Internal Properties</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-sensor-object-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object anomaly detection is essential for industrial quality inspection, yet traditional single-sensor methods face critical limitations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-sensor-object-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face the Facts! Evaluating RAG-based Fact-checking Pipelines in Realistic Settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-the-facts-evaluating-rag-based-fact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Natural Language Processing and Generation systems have recently shown the potential to complement and streamline the costly and time-consuming job of professional fact-checkers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-the-facts-evaluating-rag-based-fact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeviTor: 3D Trajectory Oriented Image-to-Video Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/levitor-3d-trajectory-oriented-image-to-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The intuitive nature of drag-based interaction has led to its growing adoption for controlling object trajectories in image-to-video synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/levitor-3d-trajectory-oriented-image-to-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Distillation in RNN-Attention Models for Early Prediction of Student Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-distillation-in-rnn-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Early prediction for identifying at-risk students is a crucial and widely researched topic in EDM research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-distillation-in-rnn-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCTdiff: Intriguing Properties of Image Generative Modeling in the DCT Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dctdiff-intriguing-properties-of-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The effectiveness of DCTdiff and the introduced properties suggest a promising direction for image modeling in the frequency space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dctdiff-intriguing-properties-of-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Use of Deep Learning Models for Semantic Clone Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-of-deep-learning-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several deep learning-based clone detection models have appeared in the literature for detecting syntactic and semantic clones, widely evaluated with the BigCloneBench dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-of-deep-learning-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TDCNet: Transparent Objects Depth Completion with CNN-Transformer Dual-Branch Parallel Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tdcnet-transparent-objects-depth-completion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The sensing and manipulation of transparent objects present a critical challenge in industrial and laboratory robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tdcnet-transparent-objects-depth-completion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Image Restoration and Enhancement: Degradation Calibrated Cycle Reconstruction Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-image-restoration-and-enhancement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image restoration and enhancement are pivotal for numerous computer vision applications, yet unifying these tasks efficiently remains a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-image-restoration-and-enhancement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt-A-Video: Prompt Your Video Diffusion Model via Preference-Aligned LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-a-video-prompt-your-video-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-video models have made remarkable advancements through optimization on high-quality text-video pairs, where the textual prompts play a pivotal role in determining quality of output videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-a-video-prompt-your-video-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClusterTalk: Corpus Exploration Framework using Multi-Dimensional Exploratory Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clustertalk-corpus-exploration-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Exploratory search of large text corpora is essential in domains like biomedical research, where large amounts of research literature are continuously generated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clustertalk-corpus-exploration-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lorentzian Residual Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lorentzian-residual-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperbolic neural networks have emerged as a powerful tool for modeling hierarchical data structures prevalent in real-world datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lorentzian-residual-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhotoHolmes: a Python library for forgery detection in digital images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/photoholmes-a-python-library-for-forgery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce PhotoHolmes, an open-source Python library designed to easily run and benchmark forgery detection methods on digital images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/photoholmes-a-python-library-for-forgery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAE-T: A Channelwise AutoEncoder with Transformer for EEG Abnormality Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cae-t-a-channelwise-autoencoder-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Electroencephalogram (EEG) signals are critical for detecting abnormal brain activity, but their high dimensionality and complexity pose significant challenges for effective analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cae-t-a-channelwise-autoencoder-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cirbo: A New Tool for Boolean Circuit Analysis and Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cirbo-a-new-tool-for-boolean-circuit-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an open-source tool for manipulating Boolean circuits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cirbo-a-new-tool-for-boolean-circuit-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ResoFilter: Rine-grained Synthetic Data Filtering for Large Language Models through Data-Parameter Resonance Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resofilter-rine-grained-synthetic-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose ResoFilter, a novel method that integrates models, data, and tasks to refine datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resofilter-rine-grained-synthetic-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RefHCM: A Unified Model for Referring Perceptions in Human-Centric Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refhcm-a-unified-model-for-referring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human-centric perceptions play a crucial role in real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refhcm-a-unified-model-for-referring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Successive optimization of optics and post-processing with differentiable coherent PSF operator and field information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/successive-optimization-of-optics-and-post</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This joint optimization pipeline offers innovative insights into the practical design of sophisticated optical systems and post-processing algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/successive-optimization-of-optics-and-post</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
