<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 21:10:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mixture of Attention Heads: Selecting Attention Heads Per Token</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-attention-heads-selecting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes the Mixture of Attention Heads (MoA), a new architecture that combines multi-head attention with the MoE mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-attention-heads-selecting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Kernel-Based View of Language Model Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-kernel-based-view-of-language-model-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It has become standard to solve NLP tasks by fine-tuning pre-trained language models (LMs), especially in low-data settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-kernel-based-view-of-language-model-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Causal Effects from Sets of Interventions in the Presence of Unobserved Confounders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-causal-effects-from-sets-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address this challenge by aiming to learn the effect of a single-intervention from both observational data and sets of interventions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-causal-effects-from-sets-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregating Layers for Deepfake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aggregating-layers-for-deepfake-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Crucially, most work in this domain assume that the Deepfakes in the test set come from the same Deepfake algorithms that were used for training the network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aggregating-layers-for-deepfake-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAgNet: Mesh Agnostic Neural PDE Solver</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magnet-mesh-agnostic-neural-pde-solver</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The computational complexity of classical numerical methods for solving Partial Differential Equations (PDE) scales significantly as the resolution increases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magnet-mesh-agnostic-neural-pde-solver</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreGAN: Exploiting Frequency Components for Training GANs under Limited Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fregan-exploiting-frequency-components-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training GANs under limited data often leads to discriminator overfitting and memorization issues, causing divergent training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fregan-exploiting-frequency-components-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map-free Visual Relocalization: Metric Pose Relative to a Single Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-free-visual-relocalization-metric-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Can we relocalize in a scene represented by a single reference image?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-free-visual-relocalization-metric-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighbourhood Representative Sampling for Efficient End-to-end Video Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neighbourhood-representative-sampling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, existing practices, such as resizing and cropping, will change the quality of original videos due to the loss of details and contents, and are therefore harmful to quality assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neighbourhood-representative-sampling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCL-Net: Deep Correspondence Learning Network for 6D Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcl-net-deep-correspondence-learning-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Establishment of point correspondence between camera and object coordinate systems is a promising way to solve 6D object poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcl-net-deep-correspondence-learning-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capturing Global Structural Information in Long Document Question Answering with Compressive Graph Selector Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/capturing-global-structural-information-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the proposed model consists of three modules: local graph network, global graph network and evidence memory network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/capturing-global-structural-information-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oflib: Facilitating Operations with and on Optical Flow Fields in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oflib-facilitating-operations-with-and-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a robust theoretical framework for the characterisation and manipulation of optical flow, i. e 2D vector fields, in the context of their use in motion estimation algorithms and beyond.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oflib-facilitating-operations-with-and-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ME-D2N: Multi-Expert Domain Decompositional Network for Cross-Domain Few-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/me-d2n-multi-expert-domain-decompositional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, to solve the data imbalance problem between the source data with sufficient examples and the auxiliary target data with limited examples, we build our model under the umbrella of multi-expert learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/me-d2n-multi-expert-domain-decompositional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Sharpness-Aware Minimization with Fisher Mask for Better Generalization on Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-sharpness-aware-minimization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning large pretrained language models on a limited training corpus usually suffers from poor generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-sharpness-aware-minimization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EOCSA: Predicting Prognosis of Epithelial Ovarian Cancer with Whole Slide Histopathological Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eocsa-predicting-prognosis-of-epithelial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, we developed a survival prediction model, named DeepConvAttentionSurv (DCAS), which was able to extract patch-level features, removed less discriminative clusters and predicted the EOC survival precisely.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eocsa-predicting-prognosis-of-epithelial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cluster-level pseudo-labelling for source-free cross-domain facial expression recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-level-pseudo-labelling-for-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatically understanding emotions from visual data is a fundamental task for human behaviour understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-level-pseudo-labelling-for-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAE: Fine-Grained Controllable Story Generation with Characters, Actions and Emotions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chae-fine-grained-controllable-story</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Story generation has emerged as an interesting yet challenging NLP task in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chae-fine-grained-controllable-story</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VER: Scaling On-Policy RL Leads to the Emergence of Navigation in Embodied Rearrangement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ver-scaling-on-policy-rl-leads-to-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the Pick skill involves a robot picking an object from a table.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ver-scaling-on-policy-rl-leads-to-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTet: Multi-domain Translation for English and Vietnamese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtet-multi-domain-translation-for-english-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce MTet, the largest publicly available parallel corpus for English-Vietnamese translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtet-multi-domain-translation-for-english-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entity Disambiguation with Entity Definitions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entity-disambiguation-with-entity-definitions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Local models have recently attained astounding performances in Entity Disambiguation (ED), with generative and extractive formulations being the most promising research directions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entity-disambiguation-with-entity-definitions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APSNet: Attention Based Point Cloud Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apsnet-attention-based-point-cloud-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional task-agnostic sampling methods, such as farthest point sampling (FPS), do not consider downstream tasks when sampling point clouds, and thus non-informative points to the tasks are often sampled.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apsnet-attention-based-point-cloud-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does a deep neural network confidently perceive? The effective dimension of high certainty class manifolds and their low confidence boundaries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-does-a-deep-neural-network-confidently</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural network classifiers partition input space into high confidence regions for each class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-does-a-deep-neural-network-confidently</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IsoVec: Controlling the Relative Isomorphism of Word Embedding Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isovec-controlling-the-relative-isomorphism</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to extract high-quality translation dictionaries from monolingual word embedding spaces depends critically on the geometric similarity of the spaces -- their degree of "isomorphism."]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isovec-controlling-the-relative-isomorphism</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Failure of Batch Normalization for Transformers in NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-failure-of-batch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Batch Normalization (BN) is a core and prevalent technique in accelerating the training of deep neural networks and improving the generalization on Computer Vision (CV) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-failure-of-batch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAN You Hear Me? Reclaiming Unconditional Speech Synthesis from Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gan-you-hear-me-reclaiming-unconditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As in the StyleGAN family of image synthesis models, ASGAN maps sampled noise to a disentangled latent vector which is then mapped to a sequence of audio features so that signal aliasing is suppressed at every layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gan-you-hear-me-reclaiming-unconditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Win-win Deal: Towards Sparse and Robust Pre-trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-win-win-deal-towards-sparse-and-robust-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response to the efficiency problem, recent studies show that dense PLMs can be replaced with sparse subnetworks without hurting the performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-win-win-deal-towards-sparse-and-robust-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Long-tailed Object Detection with Image-Level Supervision by Multi-Task Collaborative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-long-tailed-object-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, there are an object detection task (consisting of an instance-classification task and a localization task) and an image-classification task in our framework, responsible for utilizing the two types of supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-long-tailed-object-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Equalization Losses: Gradient-Driven Training for Long-tailed Object Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-equalization-losses-gradient-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long-tail distribution is widely spread in real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-equalization-losses-gradient-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Spectral Filter Memory Network for Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-spectral-filter-memory-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, we empirically find low frequency feature should be enhanced in encoder (backbone) while high frequency for decoder (segmentation head).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-spectral-filter-memory-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototypical VoteNet for Few-Shot 3D Point Cloud Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-votenet-for-few-shot-3d-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing 3D point cloud object detection approaches heavily rely on large amounts of labeled training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-votenet-for-few-shot-3d-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Segmentation under Adverse Conditions: A Weather and Nighttime-aware Synthetic Data-based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-segmentation-under-adverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent semantic segmentation models perform well under standard weather conditions and sufficient illumination but struggle with adverse weather conditions and nighttime.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-segmentation-under-adverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained Image Style Transfer with Visual Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-image-style-transfer-with-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such a design usually destroys the spatial information of the input images and fails to transfer fine-grained style patterns into style transfer results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-image-style-transfer-with-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Embodied Reference with Touch-Line Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-embodied-reference-with-touch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human studies have revealed that objects referred to or pointed to do not lie on the elbow-wrist line, a common misconception; instead, they lie on the so-called virtual touch line.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-embodied-reference-with-touch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point Transformer V2: Grouped Vector Attention and Partition-based Pooling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-transformer-v2-grouped-vector-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we analyze the limitations of the Point Transformer and propose our powerful and efficient Point Transformer V2 model with novel designs that overcome the limitations of previous work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-transformer-v2-grouped-vector-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factors of Influence of the Overestimation Bias of Q-Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factors-of-influence-of-the-overestimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study whether the learning rate $\alpha$, the discount factor $\gamma$ and the reward signal $r$ have an influence on the overestimation bias of the Q-Learning algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factors-of-influence-of-the-overestimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConserWeightive Behavioral Cloning for Reliable Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conserweightive-behavioral-cloning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Behavioral cloning (BC) provides a straightforward solution to offline RL by mimicking offline trajectories via supervised learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conserweightive-behavioral-cloning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPERA: Omni-Supervised Representation Learning with Hierarchical Supervisions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opera-omni-supervised-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pretrain-finetune paradigm in modern computer vision facilitates the success of self-supervised learning, which tends to achieve better transferability than supervised learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opera-omni-supervised-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intrinsic Dimension for Large-Scale Geometric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsic-dimension-for-large-scale-geometric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the present work, we derive a computationally feasible method for determining said axiomatic ID functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsic-dimension-for-large-scale-geometric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARF: Two-level Attention-based Random Forests with a Mixture of Contamination Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/larf-two-level-attention-based-random-forests</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first idea behind the models is to introduce a two-level attention, where one of the levels is the "leaf" attention and the attention mechanism is applied to every leaf of trees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/larf-two-level-attention-based-random-forests</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PatternRank: Leveraging Pretrained Language Models and Part of Speech for Unsupervised Keyphrase Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patternrank-leveraging-pretrained-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Keyphrase extraction is the process of automatically selecting a small set of most relevant phrases from a given text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patternrank-leveraging-pretrained-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed-modality Representation Learning and Pre-training for Joint Table-and-Text Retrieval in OpenQA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-modality-representation-learning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, training an effective dense table-text retriever is difficult due to the challenges of table-text discrepancy and data sparsity problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-modality-representation-learning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Sharpness-Aware Minimization Stronger: A Sparsified Perturbation Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-sharpness-aware-minimization-stronger-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the popular solutions is Sharpness-Aware Minimization (SAM), which smooths the loss landscape via minimizing the maximized change of training loss when adding a perturbation to the weight.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-sharpness-aware-minimization-stronger-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Scrambling Phenomena for Randomly Initialized Recurrent Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-scrambling-phenomena-for-randomly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recurrent Neural Networks (RNNs) frequently exhibit complicated dynamics, and their sensitivity to the initialization process often renders them notoriously hard to train.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-scrambling-phenomena-for-randomly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A General Learning Framework for Open Ad Hoc Teamwork Using Graph-based Policy Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-learning-framework-for-open-ad-hoc</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These belief estimates are combined with our solution for the fully observable case to compute an agent's optimal policy under partial observability in open ad hoc teamwork.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-learning-framework-for-open-ad-hoc</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance Regularization for Discriminative Language Model Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-regularization-for-discriminative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[They treat training instances equally throughout the training process, with little attention on the individual contribution of those instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-regularization-for-discriminative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Interpolation of Contextualized Term-based Ranking with BM25 for Query-by-Example Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-interpolation-of-contextualized-term</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we examine the generalizability of two of these deep contextualized term-based models in the context of query-by-example (QBE) retrieval in which a seed document acts as the query to find relevant documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-interpolation-of-contextualized-term</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUE: Pretrained Model and Dataset for Understanding Hanja Documents of Ancient Korea</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hue-pretrained-model-and-dataset-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Historical records in Korea before the 20th century were primarily written in Hanja, an extinct language based on Chinese characters and not understood by modern Korean or Chinese speakers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hue-pretrained-model-and-dataset-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CD-FSOD: A Benchmark for Cross-domain Few-shot Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cd-fsod-a-benchmark-for-cross-domain-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although few-shot object detection (FSOD) has attracted great research attention, no work yet exists that studies FSOD across the different domains seen in real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cd-fsod-a-benchmark-for-cross-domain-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InQMAD: Incremental Quantum Measurement Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inqmad-incremental-quantum-measurement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art flow anomaly detection methods rely on fixed memory using hash functions or nearest neighbors that may not be able to constrain high-frequency values as in a moving average or remove seamless outliers and cannot be trained in an end-to-end deep learning architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inqmad-incremental-quantum-measurement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIGAT: Modeling News Recommendation with Dual-Graph Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/digat-modeling-news-recommendation-with-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, existing graph-based NR methods are promising but lack effective news-user feature interaction, rendering the graph-based recommendation suboptimal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/digat-modeling-news-recommendation-with-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion Aware Self-Supervision for Generic Event Boundary Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-aware-self-supervision-for-generic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address this issue by revisiting a simple and effective self-supervised method and augment it with a differentiable motion feature learning module to tackle the spatial and temporal diversities in the GEBD task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-aware-self-supervision-for-generic</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
