<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 21:08:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Arabic Sentiment Analysis: ArSen Benchmark and the Improved Fuzzy Deep Hybrid Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-arabic-sentiment-analysis-arsen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sentiment analysis is pivotal in Natural Language Processing for understanding opinions and emotions in text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-arabic-sentiment-analysis-arsen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Hybrid Artificial Intelligence System for Automated EEG Background Analysis and Report Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-artificial-intelligence-system-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study proposes an innovative hybrid artificial intelligence (AI) system for automatic interpretation of EEG background activity and report generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-artificial-intelligence-system-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number it: Temporal Grounding Videos like Flipping Manga</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/number-it-temporal-grounding-videos-like</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video Large Language Models (Vid-LLMs) have made remarkable advancements in comprehending video content for QA dialogue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/number-it-temporal-grounding-videos-like</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Creativity and Deception in Large Language Models: A Simulation Framework for Multi-Agent Balderdash</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-creativity-and-deception-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a simulation framework utilizing the game Balderdash to evaluate both the creativity and logical reasoning of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-creativity-and-deception-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScribbleVS: Scribble-Supervised Medical Image Segmentation via Dynamic Competitive Pseudo Label Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scribblevs-scribble-supervised-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In clinical medicine, precise image segmentation can provide substantial support to clinicians.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scribblevs-scribble-supervised-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dawn of GUI Agent: A Preliminary Case Study with Claude 3.5 Computer Use</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dawn-of-gui-agent-a-preliminary-case</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recently released model, Claude 3. 5 Computer Use, stands out as the first frontier AI model to offer computer use in public beta as a graphical user interface (GUI) agent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dawn-of-gui-agent-a-preliminary-case</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step-wise Distribution Alignment Guided Style Prompt Tuning for Source-free Cross-domain Few-shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/step-wise-distribution-alignment-guided-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the source-free CDFSL (SF-CDFSL) problem, tackling few-shot learning (FSL) in the target domain using only pre-trained models and a few target samples without source data or strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/step-wise-distribution-alignment-guided-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mmSpyVR: Exploiting mmWave Radar for Penetrating Obstacles to Uncover Privacy Vulnerability of Virtual Reality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmspyvr-exploiting-mmwave-radar-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The mmSpyVR demonstrates the capability to extract critical VR privacy from the mmWave signals that have penetrated through obstacles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmspyvr-exploiting-mmwave-radar-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modification Takes Courage: Seamless Image Stitching via Reference-Driven Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modification-takes-courage-seamless-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current image stitching methods often produce noticeable seams in challenging scenarios such as uneven hue and large parallax.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modification-takes-courage-seamless-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GGAvatar: Reconstructing Garment-Separated 3D Gaussian Splatting Avatars from Monocular Video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ggavatar-reconstructing-garment-separated-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Avatar modelling has broad applications in human animation and virtual try-ons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ggavatar-reconstructing-garment-separated-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partial Scene Text Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-scene-text-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a Ranking MIL (RankMIL) approach to adaptively filter those noisy samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-scene-text-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing the Evolution of Order in Materials Microstructures Using Multi-Modal Computer Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-the-evolution-of-order-in-materials</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of high-performance materials for microelectronics, energy storage, and extreme environments depends on our ability to describe and direct property-defining microstructural order.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-the-evolution-of-order-in-materials</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Sycophancy in Decoder-Only Transformer Architectures: Synthetic Data Intervention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-sycophancy-in-decoder-only</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the sycophancy problem caused by reinforcement learning from human feedback in large language models, this research applies synthetic data intervention technology to the decoder-only transformer architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-sycophancy-in-decoder-only</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEAGULL: No-reference Image Quality Assessment for Regions of Interest via Vision-Language Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seagull-no-reference-image-quality-assessment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The quality analysis of ROIs can provide fine-grained guidance for image quality improvement and is crucial for scenarios focusing on region-level quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seagull-no-reference-image-quality-assessment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M3TR: Generalist HD Map Construction with Variable Map Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3tr-generalist-hd-map-construction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address shortcomings in ground truth generation for Argoverse 2 and nuScenes and propose the first realistic scenarios with semantically diverse map priors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3tr-generalist-hd-map-construction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCL: Multi-view Enhanced Contrastive Learning for Chest X-ray Report Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcl-multi-view-enhanced-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Radiology reports are crucial for planning treatment strategies and enhancing doctor-patient communication, yet manually writing these reports is burdensome for radiologists.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcl-multi-view-enhanced-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Algorithms to Assess Site Closure Time Frames for Soil and Groundwater Contamination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-algorithms-to-assess-site</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monitored Natural Attenuation (MNA) is gaining prominence as an effective method for managing soil and groundwater contamination due to its cost-efficiency and minimal environmental disruption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-algorithms-to-assess-site</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xmodel-1.5: An 1B-scale Multilingual LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xmodel-1-5-an-1b-scale-multilingual-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Xmodel-1. 5, a novel 1-billion-parameter multilingual large model pretrained on approximately 2 trillion tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xmodel-1-5-an-1b-scale-multilingual-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Causal Effects in a Nonlinear World: the Good, the Bad, and the Ugly</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-causal-effects-in-a-nonlinear-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applied macroeconomists frequently use impulse response estimators motivated by linear models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-causal-effects-in-a-nonlinear-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4DPV: 4D Pet from Videos by Coarse-to-Fine Non-Rigid Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4dpv-4d-pet-from-videos-by-coarse-to-fine-non</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a coarse-to-fine neural deformation model to simultaneously recover the camera pose and the 4D reconstruction of an unknown object from multiple RGB sequences in the wild.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4dpv-4d-pet-from-videos-by-coarse-to-fine-non</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Domain Generalization via Prompt Learning and Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-domain-generalization-via-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a novel FedDG framework through Prompt Learning and AggregatioN (PLAN), which comprises two training stages to collaboratively generate local prompts and global prompts at each federated round.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-domain-generalization-via-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Height Estimation Using Shadow Length in Satellite Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-height-estimation-using-shadow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We addressed this issue by using shadow length as an additional cue to compensate for the loss of building height estimation using single-view imagery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-height-estimation-using-shadow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing Reasoning Costs - The Path of Optimization for Chain of Thought via Sparse Attention Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-reasoning-costs-the-path-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to address the chain of thought in the large language model inference cost surge, this research proposes to use a sparse attention mechanism that only focuses on a few relevant tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-reasoning-costs-the-path-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DROJ: A Prompt-Driven Attack against Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/droj-a-prompt-driven-attack-against-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we introduce a novel approach, Directed Rrepresentation Optimization Jailbreak (DROJ), which optimizes jailbreak prompts at the embedding level to shift the hidden representations of harmful queries towards directions that are more likely to elicit affirmative responses from the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/droj-a-prompt-driven-attack-against-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DTELS: Towards Dynamic Granularity of Timeline Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dtels-towards-dynamic-granularity-of-timeline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid proliferation of online news has posed significant challenges in tracking the continuous development of news topics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dtels-towards-dynamic-granularity-of-timeline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ModelPredictiveControl.jl: advanced process control made easy in Julia</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelpredictivecontrol-jl-advanced-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents ModelPredictiveControl. jl, an open-source software package for designing model predictive controllers in the Julia programming language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelpredictivecontrol-jl-advanced-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Fixed Watermark is Fragile: Towards Semantic-Aware Watermark for EaaS Copyright Protection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/your-fixed-watermark-is-fragile-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we reveal that previous watermarking schemes possess semantic-independent characteristics and propose the Semantic Perturbation Attack (SPA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/your-fixed-watermark-is-fragile-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravan MultiMet: Extending Caravan with Multiple Weather Nowcasts and Forecasts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caravan-multimet-extending-caravan-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Caravan large-sample hydrology dataset (Kratzert et al., 2023) was created to standardize and harmonize streamflow data from various regional datasets, combined with globally available meteorological forcing and catchment attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caravan-multimet-extending-caravan-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MFTIQ: Multi-Flow Tracker with Independent Matching Quality Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mftiq-multi-flow-tracker-with-independent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present MFTIQ, a novel dense long-term tracking model that advances the Multi-Flow Tracker (MFT) framework to address challenges in point-level visual tracking in video sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mftiq-multi-flow-tracker-with-independent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Adaptive Open-Source Dataset Generation Framework for Machine Learning Tasks in Logic Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-open-source-dataset-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces an adaptive logic synthesis dataset generation framework designed to enhance machine learning applications within the logic synthesis process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-open-source-dataset-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCAN: Bootstrapping Contrastive Pre-training for Data Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scan-bootstrapping-contrastive-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we individually pre-train seven CLIP models on two large-scale image-text pair datasets, and two MoCo models on the ImageNet dataset, resulting in a total of 16 pre-trained models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scan-bootstrapping-contrastive-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Matching Filtering and Refinement by Planes and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-matching-filtering-and-refinement-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a modular, non-deep learning method for filtering and refining sparse correspondences in image matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-matching-filtering-and-refinement-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINETRA: a Versatile Framework for Evaluating Single Neuron Tracking in Behaving Animals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sinetra-a-versatile-framework-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurately tracking neuronal activity in behaving animals presents significant challenges due to complex motions and background noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sinetra-a-versatile-framework-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The \emph{Optimist}: Towards Fully Automated Graph Theory Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-emph-optimist-towards-fully-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the \emph{Optimist}, an autonomous system developed to advance automated conjecture generation in graph theory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-emph-optimist-towards-fully-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Vision Foundation Models for High-Performance, Training-Free Open Vocabulary Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-vision-foundation-models-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce Trident, a training-free framework that first splices features extracted by CLIP and DINO from sub-images, then leverages SAM's encoder to create a correlation matrix for global aggregation, enabling a broadened receptive field for effective segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-vision-foundation-models-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heuristical Comparison of Vision Transformers Against Convolutional Neural Networks for Semantic Segmentation on Remote Sensing Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heuristical-comparison-of-vision-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper focuses on the heuristic comparison of three key factors of using (or not using) ViT for semantic segmentation of remote sensing aerial images on the iSAID.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heuristical-comparison-of-vision-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Deviation Learning for Visual Anomaly Detection with Data Contamination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-deviation-learning-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual anomaly detection targets to detect images that notably differ from normal pattern, and it has found extensive application in identifying defective parts within the manufacturing industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-deviation-learning-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEARD: Benchmarking the Adversarial Robustness for Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beard-benchmarking-the-adversarial-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dataset Distillation (DD) is an emerging technique that compresses large-scale datasets into significantly smaller synthesized datasets while preserving high test performance and enabling the efficient training of large models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beard-benchmarking-the-adversarial-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are nuclear masks all you need for improved out-of-domain generalisation? A closer look at cancer classification in histopathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-nuclear-masks-all-you-need-for-improved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain generalisation in computational histopathology is challenging because the images are substantially affected by differences among hospitals due to factors like fixation and staining of tissue and imaging equipment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-nuclear-masks-all-you-need-for-improved</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAHL: Domain-specific Automated Hallucination Evaluation of Long-Form Text through a Benchmark Dataset in Biomedicine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dahl-domain-specific-automated-hallucination</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce DAHL, a benchmark dataset and automated evaluation system designed to assess hallucination in long-form text generation, specifically within the biomedical domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dahl-domain-specific-automated-hallucination</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the "Heatmap + Monte Carlo Tree Search" Paradigm for Solving Large Scale TSP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-heatmap-monte-carlo-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Travelling Salesman Problem (TSP) remains a fundamental challenge in combinatorial optimization, inspiring diverse algorithmic strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-heatmap-monte-carlo-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TockyLocus: Quantitative Analysis Methods for Flow Cytometric Fluorescent Timer Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tockylocus-quantitative-analysis-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce rigorous algorithms for a data categorization method, designated as the Tocky locus approach, which uses normalized and trigonometric-transformed Fluorescent Timer data, suitable for quantitative analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tockylocus-quantitative-analysis-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneNet: A Channel-Wise 1D Convolutional U-Net</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onenet-a-channel-wise-1d-convolutional-u-net</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we explore a fully 1D encoder-decoder that achieves a 71% reduction in size, albeit with some accuracy loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onenet-a-channel-wise-1d-convolutional-u-net</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmark for Long-Form Medical Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-long-form-medical-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a lack of benchmarks for evaluating large language models (LLMs) in long-form medical question answering (QA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-long-form-medical-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICCAI-CDMRI 2023 QuantConn Challenge Findings on Achieving Robust Quantitative Connectivity through Harmonized Preprocessing of Diffusion MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miccai-cdmri-2023-quantconn-challenge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a pressing need to harmonize the preprocessing of DW-MRI datasets to ensure the derivation of robust quantitative diffusion metrics across acquisitions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miccai-cdmri-2023-quantconn-challenge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lattice-based stochastic models motivate non-linear diffusion descriptions of memory-based dispersal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lattice-based-stochastic-models-motivate-non</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advantage of working with the individual-based model is that it is straightforward to propose and implement memory effects within the simulation in a way that is more biologically intuitive than simply proposing heuristic extensions of classical PDE models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lattice-based-stochastic-models-motivate-non</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DriveThru: a Document Extraction Platform and Benchmark Datasets for Indonesian Local Language Archives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivethru-a-document-extraction-platform-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most of these efforts have been focused on creating manual resources thus difficult to scale to more languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivethru-a-document-extraction-platform-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LHRS-Bot-Nova: Improved Multimodal Large Language Model for Remote Sensing Vision-Language Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lhrs-bot-nova-improved-multimodal-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce LHRS-Bot-Nova, an MLLM specialized in understanding remote sensing (RS) images, designed to expertly perform a wide range of RS understanding tasks aligned with human instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lhrs-bot-nova-improved-multimodal-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Machine Learning for Single-Shot Measurement of Free Electron Laser Pulse Power</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-machine-learning-for-single-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is a crucial hurdle in the exact reconstruction of the photon pulse profile.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-machine-learning-for-single-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local-Global Attention: An Adaptive Mechanism for Multi-Scale Feature Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-global-attention-an-adaptive-mechanism</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, attention mechanisms have significantly enhanced the performance of object detection by focusing on key feature information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-global-attention-an-adaptive-mechanism</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
