<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 09:15:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Pairwise Comparisons without Stochastic Transitivity: Model, Theory and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pairwise-comparisons-without-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most statistical models for pairwise comparisons, including the Bradley-Terry (BT) and Thurstone models and many extensions, make a relatively strong assumption of stochastic transitivity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pairwise-comparisons-without-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging ASIC AI Chips for Homomorphic Encryption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-asic-ai-chips-for-homomorphic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cloud-based services are making the outsourcing of sensitive client data increasingly common.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-asic-ai-chips-for-homomorphic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>disco: Distributional Synthetic Controls</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disco-distributional-synthetic-controls</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The method of synthetic controls is widely used for evaluating causal effects of policy changes in settings with observational data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disco-distributional-synthetic-controls</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomalous Agreement: How to find the Ideal Number of Anomaly Classes in Correlated, Multivariate Time Series Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalous-agreement-how-to-find-the-ideal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting and classifying abnormal system states is critical for condition monitoring, but supervised methods often fall short due to the rarity of anomalies and the lack of labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalous-agreement-how-to-find-the-ideal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Multimodal Fusion via Meta-Learning Towards Micro-Video Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-multimodal-fusion-via-meta-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we develop a novel meta-learning-based multimodal fusion framework called Meta Multimodal Fusion (MetaMMF), which dynamically assigns parameters to the multimodal fusion function for each micro-video during its representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-multimodal-fusion-via-meta-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Enhanced Zeroth-Order Stochastic Frank-Wolfe Framework for Constrained Finite-Sum Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-enhanced-zeroth-order-stochastic-frank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For non-convex objectives, it achieves a query complexity of O(d^{3/2}\sqrt{n}/\epsilon^2 ) without requiring the computation ofd partial derivatives at each iteration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-enhanced-zeroth-order-stochastic-frank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparative analysis of optical character recognition methods for Sámi texts from the National Library of Norway</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-analysis-of-optical-character</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optical Character Recognition (OCR) is crucial to the National Library of Norway's (NLN) digitisation process as it converts scanned documents into machine-readable text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-analysis-of-optical-character</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SST-EM: Advanced Metrics for Evaluating Semantic, Spatial and Temporal Aspects in Video Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sst-em-advanced-metrics-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The name SST-EM reflects its focus on Semantic, Spatial, and Temporal aspects of video evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sst-em-advanced-metrics-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Single-Snapshot DOA Estimation with Siamese Neural Networks for Sparse Linear Arrays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-single-snapshot-doa-estimation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Single-snapshot signal processing in sparse linear arrays has become increasingly vital, particularly in dynamic environments like automotive radar systems, where only limited snapshots are available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-single-snapshot-doa-estimation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skip Mamba Diffusion for Monocular 3D Semantic Scene Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skip-mamba-diffusion-for-monocular-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a unique neural model, leveraging advances from the state space and diffusion generative modeling to achieve remarkable 3D semantic scene completion performance with monocular image input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skip-mamba-diffusion-for-monocular-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Online Reinforcement Learning with Meta-Learned Objective from Offline Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-online-reinforcement-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior works enhance online RL with conventional Imitation Learning (IL) via a handcrafted auxiliary objective, at the cost of restricting the RL policy to be sub-optimal when the offline data is generated by a non-expert policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-online-reinforcement-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confident Pseudo-labeled Diffusion Augmentation for Canine Cardiomegaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confident-pseudo-labeled-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Canine cardiomegaly, marked by an enlarged heart, poses serious health risks if undetected, requiring accurate diagnostic methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confident-pseudo-labeled-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inductive Learning of Robot Task Knowledge from Raw Data and Online Expert Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inductive-learning-of-robot-task-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an offline algorithm based on inductive logic programming from noisy examples to extract task specifications (i. e., action preconditions, constraints and effects) directly from raw data of few heterogeneous (i. e., not repetitive) robotic executions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inductive-learning-of-robot-task-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking Memory Limits: Gradient Wavelet Transform Enhances LLMs Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-memory-limits-gradient-wavelet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown impressive performance across a range of natural language processing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-memory-limits-gradient-wavelet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIOMEDICA: An Open Biomedical Image-Caption Archive, Dataset, and Vision-Language Models Derived from Scientific Literature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomedica-an-open-biomedical-image-caption</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of vision-language models (VLMs) is driven by large-scale and diverse multimodal datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomedica-an-open-biomedical-image-caption</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Retrieval-Augmented Generation: A Study of Best Practices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-retrieval-augmented-generation-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) systems have recently shown remarkable advancements by integrating retrieval mechanisms into language models, enhancing their ability to produce more accurate and contextually relevant responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-retrieval-augmented-generation-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How GPT learns layer by layer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-gpt-learns-layer-by-layer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding how LLMs build internal world models is key to developing agents capable of consistent, adaptive behavior across tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-gpt-learns-layer-by-layer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViSoLex: An Open-Source Repository for Vietnamese Social Media Lexical Normalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visolex-an-open-source-repository-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ViSoLex is an open-source system designed to address the unique challenges of lexical normalization for Vietnamese social media text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visolex-an-open-source-repository-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthesis and Analysis of Data as Probability Measures with Entropy-Regularized Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesis-and-analysis-of-data-as-probability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The synthesis problem consists of computing the barycenter, with respect to these costs, of $m$ reference measures given a set of coefficients belonging to the $m$-dimensional simplex.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesis-and-analysis-of-data-as-probability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Realistic Camouflaged Object Detection: Benchmarks and Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-realistic-camouflaged-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since camouflaged objects are not rare categories, CAFR fully utilizes a clear perception of the current object within the prior knowledge of large models to assist detectors in deeply understanding the distinctions between background and foreground.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-realistic-camouflaged-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CureGraph: Contrastive Multi-Modal Graph Representation Learning for Urban Living Circle Health Profiling and Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curegraph-contrastive-multi-modal-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The early detection and prediction of health status decline among the elderly at the neighborhood level are of great significance for urban planning and public health policymaking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curegraph-contrastive-multi-modal-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinerWeb-10BT: Refining Web Data with LLM-Based Line-Level Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finerweb-10bt-refining-web-data-with-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To test the impact of our filtering, we train GPT-2 models on both the original and the filtered datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finerweb-10bt-refining-web-data-with-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Superpixel Segmentation via Structural Information Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-superpixel-segmentation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Superpixel segmentation is a foundation for many higher-level computer vision tasks, such as image segmentation, object recognition, and scene understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-superpixel-segmentation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataset Distillation via Committee Voting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-distillation-via-committee-voting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dataset distillation aims to synthesize a smaller, representative dataset that preserves the essential properties of the original data, enabling efficient model training with reduced computational resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-distillation-via-committee-voting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebWalker: Benchmarking LLMs in Web Traversal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webwalker-benchmarking-llms-in-web-traversal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experimental results show that WebWalkerQA is challenging and demonstrates the effectiveness of RAG combined with WebWalker, through the horizontal and vertical integration in real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webwalker-benchmarking-llms-in-web-traversal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEO: Boosting Mixture of Vision Encoders for Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leo-boosting-mixture-of-vision-encoders-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Enhanced visual understanding serves as a cornerstone for multimodal large language models (MLLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leo-boosting-mixture-of-vision-encoders-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADKGD: Anomaly Detection in Knowledge Graphs with Dual-Channel Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adkgd-anomaly-detection-in-knowledge-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge graphs (KGs), as a powerful structural tool, could serve as a vital external information source to mitigate the aforementioned issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adkgd-anomaly-detection-in-knowledge-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foundation Models at Work: Fine-Tuning for Fairness in Algorithmic Hiring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-models-at-work-fine-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experiments on a public hiring dataset and a real-world hiring platform showcase how large language models can assist in identifying and mitigation biases in the real world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-models-at-work-fine-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three-view Focal Length Recovery From Homographies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/three-view-focal-length-recovery-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach for recovering focal lengths from three-view homographies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/three-view-focal-length-recovery-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language-Assisted Multi-modal Medication Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-assisted-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, NLA-MMR formulates CMR as an alignment problem from patient and medication modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-assisted-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Text-To-Image Generation via Multilingual Prompting in Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-text-to-image-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, as demand for more complex and flexible image descriptions grows, enhancing comprehension of input text within the ICL paradigm remains a critical yet underexplored area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-text-to-image-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Likelihood Training of Cascaded Diffusion Models via Hierarchical Volume-preserving Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/likelihood-training-of-cascaded-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show that they can also be excellent likelihood models, so long as we overcome a fundamental difficulty with probabilistic multi-scale models: the intractability of the likelihood function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/likelihood-training-of-cascaded-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D3MES: Diffusion Transformer with multihead equivariant self-attention for 3D molecule generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d3mes-diffusion-transformer-with-multihead</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding and predicting the diverse conformational states of molecules is crucial for advancing fields such as chemistry, material science, and drug development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d3mes-diffusion-transformer-with-multihead</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Potential of Text in High-Dimensional Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-potential-of-text-in-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series forecasting has traditionally focused on univariate and multivariate numerical data, often overlooking the benefits of incorporating multimodal information, particularly textual data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-potential-of-text-in-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MathReader : Text-to-Speech for Mathematical Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathreader-text-to-speech-for-mathematical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MathReader reduced the WER from 0. 510 to 0. 281 compared to Microsoft Edge, and from 0. 617 to 0. 281 compared to Adobe Acrobat.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathreader-text-to-speech-for-mathematical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RadAlign: Advancing Radiology Report Generation with Vision-Language Concept Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radalign-advancing-radiology-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated chest radiographs interpretation requires both accurate disease classification and detailed radiology report generation, presenting a significant challenge in the clinical workflow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radalign-advancing-radiology-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A User's Guide to $\texttt{KSig}$: GPU-Accelerated Computation of the Signature Kernel</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-user-s-guide-to-texttt-ksig-gpu-accelerated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The signature kernel is a positive definite kernel for sequential and temporal data that has become increasingly popular in machine learning applications due to powerful theoretical guarantees, strong empirical performance, and recently introduced various scalable variations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-user-s-guide-to-texttt-ksig-gpu-accelerated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnCommon Objects in 3D</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncommon-objects-in-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Uncommon Objects in 3D (uCO3D), a new object-centric dataset for 3D deep learning and 3D generative AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncommon-objects-in-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Neural Representations for Registration of Left Ventricle Myocardium During a Cardiac Cycle</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-neural-representations-for-4</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the movement of the left ventricle myocardium (LVmyo) during the cardiac cycle is essential for assessing cardiac function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-neural-representations-for-4</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3DGS-to-PC: Convert a 3D Gaussian Splatting Scene into a Dense Point Cloud or Mesh</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dgs-to-pc-convert-a-3d-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The result is a point cloud that closely represents the shape encoded into the 3D Gaussian scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dgs-to-pc-convert-a-3d-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifelong Learning of Large Language Model based Agents: A Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelong-learning-of-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This survey is the first to systematically summarize the potential techniques for incorporating lifelong learning into LLM-based agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelong-learning-of-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Image Generation Fidelity via Progressive Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-image-generation-fidelity-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that deeper layers are always responsible for high - level content control, while shallow layers handle low - level content control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-image-generation-fidelity-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Modal Deep Learning Framework for Pan-Cancer Prognosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-modal-deep-learning-framework-for-pan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating the multi-modality of patient data and joint training, UMPSNet outperforms all SOTA approaches, and moreover, it demonstrates the effectiveness and generalization ability of the proposed learning paradigm of a single model for multiple cancer types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-modal-deep-learning-framework-for-pan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-task Visual Grounding with Coarse-to-Fine Consistency Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-visual-grounding-with-coarse-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, to address the challenge of insufficient multimodal understanding, we leverage pre-trained models based on visual-linguistic fusion representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-visual-grounding-with-coarse-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Procedural Fairness and Its Relationship with Distributive Fairness in Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procedural-fairness-and-its-relationship-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On one hand, the impact of dataset bias and the procedural fairness of ML model on its distributive fairness is examined.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procedural-fairness-and-its-relationship-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSRefSeg: Referring Remote Sensing Image Segmentation with Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsrefseg-referring-remote-sensing-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Referring remote sensing image segmentation is crucial for achieving fine-grained visual understanding through free-format textual input, enabling enhanced scene and object extraction in remote sensing applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsrefseg-referring-remote-sensing-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZNO-Eval: Benchmarking reasoning capabilities of large language models in Ukrainian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zno-eval-benchmarking-reasoning-capabilities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The purpose of this work is to establish a comprehensive benchmark for the reasoning capabilities evaluation of large language models in the Ukrainian language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zno-eval-benchmarking-reasoning-capabilities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAPO: Task-Referenced Adaptation for Prompt Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tapo-task-referenced-adaptation-for-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompt engineering can significantly improve the performance of large language models (LLMs), with automated prompt optimization (APO) gaining significant attention due to the time-consuming and laborious nature of manual prompt design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tapo-task-referenced-adaptation-for-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3DCoMPaT200: Language-Grounded Compositional Understanding of Parts and Materials of 3D Shapes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dcompat200-language-grounded-compositional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To foster richer and fine-grained part-level 3D understanding, we introduce 3DCoMPaT200, a large-scale dataset tailored for compositional understanding of object parts and materials, with 200 object categories with $\approx$5 times larger object vocabulary compared to 3DCoMPaT and $\approx$ 4 times larger part categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dcompat200-language-grounded-compositional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A General Framework for Inference-time Scaling and Steering of Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-framework-for-inference-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For steering text-to-image models with a human preference reward, we find that FK steering a 0. 8B parameter model outperforms a 2. 6B parameter fine-tuned model on prompt fidelity, with faster sampling and no training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-framework-for-inference-time</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
