<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 21:06:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>IBISCape: A Simulated Benchmark for multi-modal SLAM Systems Evaluation in Large-scale Dynamic Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ibiscape-a-simulated-benchmark-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Keywords: benchmark, multi-modal, datasets, Odometry, Calibration, DVS, SLAM]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ibiscape-a-simulated-benchmark-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A General Recipe for Likelihood-free Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-recipe-for-likelihood-free-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To extend BO to a broader class of models and utilities, we propose likelihood-free BO (LFBO), an approach based on likelihood-free inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-recipe-for-likelihood-free-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchopt: Reproducible, efficient and collaborative optimization benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchopt-reproducible-efficient-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerical validation is at the core of machine learning research as it allows to assess the actual impact of new methods, and to confirm the agreement between theory and practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchopt-reproducible-efficient-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Semantic Annotations of SMCalFlow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-semantic-annotations-of-smcalflow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SMCalFlow is a large corpus of semantically detailed annotations of task-oriented natural dialogues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-semantic-annotations-of-smcalflow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributional Gaussian Processes Layers for Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-gaussian-processes-layers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, by applying the same segmentation model to out-of-distribution data (i. e., images with pathology such as brain tumors), we show that our uncertainty estimates result in out-of-distribution detection that outperforms the capabilities of previous Bayesian networks and reconstruction-based approaches that learn normative distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-gaussian-processes-layers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$u^* = \sqrt{uv}$</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-sqrt-uv</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The nonproductive use of labor is well measured by the number of jobseekers and vacancies, $u + v$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-sqrt-uv</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prior-Guided One-shot Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prior-guided-one-shot-neural-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present Prior-Guided One-shot NAS (PGONAS) to strengthen the ranking correlation of supernets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prior-guided-one-shot-neural-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iso-CapsNet: Isomorphic Capsule Network for Brain Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iso-capsnet-isomorphic-capsule-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Brain graph representation learning serves as the fundamental technique for brain diseases diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iso-capsnet-isomorphic-capsule-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Learning in Remote Sensing: A Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-in-remote-sensing-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In deep learning research, self-supervised learning (SSL) has received great attention triggering interest within both the computer vision and remote sensing communities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-in-remote-sensing-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pen and Paper Exercises in Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pen-and-paper-exercises-in-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is a collection of (mostly) pen-and-paper exercises in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pen-and-paper-exercises-in-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Bank Learning for Semi-supervised Federated Image Diagnosis with Class Imbalance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-bank-learning-for-semi-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent progress on semi-supervised federated learning (FL) for medical image diagnosis, the problem of imbalanced class distributions among unlabeled clients is still unsolved for real-world use.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-bank-learning-for-semi-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endowing Language Models with Multimodal Knowledge Graph Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/endowing-language-models-with-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use the recently released VisualSem KG as our external knowledge repository, which covers a subset of Wikipedia and WordNet entities, and compare a mix of tuple-based and graph-based algorithms to learn entity and relation representations that are grounded on the KG multimodal information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/endowing-language-models-with-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring and Improving the Use of Graph Information in Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-and-improving-the-use-of-graph-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) have been widely used for representation learning on graph data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-and-improving-the-use-of-graph-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Representation Learning Framework for Property Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-representation-learning-framework-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representation learning on graphs, also called graph embedding, has demonstrated its significant impact on a series of machine learning applications such as classification, prediction and recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-representation-learning-framework-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic identification of segmentation errors for radiotherapy using geometric learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-identification-of-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed model is trained using self-supervised learning using a synthetically-generated dataset of segmentations of the parotid and with realistic contouring errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-identification-of-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auditing Visualizations: Transparency Methods Struggle to Detect Anomalous Behavior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auditing-visualizations-transparency-methods</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transparency methods such as model visualizations provide information that outputs alone might miss, since they describe the internals of neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auditing-visualizations-transparency-methods</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Encoded Concepts in Transformer Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-encoded-concepts-in-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel framework ConceptX, to analyze how latent concepts are encoded in representations learned within pre-trained language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-encoded-concepts-in-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A penalisation method for batch multi-objective Bayesian optimisation with application in heat exchanger design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-penalisation-method-for-batch-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present HIghly Parallelisable Pareto Optimisation (HIPPO) -- a batch acquisition function that enables multi-objective Bayesian optimisation methods to efficiently exploit parallel processing resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-penalisation-method-for-batch-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insights into Deep Non-linear Filters for Improved Multi-channel Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insights-into-deep-non-linear-filters-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key advantage of using multiple microphones for speech enhancement is that spatial filtering can be used to complement the tempo-spectral processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insights-into-deep-non-linear-filters-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study of Personalized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-personalized-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is a distributed machine learning approach in which a single server and multiple clients collaboratively build machine learning models without sharing datasets on clients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-personalized-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning of Dynamical Systems with Competitive Federated Reservoir Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-of-dynamical-systems-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results suggest that reservoir computing is a promising candidate framework for the continual learning of dynamical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-of-dynamical-systems-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thermodynamics of Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermodynamics-of-interpretation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the past few years, different types of data-driven Artificial Intelligence (AI) techniques have been widely adopted in various domains of science for generating predictive black-box models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermodynamics-of-interpretation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When to Trust Your Simulator: Dynamics-Aware Hybrid Offline-and-Online Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-trust-your-simulator-dynamics-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This brings up a new question: is it possible to combine learning from limited real data in offline RL and unrestricted exploration through imperfect simulators in online RL to address the drawbacks of both approaches?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-trust-your-simulator-dynamics-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Deep Feature Correspondence for Unsupervised Anomaly Detection and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-deep-feature-correspondence-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop our DFC in an asymmetric dual network framework that consists of a generic feature extraction network and an elaborated feature estimation network, and detect the possible anomalies within images by modeling and evaluating the associated deep feature correspondence between the two dual network branches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-deep-feature-correspondence-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centralized and Decentralized Control in Modular Robots and Their Effect on Morphology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centralized-and-decentralized-control-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, if these findings translate to other robot systems, our results and issues encountered can help future researchers make a choice of control method when co-optimizing morphology and control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centralized-and-decentralized-control-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Center-Embedding and Constituency in the Brain and a New Characterization of Context-Free Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/center-embedding-and-constituency-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address two of the most important questions left open by that work: constituency (the identification of key parts of the sentence such as the verb phrase) and the processing of dependent sentences, especially center-embedded ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/center-embedding-and-constituency-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RankSEG: A Consistent Ranking-based Framework for Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankseg-a-consistent-ranking-based-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we establish a theoretical foundation of segmentation with respect to the Dice/IoU metrics, including the Bayes rule and Dice/IoU-calibration, analogous to classification-calibration or Fisher consistency in classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankseg-a-consistent-ranking-based-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Acoustic Representation Learning on Breathing and Speech Signals for COVID-19 Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-acoustic-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we describe an approach for representation learning of audio signals for the task of COVID-19 detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-acoustic-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Calibration for Deep Audio Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-calibration-for-deep-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate the uncertainty calibration for deep audio classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-calibration-for-deep-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Split Localized Conformal Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/split-localized-conformal-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The modified score inherits the spirit of split conformal methods, which is simple and efficient compared with full conformal methods but better approximates conditional coverage guarantee.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/split-localized-conformal-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Deep Input-Output Stable Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-deep-input-output-stable-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method to learn nonlinear systems guaranteeing the input-output stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-deep-input-output-stable-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Stability Well Predicts Performance of Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-stability-well-predicts-performance-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first give the interpretation of zero stability in the context of deep learning and then investigate the performance of existing first- and second-order CNNs under different zero-stable circumstances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-stability-well-predicts-performance-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Stochastic Petri Net-based Remaining Time Prediction using k-Nearest Neighbors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-stochastic-petri-net-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For realising timely delivery, an accurate prediction of the remaining time of the delivery process is crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-stochastic-petri-net-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SARNet: Semantic Augmented Registration of Large-Scale Urban Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sarnet-semantic-augmented-registration-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Registering urban point clouds is a quite challenging task due to the large-scale, noise and data incompleteness of LiDAR scanning data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sarnet-semantic-augmented-registration-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistency-preserving Visual Question Answering in Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-preserving-visual-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Question Answering (VQA) models take an image and a natural-language question as input and infer the answer to the question.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-preserving-visual-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kernel Attention Transformer (KAT) for Histopathology Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernel-attention-transformer-kat-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer has been widely used in histopathology whole slide image (WSI) classification for the purpose of tumor grading, prognosis analysis, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernel-attention-transformer-kat-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Weak Annotations for Robust Maritime Obstacle Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-weak-annotations-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments show that maritime obstacle segmentation networks trained using SLR on weak labels not only match, but outperform the same networks trained with dense ground truth labels, which is a remarkable result.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-weak-annotations-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iExam: A Novel Online Exam Monitoring and Analysis System Based on Face Detection and Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iexam-a-novel-online-exam-monitoring-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose iExam, an intelligent online exam monitoring and analysis system that can not only use face detection to assist invigilators in real-time student identification, but also be able to detect common abnormal behaviors (including face disappearing, rotating faces, and replacing with a different person during the exams) via a face recognition-based post-exam video analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iexam-a-novel-online-exam-monitoring-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGNet: Monocular Geometric Scene Understanding for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgnet-monocular-geometric-scene-understanding-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We define monocular geometric scene understanding as the combination of two known tasks: Panoptic segmentation and self-supervised monocular depth estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgnet-monocular-geometric-scene-understanding-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Evaluation of Time Series Anomaly Detection Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-evaluation-of-time-series-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, specific evaluation metrics for time series anomaly detection algorithms have been developed to handle the limitations of the classical precision and recall.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-evaluation-of-time-series-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Fast, Segment Well: Fast Object Segmentation Learning on the iCub Robot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-fast-segment-well-fast-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we focus on the instance segmentation task and provide a comprehensive study of different techniques that allow adapting an object segmentation model in presence of novel objects or different domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-fast-segment-well-fast-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key-frame Guided Network for Thyroid Nodule Recognition using Ultrasound Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/key-frame-guided-network-for-thyroid-nodule</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ultrasound examination is widely used in the clinical diagnosis of thyroid nodules (benign/malignant).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/key-frame-guided-network-for-thyroid-nodule</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesion-Aware Contrastive Representation Learning for Histopathology Whole Slide Images Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesion-aware-contrastive-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we proposed a novel contrastive representation learning framework named Lesion-Aware Contrastive Learning (LACL) for histopathology whole slide image analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesion-aware-contrastive-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Scale Spatial Temporal Graph Convolutional Network for Skeleton-Based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-spatial-temporal-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve this problem, we present a multi-scale spatial graph convolution (MS-GC) module and a multi-scale temporal graph convolution (MT-GC) module to enrich the receptive field of the model in spatial and temporal dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-spatial-temporal-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Control Local Search for Combinatorial Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-control-local-search-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combinatorial optimization problems are encountered in many practical contexts such as logistics and production, but exact solutions are particularly difficult to find and usually NP-hard for considerable problem sizes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-control-local-search-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RES: A Robust Framework for Guiding Visual Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/res-a-robust-framework-for-guiding-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the fast progress of explanation techniques in modern Deep Neural Networks (DNNs) where the main focus is handling "how to generate the explanations", advanced research questions that examine the quality of the explanation itself (e. g., "whether the explanations are accurate") and improve the explanation quality (e. g., "how to adjust the model to generate more accurate explanations when explanations are inaccurate") are still relatively under-explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/res-a-robust-framework-for-guiding-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Deformable Model for 4D Temporal Medical Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-deformable-model-for-4d-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed DDM is composed of the diffusion and the deformation modules so that DDM can learn spatial deformation information between the source and target volumes and provide a latent code for generating intermediate frames along a geodesic path.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-deformable-model-for-4d-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Instance Learning with Mixed Supervision in Gleason Grading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-instance-learning-with-mixed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We achieve the state-of-the-art performance on the SICAPv2 dataset, and the visual analysis shows the accurate prediction results of instance level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-instance-learning-with-mixed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextual embedding and model weighting by fusing domain knowledge on Biomedical Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-embedding-and-model-weighting-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Biomedical Question Answering aims to obtain an answer to the given question from the biomedical domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-embedding-and-model-weighting-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Your Sparse Neural Network Better with Any Mask</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-your-sparse-neural-network-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pruning large neural networks to create high-quality, independently trainable sparse masks, which can maintain similar performance to their dense counterparts, is very desirable due to the reduced space and time complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-your-sparse-neural-network-better</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
