<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 21:09:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Precision-Focused Reinforcement Learning Model for Robotic Object Pushing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precision-focused-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Non-prehensile manipulation, such as pushing objects to a desired target position, is an important skill for robots to assist humans in everyday situations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precision-focused-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Short Note on Evaluating RepNet for Temporal Repetition Counting in Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-short-note-on-evaluating-repnet-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discuss some consistent issues on how RepNet has been evaluated in various papers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-short-note-on-evaluating-repnet-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESOLVE: Relational Reasoning with Symbolic and Object-Level Features Using Vector Symbolic Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resolve-relational-reasoning-with-symbolic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the Abstractor layer while excelling at capturing relational information (pure relational reasoning), faces challenges in tasks that require both object and relational-level reasoning (partial relational reasoning).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resolve-relational-reasoning-with-symbolic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepUQ: Assessing the Aleatoric Uncertainties from two Deep Learning Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepuq-assessing-the-aleatoric-uncertainties</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The predicted uncertainty is the least accurate for both UQ methods for the 2D input uncertainty experiment and the high-noise level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepuq-assessing-the-aleatoric-uncertainties</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Properties of fairness measures in the context of varying class imbalance and protected group ratios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/properties-of-fairness-measures-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the general properties of fairness measures for changing class and protected group proportions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/properties-of-fairness-measures-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinRobot: AI Agent for Equity Research and Valuation with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finrobot-ai-agent-for-equity-research-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The system is structured around three specialized agents: the Data-CoT Agent, which aggregates diverse data sources for robust financial integration; the Concept-CoT Agent, which mimics an analysts reasoning to generate actionable insights; and the Thesis-CoT Agent, which synthesizes these insights into a coherent investment thesis and report.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finrobot-ai-agent-for-equity-research-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Multimodal Query Representation via Visual Dialogues for End-to-End Knowledge Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-multimodal-query-representation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing multimodal retrieval systems often rely on disjointed models for image comprehension, such as object detectors and caption generators, leading to cumbersome implementations and training processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-multimodal-query-representation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics Informed Distillation for Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-distillation-for-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon these foundational insights, we introduce Physics Informed Distillation (PID), which employs a student model to represent the solution of the ODE system corresponding to the teacher diffusion model, akin to the principles employed in PINNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-distillation-for-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Searching Latent Program Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/searching-latent-program-spaces</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Program synthesis methods aim to automatically generate programs restricted to a language that can explain a given specification of input-output pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/searching-latent-program-spaces</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaussian Mixture Models Based Augmentation Enhances GNN Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-mixture-models-based-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have shown great promise in tasks like node and graph classification, but they often struggle to generalize, particularly to unseen or out-of-distribution (OOD) data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-mixture-models-based-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Chinese Multi-label Affective Computing Dataset Based on Social Media Network Users</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-chinese-multi-label-affective-computing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chinese emotion datasets are extremely scarce, and datasets capturing Chinese user personality traits are even more limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-chinese-multi-label-affective-computing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trap-MID: Trapdoor-based Defense against Model Inversion Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trap-mid-trapdoor-based-defense-against-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model Inversion (MI) attacks pose a significant threat to the privacy of Deep Neural Networks by recovering training data distribution from well-trained models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trap-mid-trapdoor-based-defense-against-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APDDv2: Aesthetics of Paintings and Drawings Dataset with Artist Labeled Scores and Comments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apddv2-aesthetics-of-paintings-and-drawings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Datasets play a pivotal role in training visual models, facilitating the development of abstract understandings of visual features through diverse image samples and multidimensional attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apddv2-aesthetics-of-paintings-and-drawings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can sparse autoencoders be used to decompose and interpret steering vectors?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-sparse-autoencoders-be-used-to-decompose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Steering vectors are a promising approach to control the behaviour of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-sparse-autoencoders-be-used-to-decompose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Explanations for Image Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-explanations-for-image-classifiers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, none of the existing tools use a principled approach based on formal definitions of causes and explanations for the explanation extraction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-explanations-for-image-classifiers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional Variable Flow Matching: Transforming Conditional Densities with Amortized Conditional Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-variable-flow-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Forecasting stochastic nonlinear dynamical systems under the influence of conditioning variables is a fundamental challenge repeatedly encountered across the biological and physical sciences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-variable-flow-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Separating Tongue from Thought: Activation Patching Reveals Language-Agnostic Concept Representations in Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/separating-tongue-from-thought-activation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we address this question by analyzing latent representations (latents) during a word translation task in transformer-based LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/separating-tongue-from-thought-activation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V2X-R: Cooperative LiDAR-4D Radar Fusion for 3D Object Detection with Denoising Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2x-r-cooperative-lidar-4d-radar-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve weather-robust detection, we additionally propose a Multi-modal Denoising Diffusion (MDD) module in our fusion pipeline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2x-r-cooperative-lidar-4d-radar-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VALTEST: Automated Validation of Language Model Generated Test Cases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valtest-automated-validation-of-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated significant potential in automating software testing, specifically in generating unit test cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valtest-automated-validation-of-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLV$^2$-Net: Rater-Based Majority-Label Voting for Consistent Meningeal Lymphatic Vessel Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlv-2-net-rater-based-majority-label-voting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meningeal lymphatic vessels (MLVs) are responsible for the drainage of waste products from the human brain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlv-2-net-rater-based-majority-label-voting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Perspective Stance Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-perspective-stance-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subjective NLP tasks usually rely on human annotations provided by multiple annotators, whose judgments may vary due to their diverse backgrounds and life experiences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-perspective-stance-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hopfield-Fenchel-Young Networks: A Unified Framework for Associative Memory Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hopfield-fenchel-young-networks-a-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Associative memory models, such as Hopfield networks and their modern variants, have garnered renewed interest due to advancements in memory capacity and connections with self-attention in transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hopfield-fenchel-young-networks-a-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interaction Testing in Variation Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interaction-testing-in-variation-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this way, the TV measure is suitable for providing explanations in the natural regime and answering questions such as ``why is $X$ associated with $Y$?''.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interaction-testing-in-variation-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning Accelerated Quantum Transport Simulations in Nanoelectronics: From Break Junctions to Field-Effect Transistors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-accelerated-quantum-transport</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantum transport calculations are essential for understanding and designing nanoelectronic devices, yet the trade-off between accuracy and computational efficiency has long limited their practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-accelerated-quantum-transport</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LogLLM: Log-based Anomaly Detection Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logllm-log-based-anomaly-detection-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Software systems often record important runtime information in logs to help with troubleshooting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logllm-log-based-anomaly-detection-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XiYan-SQL: A Multi-Generator Ensemble Framework for Text-to-SQL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xiyan-sql-a-multi-generator-ensemble</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, we implement the ICL approach with an example selection method based on named entity recognition to prevent overemphasis on entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xiyan-sql-a-multi-generator-ensemble</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScaleNet: Scale Invariance Learning in Directed Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalenet-scale-invariance-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research extends the scale invariance concept to node classification by drawing an analogy to image processing: just as scale invariance being used in image classification to capture multi-scale features, we propose the concept of ``scaled ego-graphs''.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalenet-scale-invariance-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MBA-SLAM: Motion Blur Aware Dense Visual SLAM with Radiance Fields Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mba-slam-motion-blur-aware-dense-visual-slam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our experiments, we demonstrate that MBA-SLAM surpasses previous state-of-the-art methods in both camera localization and map reconstruction, showcasing superior performance across a range of datasets, including synthetic and real datasets featuring sharp images as well as those affected by motion blur, highlighting the versatility and robustness of our approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mba-slam-motion-blur-aware-dense-visual-slam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy Dissipation Preserving Physics Informed Neural Network for Allen-Cahn Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-dissipation-preserving-physics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates a numerical solution of Allen-Cahn equation with constant and degenerate mobility, with polynomial and logarithmic energy functionals, with deterministic and random initial functions, and with advective term in one, two, and three spatial dimensions, based on the physics-informed neural network (PINN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-dissipation-preserving-physics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JanusFlow: Harmonizing Autoregression and Rectified Flow for Unified Multimodal Understanding and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/janusflow-harmonizing-autoregression-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further improve the performance of our unified model, we adopt two key strategies: (i) decoupling the understanding and generation encoders, and (ii) aligning their representations during unified training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/janusflow-harmonizing-autoregression-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint multi-dimensional dynamic attention and transformer for general image restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-multi-dimensional-dynamic-attention-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Outdoor images often suffer from severe degradation due to rain, haze, and noise, impairing image quality and challenging high-level tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-multi-dimensional-dynamic-attention-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FM-TS: Flow Matching for Time Series Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fm-ts-flow-matching-for-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FM-TS is more efficient in terms of training and inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fm-ts-flow-matching-for-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Likelihood as a Performance Gauge for Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/likelihood-as-a-performance-gauge-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on these findings, we propose two methods that use question likelihood as a gauge for selecting and constructing prompts that lead to better performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/likelihood-as-a-performance-gauge-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Low-Rank Dilemma of Linear Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-low-rank-dilemma-of-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Softmax attention mechanism in Transformer models is notoriously computationally expensive, particularly due to its quadratic complexity, posing significant challenges in vision applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-low-rank-dilemma-of-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPU: Dynamic Prototype Updating for Multimodal Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpu-dynamic-prototype-updating-for-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on two tasks, five datasets, and nine base OOD algorithms demonstrate that DPU significantly improves OOD detection performance, setting a new state-of-the-art in multimodal OOD detection, with improvements of up to 80 percent in Far-OOD detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpu-dynamic-prototype-updating-for-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xCG: Explainable Cell Graphs for Survival Prediction in Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xcg-explainable-cell-graphs-for-survival</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding how deep learning models predict oncology patient risk can provide critical insights into disease progression, support clinical decision-making, and pave the way for trustworthy and data-driven precision medicine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xcg-explainable-cell-graphs-for-survival</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Material Transforms from Disentangled NeRF Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/material-transforms-from-disentangled-nerf</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we first propose a novel method for transferring material transformations across different scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/material-transforms-from-disentangled-nerf</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Memory Mechanisms for Decision Making through Demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-memory-mechanisms-for-decision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Partially Observable Markov Decision Processes, integrating an agent's history into memory poses a significant challenge for decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-memory-mechanisms-for-decision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GTA: Global Tracklet Association for Multi-Object Tracking in Sports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gta-global-tracklet-association-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method achieved a new state-of-the-art performance on the SportsMOT dataset with HOTA score of 81. 04%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gta-global-tracklet-association-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Truths: A Large-Scale Dataset of AI-Augmented Images for Evaluating Robustness of AI-Generated Image detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-truths-a-large-scale-dataset-of-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image diffusion models have impactful applications in art, design, and entertainment, yet these technologies also pose significant risks by enabling the creation and dissemination of misinformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-truths-a-large-scale-dataset-of-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deceiving Question-Answering Models: A Hybrid Word-Level Adversarial Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deceiving-question-answering-models-a-hybrid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning underpins most of the currently advanced natural language processing (NLP) tasks such as textual classification, neural machine translation (NMT), abstractive summarization and question-answering (QA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deceiving-question-answering-models-a-hybrid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval Augmented Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-time-series-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) is a central component of modern LLM systems, particularly in scenarios where up-to-date information is crucial for accurately responding to user queries or when queries exceed the scope of the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-time-series-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MureObjectStitch: Multi-reference Image Composition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mureobjectstitch-multi-reference-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative image composition aims to regenerate the given foreground object in the background image to produce a realistic composite image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mureobjectstitch-multi-reference-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verbosity $\neq$ Veracity: Demystify Verbosity Compensation Behavior of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verbosity-neq-veracity-demystify-verbosity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[2) We reveal the large performance gap between verbose and concise responses, with a notable difference of 27. 61% on the Qasper dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verbosity-neq-veracity-demystify-verbosity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interaction Asymmetry: A General Principle for Learning Composable Abstractions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interaction-asymmetry-a-general-principle-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using this formalism, we prove that interaction asymmetry enables both disentanglement and compositional generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interaction-asymmetry-a-general-principle-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models as Causal Effect Generators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-as-causal-effect-generators</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we define a procedure for turning any language model and any directed acyclic graph (DAG) into a sequence-driven structural causal model (SD-SCM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-as-causal-effect-generators</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Album Sequencing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-album-sequencing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce a new user-friendly web-based tool that allows a less technical audience to upload music tracks, execute this technique in one click, and subsequently presents the result in a clean visualization to the user.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-album-sequencing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mapping the Podcast Ecosystem with the Structured Podcast Research Corpus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-the-podcast-ecosystem-with-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Podcasts provide highly diverse content to a massive listener base through a unique on-demand modality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-the-podcast-ecosystem-with-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Stochastic Optimization Framework for Private and Fair Learning From Decentralized Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stochastic-optimization-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we develop a novel algorithm for private and fair federated learning (FL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stochastic-optimization-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models Can Self-Improve in Long-context Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-can-self-improve-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have achieved substantial progress in processing long contexts but still struggle with long-context reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-can-self-improve-in</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
