<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 21:07:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Summarizing Videos using Concentrated Attention and Considering the Uniqueness and Diversity of the Video Frames</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/summarizing-videos-using-concentrated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of simply modeling the frames' dependencies based on global attention, our method integrates a concentrated attention mechanism that is able to focus on non-overlapping blocks in the main diagonal of the attention matrix, and to enrich the existing information by extracting and exploiting knowledge about the uniqueness and diversity of the associated frames of the video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/summarizing-videos-using-concentrated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Data Collection System for Brownfield CNC Milling Machines: A New Benchmark Dataset for Data-Driven Machine Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-data-collection-system-for-brownfield</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enhance the scalability of machine learning in real-world applications, this paper presents a benchmark dataset for process monitoring of brownfield milling machines based on acceleration data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-data-collection-system-for-brownfield</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pedestrian 3D Bounding Box Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pedestrian-3d-bounding-box-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safety is still the main issue of autonomous driving, and in order to be globally deployed, they need to predict pedestrians' motions sufficiently in advance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pedestrian-3d-bounding-box-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Impact of Noises in Crowd-Sourced Data for Speech Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-impact-of-noises-in-crowd-sourced-data-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training speech translation (ST) models requires large and high-quality datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-impact-of-noises-in-crowd-sourced-data-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Symmetric Rules with SATNet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-symmetric-rules-with-satnet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SATNet is a differentiable constraint solver with a custom backpropagation algorithm, which can be used as a layer in a deep-learning system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-symmetric-rules-with-satnet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TTS-CGAN: A Transformer Time-Series Conditional GAN for Biosignal Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tts-cgan-a-transformer-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For time-series data, the suite of data augmentation strategies we can use to expand the size of the dataset is limited by the need to maintain the basic properties of the signal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tts-cgan-a-transformer-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Dataflow Dialogue Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-dataflow-dialogue-design-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper argues that this perception is wrong: 1) Suggestions for a simplified format for the annotation of the dataset are presented, 2) An implementation of the DF execution engine is released\footnote{https://github. com/telepathylabsai/OpenDF}, which can serve as a sandbox allowing researchers to easily implement, and experiment with, new DF dialogue designs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-dataflow-dialogue-design-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show Me Your Face, And I'll Tell You How You Speak</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-me-your-face-and-i-ll-tell-you-how-you</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When we speak, the prosody and content of the speech can be inferred from the movement of our lips.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-me-your-face-and-i-ll-tell-you-how-you</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSL-Lanes: Self-Supervised Learning for Motion Forecasting in Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssl-lanes-self-supervised-learning-for-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning (SSL) is an emerging technique that has been successfully employed to train convolutional neural networks (CNNs) and graph neural networks (GNNs) for more transferable, generalizable, and robust representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssl-lanes-self-supervised-learning-for-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Gait Representation from Massive Unlabelled Walking Videos: A Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-gait-representation-from-massive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As far as we know, GaitLU-1M is the first large-scale unlabelled gait dataset, and GaitSSB is the first method that achieves remarkable unsupervised results on the aforementioned benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-gait-representation-from-massive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing and extending the use of defeasible argumentation with quantitative data in real-world contexts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-and-extending-the-use-of-defeasible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computational trust was selected as the domain of application of such models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-and-extending-the-use-of-defeasible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extended U-Net for Speaker Verification in Noisy Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extended-u-net-for-speaker-verification-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Background noise is a well-known factor that deteriorates the accuracy and reliability of speaker verification (SV) systems by blurring speech intelligibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extended-u-net-for-speaker-verification-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RankSEG: A Consistent Ranking-based Framework for Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankseg-a-consistent-ranking-based-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we establish a theoretical foundation of segmentation with respect to the Dice/IoU metrics, including the Bayes rule and Dice/IoU-calibration, analogous to classification-calibration or Fisher consistency in classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankseg-a-consistent-ranking-based-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Semantic Annotations of SMCalFlow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-semantic-annotations-of-smcalflow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SMCalFlow is a large corpus of semantically detailed annotations of task-oriented natural dialogues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-semantic-annotations-of-smcalflow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Evaluation of Time Series Anomaly Detection Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-evaluation-of-time-series-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, specific evaluation metrics for time series anomaly detection algorithms have been developed to handle the limitations of the classical precision and recall.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-evaluation-of-time-series-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RES: A Robust Framework for Guiding Visual Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/res-a-robust-framework-for-guiding-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the fast progress of explanation techniques in modern Deep Neural Networks (DNNs) where the main focus is handling "how to generate the explanations", advanced research questions that examine the quality of the explanation itself (e. g., "whether the explanations are accurate") and improve the explanation quality (e. g., "how to adjust the model to generate more accurate explanations when explanations are inaccurate") are still relatively under-explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/res-a-robust-framework-for-guiding-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Deformable Model for 4D Temporal Medical Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-deformable-model-for-4d-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed DDM is composed of the diffusion and the deformation modules so that DDM can learn spatial deformation information between the source and target volumes and provide a latent code for generating intermediate frames along a geodesic path.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-deformable-model-for-4d-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGNet: Monocular Geometric Scene Understanding for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgnet-monocular-geometric-scene-understanding-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We define monocular geometric scene understanding as the combination of two known tasks: Panoptic segmentation and self-supervised monocular depth estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgnet-monocular-geometric-scene-understanding-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistency-preserving Visual Question Answering in Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-preserving-visual-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Question Answering (VQA) models take an image and a natural-language question as input and infer the answer to the question.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-preserving-visual-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Weak Annotations for Robust Maritime Obstacle Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-weak-annotations-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments show that maritime obstacle segmentation networks trained using SLR on weak labels not only match, but outperform the same networks trained with dense ground truth labels, which is a remarkable result.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-weak-annotations-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kernel Attention Transformer (KAT) for Histopathology Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernel-attention-transformer-kat-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer has been widely used in histopathology whole slide image (WSI) classification for the purpose of tumor grading, prognosis analysis, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernel-attention-transformer-kat-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SARNet: Semantic Augmented Registration of Large-Scale Urban Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sarnet-semantic-augmented-registration-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Registering urban point clouds is a quite challenging task due to the large-scale, noise and data incompleteness of LiDAR scanning data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sarnet-semantic-augmented-registration-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Scale Spatial Temporal Graph Convolutional Network for Skeleton-Based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-spatial-temporal-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve this problem, we present a multi-scale spatial graph convolution (MS-GC) module and a multi-scale temporal graph convolution (MT-GC) module to enrich the receptive field of the model in spatial and temporal dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-spatial-temporal-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesion-Aware Contrastive Representation Learning for Histopathology Whole Slide Images Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesion-aware-contrastive-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we proposed a novel contrastive representation learning framework named Lesion-Aware Contrastive Learning (LACL) for histopathology whole slide image analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesion-aware-contrastive-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key-frame Guided Network for Thyroid Nodule Recognition using Ultrasound Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/key-frame-guided-network-for-thyroid-nodule</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ultrasound examination is widely used in the clinical diagnosis of thyroid nodules (benign/malignant).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/key-frame-guided-network-for-thyroid-nodule</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Fast, Segment Well: Fast Object Segmentation Learning on the iCub Robot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-fast-segment-well-fast-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we focus on the instance segmentation task and provide a comprehensive study of different techniques that allow adapting an object segmentation model in presence of novel objects or different domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-fast-segment-well-fast-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Learning in Remote Sensing: A Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-in-remote-sensing-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In deep learning research, self-supervised learning (SSL) has received great attention triggering interest within both the computer vision and remote sensing communities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-in-remote-sensing-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iso-CapsNet: Isomorphic Capsule Network for Brain Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iso-capsnet-isomorphic-capsule-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Brain graph representation learning serves as the fundamental technique for brain diseases diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iso-capsnet-isomorphic-capsule-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prior-Guided One-shot Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prior-guided-one-shot-neural-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present Prior-Guided One-shot NAS (PGONAS) to strengthen the ranking correlation of supernets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prior-guided-one-shot-neural-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributional Gaussian Processes Layers for Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-gaussian-processes-layers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, by applying the same segmentation model to out-of-distribution data (i. e., images with pathology such as brain tumors), we show that our uncertainty estimates result in out-of-distribution detection that outperforms the capabilities of previous Bayesian networks and reconstruction-based approaches that learn normative distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-gaussian-processes-layers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Encoded Concepts in Transformer Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-encoded-concepts-in-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel framework ConceptX, to analyze how latent concepts are encoded in representations learned within pre-trained language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-encoded-concepts-in-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Stability Well Predicts Performance of Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-stability-well-predicts-performance-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first give the interpretation of zero stability in the context of deep learning and then investigate the performance of existing first- and second-order CNNs under different zero-stable circumstances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-stability-well-predicts-performance-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Stochastic Petri Net-based Remaining Time Prediction using k-Nearest Neighbors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-stochastic-petri-net-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For realising timely delivery, an accurate prediction of the remaining time of the delivery process is crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-stochastic-petri-net-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insights into Deep Non-linear Filters for Improved Multi-channel Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insights-into-deep-non-linear-filters-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key advantage of using multiple microphones for speech enhancement is that spatial filtering can be used to complement the tempo-spectral processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insights-into-deep-non-linear-filters-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBISCape: A Simulated Benchmark for multi-modal SLAM Systems Evaluation in Large-scale Dynamic Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ibiscape-a-simulated-benchmark-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Keywords: benchmark, multi-modal, datasets, Odometry, Calibration, DVS, SLAM]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ibiscape-a-simulated-benchmark-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When to Trust Your Simulator: Dynamics-Aware Hybrid Offline-and-Online Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-trust-your-simulator-dynamics-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This brings up a new question: is it possible to combine learning from limited real data in offline RL and unrestricted exploration through imperfect simulators in online RL to address the drawbacks of both approaches?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-trust-your-simulator-dynamics-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iExam: A Novel Online Exam Monitoring and Analysis System Based on Face Detection and Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iexam-a-novel-online-exam-monitoring-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose iExam, an intelligent online exam monitoring and analysis system that can not only use face detection to assist invigilators in real-time student identification, but also be able to detect common abnormal behaviors (including face disappearing, rotating faces, and replacing with a different person during the exams) via a face recognition-based post-exam video analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iexam-a-novel-online-exam-monitoring-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Control Local Search for Combinatorial Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-control-local-search-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combinatorial optimization problems are encountered in many practical contexts such as logistics and production, but exact solutions are particularly difficult to find and usually NP-hard for considerable problem sizes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-control-local-search-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Split Localized Conformal Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/split-localized-conformal-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The modified score inherits the spirit of split conformal methods, which is simple and efficient compared with full conformal methods but better approximates conditional coverage guarantee.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/split-localized-conformal-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Deep Input-Output Stable Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-deep-input-output-stable-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method to learn nonlinear systems guaranteeing the input-output stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-deep-input-output-stable-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Deep Feature Correspondence for Unsupervised Anomaly Detection and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-deep-feature-correspondence-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop our DFC in an asymmetric dual network framework that consists of a generic feature extraction network and an elaborated feature estimation network, and detect the possible anomalies within images by modeling and evaluating the associated deep feature correspondence between the two dual network branches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-deep-feature-correspondence-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A penalisation method for batch multi-objective Bayesian optimisation with application in heat exchanger design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-penalisation-method-for-batch-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present HIghly Parallelisable Pareto Optimisation (HIPPO) -- a batch acquisition function that enables multi-objective Bayesian optimisation methods to efficiently exploit parallel processing resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-penalisation-method-for-batch-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thermodynamics of Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermodynamics-of-interpretation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the past few years, different types of data-driven Artificial Intelligence (AI) techniques have been widely adopted in various domains of science for generating predictive black-box models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermodynamics-of-interpretation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning of Dynamical Systems with Competitive Federated Reservoir Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-of-dynamical-systems-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results suggest that reservoir computing is a promising candidate framework for the continual learning of dynamical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-of-dynamical-systems-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrete Morse Sandwich: Fast Computation of Persistence Diagrams for Scalar Data -- An Algorithm and A Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-morse-sandwich-fast-computation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This fast processing of the dimensions 0 and (d-1) further reduces, and drastically, the number of critical simplices to consider for the computation of $D_1(f)$, the intermediate layer of the sandwich.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-morse-sandwich-fast-computation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omni-Seg+: A Scale-aware Dynamic Network for Pathological Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omni-seg-a-scale-aware-dynamic-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The contribution of this paper is three-fold: (1) a novel scale-aware controller is proposed to generalize the dynamic neural network from single-scale to multi-scale; (2) semi-supervised consistency regularization of pseudo-labels is introduced to model the inter-scale correlation of unannotated tissue types into a single end-to-end learning paradigm; and (3) superior scale-aware generalization is evidenced by directly applying a model trained on human kidney images to mouse kidney images, without retraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omni-seg-a-scale-aware-dynamic-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supernova Light Curves Approximation based on Neural Network Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supernova-light-curves-approximation-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Normalizing Flows exceeds Gaussian processes in terms of approximation quality as well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supernova-light-curves-approximation-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Acoustic Representation Learning on Breathing and Speech Signals for COVID-19 Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-acoustic-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we describe an approach for representation learning of audio signals for the task of COVID-19 detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-acoustic-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Calibration for Deep Audio Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-calibration-for-deep-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate the uncertainty calibration for deep audio classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-calibration-for-deep-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study of Personalized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-personalized-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is a distributed machine learning approach in which a single server and multiple clients collaboratively build machine learning models without sharing datasets on clients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-personalized-federated</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
