<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 09:12:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Tensor Graph Neural Networks Through Reinforced Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-tensor-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, RTGNN first uses tensor decomposition to extract the graph structure features (GSFs) of each view in the common feature space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-tensor-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Domain Generalization Methods are Strong Baselines for Open Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-domain-generalization-methods-are</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In real-world applications, a machine learning model is required to handle an open-set recognition (OSR), where unknown classes appear during the inference, in addition to a domain shift, where the distribution of data differs between the training and inference phases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-domain-generalization-methods-are</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERTino: an Italian DistilBERT model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bertino-an-italian-distilbert-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent introduction of Transformers language representation models allowed great improvements in many natural language processing (NLP) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bertino-an-italian-distilbert-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-shot Referring Image Segmentation with Global-Local Context Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-referring-image-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this issue, we propose a simple yet effective zero-shot referring image segmentation method by leveraging the pre-trained cross-modal knowledge from CLIP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-referring-image-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Distillation for Feature Extraction in Underwater VSLAM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-distillation-for-feature-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a cross-modal knowledge distillation framework for training an underwater feature detection and matching network (UFEN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-distillation-for-feature-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMEL: Communicative Agents for "Mind" Exploration of Large Scale Language Model Society</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camel-communicative-agents-for-mind</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the challenges of achieving autonomous cooperation, we propose a novel communicative agent framework named role-playing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camel-communicative-agents-for-mind</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoSMo: a Framework for Implementing Conditioned Process Simulation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosmo-a-framework-for-implementing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the literature, several process simulation techniques are available and they are usually built upon process models discovered from a given event log or learned via deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosmo-a-framework-for-implementing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interval Logic Tensor Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interval-logic-tensor-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Interval Real Logic (IRL), a two-sorted logic that interprets knowledge such as sequential properties (traces) and event properties using sequences of real-featured data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interval-logic-tensor-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$\infty$-Diff: Infinite Resolution Diffusion with Subsampled Mollified States</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infty-diff-infinite-resolution-diffusion-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce $\infty$-Diff, a generative diffusion model which directly operates on infinite resolution data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infty-diff-infinite-resolution-diffusion-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Procedure-Aware Pretraining for Instructional Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procedure-aware-pretraining-for-instructional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This graph can then be used to generate pseudo labels to train a video representation that encodes the procedural knowledge in a more accessible form to generalize to multiple procedure understanding tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procedure-aware-pretraining-for-instructional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence in Ovarian Cancer Histopathology: A Systematic Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artificial-intelligence-in-ovarian-cancer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Purpose - To characterise and assess the quality of published research evaluating artificial intelligence (AI) methods for ovarian cancer diagnosis or prognosis using histopathology data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artificial-intelligence-in-ovarian-cancer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Anomaly Detection and Localization of Machine Audio: A GAN-based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-anomaly-detection-and-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic detection of machine anomaly remains challenging for machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-anomaly-detection-and-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Sparse Pairwise Loss for Object Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-sparse-pairwise-loss-for-object-re</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we propose a novel loss paradigm termed Sparse Pairwise (SP) loss that only leverages few appropriate pairs for each class in a mini-batch, and empirically demonstrate that it is sufficient for the ReID tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-sparse-pairwise-loss-for-object-re</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Difference Images for Change Detection Classifiers in SAR Imagery Using Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-difference-images-for-change</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Satellite-based Synthetic Aperture Radar (SAR) images can be used as a source of remote sensed imagery regardless of cloud cover and day-night cycle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-difference-images-for-change</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Bayesian Meta-Learning through Generalized Implicit Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-bayesian-meta-learning-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meta-learning owns unique effectiveness and swiftness in tackling emerging tasks with limited data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-bayesian-meta-learning-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating GPT-4 and ChatGPT on Japanese Medical Licensing Examinations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-gpt-4-and-chatgpt-on-japanese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we evaluate LLM APIs (ChatGPT, GPT-3, and GPT-4) on the Japanese national medical licensing examinations from the past five years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-gpt-4-and-chatgpt-on-japanese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To discriminate the difference in parameter scale, the research community has coined the term large language models (LLM) for the PLMs of significant size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shepherding Slots to Objects: Towards Stable and Robust Object-Centric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shepherding-slots-to-objects-towards-stable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object-centric learning (OCL) aspires general and compositional understanding of scenes by representing a scene as a collection of object-centric representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shepherding-slots-to-objects-towards-stable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Depth Estimation and Mixture of Rain Removal From a Single Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-depth-estimation-and-mixture-of-rain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose an effective image deraining paradigm for Mixture of rain REmoval, called DEMore-Net, which takes full account of the MOR effect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-depth-estimation-and-mixture-of-rain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A fast Multiplicative Updates algorithm for Non-negative Matrix Factorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fast-multiplicative-updates-algorithm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nonnegative Matrix Factorization is an important tool in unsupervised machine learning to decompose a data matrix into a product of parts that are often interpretable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fast-multiplicative-updates-algorithm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Only Train Once: Learning a General Anomaly Enhancement Network with Random Masks for Hyperspectral Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-train-once-learning-a-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trained on a set of anomaly-free hyperspectral images with random masks, our network can learn the spatial context characteristics between anomalies and background in an unsupervised way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-train-once-learning-a-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scardina: Scalable Join Cardinality Estimation by Multiple Density Estimators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scardina-scalable-join-cardinality-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, machine learning-based cardinality estimation methods are replacing traditional methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scardina-scalable-join-cardinality-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeGeeX: A Pre-Trained Model for Code Generation with Multilingual Evaluations on HumanEval-X</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codegeex-a-pre-trained-model-for-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large pre-trained code generation models, such as OpenAI Codex, can generate syntax- and function-correct code, making the coding of programmers more productive and our pursuit of artificial general intelligence closer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codegeex-a-pre-trained-model-for-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complementary Random Masking for RGB-Thermal Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complementary-random-masking-for-rgb-thermal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Also, the proposed self-distillation loss encourages the network to extract complementary and meaningful representations from a single modality or complementary masked modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complementary-random-masking-for-rgb-thermal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Approximation Error in 3D Surface Fitting for Point Cloud Normal Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-approximation-error-in-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing approaches for point cloud normal estimation aim to locally fit a geometric surface and calculate the normal from the fitted surface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-approximation-error-in-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mole Recruitment: Poisoning of Image Classifiers via Selective Batch Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mole-recruitment-poisoning-of-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a data poisoning attack that confounds machine learning models without any manipulation of the image or label.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mole-recruitment-poisoning-of-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WavCaps: A ChatGPT-Assisted Weakly-Labelled Audio Captioning Dataset for Audio-Language Multimodal Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavcaps-a-chatgpt-assisted-weakly-labelled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this data scarcity issue, we introduce WavCaps, the first large-scale weakly-labelled audio captioning dataset, comprising approximately 400k audio clips with paired captions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavcaps-a-chatgpt-assisted-weakly-labelled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neglected Free Lunch -- Learning Image Classifiers Using Annotation Byproducts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neglected-free-lunch-learning-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We refer to the new paradigm of training models with annotation byproducts as learning using annotation byproducts (LUAB).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neglected-free-lunch-learning-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recognition, recall, and retention of few-shot memories in large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recognition-recall-and-retention-of-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recognition experiments, we ask if the model can distinguish the seen example from a novel example; in recall experiments, we ask if the model can correctly recall the seen example when cued by a part of it; and in retention experiments, we periodically probe the model's memory for the original examples as the model is trained continuously with new examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recognition-recall-and-retention-of-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task Oriented Conversational Modelling With Subjective Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-oriented-conversational-modelling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing conversational models are handled by a database(DB) and API based systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-oriented-conversational-modelling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HuggingGPT: Solving AI Tasks with ChatGPT and its Friends in HuggingFace</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hugginggpt-solving-ai-tasks-with-chatgpt-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Solving complicated AI tasks with different domains and modalities is a key step toward artificial general intelligence (AGI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hugginggpt-solving-ai-tasks-with-chatgpt-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked and Adaptive Transformer for Exemplar Based Image Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-and-adaptive-transformer-for-exemplar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this challenge, we improve the accuracy of matching on the one hand, and diminish the role of matching in image generation on the other hand.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-and-adaptive-transformer-for-exemplar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget-Me-Not: Learning to Forget in Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forget-me-not-learning-to-forget-in-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The unlearning problem of deep learning models, once primarily an academic concern, has become a prevalent issue in the industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forget-me-not-learning-to-forget-in-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XPert: Peripheral Circuit &amp; Neural Architecture Co-search for Area and Energy-efficient Xbar-based Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xpert-peripheral-circuit-neural-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The hardware-efficiency and accuracy of Deep Neural Networks (DNNs) implemented on In-memory Computing (IMC) architectures primarily depend on the DNN architecture and the peripheral circuit parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xpert-peripheral-circuit-neural-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Cross-Attention for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-cross-attention-for-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DCA addresses the semantic gap between encoder and decoder features by sequentially capturing channel and spatial dependencies across multi-scale encoder features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-cross-attention-for-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sasaki Metric for Spline Models of Manifold-Valued Trajectories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sasaki-metric-for-spline-models-of-manifold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a generic spatiotemporal framework to analyze manifold-valued measurements, which allows for employing an intrinsic and computationally efficient Riemannian hierarchical model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sasaki-metric-for-spline-models-of-manifold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient distributed representations beyond negative sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-distributed-representations-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our contribution is to show that the sotfmax normalization constants can be estimated in linear time, allowing us to design an efficient optimization strategy to learn distributed representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-distributed-representations-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invertible Convolution with Symmetric Paddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invertible-convolution-with-symmetric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that symmetrically padded convolution can be analytically inverted via DFT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invertible-convolution-with-symmetric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whose Opinions Do Language Models Reflect?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whose-opinions-do-language-models-reflect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models (LMs) are increasingly being used in open-ended contexts, where the opinions reflected by LMs in response to subjective queries can have a profound impact, both on user satisfaction, as well as shaping the views of society at large.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whose-opinions-do-language-models-reflect</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shapley Chains: Extending Shapley Values to Classifier Chains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapley-chains-extending-shapley-values-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to existing methods, this approach allows to attribute a more complete feature contribution to the predictions of multi-output classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapley-chains-extending-shapley-values-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAIR-Diffusion: Object-Level Image Editing with Structure-and-Appearance Paired Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pair-diffusion-object-level-image-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nevertheless, most of them lack fine-grained control over the properties of the different objects present in the image, i. e. object-level image editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pair-diffusion-object-level-image-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeRF-Supervised Deep Stereo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerf-supervised-deep-stereo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel framework for training deep stereo networks effortlessly and without any ground-truth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerf-supervised-deep-stereo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Weight Removal for Faithful and Abstractive Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elastic-weight-removal-for-faithful-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our method -- using different variants of Flan-T5 as a backbone language model -- on multiple datasets for information-seeking dialogue generation and compare our method with state-of-the-art techniques for faithfulness, such as CTRL, Quark, DExperts, and Noisy Channel reranking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elastic-weight-removal-for-faithful-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Line Mapping Revisited</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-line-mapping-revisited</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to sparse keypoints, a handful of line segments can concisely encode the high-level scene layout, as they often delineate the main structural elements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-line-mapping-revisited</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoseFormerV2: Exploring Frequency Domain for Efficient and Robust 3D Human Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poseformerv2-exploring-frequency-domain-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in real scenarios, the performance of PoseFormer and its follow-ups is limited by two factors: (a) The length of the input joint sequence; (b) The quality of 2D joint detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poseformerv2-exploring-frequency-domain-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An evaluation framework for comparing epidemic intelligence systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-evaluation-framework-for-comparing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of Epidemic Intelligence, many Event-Based Surveillance (EBS) systems have been proposed in the literature to promote the early identification and characterization of potential health threats from online sources of any nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-evaluation-framework-for-comparing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Q-learning Based System for Path Planning with UAV Swarms in Obstacle Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-learning-based-system-for-path-planning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Regardless of the size of the map or the number of UAVs in the swarm, the goal of these paths is to ensure complete coverage of an area with fixed obstacles for tasks, like field prospecting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-learning-based-system-for-path-planning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Video Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-video-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe that the concept of streaming video model and the implementation of S-ViT are solid steps towards a unified deep learning architecture for video understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-video-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenMix: Exploring Outlier Samples for Misclassification Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openmix-exploring-outlier-samples-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reliable confidence estimation for deep neural classifiers is a challenging yet fundamental requirement in high-stakes applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openmix-exploring-outlier-samples-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Conceptional Contrastive Learning for Generalized Category Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-conceptional-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This leads traditional novel category discovery (NCD) methods to be incapacitated for GCD, due to their assumption of unlabeled data are only from novel categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-conceptional-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
