<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:06:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SELFormer: Molecular Representation Learning via SELFIES Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selformer-molecular-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, our research demonstrates the benefit of using the SELFIES notations in the context of chemical language modeling and opens up new possibilities for the design and discovery of novel drug candidates with desired features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selformer-molecular-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOOD: Towards Semi-Supervised Oriented Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sood-towards-semi-supervised-oriented-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-Supervised Object Detection (SSOD), aiming to explore unlabeled data for boosting object detectors, has become an active task in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sood-towards-semi-supervised-oriented-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention at SemEval-2023 Task 10: Explainable Detection of Online Sexism (EDOS)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-at-semeval-2023-task-10-explainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we have worked on interpretability, trust, and understanding of the decisions made by models in the form of classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-at-semeval-2023-task-10-explainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-ToolFormer: To Empower LLMs with Graph Reasoning Ability via Prompt Dataset Augmented by ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-toolformer-to-empower-llms-with-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the latest ChatGPT and Toolformer models, we propose the Graph-ToolFormer (Graph Reasoning oriented Toolformer) framework to teach LLMs themselves with prompts augmented by ChatGPT to use external graph reasoning API tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-toolformer-to-empower-llms-with-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambiguous Medical Image Segmentation using Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambiguous-medical-image-segmentation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Collective insights from a group of experts have always proven to outperform an individual's best diagnostic for clinical tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambiguous-medical-image-segmentation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the Detection Transformer as a Data Augmenter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/use-the-detection-transformer-as-a-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, DeMix elaborately selects a semantically rich patch, located by a pre-trained DETR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/use-the-detection-transformer-as-a-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Effective Factors for Improving Visual In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-effective-factors-for-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By doing this, the model can leverage the diverse knowledge stored in different parts of the model to improve its performance on new tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-effective-factors-for-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monte Carlo Linear Clustering with Single-Point Supervision is Enough for Infrared Small Target Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-linear-clustering-with-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core idea of this work is to recover the per-pixel mask of each target from the given single point label by using clustering approaches, which looks simple but is indeed challenging since targets are always insalient and accompanied with background clutters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-linear-clustering-with-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Image Matting: A Comprehensive Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-image-matting-a-comprehensive-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image matting refers to extracting precise alpha matte from natural images, and it plays a critical role in various downstream applications, such as image editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-image-matting-a-comprehensive-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebBrain: Learning to Generate Factually Correct Articles for Queries by Grounding on Large Web Corpus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webbrain-learning-to-generate-factually</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a new NLP task -- generating short factual articles with references for queries by mining supporting evidence from the Web.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webbrain-learning-to-generate-factually</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Learning for Low-Resource Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-low-resource-sentiment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sentiment analysis is the process of identifying and extracting subjective information from text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-low-resource-sentiment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Aware Natural Language Inference with Stochastic Weight Averaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-natural-language-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces Bayesian uncertainty modeling using Stochastic Weight Averaging-Gaussian (SWAG) in Natural Language Understanding (NLU) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-natural-language-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can SAM Segment Anything? When SAM Meets Camouflaged Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-sam-segment-anything-when-sam-meets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we try to ask if SAM can address the COD task and evaluate the performance of SAM on the COD benchmark by employing maximum segmentation evaluation and camouflage location evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-sam-segment-anything-when-sam-meets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coherent Concept-based Explanations in Medical Image and Its Application to Skin Lesion Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coherent-concept-based-explanations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Early detection of melanoma is crucial for preventing severe complications and increasing the chances of successful treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coherent-concept-based-explanations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Localise to segment: crop to improve organ at risk segmentation accuracy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localise-to-segment-crop-to-improve-organ-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some deep learning methods for the segmentation of organs at risk use a two stage process where a localisation network first crops an image to the relevant region and then a locally specialised network segments the cropped organ of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localise-to-segment-crop-to-improve-organ-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detection Transformer with Stable Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-transformer-with-stable-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We point out that the unstable matching in DETR is caused by a multi-optimization path problem, which is highlighted by the one-to-one matching design in DETR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-transformer-with-stable-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Cheaper and Better Diffusion Language Model with Soft-Masked Noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cheaper-and-better-diffusion-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models that are based on iterative denoising have been recently proposed and leveraged in various generation tasks like image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cheaper-and-better-diffusion-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Pre-Training with Twenty-Thousand Classes for Open-Vocabulary Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-pre-training-with-twenty-thousand</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes POMP, a prompt pre-training method for vision-language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-pre-training-with-twenty-thousand</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster Lead Optimization Mapper Algorithm for Large-Scale Relative Free Energy Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-lead-optimization-mapper-algorithm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we aimed to reduce the computational cost of Lomap to enable the construction of FEP graphs for hundreds of compounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-lead-optimization-mapper-algorithm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESPECT: Reinforcement Learning based Edge Scheduling on Pipelined Coral Edge TPUs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/respect-reinforcement-learning-based-edge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNNs) have substantial computational and memory requirements, and the compilation of its computational graphs has a great impact on the performance of resource-constrained (e. g., computation, I/O, and memory-bound) edge computing systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/respect-reinforcement-learning-based-edge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local-Global Temporal Difference Learning for Satellite Video Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-global-temporal-difference-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optical-flow-based and kernel-based approaches have been widely explored for temporal compensation in satellite video super-resolution (VSR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-global-temporal-difference-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Incremental Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-incremental-semantic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, new clients collecting novel classes may join in the global training of FSS, which further exacerbates catastrophic forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-incremental-semantic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagle: End-to-end Deep Reinforcement Learning based Autonomous Control of PTZ Cameras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eagle-end-to-end-deep-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing approaches for autonomous control of pan-tilt-zoom (PTZ) cameras use multiple stages where object detection and localization are performed separately from the control of the PTZ mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eagle-end-to-end-deep-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPnet-ST-v2: Multipurpose Spoken Language Translation Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/espnet-st-v2-multipurpose-spoken-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ESPnet-ST-v2 is a revamp of the open-source ESPnet-ST toolkit necessitated by the broadening interests of the spoken language translation community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/espnet-st-v2-multipurpose-spoken-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing Data Imputation with Graph Laplacian Pyramid Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/missing-data-imputation-with-graph-laplacian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data imputation is a prevalent and important task due to the ubiquitousness of missing data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/missing-data-imputation-with-graph-laplacian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluate Geometry of Radiance Field with Low-frequency Color Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluate-geometry-of-radiance-field-with-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our key insight is that the better the geometry is, the lower-frequency the computed color field is.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluate-geometry-of-radiance-field-with-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is ChatGPT a Good Sentiment Analyzer? A Preliminary Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-chatgpt-a-good-sentiment-analyzer-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, ChatGPT has drawn great attention from both the research community and the public.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-chatgpt-a-good-sentiment-analyzer-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Real-time Text-driven Image Manipulation with Unconditional Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-time-text-driven-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we show that our approach can adapt the pretrained model to the user-specified image and text description on the fly just for 4 seconds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-time-text-driven-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Point-based Algorithm for Multi-agent Control Using the Common Information Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-point-based-algorithm-for-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Common Information (CI) approach provides a systematic way to transform a multi-agent stochastic control problem to a single-agent partially observed Markov decision problem (POMDP) called the coordinator's POMDP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-point-based-algorithm-for-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monocular 3D Human Pose Estimation for Sports Broadcasts using Partial Sports Field Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-3d-human-pose-estimation-for-sports</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recovering the actual 3D movement of the limbs (kinematics) of the athletes requires lifting these 2D pixel locations back into a third dimension, implying a certain scene geometry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-3d-human-pose-estimation-for-sports</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H2RBox-v2: Boosting HBox-supervised Oriented Object Detection via Symmetric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h2rbox-v2-boosting-hbox-supervised-oriented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increasing demand for oriented object detection e. g. in autonomous driving and remote sensing, the oriented annotation has become a labor-intensive work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h2rbox-v2-boosting-hbox-supervised-oriented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Evaluation of Bangla Word Analogies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-evaluation-of-bangla-word-analogies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a high-quality dataset for evaluating the quality of Bangla word embeddings, which is a fundamental task in the field of Natural Language Processing (NLP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-evaluation-of-bangla-word-analogies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Active Alignment of Knowledge Graph Entities and Schemata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-active-alignment-of-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With deep learning, it learns the embeddings of entities, relations and classes, and jointly aligns them in a semi-supervised manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-active-alignment-of-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAGI: When LLM Meets Domain Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openagi-when-llm-meets-domain-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, the LLM is responsible for synthesizing various external models for solving complex tasks, while RLTF provides feedback to improve its task-solving ability, enabling a feedback loop for self-improving AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openagi-when-llm-meets-domain-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAN: Fatigue-Aware Network for Click-Through Rate Prediction in E-commerce Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fan-fatigue-aware-network-for-click-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then the frequency spectrum is modulated by category information of the target item to model the bias that both the upper bound of fatigue and users' patience is different for different categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fan-fatigue-aware-network-for-click-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experience-Based Evolutionary Algorithms for Expensive Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/experience-based-evolutionary-algorithms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental results on expensive multi-objective and constrained optimization problems demonstrate that experiences gained from related tasks are beneficial for the saving of evaluation budgets on the target problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/experience-based-evolutionary-algorithms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Operational Flexibility of Active Distribution Networks with Low Observability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-operational-flexibility-of-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing approaches estimating the distribution network flexibility require the full observability of the system, meaning topological and state knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-operational-flexibility-of-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoboPianist: A Benchmark for High-Dimensional Robot Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robopianist-a-benchmark-for-high-dimensional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new benchmarking suite for high-dimensional control, targeted at testing high spatial and temporal precision, coordination, and planning, all with an underactuated system frequently making-and-breaking contacts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robopianist-a-benchmark-for-high-dimensional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video ChatCaptioner: Towards the Enriched Spatiotemporal Descriptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-chatcaptioner-towards-the-enriched</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video captioning aims to convey dynamic scenes from videos using natural language, facilitating the understanding of spatiotemporal information within our environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-chatcaptioner-towards-the-enriched</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PriorCVAE: scalable MCMC parameter inference with Bayesian deep generative modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/priorcvae-scalable-mcmc-parameter-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In applied fields where the speed of inference and model flexibility are crucial, the use of Bayesian inference for models with a stochastic process as their prior, e. g. Gaussian processes (GPs) is ubiquitous.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/priorcvae-scalable-mcmc-parameter-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class-Imbalanced Learning on Graphs: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-imbalanced-learning-on-graphs-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concerning the latter, we critically analyze recent work in CILG and discuss urgent lines of inquiry within the topic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-imbalanced-learning-on-graphs-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An investigation of speaker independent phrase break models in End-to-End TTS systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-investigation-of-speaker-independent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents our work on phrase break prediction in the context of end-to-end TTS systems, motivated by the following questions: (i) Is there any utility in incorporating an explicit phrasing model in an end-to-end TTS system?, and (ii) How do you evaluate the effectiveness of a phrasing model in an end-to-end TTS system?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-investigation-of-speaker-independent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slide-Transformer: Hierarchical Vision Transformer with Local Self-Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slide-transformer-hierarchical-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-attention mechanism has been a key factor in the recent progress of Vision Transformer (ViT), which enables adaptive feature extraction from global contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slide-transformer-hierarchical-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARNOLD: A Benchmark for Language-Grounded Task Learning With Continuous States in Realistic 3D Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arnold-a-benchmark-for-language-grounded-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these challenges, we present ARNOLD, a benchmark that evaluates language-grounded task learning with continuous states in realistic 3D scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arnold-a-benchmark-for-language-grounded-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISC: Generating Realistic Synthetic Bilingual Insurance Contract</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risc-generating-realistic-synthetic-bilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RISC generates look-alike automobile insurance contracts based on the Quebec regulatory insurance form in French and English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risc-generating-realistic-synthetic-bilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curricular Object Manipulation in LiDAR-based Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curricular-object-manipulation-in-lidar-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the loss design, we propose the COMLoss to dynamically predict object-level difficulties and emphasize objects of different difficulties based on training stages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curricular-object-manipulation-in-lidar-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdCLIP: Unsupervised Crowd Counting via Vision-Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crowdclip-unsupervised-crowd-counting-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, CrowdCLIP is the first to investigate the vision language knowledge to solve the counting problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crowdclip-unsupervised-crowd-counting-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Sampling Promoting for Stochastic Human Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-sampling-promoting-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we model the trajectory sampling as a Gaussian process and construct an acquisition function to measure the potential sampling value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-sampling-promoting-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeRF applied to satellite imagery for surface reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerf-applied-to-satellite-imagery-for-surface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[S-NeRF improves on the standard Neural Radiance Field (NeRF) method by considering the radiance as a function of the albedo and the irradiance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerf-applied-to-satellite-imagery-for-surface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLVOS23: A Long Video Object Segmentation Dataset for Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clvos23-a-long-video-object-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual learning in real-world scenarios is a major challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clvos23-a-long-video-object-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
