<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 09:14:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating ChatGPT-4 Vision on Brazil's National Undergraduate Computer Science Exam</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-chatgpt-4-vision-on-brazil-s</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent integration of visual capabilities into Large Language Models (LLMs) has the potential to play a pivotal role in science and technology education, where visual elements such as diagrams, charts, and tables are commonly used to improve the learning experience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-chatgpt-4-vision-on-brazil-s</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tilt and Average : Geometric Adjustment of the Last Layer for Recalibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tilt-and-average-geometric-adjustment-of-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we offer an algorithm that transforms the weights of the last layer of the classifier, distinct from the calibration-map-based approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tilt-and-average-geometric-adjustment-of-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCKansformer: Fine-Grained Classification of Bone Marrow Cells via Kansformer Backbone and Hierarchical Attention Mechanisms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sckansformer-fine-grained-classification-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model integrates the Kansformer Encoder, SCConv Encoder, and Global-Local Attention Encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sckansformer-fine-grained-classification-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Will Gradient Regularization Be Harmful?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-will-gradient-regularization-be-harmful</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, we note that scalable models tend to rely more on the GR warmup, where the performance can be improved by up to 3\% on Cifar10 compared to baseline GR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-will-gradient-regularization-be-harmful</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harm Mitigation in Recommender Systems under User Preference Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harm-mitigation-in-recommender-systems-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider a recommender system that takes into account the interplay between recommendations, the evolution of user interests, and harmful content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harm-mitigation-in-recommender-systems-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sim-to-Real Transfer via 3D Feature Fields for Vision-and-Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim-to-real-transfer-via-3d-feature-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-and-language navigation (VLN) enables the agent to navigate to a remote location in 3D environments following the natural language instruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim-to-real-transfer-via-3d-feature-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntentionQA: A Benchmark for Evaluating Purchase Intention Comprehension Abilities of Language Models in E-commerce</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intentionqa-a-benchmark-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Enhancing Language Models' (LMs) ability to understand purchase intentions in E-commerce scenarios is crucial for their effective assistance in various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intentionqa-a-benchmark-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FZI-WIM at SemEval-2024 Task 2: Self-Consistent CoT for Complex NLI in Biomedical Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fzi-wim-at-semeval-2024-task-2-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes the inference system of FZI-WIM at the SemEval-2024 Task 2: Safe Biomedical Natural Language Inference for Clinical Trials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fzi-wim-at-semeval-2024-task-2-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Benefits of Vision Foundation Models for Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-benefits-of-vision-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These results underscore the significant benefits of combining VFMs with UDA, setting new standards and baselines for Unsupervised Domain Adaptation in semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-benefits-of-vision-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving rule mining via embedding-based link prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-rule-mining-via-embedding-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rule mining on knowledge graphs allows for explainable link prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-rule-mining-via-embedding-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GradeADreamer: Enhanced Text-to-3D Generation Using Gaussian Splatting and Multi-View Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradeadreamer-enhanced-text-to-3d-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-3D generation has shown promising results, yet common challenges such as the Multi-face Janus problem and extended generation time for high-quality assets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradeadreamer-enhanced-text-to-3d-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RaNeuS: Ray-adaptive Neural Surface Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raneus-ray-adaptive-neural-surface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our objective is to leverage a differentiable radiance field \eg NeRF to reconstruct detailed 3D surfaces in addition to producing the standard novel view renderings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raneus-ray-adaptive-neural-surface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable AI for Comparative Analysis of Intrusion Detection Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-ai-for-comparative-analysis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We trained all models to the accuracy of 90\% on the UNSW-NB15 Dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-ai-for-comparative-analysis-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coralai: Intrinsic Evolution of Embodied Neural Cellular Automata Ecosystems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coralai-intrinsic-evolution-of-embodied</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents Coralai, a framework for exploring diverse ecosystems of Neural Cellular Automata (NCA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coralai-intrinsic-evolution-of-embodied</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear Contextual Bandits with Hybrid Payoff: Revisited</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-contextual-bandits-with-hybrid-payoff</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We can reduce this setting to two closely related settings (a) Shared - no arm specific parameters, and (b) Disjoint - only arm specific parameters, enabling the application of two popular state of the art algorithms - $\texttt{LinUCB}$ and $\texttt{DisLinUCB}$ (Algorithm 1 in (Li et al. 2010)).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-contextual-bandits-with-hybrid-payoff</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unraveling Anomalies in Time: Unsupervised Discovery and Isolation of Anomalous Behavior in Bio-regenerative Life Support System Telemetry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-anomalies-in-time-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The detection of abnormal or critical system states is essential in condition monitoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-anomalies-in-time-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Concept Binder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-concept-binder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The challenge in object-based visual reasoning lies in generating descriptive yet distinct concept representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-concept-binder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeltaPhi: Learning Physical Trajectory Residual for PDE Solving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deltaphi-learning-physical-trajectory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although neural operator networks theoretically approximate any operator mapping, the limited generalization capability prevents them from learning correct physical dynamics when potential data biases exist, particularly in the practical PDE solving scenario where the available data amount is restricted or the resolution is extremely low.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deltaphi-learning-physical-trajectory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLEnD: A Benchmark for LLMs on Everyday Knowledge in Diverse Cultures and Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blend-a-benchmark-for-llms-on-everyday</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we introduce BLEnD, a hand-crafted benchmark designed to evaluate LLMs' everyday knowledge across diverse cultures and languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blend-a-benchmark-for-llms-on-everyday</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IGL-Bench: Establishing the Comprehensive Benchmark for Imbalanced Graph Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/igl-bench-establishing-the-comprehensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep graph learning has gained grand popularity over the past years due to its versatility and success in representing graph data across a wide range of domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/igl-bench-establishing-the-comprehensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiVLC: Extending Vision-Language Compositionality Evaluation with Text-to-Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bivlc-extending-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The novelty of BiVLC is to add a synthetic hard negative image generated from the synthetic text, resulting in two image-to-text retrieval examples (one for each image) and, more importantly, two text-to-image retrieval examples (one for each text).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bivlc-extending-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Efficient Pareto Set Approximation via Mixture of Experts Based Model Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-pareto-set-approximation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Once the routers are learned and a preference vector is set, the MoE module can be unloaded, thus no additional computational cost is introduced during inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-pareto-set-approximation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeshAnything: Artist-Created Mesh Generation with Autoregressive Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meshanything-artist-created-mesh-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, 3D assets created via reconstruction and generation have matched the quality of manually crafted assets, highlighting their potential for replacement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meshanything-artist-created-mesh-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Be like a Goldfish, Don't Memorize! Mitigating Memorization in Generative LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/be-like-a-goldfish-don-t-memorize-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models can memorize and repeat their training data, causing privacy and copyright risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/be-like-a-goldfish-don-t-memorize-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Vocabulary Semantic Segmentation with Image Embedding Balancing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-semantic-segmentation-with-4</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To learn a consistent semantic structure from CLIP, the SSC Loss aligns the inter-classes affinity in the image feature space with that in the text feature space of CLIP, thereby improving the generalization ability of our model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-semantic-segmentation-with-4</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TACCO: Task-guided Co-clustering of Clinical Concepts and Patient Visits for Disease Subtyping based on EHR Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tacco-task-guided-co-clustering-of-clinical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce TACCO, a novel framework that jointly discovers clusters of clinical concepts and patient visits based on a hypergraph modeling of EHR data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tacco-task-guided-co-clustering-of-clinical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some contributions to Lagrangian modelling of Power Converters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/some-contributions-to-lagrangian-modelling-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, contributions are made regarding the procedure to be followed for the Lagrangian modelling of power converters and the incorporation of constraints within the Lagrangian framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/some-contributions-to-lagrangian-modelling-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Know How: Combining Prior Policies to Solve New Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-know-how-combining-prior-policies-to-solve</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-Task Reinforcement Learning aims at developing agents that are able to continually evolve and adapt to new scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-know-how-combining-prior-policies-to-solve</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Multi-view Molecular Representations with Structured and Unstructured Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-multi-view-molecular-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we present MV-Mol, a molecular representation learning model that harvests multi-view molecular expertise from chemical structures, unstructured knowledge from biomedical texts, and structured knowledge from knowledge graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-multi-view-molecular-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Spectral Graph Neural Networks: A Comprehensive Study on Effectiveness and Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-spectral-graph-neural-networks-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the recent advancements in graph neural networks (GNNs), spectral GNNs have received increasing popularity by virtue of their specialty in capturing graph signals in the frequency domain, demonstrating promising capability in specific tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-spectral-graph-neural-networks-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sycophancy to Subterfuge: Investigating Reward-Tampering in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sycophancy-to-subterfuge-investigating-reward</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We construct a curriculum of increasingly sophisticated gameable environments and find that training on early-curriculum environments leads to more specification gaming on remaining environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sycophancy-to-subterfuge-investigating-reward</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScaLES: Scalable Latent Exploration Score for Pre-Trained Generative Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scales-scalable-latent-exploration-score-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop Scalable Latent Exploration Score (ScaLES) to mitigate over-exploration in Latent Space Optimization (LSO), a popular method for solving black-box discrete optimization problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scales-scalable-latent-exploration-score-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision-Language Models Meet Meteorology: Developing Models for Extreme Weather Events Detection with Heatmaps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-language-models-meet-meteorology</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-time detection and prediction of extreme weather protect human lives and infrastructure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-language-models-meet-meteorology</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SkySenseGPT: A Fine-Grained Instruction Tuning Dataset and Model for Remote Sensing Vision-Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skysensegpt-a-fine-grained-instruction-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remote Sensing Large Multi-Modal Models (RSLMMs) are developing rapidly and showcase significant capabilities in remote sensing imagery (RSI) comprehension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skysensegpt-a-fine-grained-instruction-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChartMimic: Evaluating LMM's Cross-Modal Reasoning Capability via Chart-to-Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chartmimic-evaluating-lmm-s-cross-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new benchmark, ChartMimic, aimed at assessing the visually-grounded code generation capabilities of large multimodal models (LMMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chartmimic-evaluating-lmm-s-cross-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUMA: A Benchmark Dataset for Learning from Uncertain and Multimodal Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/luma-a-benchmark-dataset-for-learning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LUMA is also available as a Python package including the functions for generating multiple variants of the dataset with controlling the diversity of the data, the amount of noise for each modality, and adding out-of-distribution samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/luma-a-benchmark-dataset-for-learning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAnimalTracks: A Dataset for Animal Track Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openanimaltracks-a-dataset-for-animal-track</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce OpenAnimalTracks dataset, the first publicly available labeled dataset designed to facilitate the automated classification and detection of animal footprints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openanimaltracks-a-dataset-for-animal-track</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperSVG: Superpixel-based Scalable Vector Graphics Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supersvg-superpixel-based-scalable-vector-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we propose a two-stage self-training framework, where a coarse-stage model is employed to reconstruct the main structure and a refinement-stage model is used for enriching the details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supersvg-superpixel-based-scalable-vector-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIRO: Hierarchical Information Retrieval Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiro-hierarchical-information-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) excel in natural language tasks but face limitations due to static training datasets, resulting in outdated or contextually shallow responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiro-hierarchical-information-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Two-Stage Masked Autoencoder Based Network for Indoor Depth Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-stage-masked-autoencoder-based-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to the existing methods, our proposed network, achieves the state-of-the-art performance on the Matterport3D dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-stage-masked-autoencoder-based-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large language model validity via enhanced conformal prediction methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-validity-via-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These methods work by filtering claims from the LLM's original response if a scoring function evaluated on the claim fails to exceed a threshold calibrated via split conformal prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-validity-via-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CliBench: Multifaceted Evaluation of Large Language Models in Clinical Decisions on Diagnoses, Procedures, Lab Tests Orders and Prescriptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clibench-multifaceted-evaluation-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The integration of Artificial Intelligence (AI), especially Large Language Models (LLMs), into the clinical diagnosis process offers significant potential to improve the efficiency and accessibility of medical care.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clibench-multifaceted-evaluation-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal randomised signatures for generative time series modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-randomised-signatures-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, we employ randomised signature to introduce a generative model for financial time series data in the spirit of reservoir computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-randomised-signatures-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Model-Based Reinforcement Learning with an Adversarial Auxiliary Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-model-based-reinforcement-learning-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By learning a pessimistic world model and demonstrating its role in improving policy robustness, our research contributes towards making (model-based) RL more robust.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-model-based-reinforcement-learning-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POWN: Prototypical Open-World Node Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pown-prototypical-open-world-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of \textit{true} open-world semi-supervised node classification, in which nodes in a graph either belong to known or new classes, with the latter not present during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pown-prototypical-open-world-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DurLAR: A High-fidelity 128-channel LiDAR Dataset with Panoramic Ambient and Reflectivity Imagery for Multi-modal Autonomous Driving Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/durlar-a-high-fidelity-128-channel-lidar-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present DurLAR, a high-fidelity 128-channel 3D LiDAR dataset with panoramic ambient (near infrared) and reflectivity imagery, as well as a sample benchmark task using depth estimation for autonomous driving applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/durlar-a-high-fidelity-128-channel-lidar-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Does Distribution Matching Help Domain Generalization: An Information-theoretic Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-does-distribution-matching-help-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain generalization aims to learn invariance across multiple training domains, thereby enhancing generalization against out-of-distribution data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-does-distribution-matching-help-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Details Make a Difference: Object State-Sensitive Neurorobotic Task Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/details-make-a-difference-object-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The state of an object reflects its current status or condition and is important for a robot's task planning and manipulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/details-make-a-difference-object-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Solution-Aware Transformers for Efficiently Solving Quadratic Assignment Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-solution-aware-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently various optimization problems, such as Mixed Integer Linear Programming Problems (MILPs), have undergone comprehensive investigation, leveraging the capabilities of machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-solution-aware-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Evaluation of Out-of-Distribution Detection: A Sorites Paradox</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-evaluation-of-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we construct a benchmark named Incremental Shift OOD (IS-OOD) to address the issue, in which we divide the test samples into subsets with different semantic and covariate shift degrees relative to the ID dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-evaluation-of-out-of</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
