<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 09:13:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>LION: Linear Group RNN for 3D Object Detection in Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lion-linear-group-rnn-for-3d-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, we simply introduce a 3D spatial feature descriptor and integrate it into the linear group RNN operators to enhance their spatial features rather than blindly increasing the number of scanning orders for voxel features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lion-linear-group-rnn-for-3d-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervision Improves Diffusion Models for Tabular Data Imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervision-improves-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, the sparsity inherent in tabular data poses challenges for diffusion models in accurately modeling the data manifold, impacting the robustness of these models for data imputation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervision-improves-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KiVA: Kid-inspired Visual Analogies for Testing Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kiva-kid-inspired-visual-analogies-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates visual analogical reasoning in large multimodal models (LMMs) compared to human adults and children.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kiva-kid-inspired-visual-analogies-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AsEP: Benchmarking Deep Learning Methods for Antibody-specific Epitope Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asep-benchmarking-deep-learning-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AsEP comes with an easy-to-use interface in Python and pre-built graph representations of each antibody-antigen complex while also supporting customizable embedding methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asep-benchmarking-deep-learning-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RefMask3D: Language-Guided Transformer for 3D Referring Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refmask3d-language-guided-transformer-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D referring segmentation is an emerging and challenging vision-language task that aims to segment the object described by a natural language expression in a point cloud scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refmask3d-language-guided-transformer-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Side of Function Calling: Pathways to Jailbreaking Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dark-side-of-function-calling-pathways-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable capabilities, but their power comes with significant security considerations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dark-side-of-function-calling-pathways-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Inference of Vision Instruction-Following Models with Elastic Cache</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-inference-of-vision-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Surrounding less important caches are then merged with these anchors, enhancing the preservation of contextual information in the KV caches while yielding an arbitrary acceleration ratio.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-inference-of-vision-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Brain Tumor Connectomics using Graphs and Persistent Homology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-brain-tumor-connectomics-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The findings obtained from this study underscore the potential of persistent homology and graph theoretical analysis of the whole-brain connectome in detecting alterations in structural connectivity patterns specific to different types of brain tumors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-brain-tumor-connectomics-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Train the Teacher Model for Effective Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-train-the-teacher-model-for-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, it was shown that the role of the teacher in knowledge distillation (KD) is to provide the student with an estimate of the true Bayes conditional probability density (BCPD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-train-the-teacher-model-for-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost-effective Instruction Learning for Pathology Vision and Language Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-effective-instruction-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we propose a cost-effective instruction learning framework for conversational pathology named as CLOVER.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-effective-instruction-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Deepsets for Off-policy Evaluation under Spatial or Spatio-temporal Interferences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-deepsets-for-off-policy-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Off-policy evaluation (OPE) is widely applied in sectors such as pharmaceuticals and e-commerce to evaluate the efficacy of novel products or policies from offline datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-deepsets-for-off-policy-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keypoint Promptable Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/keypoint-promptable-re-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by recent work on prompting in vision, we introduce Keypoint Promptable ReID (KPR), a novel formulation of the ReID problem that explicitly complements the input bounding box with a set of semantic keypoints indicating the intended target.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/keypoint-promptable-re-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reshape Dimensions Network for Speaker Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reshape-dimensions-network-for-speaker-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present Reshape Dimensions Network (ReDimNet), a novel neural network architecture for extracting utterance-level speaker representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reshape-dimensions-network-for-speaker-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large-Scale Sensitivity Analysis on Latent Embeddings and Dimensionality Reductions for Text Spatializations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-sensitivity-analysis-on-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we analyzed the resulting 42817 tabular data points in a descriptive statistical analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-sensitivity-analysis-on-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Fine-grained Object Detection in Aerial Images via Orthogonal Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-fine-grained-object-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This letter introduces Orthogonal Mapping (OM), a simple yet effective method aimed at addressing the challenge of semantic confusion inherent in FGOD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-fine-grained-object-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Limitations of Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks in Classification: Insights to Software Training and Hardware Implementation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-limitations-of-kolmogorov</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks (KANs), a novel type of neural network, have recently gained popularity and attention due to the ability to substitute multi-layer perceptions (MLPs) in artificial intelligence (AI) with higher accuracy and interoperability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-limitations-of-kolmogorov</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmentation by registration-enabled SAM prompt engineering using five reference images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-by-registration-enabled-sam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach utilises established image registration algorithms to align the new image (to-be-segmented) and a small number of reference images, without requiring segmentation labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-by-registration-enabled-sam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move and Act: Enhanced Object Manipulation and Background Integrity for Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/move-and-act-enhanced-object-manipulation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these methods lack control over the generation position of the edited object and have issues with background preservation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/move-and-act-enhanced-object-manipulation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-informed nonlinear vector autoregressive models for the prediction of dynamical systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-nonlinear-vector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning techniques have recently been of great interest for solving differential equations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-nonlinear-vector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Numerical Literals in Link Prediction: A Critical Examination of Models and Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/numerical-literals-in-link-prediction-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a methodology to evaluate LP models that incorporate numerical literals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/numerical-literals-in-link-prediction-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Very Large-Scale Multi-Agent Simulation in AgentScope</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/very-large-scale-multi-agent-simulation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in large language models (LLMs) have opened new avenues for applying multi-agent systems in very large-scale simulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/very-large-scale-multi-agent-simulation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StreamMOS: Streaming Moving Object Segmentation with Multi-View Perception and Dual-Span Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streammos-streaming-moving-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we utilize a short-term memory to convey historical features, which can be regarded as spatial prior of moving objects and adopted to enhance current inference by temporal fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streammos-streaming-moving-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HVM-1: Large-scale video models pretrained with nearly 5000 hours of human-like video data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hvm-1-large-scale-video-models-pretrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Human-like Video Models (HVM-1), large-scale video models pretrained with nearly 5000 hours of curated human-like video data (mostly egocentric, temporally extended, continuous video recordings), using the spatiotemporal masked autoencoder (ST-MAE) algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hvm-1-large-scale-video-models-pretrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Data Labeling for Software Vulnerability Prediction Models: How Far Are We?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-data-labeling-for-software</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Background: Software Vulnerability (SV) prediction needs large-sized and high-quality data to perform well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-data-labeling-for-software</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoRA-Pro: Are Low-Rank Adapters Properly Optimized?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lora-pro-are-low-rank-adapters-properly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method constrains the optimization process, shrinking the performance gap between LoRA and full fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lora-pro-are-low-rank-adapters-properly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNA: Hard-constraint Neural Network for Consistent Activity Coefficient Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hanna-hard-constraint-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the first hard-constraint neural network for predicting activity coefficients (HANNA), a thermodynamic mixture property that is the basis for many applications in science and engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hanna-hard-constraint-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Training with Direct Preference Optimization Improves Chain-of-Thought Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-training-with-direct-preference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also show that the conventional self-training can be further augmented by a preference learning algorithm called Direct Preference Optimization (DPO).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-training-with-direct-preference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Driven Neural Collaborative Filtering Model for Paper Source Tracing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-driven-neural-collaborative-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identifying significant references within the complex interrelations of a citation knowledge graph is challenging, which encompasses connections through citations, authorship, keywords, and other relational attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-driven-neural-collaborative-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MapTune: Advancing ASIC Technology Mapping via Reinforcement Learning Guided Library Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maptune-advancing-asic-technology-mapping-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The effectiveness of MapTune is evaluated on a wide range of benchmarks, different technology libraries and technology mappers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maptune-advancing-asic-technology-mapping-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint RGB-Spectral Decomposition Model Guided Image Enhancement in Mobile Photography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-rgb-spectral-decomposition-model-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The integration of miniaturized spectrometers into mobile devices offers new avenues for image quality enhancement and facilitates novel downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-rgb-spectral-decomposition-model-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topology-Preserving Downsampling of Binary Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-preserving-downsampling-of-binary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel discrete optimization-based approach to generate downsampled versions of binary images that are guaranteed to have the same topology as the original, measured by the zeroth and first Betti numbers of the black regions, while having good similarity to the original image as measured by IoU and Dice scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-preserving-downsampling-of-binary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDS-ED: Multimodal Decision Support in the Emergency Department -- a Benchmark Dataset for Diagnoses and Deterioration Prediction in Emergency Medicine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mds-ed-multimodal-decision-support-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods: We introduce a dataset based on MIMIC-IV, benchmarking protocol, and initial results for evaluating multimodal decision support in the emergency department (ED).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mds-ed-multimodal-decision-support-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LKCell: Efficient Cell Nuclei Instance Segmentation with Large Convolution Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lkcell-efficient-cell-nuclei-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our method on the most challenging benchmark and achieve state-of-the-art results (0. 5080 mPQ) in cell nuclei instance segmentation with only 21. 6% FLOPs compared with the previous leading method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lkcell-efficient-cell-nuclei-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Training Data with Lossy Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-training-data-with-lossy-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to capture this trade-off and optimize storage of training data, we propose a `storage scaling law' that describes the joint evolution of test error with sample size and number of bits per image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-training-data-with-lossy-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Temporal Causality for Advanced Temporal Action Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-temporal-causality-for-advanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a fundamental task in long-form video understanding, temporal action detection (TAD) aims to capture inherent temporal relations in untrimmed videos and identify candidate actions with precise boundaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-temporal-causality-for-advanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Query Refinement Framework for Bird's-Eye-View Semantic Segmentation from Surrounding Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-query-refinement-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During training, we enforce both the lowest and final query maps to align with the ground-truth BEV semantic map to help our model effectively capture the global and local characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-query-refinement-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dependency Transformer Grammars: Integrating Dependency Structures into Transformer Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dependency-transformer-grammars-integrating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Syntactic Transformer language models aim to achieve better generalization through simultaneously modeling syntax trees and sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dependency-transformer-grammars-integrating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward an Integrated Decision Making Framework for Optimized Stroke Diagnosis with DSA and Treatment under Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-an-integrated-decision-making</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study addresses the challenge of stroke diagnosis and treatment under uncertainty, a critical issue given the rapid progression and severe consequences of stroke conditions such as aneurysms, arteriovenous malformations (AVM), and occlusions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-an-integrated-decision-making</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden or Inferred: Fair Learning-To-Rank with Unknown Demographics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-or-inferred-fair-learning-to-rank-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We examine a spectrum of fair LTR strategies ranging from fair LTR with and without demographic features hidden versus inferred to fairness-unaware LTR followed by fair re-ranking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-or-inferred-fair-learning-to-rank-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Tensor PCA via Tensor Decomposition for Unsupervised Feature Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-tensor-pca-via-tensor-decomposition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, introducing Tensor Decomposition (TD) methods into unsupervised feature selection (UFS) has been a rising research point.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-tensor-pca-via-tensor-decomposition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SepsisLab: Early Sepsis Prediction with Uncertainty Quantification and Active Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sepsislab-early-sepsis-prediction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clinicians and potential sepsis patients can benefit from the system in early prediction and diagnosis of sepsis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sepsislab-early-sepsis-prediction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEEKABOO: Hiding parts of an image for unsupervised object localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peekaboo-hiding-parts-of-an-image-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Localizing objects in an unsupervised manner poses significant challenges due to the absence of key visual information such as the appearance, type and number of objects, as well as the lack of labeled object classes typically available in supervised settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peekaboo-hiding-parts-of-an-image-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RT-DETRv2: Improved Baseline with Bag-of-Freebies for Real-Time Detection Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rt-detrv2-improved-baseline-with-bag-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RT-DETRv2 builds upon the previous state-of-the-art real-time detector, RT-DETR, and opens up a set of bag-of-freebies for flexibility and practicality, as well as optimizing the training strategy to achieve enhanced performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rt-detrv2-improved-baseline-with-bag-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-aware Multi-task Learning for Pedestrian Intent and Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-multi-task-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The effectiveness of PTINet in predicting pedestrian behavior paves the way for the development of automated systems capable of seamlessly interacting with pedestrians in urban settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-multi-task-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MuST: Multi-Scale Transformers for Surgical Phase Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/must-multi-scale-transformers-for-surgical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Phase recognition in surgical videos is crucial for enhancing computer-aided surgical systems as it enables automated understanding of sequential procedural stages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/must-multi-scale-transformers-for-surgical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Knowledge Tracing Models via k-Sparse Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-knowledge-tracing-models-via-k</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that our \textsc{sparseKT} is able to help attentional KT models get rid of irrelevant student interactions and have comparable predictive performance when compared to 11 state-of-the-art KT models on three publicly available real-world educational datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-knowledge-tracing-models-via-k</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Train-Attention: Meta-Learning Where to Focus in Continual Knowledge Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/train-attention-meta-learning-where-to-focus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous studies on continual knowledge learning (CKL) in large language models (LLMs) have predominantly focused on approaches such as regularization, architectural modifications, and rehearsal techniques to mitigate catastrophic forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/train-attention-meta-learning-where-to-focus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take a Step and Reconsider: Sequence Decoding for Self-Improved Neural Combinatorial Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-a-step-and-reconsider-sequence-decoding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The constructive approach within Neural Combinatorial Optimization (NCO) treats a combinatorial optimization problem as a finite Markov decision process, where solutions are built incrementally through a sequence of decisions guided by a neural policy network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-a-step-and-reconsider-sequence-decoding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M4: Multi-Proxy Multi-Gate Mixture of Experts Network for Multiple Instance Learning in Histopathology Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m4-multi-proxy-multi-gate-mixture-of-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiple instance learning (MIL) has been successfully applied for whole slide images (WSIs) analysis in computational pathology, enabling a wide range of prediction tasks from tumor subtyping to inferring genetic mutations and multi-omics biomarkers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m4-multi-proxy-multi-gate-mixture-of-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Channel-Aware Low-Rank Adaptation in Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/channel-aware-low-rank-adaptation-in-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The former adopts individual channel treatment and has been shown to be more robust to distribution shifts, but lacks sufficient capacity to model meaningful channel interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/channel-aware-low-rank-adaptation-in-time</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
