<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 09:12:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Applying Bayesian Ridge Regression AI Modeling in Virus Severity Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applying-bayesian-ridge-regression-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) is a powerful tool for reshaping healthcare systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applying-bayesian-ridge-regression-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Node-based Knowledge Graph Contrastive Learning for Medical Relationship Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/node-based-knowledge-graph-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly in biomedical relationship prediction tasks, NC-KGE outperforms all baselines on datasets such as PharmKG8k-28, DRKG17k-21, and BioKG72k-14, especially in predicting drug combination relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/node-based-knowledge-graph-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$\textit{Swap and Predict}$ -- Predicting the Semantic Changes in Words across Corpora by Context Swapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textit-swap-and-predict-predicting-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intuitively, if the meaning of $w$ does not change between $\mathcal{C}_1$ and $\mathcal{C}_2$, we would expect the distributions of contextualised word embeddings of $w$ to remain the same before and after this random swapping process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textit-swap-and-predict-predicting-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Stage Pre-training Enhanced by ChatGPT for Multi-Scenario Multi-Domain Dialogue Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stage-pre-training-enhanced-by-chatgpt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we first conduct domain-aware pre-training using large-scale multi-scenario multi-domain dialogue data to enhance the adaptability of our pre-trained model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stage-pre-training-enhanced-by-chatgpt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G-SPEED: General SParse Efficient Editing MoDel</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g-speed-general-sparse-efficient-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models~(LLMs) have demonstrated incredible capabilities in understanding, generating, and manipulating languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g-speed-general-sparse-efficient-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Bias in Multilingual Language Models: Cross-Lingual Transfer of Debiasing Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-bias-in-multilingual-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the transferability of debiasing techniques across different languages within multilingual models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-bias-in-multilingual-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Body Neural Scene Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-body-neural-scene-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The test-time optimization of scene flow - using a coordinate network as a neural prior - has gained popularity due to its simplicity, lack of dataset bias, and state-of-the-art performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-body-neural-scene-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decomposed Prompt Tuning via Low-Rank Reparameterization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decomposed-prompt-tuning-via-low-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While prompt tuning approaches have achieved competitive performance with high efficiency, we observe that they invariably employ the same initialization process, wherein the soft prompt is either randomly initialized or derived from an existing embedding vocabulary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decomposed-prompt-tuning-via-low-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNO-DST: Leveraging Unlabelled Data in Zero-Shot Dialogue State Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uno-dst-leveraging-unlabelled-data-in-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous zero-shot dialogue state tracking (DST) methods only apply transfer learning, but ignore unlabelled data in the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uno-dst-leveraging-unlabelled-data-in-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repetition In Repetition Out: Towards Understanding Neural Text Degeneration from the Data Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repetition-in-repetition-out-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are a number of diverging hypotheses about the neural text degeneration problem, i. e., generating repetitive and dull loops, which makes this problem both interesting and confusing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repetition-in-repetition-out-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Calibration for In-context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-calibration-for-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we for the first time theoretically and empirically identify that such a paradox is mainly due to the label shift of the in-context model to the data distribution, in which LLMs shift the label marginal $p(y)$ while having a good label conditional $p(x|y)$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-calibration-for-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning optimal integration of spatial and temporal information in noisy chemotaxis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-optimal-integration-of-spatial-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the boundary between chemotaxis driven by spatial estimation of gradients and chemotaxis driven by temporal estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-optimal-integration-of-spatial-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bounding and Filling: A Fast and Flexible Framework for Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bounding-and-filling-a-fast-and-flexible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several models adopted a non-autoregressive manner to speed up the process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bounding-and-filling-a-fast-and-flexible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can GPT-4V(ision) Serve Medical Applications? Case Studies on GPT-4V for Multimodal Medical Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-gpt-4v-ision-serve-medical-applications</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driven by the large foundation models, the development of artificial intelligence has witnessed tremendous progress lately, leading to a surge of general interest from the public.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-gpt-4v-ision-serve-medical-applications</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KGQUIZ: Evaluating the Generalization of Encoded Knowledge in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kgquiz-evaluating-the-generalization-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To gain a better understanding of LLMs' knowledge abilities and their generalization, we evaluate 10 open-source and black-box LLMs on the KGQuiz benchmark across the five knowledge-intensive tasks and knowledge domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kgquiz-evaluating-the-generalization-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Statistical Learning of Branch and Bound for Vehicle Routing Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-statistical-learning-of-branch-and-bound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, machine learning of the branch and bound algorithm has shown promise in approximating competent solutions to NP-hard problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-statistical-learning-of-branch-and-bound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merging Experts into One: Improving Computational Efficiency of Mixture of Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merging-experts-into-one-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although a sparse Mixture of Experts (MoE) can reduce the cost by activating a small subset of parameters (e. g., one expert) for each input, its computation escalates significantly if increasing the number of activated experts, limiting its practical utility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merging-experts-into-one-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Few-Shot Named Entity Recognizers to Unseen Domains with Type-Related Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-few-shot-named-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, recent studies enable generalization to an unseen target domain with only a few labeled examples using data augmentation techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-few-shot-named-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-Temporal Graph Mixformer for Traffic Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-graph-mixformer-for-traffic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we train an estimator model that express the contribution of a node over the desired prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-graph-mixformer-for-traffic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Semiparametric Instrumented Difference-in-Differences Approach to Policy Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semiparametric-instrumented-difference-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, we propose a general instrumented DiD approach for learning the optimal treatment policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semiparametric-instrumented-difference-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARTree: A Deep Autoregressive Model for Phylogenetic Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artree-a-deep-autoregressive-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing flexible probabilistic models over tree topologies is important for developing efficient phylogenetic inference methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artree-a-deep-autoregressive-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Math Word Problems with Reexamination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-math-word-problems-with-reexamination</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Math word problem (MWP) solving aims to understand the descriptive math problem and calculate the result, for which previous efforts are mostly devoted to upgrade different technical modules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-math-word-problems-with-reexamination</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-aware Session-based Recommendation with Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-session-based-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Session-based recommendation (SBR) is a task that aims to predict items based on anonymous sequences of user behaviors in a session.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-session-based-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Adversarial Training for Text-to-Speech Synthesis Based on Raw Phonetic Input and Explicit Prosody Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-adversarial-training-for-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe an end-to-end speech synthesis system that uses generative adversarial training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-adversarial-training-for-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASSERT: Automated Safety Scenario Red Teaming for Evaluating the Robustness of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assert-automated-safety-scenario-red-teaming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As large language models are integrated into society, robustness toward a suite of prompts is increasingly important to maintain reliability in a high-variance environment. Robustness evaluations must comprehensively encapsulate the various settings in which a user may invoke an intelligent system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assert-automated-safety-scenario-red-teaming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RethinkingTMSC: An Empirical Study for Target-Oriented Multimodal Sentiment Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinkingtmsc-an-empirical-study-for-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, Target-oriented Multimodal Sentiment Classification (TMSC) has gained significant attention among scholars.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinkingtmsc-an-empirical-study-for-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Detoxifying Language Models via Toxification Reversal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-detoxifying-language-models-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Drawing on this idea, we devise a method to identify the toxification direction from the normal generation process to the one prompted with the negative prefix, and then steer the generation to the reversed direction by manipulating the information movement within the attention layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-detoxifying-language-models-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attentive Multi-Layer Perceptron for Non-autoregressive Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attentive-multi-layer-perceptron-for-non</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we marry AMLP with popular NAR models, deriving a highly efficient NAR-AMLP architecture with linear time and space complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attentive-multi-layer-perceptron-for-non</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Setwise Approach for Effective and Highly Efficient Zero-shot Ranking with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-setwise-approach-for-effective-and-highly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach reduces the number of LLM inferences and the amount of prompt token consumption during the ranking procedure, significantly improving the efficiency of LLM-based zero-shot ranking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-setwise-approach-for-effective-and-highly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An End-to-End System for Reproducibility Assessment of Source Code Repositories via Their Readmes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-end-to-end-system-for-reproducibility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an end-to-end system that operates on the Readme file of the source code repositories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-end-to-end-system-for-reproducibility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BanglaNLP at BLP-2023 Task 2: Benchmarking different Transformer Models for Sentiment Analysis of Bangla Social Media Posts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/banglanlp-at-blp-2023-task-2-benchmarking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bangla is the 7th most widely spoken language globally, with a staggering 234 million native speakers primarily hailing from India and Bangladesh.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/banglanlp-at-blp-2023-task-2-benchmarking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer-based Multimodal Change Detection with Multitask Consistency Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-multimodal-change-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that the current change detection methods struggle with the multitask conflicts between semantic and height change detection tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-multimodal-change-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Systematic Evaluation of Large Language Models on Out-of-Distribution Logical Reasoning Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-evaluation-of-large-language-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We carry out experiments on these datasets with both discriminative and generative LLMs and show that these simple tricks greatly hinder the performance of the language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-evaluation-of-large-language-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relation-aware Ensemble Learning for Knowledge Graph Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relation-aware-ensemble-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge graph (KG) embedding is a fundamental task in natural language processing, and various methods have been proposed to explore semantic patterns in distinctive ways.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relation-aware-ensemble-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatKBQA: A Generate-then-Retrieve Framework for Knowledge Base Question Answering with Fine-tuned Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatkbqa-a-generate-then-retrieve-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Base Question Answering (KBQA) aims to derive answers to natural language questions over large-scale knowledge bases (KBs), which are generally divided into two research components: knowledge retrieval and semantic parsing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatkbqa-a-generate-then-retrieve-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Graph Distillation See Like Vision Dataset Counterpart?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-graph-distillation-see-like-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We validate the proposed SGDD across 9 datasets and achieve state-of-the-art results on all of them: for example, on the YelpChi dataset, our approach maintains 98. 6% test accuracy of training on the original graph dataset with 1, 000 times saving on the scale of the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-graph-distillation-see-like-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster 3D cardiac CT segmentation with Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-3d-cardiac-ct-segmentation-with-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate segmentation of the heart is essential for personalized blood flow simulations and surgical intervention planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-3d-cardiac-ct-segmentation-with-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SiamAF: Learning Shared Information from ECG and PPG Signals for Robust Atrial Fibrillation Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siamaf-learning-shared-information-from-ecg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous deep learning models learn from a single modality, either electrocardiogram (ECG) or photoplethysmography (PPG) signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siamaf-learning-shared-information-from-ecg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-in-the-loop Machine Translation with Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-in-the-loop-machine-translation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The large language model (LLM) has garnered significant attention due to its in-context learning mechanisms and emergent capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-in-the-loop-machine-translation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIDE: Temporally Incremental Disparity Estimation via Pattern Flow in Structured Light System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tide-temporally-incremental-disparity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from most former disparity estimation methods that operate in a frame-wise manner, our network acquires disparity maps in a temporally incremental way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tide-temporally-incremental-disparity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Textual Analysis of ICALEPCS and IPAC Conference Proceedings: Revealing Research Trends, Topics, and Collaborations for Future Insights and Advanced Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textual-analysis-of-icalepcs-and-ipac</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show a textual analysis of past ICALEPCS and IPAC conference proceedings to gain insights into the research trends and topics discussed in the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textual-analysis-of-icalepcs-and-ipac</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differential Evolution Algorithm based Hyper-Parameters Selection of Convolutional Neural Network for Speech Command Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-evolution-algorithm-based-hyper-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speech Command Recognition (SCR), which deals with identification of short uttered speech commands, is crucial for various applications, including IoT devices and assistive technology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-evolution-algorithm-based-hyper-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pose-format: Library for Viewing, Augmenting, and Handling .pose Files</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-format-library-for-viewing-augmenting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The library includes a specialized file format that encapsulates various types of pose data, accommodating multiple individuals and an indefinite number of time frames, thus proving its utility for both image and video data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-format-library-for-viewing-augmenting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>METRA: Scalable Unsupervised RL with Metric-Aware Abstraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metra-scalable-unsupervised-rl-with-metric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through our experiments in five locomotion and manipulation environments, we demonstrate that METRA can discover a variety of useful behaviors even in complex, pixel-based environments, being the first unsupervised RL method that discovers diverse locomotion behaviors in pixel-based Quadruped and Humanoid.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metra-scalable-unsupervised-rl-with-metric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welfare Diplomacy: Benchmarking Language Model Cooperation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/welfare-diplomacy-benchmarking-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The growing capabilities and increasingly widespread deployment of AI systems necessitate robust benchmarks for measuring their cooperative capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/welfare-diplomacy-benchmarking-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Screening Rules for Optimal Design via Quadratic Lasso Reformulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-screening-rules-for-optimal-design-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The problems of Lasso regression and optimal design of experiments share a critical property: their optimal solutions are typically \emph{sparse}, i. e., only a small fraction of the optimal variables are non-zero.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-screening-rules-for-optimal-design-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HierarchicalContrast: A Coarse-to-Fine Contrastive Learning Framework for Cross-Domain Zero-Shot Slot Filling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchicalcontrast-a-coarse-to-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate this issue, we present a novel Hierarchical Contrastive Learning Framework (HiCL) for zero-shot slot filling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchicalcontrast-a-coarse-to-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PerturbScore: Connecting Discrete and Continuous Perturbations in NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perturbscore-connecting-discrete-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through experimental results, we find that we can build a connection between discrete and continuous perturbations and use the proposed PerturbScore to learn such correlation, surpassing previous methods used in discrete perturbation measuring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perturbscore-connecting-discrete-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniParser: Multi-Human Parsing with Unified Correlation Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniparser-multi-human-parsing-with-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-human parsing is an image segmentation task necessitating both instance-level and fine-grained category-level information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniparser-multi-human-parsing-with-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guiding AMR Parsing with Reverse Graph Linearization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-amr-parsing-with-reverse-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Abstract Meaning Representation (AMR) parsing aims to extract an abstract semantic graph from a given sentence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-amr-parsing-with-reverse-graph</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
