<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 09:15:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Verbosity $\neq$ Veracity: Demystify Verbosity Compensation Behavior of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verbosity-neq-veracity-demystify-verbosity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[2) We reveal the large performance gap between verbose and concise responses, with a notable difference of 27. 61% on the Qasper dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verbosity-neq-veracity-demystify-verbosity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MureObjectStitch: Multi-reference Image Composition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mureobjectstitch-multi-reference-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative image composition aims to regenerate the given foreground object in the background image to produce a realistic composite image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mureobjectstitch-multi-reference-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models as Causal Effect Generators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-as-causal-effect-generators</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we define a procedure for turning any language model and any directed acyclic graph (DAG) into a sequence-driven structural causal model (SD-SCM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-as-causal-effect-generators</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interaction Asymmetry: A General Principle for Learning Composable Abstractions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interaction-asymmetry-a-general-principle-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using this formalism, we prove that interaction asymmetry enables both disentanglement and compositional generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interaction-asymmetry-a-general-principle-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Album Sequencing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-album-sequencing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce a new user-friendly web-based tool that allows a less technical audience to upload music tracks, execute this technique in one click, and subsequently presents the result in a clean visualization to the user.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-album-sequencing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Stochastic Optimization Framework for Private and Fair Learning From Decentralized Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stochastic-optimization-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we develop a novel algorithm for private and fair federated learning (FL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stochastic-optimization-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accident Impact Prediction based on a deep convolutional and recurrent neural network model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accident-impact-prediction-based-on-a-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of predictive models capable of real-time forecasting of post-accident impact using readily available data can play a crucial role in preventing adverse outcomes and enhancing overall safety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accident-impact-prediction-based-on-a-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Memory Mechanisms for Decision Making through Demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-memory-mechanisms-for-decision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Partially Observable Markov Decision Processes, integrating an agent's history into memory poses a significant challenge for decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-memory-mechanisms-for-decision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problem-Oriented Segmentation and Retrieval: Case Study on Tutoring Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/problem-oriented-segmentation-and-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many open-ended conversations (e. g., tutoring lessons or business meetings) revolve around pre-defined reference materials, like worksheets or meeting bullets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/problem-oriented-segmentation-and-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Sustainability via Recommender Systems: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-sustainability-via-recommender</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human behavioral patterns and consumption paradigms have emerged as pivotal determinants in environmental degradation and climate change, with quotidian decisions pertaining to transportation, energy utilization, and resource consumption collectively precipitating substantial ecological impacts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-sustainability-via-recommender</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDXFormer: Boosting Remote Sensing Change Detection with Extended Long Short-Term Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdxformer-boosting-remote-sensing-change</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose CDXFormer, with a core component that is a powerful XLSTM-based feature enhancement layer, integrating the advantages of linear computational complexity, global context perception, and strong interpret-ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdxformer-boosting-remote-sensing-change</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Truths: A Large-Scale Dataset of AI-Augmented Images for Evaluating Robustness of AI-Generated Image detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-truths-a-large-scale-dataset-of-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image diffusion models have impactful applications in art, design, and entertainment, yet these technologies also pose significant risks by enabling the creation and dissemination of misinformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-truths-a-large-scale-dataset-of-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSEG-VCUQ: Multimodal SEGmentation with Enhanced Vision Foundation Models, Convolutional Neural Networks, and Uncertainty Quantification for High-Speed Video Phase Detection Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mseg-vcuq-multimodal-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Purpose: High-speed video (HSV) phase detection (PD) segmentation is vital in nuclear reactors, chemical processing, and electronics cooling for detecting vapor, liquid, and microlayer phases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mseg-vcuq-multimodal-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt-enhanced Network for Hateful Meme Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-enhanced-network-for-hateful-meme</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, after constructing the sequence through the prompt method and encoding it with a language model, we performed region information global extraction on the encoded sequence for multi-view perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-enhanced-network-for-hateful-meme</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PatchCTG: Patch Cardiotocography Transformer for Antepartum Fetal Health Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchctg-patch-cardiotocography-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Antepartum Cardiotocography (CTG) is vital for fetal health monitoring, but traditional methods like the Dawes-Redman system are often limited by high inter-observer variability, leading to inconsistent interpretations and potential misdiagnoses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchctg-patch-cardiotocography-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Attack Traffic Identification Method Based on Temporal Spectrum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attack-traffic-identification-method-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the issues of insufficient robustness, unstable features, and data noise interference in existing network attack detection and identification models, this paper proposes an attack traffic detection and identification method based on temporal spectrum.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attack-traffic-identification-method-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiCoM: Hierarchical Coherent Motion for Streamable Dynamic Scene with 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hicom-hierarchical-coherent-motion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The online reconstruction of dynamic scenes from multi-view streaming videos faces significant challenges in training, rendering and storage efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hicom-hierarchical-coherent-motion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horticultural Temporal Fruit Monitoring via 3D Instance Segmentation and Re-Identification using Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/horticultural-temporal-fruit-monitoring-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results on a real dataset of strawberries demonstrate that our approach outperforms other methods for fruits re-identification over time, allowing for precise temporal fruit monitoring in real and complex scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/horticultural-temporal-fruit-monitoring-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair Summarization: Bridging Quality and Diversity in Extractive Summaries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-summarization-bridging-quality-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work highlights the importance of fairness in summarization and sets a benchmark for future research in fairness-aware NLP models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-summarization-bridging-quality-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving Verifiable Neural Network Inference Service</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-verifiable-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose vPIN, a privacy-preserving and verifiable CNN inference scheme that preserves privacy for client data samples while ensuring verifiability for the inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-verifiable-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do Learning Dynamics Reveal About Generalization in LLM Reasoning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-learning-dynamics-reveal-about</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that a model's generalization behavior can be effectively characterized by a training metric we call pre-memorization train accuracy: the accuracy of model samples on training queries before they begin to copy the exact reasoning steps from the training set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-learning-dynamics-reveal-about</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Bias in Queer Representation within Large Language Models: A Collaborative Agent Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-bias-in-queer-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) often perpetuate biases in pronoun usage, leading to misrepresentation or exclusion of queer individuals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-bias-in-queer-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubly Mild Generalization for Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doubly-mild-generalization-for-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even under worst-case generalization, DMG can still control value overestimation at a certain level and lower bound the performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doubly-mild-generalization-for-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DecoPrompt : Decoding Prompts Reduces Hallucinations when Large Language Models Meet False Premises</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoprompt-decoding-prompts-reduces</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated increasing power, they have also called upon studies on their hallucinated outputs that deviate from factually correct statements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoprompt-decoding-prompts-reduces</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SparrowVQE: Visual Question Explanation for Course Content Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparrowvqe-visual-question-explanation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We trained our model with a three-stage training mechanism consisting of multimodal pre-training (slide images and transcripts feature alignment), instruction tuning (tuning the pre-trained model with transcripts and QA pairs), and domain fine-tuning (fine-tuning slide image and QA pairs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparrowvqe-visual-question-explanation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isometric Transformations for Image Augmentation in Mueller Matrix Polarimetry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isometric-transformations-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study underscores the necessity of physics-informed data augmentation for polarimetric imaging in deep learning (DL), paving the way for broader adoption and more robust applications across diverse research in the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isometric-transformations-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Control of Mechanical Ventilators with Learned Respiratory Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-control-of-mechanical-ventilators</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We implement and compare controllers based on clinical guidelines contained in the ARDSnet protocol, optimal control theory, and learned latent dynamics represented as neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-control-of-mechanical-ventilators</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-scale Remote Sensing Image Target Recognition and Automatic Annotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-remote-sensing-image-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a method for object recognition and automatic labeling in large-area remote sensing images called LRSAA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-remote-sensing-image-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Low-Rank Dilemma of Linear Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-low-rank-dilemma-of-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Softmax attention mechanism in Transformer models is notoriously computationally expensive, particularly due to its quadratic complexity, posing significant challenges in vision applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-low-rank-dilemma-of-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FM-TS: Flow Matching for Time Series Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fm-ts-flow-matching-for-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FM-TS is more efficient in terms of training and inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fm-ts-flow-matching-for-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleep Staging from Airflow Signals Using Fourier Approximations of Persistence Curves</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sleep-staging-from-airflow-signals-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sleep staging is a challenging task, typically manually performed by sleep technologists based on electroencephalogram and other biosignals of patients taken during overnight sleep studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sleep-staging-from-airflow-signals-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Material Transforms from Disentangled NeRF Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/material-transforms-from-disentangled-nerf</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we first propose a novel method for transferring material transformations across different scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/material-transforms-from-disentangled-nerf</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint multi-dimensional dynamic attention and transformer for general image restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-multi-dimensional-dynamic-attention-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Outdoor images often suffer from severe degradation due to rain, haze, and noise, impairing image quality and challenging high-level tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-multi-dimensional-dynamic-attention-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Likelihood as a Performance Gauge for Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/likelihood-as-a-performance-gauge-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on these findings, we propose two methods that use question likelihood as a gauge for selecting and constructing prompts that lead to better performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/likelihood-as-a-performance-gauge-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMPart3D: Segment Any Part in 3D Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampart3d-segment-any-part-in-3d-objects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For flexibility, we distill scale-conditioned part-aware 3D features for 3D part segmentation at multiple granularities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampart3d-segment-any-part-in-3d-objects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENAT: Rethinking Spatial-temporal Interactions in Token-based Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enat-rethinking-spatial-temporal-interactions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the spatial level, we disentangle the computations of visible and mask tokens by encoding visible tokens independently, while decoding mask tokens conditioned on the fully encoded visible tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enat-rethinking-spatial-temporal-interactions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Token Merging for Training-Free Semantic Binding in Text-to-Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-merging-for-training-free-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we define semantic binding as the task of associating a given object with its attribute, termed attribute binding, or linking it to other related sub-objects, referred to as object binding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-merging-for-training-free-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConvMixFormer- A Resource-efficient Convolution Mixer for Transformer-based Dynamic Hand Gesture Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convmixformer-a-resource-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We have considered this drawback of the transformer and designed a resource-efficient model that replaces the self-attention in the transformer with the simple convolutional layer-based token mixer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convmixformer-a-resource-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AssistRAG: Boosting the Potential of Large Language Models with an Intelligent Information Assistant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assistrag-boosting-the-potential-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emergence of Large Language Models (LLMs) has significantly advanced natural language processing, but these models often generate factually incorrect information, known as "hallucination".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assistrag-boosting-the-potential-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Super Weight in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-super-weight-in-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For weight quantization, we similarly find that by preserving the super weight and clipping other weight outliers, round-to-nearest quantization can scale to much larger block sizes than previously considered.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-super-weight-in-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Efficient Transformer-based Method for Bird's Eye View Instance Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-efficient-transformer-based-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate object detection and prediction are critical to ensure the safety and efficiency of self-driving architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-efficient-transformer-based-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Explaining RL Decisions with Trajectories': A Reproducibility Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-rl-decisions-with-trajectories-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work investigates the reproducibility of the paper 'Explaining RL decisions with trajectories'.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-rl-decisions-with-trajectories-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-scale moral machine experiment on large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-moral-machine-experiment-on-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we evaluate moral judgments across 51 different LLMs, including multiple versions of proprietary models (GPT, Claude, Gemini) and open-source alternatives (Llama, Gemma), to assess their alignment with human moral preferences in autonomous driving scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-moral-machine-experiment-on-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White-Box Diffusion Transformer for single-cell RNA-seq generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/white-box-diffusion-transformer-for-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our White-Box Diffusion Transformer combines the generative capabilities of Diffusion model with the mathematical interpretability of White-Box transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/white-box-diffusion-transformer-for-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renaissance: Investigating the Pretraining of Vision-Language Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/renaissance-investigating-the-pretraining-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we seek to answer several questions related to the pretraining of vision-language encoders through meta-analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/renaissance-investigating-the-pretraining-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XPoint: A Self-Supervised Visual-State-Space based Architecture for Multispectral Image Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xpoint-a-self-supervised-visual-state-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate multispectral image matching presents significant challenges due to non-linear intensity variations across spectral modalities, extreme viewpoint changes, and the scarcity of labeled datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xpoint-a-self-supervised-visual-state-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScaleKD: Strong Vision Transformers Could Be Excellent Teachers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalekd-strong-vision-transformers-could-be</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The student backbones trained by our method transfer well on downstream MS-COCO and ADE20K datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalekd-strong-vision-transformers-could-be</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Graph Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-graph-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach introduces a subgraph Gaussian embedding module, which adaptively maps subgraphs to a structured Gaussian space, ensuring the preservation of graph characteristics while controlling the distribution of generated subgraphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-graph-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T2-Only Prostate Cancer Prediction by Meta-Learning from Bi-Parametric MR Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t2-only-prostate-cancer-prediction-by-meta</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current imaging-based prostate cancer diagnosis requires both MR T2-weighted (T2w) and diffusion-weighted imaging (DWI) sequences, with additional sequences for potentially greater accuracy improvement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t2-only-prostate-cancer-prediction-by-meta</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniHR: Hierarchical Representation Learning for Unified Knowledge Graph Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unihr-hierarchical-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results across 7 datasets from 3 types of KGs demonstrate that our UniHR outperforms baselines designed for one specific kind of KG, indicating strong generalization capability of HiDR form and the effectiveness of HiSL module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unihr-hierarchical-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
