<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 21:07:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>COO: Comic Onomatopoeia Dataset for Recognizing Arbitrary or Truncated Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coo-comic-onomatopoeia-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To encourage research on this topic, we provide a novel comic onomatopoeia dataset (COO), which consists of onomatopoeia texts in Japanese comics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coo-comic-onomatopoeia-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Scale-Aware, Robust, and Generalizable Unsupervised Monocular Depth Estimation by Integrating IMU Motion Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-scale-aware-robust-and-generalizable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised monocular depth and ego-motion estimation has drawn extensive research attention in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-scale-aware-robust-and-generalizable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-vision-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dual-ViT is henceforth able to reduce the computational complexity without compromising much accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-vision-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDFEst: Categorical Pose and Shape Estimation of Objects from RGB-D using Signed Distance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdfest-categorical-pose-and-shape-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rich geometric understanding of the world is an important component of many robotic applications such as planning and manipulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdfest-categorical-pose-and-shape-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Penalty Approach for Normalizing Feature Distributions to Build Confounder-Free Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-penalty-approach-for-normalizing-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we extend the MDN method by applying a Penalty approach (referred to as PDMN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-penalty-approach-for-normalizing-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistency is the key to further mitigating catastrophic forgetting in continual learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-is-the-key-to-further-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we examine the role of consistency regularization in ER framework under various continual learning scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-is-the-key-to-further-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intra-Modal Constraint Loss For Image-Text Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intra-modal-constraint-loss-for-image-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-modal retrieval has drawn much attention in both computer vision and natural language processing domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intra-modal-constraint-loss-for-image-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Language Left Behind: Scaling Human-Centered Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-language-left-behind-scaling-human-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driven by the goal of eradicating language barriers on a global scale, machine translation has solidified itself as a key focus of artificial intelligence research today.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-language-left-behind-scaling-human-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalizing Federated Medical Image Segmentation via Local Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalizing-federated-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized FL tackles this issue by only utilizing partial model parameters shared from global server, while keeping the rest to adapt to its own data distribution in the local training of each site.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalizing-federated-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Baselined Gated Attention Recurrent Network for Request Prediction in Ridesharing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-baselined-gated-attention-recurrent-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ridesharing has received global popularity due to its convenience and cost efficiency for both drivers and passengers and its strong potential to contribute to the implementation of the UN Sustainable Development Goals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-baselined-gated-attention-recurrent-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Latent Structure for Multi-Modal Vehicle Trajectory Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-latent-structure-for-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that a similar problem, in which the generated trajectory is located between adjacent lanes, often arises in VAE-based trajectory forecasting models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-latent-structure-for-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-modal Prototype Driven Network for Radiology Report Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-prototype-driven-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Radiology report generation (RRG) aims to describe automatically a radiology image with human-like language and could potentially support the work of radiologists, reducing the burden of manual reporting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-prototype-driven-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance Shadow Detection with A Single-Stage Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-shadow-detection-with-a-single-stage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper formulates a new problem, instance shadow detection, which aims to detect shadow instance and the associated object instance that cast each shadow in the input image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-shadow-detection-with-a-single-stage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCCF: Deep Comprehensible Color Filter Learning Framework for High-Resolution Image Harmonization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dccf-deep-comprehensible-color-filter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image color harmonization algorithm aims to automatically match the color distribution of foreground and background images captured in different conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dccf-deep-comprehensible-color-filter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start Small, Think Big: On Hyperparameter Optimization for Large-Scale Knowledge Graph Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/start-small-think-big-on-hyperparameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge graph embedding (KGE) models are an effective and popular approach to represent and reason with multi-relational data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/start-small-think-big-on-hyperparameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast-Vid2Vid: Spatial-Temporal Compression for Video-to-Video Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-vid2vid-spatial-temporal-compression-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a spatial-temporal compression framework, \textbf{Fast-Vid2Vid}, which focuses on data aspects of generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-vid2vid-spatial-temporal-compression-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TASKOGRAPHY: Evaluating robot task planning over large 3D scene graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskography-evaluating-robot-task-planning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D scene graphs (3DSGs) are an emerging description; unifying symbolic, topological, and metric scene representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskography-evaluating-robot-task-planning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Robust is your Fair Model? Exploring the Robustness of Diverse Fairness Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-robust-is-your-fair-model-exploring-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies have shown that robustness (the ability for a model to perform well on unseen data) plays a significant role in the type of strategy that should be used when approaching a new problem and, hence, measuring the robustness of these strategies has become a fundamental problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-robust-is-your-fair-model-exploring-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCPL: Contrastive Coherence Preserving Loss for Versatile Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccpl-contrastive-coherence-preserving-loss</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CCPL can preserve the coherence of the content source during style transfer without degrading stylization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccpl-contrastive-coherence-preserving-loss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSP-HDRI$+$: A Synthetic Dataset Generator for Pre-Training of Human-Centric Computer Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psp-hdri-a-synthetic-dataset-generator-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new synthetic data generator PSP-HDRI$+$ that proves to be a superior pre-training alternative to ImageNet and other large-scale synthetic data counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psp-hdri-a-synthetic-dataset-generator-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Contextual Relationships for Cervical Abnormal Cell Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-contextual-relationships-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, both contextual relationships between cells and cell-to-global images are exploited to enhance features of each region of interest (RoI) proposals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-contextual-relationships-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A clinically motivated self-supervised approach for content-based image retrieval of CT liver images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-clinically-motivated-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address these limitations by (1) proposing a self-supervised learning framework that incorporates domain-knowledge into the training procedure and (2) providing the first representation learning explainability analysis in the context of CBIR of CT liver images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-clinically-motivated-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wave-ViT: Unifying Wavelet and Transformers for Visual Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wave-vit-unifying-wavelet-and-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the wavelet theory, we construct a new Wavelet Vision Transformer (\textbf{Wave-ViT}) that formulates the invertible down-sampling with wavelet transforms and self-attention learning in a unified way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wave-vit-unifying-wavelet-and-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradual Domain Adaptation without Indexed Intermediate Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradual-domain-adaptation-without-indexed-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This coarse domain sequence then undergoes a fine indexing step via a novel cycle-consistency loss, which encourages the next intermediate domain to preserve sufficient discriminative knowledge of the current intermediate domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradual-domain-adaptation-without-indexed-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMS: An Annotated Corpus for Causal Analysis of Mental Health Issues in Social Media Posts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cams-an-annotated-corpus-for-causal-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new dataset for Causal Analysis of Mental health issues in Social media posts (CAMS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cams-an-annotated-corpus-for-causal-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Multi-objective Optimization: Comparative Study of the State-of-the-Art</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-multi-objective-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal multi-objective problems (MMOPs) commonly arise in real-world problems where distant solutions in decision space correspond to very similar objective values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-multi-objective-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slot Filling for Extracting Reskilling and Upskilling Options from the Web</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slot-filling-for-extracting-reskilling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Disturbances in the job market such as advances in science and technology, crisis and increased competition have triggered a surge in reskilling and upskilling programs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slot-filling-for-extracting-reskilling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio-Visual Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-visual-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To deal with the AVS problem, we propose a novel method that uses a temporal pixel-wise audio-visual interaction module to inject audio semantics as guidance for the visual segmentation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-visual-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Pairwise Re-ranking with Pre-trained Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-pairwise-re-ranking-with-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pairwise re-ranking models predict which of two documents is more relevant to a query and then aggregate a final ranking from such preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-pairwise-re-ranking-with-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoMER: Modeling Coverage for Transformer-based Handwritten Mathematical Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comer-modeling-coverage-for-transformer-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose CoMER, a model that adopts the coverage information in the transformer decoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comer-modeling-coverage-for-transformer-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning Sequential Tasks on Contact Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planning-sequential-tasks-on-contact-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We devise a 3D scene graph representation, contact graph+ (cg+), for efficient sequential task planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planning-sequential-tasks-on-contact-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depthformer : Multiscale Vision Transformer For Monocular Depth Estimation With Local Global Information Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depthformer-multiscale-vision-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose a Transbins module that divides the depth range into bins whose center value is estimated adaptively per image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depthformer-multiscale-vision-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-attention on Multi-Shifted Windows for Scene Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-attention-on-multi-shifted-windows-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scene segmentation in images is a fundamental yet challenging problem in visual content understanding, which is to learn a model to assign every image pixel to a categorical label.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-attention-on-multi-shifted-windows-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bregman Proximal Langevin Monte Carlo via Bregman--Moreau Envelopes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bregman-proximal-langevin-monte-carlo-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed algorithms extend existing Langevin Monte Carlo algorithms in two aspects -- the ability to sample nonsmooth distributions with mirror descent-like algorithms, and the use of the more general Bregman--Moreau envelope in place of the Moreau envelope as a smooth approximation of the nonsmooth part of the potential.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bregman-proximal-langevin-monte-carlo-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPText-DETR: Towards Better Scene Text Detection with Dynamic Points in Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dptext-detr-towards-better-scene-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the used point label form implies the reading order of humans, which affects the robustness of Transformer model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dptext-detr-towards-better-scene-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2DPASS: 2D Priors Assisted Semantic Segmentation on LiDAR Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2dpass-2d-priors-assisted-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As camera and LiDAR sensors capture complementary information used in autonomous driving, great efforts have been made to develop semantic segmentation algorithms through multi-modality data fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2dpass-2d-priors-assisted-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mix-Teaching: A Simple, Unified and Effective Semi-Supervised Learning Framework for Monocular 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mix-teaching-a-simple-unified-and-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, by leveraging full training set and the additional 48K raw images of KITTI, it can further improve the MonoFlex by +4. 65% improvement on AP@0. 7 for car detection, reaching 18. 54% AP@0. 7, which ranks the 1st place among all monocular based methods on KITTI test leaderboard.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mix-teaching-a-simple-unified-and-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Detection of Papilledema in Pediatric Fundus Images with Explainable Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-detection-of-papilledema-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Papilledema is an ophthalmic neurologic disorder in which increased intracranial pressure leads to swelling of the optic nerves.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-detection-of-papilledema-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SFNet: Faster, Accurate, and Domain Agnostic Semantic Segmentation via Semantic Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfnet-faster-accurate-and-domain-agnostic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on exploring effective methods for faster, accurate, and domain agnostic semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfnet-faster-accurate-and-domain-agnostic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Proper Contrastive Self-supervised Learning Strategies For Music Audio Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-proper-contrastive-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The common research goal of self-supervised learning is to extract a general representation which an arbitrary downstream task would benefit from.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-proper-contrastive-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual Persuasion Detection: Video Games as an Invaluable Data Source for NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-persuasion-detection-video-games</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Role-playing games (RPGs) have a considerable amount of text in video game dialogues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-persuasion-detection-video-games</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Machine Learning for Effective Missile Launch Based on Beyond Visual Range Air Combat Simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-machine-learning-for-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work compares supervised machine learning methods using reliable data from constructive simulations to estimate the most effective moment for launching missiles during air combat.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-machine-learning-for-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Mixtures of ODEs for Inferring Cellular Gene Expression Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-mixtures-of-odes-for-inferring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By using a simple family of ODEs informed by the biochemistry of gene expression to constrain the likelihood of a deep generative model, we can simultaneously infer the latent time and latent state of each cell and predict its future gene expression state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-mixtures-of-odes-for-inferring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wasserstein Graph Distance based on $L_1$-Approximated Tree Edit Distance between Weisfeiler-Lehman Subtrees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasserstein-graph-distance-based-on-l-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this paper clarifies these facts for the first time and defines a metric we call the Wasserstein WL subtree (WWLS) distance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasserstein-graph-distance-based-on-l-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batch-efficient EigenDecomposition for Small and Medium Matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batch-efficient-eigendecomposition-for-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[EigenDecomposition (ED) is at the heart of many computer vision algorithms and applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batch-efficient-eigendecomposition-for-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Ellipsometry: Portable Acquisition of Polarimetric SVBRDF and Shape with Unstructured Flash Photography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-ellipsometry-portable-acquisition-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ellipsometry techniques allow to measure polarization information of materials, requiring precise rotations of optical components with different configurations of lights and sensors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-ellipsometry-portable-acquisition-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Legal Case Matching via Inverse Optimal Transport-based Rationale Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-legal-case-matching-via-inverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As an essential operation of legal retrieval, legal case matching plays a central role in intelligent legal systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-legal-case-matching-via-inverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Robust Deep Models for Time-Series Domain: Novel Algorithms and Theoretical Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-robust-deep-models-for-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the success of deep neural networks (DNNs) for real-world applications over time-series data such as mobile health, little is known about how to train robust DNNs for time-series domain due to its unique characteristics compared to images and text data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-robust-deep-models-for-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-label Classification with High-rank and High-order Label Correlations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-label-classification-with-high-rank-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous methods capture the high-order label correlations mainly by transforming the label matrix to a latent label space with low-rank matrix factorization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-label-classification-with-high-rank-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Diffusion Model Efficiency Through Patching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-diffusion-model-efficiency-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models are a powerful class of generative models that iteratively denoise samples to produce data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-diffusion-model-efficiency-through</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
