<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 21:06:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Real-world image dehazing with improved joint enhancement and exposure fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-world-image-dehazing-with-improved-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The visual and quantitative comparisons between the proposed method and state-of-the-art dehazing methods show that the proposed method has better dehazing performance and has a 50% improvement in terms of the FADE metric compared to the closest result.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-world-image-dehazing-with-improved-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Transformer Model for Symbolic Regression towards Scientific Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transformer-model-for-symbolic-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Once trained, we apply our best model to the SRSD datasets (Symbolic Regression for Scientific Discovery datasets) which yields state-of-the-art results using the normalized tree-based edit distance, at no extra computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transformer-model-for-symbolic-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smooth Diffusion: Crafting Smooth Latent Spaces in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smooth-diffusion-crafting-smooth-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce Step-wise Variation Regularization to enforce the proportion between the variations of an arbitrary input latent and that of the output image is a constant at any diffusion training step.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smooth-diffusion-crafting-smooth-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAVE: Randomized Noise Shuffling for Fast and Consistent Video Editing with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rave-randomized-noise-shuffling-for-fast-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in diffusion-based models have demonstrated significant success in generating images from text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rave-randomized-noise-shuffling-for-fast-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EulerMormer: Robust Eulerian Motion Magnification via Dynamic Filtering within Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eulermormer-robust-eulerian-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we introduce a novel dynamic filter that eliminates noise cues and preserves critical features in the motion magnification and amplification generation phases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eulermormer-robust-eulerian-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining inherent knowledge of vision-language models with unsupervised domain adaptation through self-knowledge distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-inherent-knowledge-of-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a first step, we generate the zero-shot predictions of the source and target dataset using the vision-language model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-inherent-knowledge-of-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Highlighter: Interactive Control for Multi-Modal LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-highlighter-interactive-control-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Without tuning on LLaVA-v1. 5, our method secured 69. 5 in the MMBench test and 1552. 5 in MME-perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-highlighter-interactive-control-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmentation-Free Dense Contrastive Knowledge Distillation for Efficient Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmentation-free-dense-contrastive-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to address this problem, we present Augmentation-free Dense Contrastive Knowledge Distillation (Af-DCD), a new contrastive distillation learning paradigm to train compact and accurate deep neural networks for semantic segmentation applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmentation-free-dense-contrastive-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the adaptation of in-context learners for system identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-adaptation-of-in-context-learners-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In-context system identification aims at constructing meta-models to describe classes of systems, differently from traditional approaches that model single systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-adaptation-of-in-context-learners-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merging by Matching Models in Task Subspaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merging-by-matching-models-in-task-subspaces</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model merging aims to cheaply combine individual task-specific models into a single multitask model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merging-by-matching-models-in-task-subspaces</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic volumetric speckle suppression in OCT using deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-volumetric-speckle-suppression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a deep learning framework for volumetric speckle reduction in optical coherence tomography (OCT) based on a conditional generative adversarial network (cGAN) that leverages the volumetric nature of OCT data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-volumetric-speckle-suppression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Impact of Multi-dimensional Local Differential Privacy on Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-impact-of-multi-dimensional-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated decision systems are increasingly used to make consequential decisions in people's lives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-impact-of-multi-dimensional-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CODEX: A Cluster-Based Method for Explainable Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codex-a-cluster-based-method-for-explainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the impressive feats demonstrated by Reinforcement Learning (RL), these algorithms have seen little adoption in high-risk, real-world applications due to current difficulties in explaining RL agent actions and building user trust.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codex-a-cluster-based-method-for-explainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoAST: Robustifying Language Models via Adversarial Perturbation with Selective Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roast-robustifying-language-models-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under a unified evaluation of fine-tuned LMs by incorporating four representative perspectives of model robustness, we demonstrate the effectiveness of RoAST compared to state-of-the-art fine-tuning methods on six different types of LMs, which indicates its usefulness in practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roast-robustifying-language-models-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Vocabulary Segmentation with Semantic-Assisted Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-segmentation-with-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We attribute this to the in-vocabulary embedding and domain-biased CLIP prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-segmentation-with-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An LLM Compiler for Parallel Function Calling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-llm-compiler-for-parallel-function-calling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLMCompiler automatically computes an optimized orchestration for the function calls and can be used with open-source models such as LLaMA-2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-llm-compiler-for-parallel-function-calling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Learnability of Watermarks for Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-learnability-of-watermarks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Watermarking of language model outputs enables statistical detection of model-generated text, which has many applications in the responsible deployment of language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-learnability-of-watermarks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost-Effective In-Context Learning for Entity Resolution: A Design Space Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-effective-in-context-learning-for-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing ICL approaches to ER typically necessitate providing a task description and a set of demonstrations for each entity pair and thus have limitations on the monetary cost of interfacing LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-effective-in-context-learning-for-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAsp: A Benchmark for Multi-document Open Aspect-based Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openasp-a-benchmark-for-multi-document-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To advance research on more realistic scenarios, we introduce OpenAsp, a benchmark for multi-document \textit{open} aspect-based summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openasp-a-benchmark-for-multi-document-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-4V with Emotion: A Zero-shot Benchmark for Multimodal Emotion Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-4v-with-emotion-a-zero-shot-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper quantitatively evaluates GPT-4V's capabilities in multimodal emotion understanding, encompassing tasks such as facial emotion recognition, visual sentiment analysis, micro-expression recognition, dynamic facial emotion recognition, and multimodal emotion recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-4v-with-emotion-a-zero-shot-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRNet: Frustum-Range Networks for Scalable LiDAR Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frnet-frustum-range-networks-for-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, a frustum feature encoder module is used to extract per-point features within the frustum region, which preserves scene consistency and is crucial for point-level predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frnet-frustum-range-networks-for-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiscoBAX: Discovery of Optimal Intervention Sets in Genomic Experiment Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discobax-discovery-of-optimal-intervention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The discovery of therapeutics to treat genetically-driven pathologies relies on identifying genes involved in the underlying disease mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discobax-discovery-of-optimal-intervention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortify the Shortest Stave in Attention: Enhancing Context Awareness of Large Language Models for Effective Tool Use</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fortify-the-shortest-stave-in-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we argue that a waveform pattern in the model's attention allocation has an impact on the tool use performance, which degrades when the position of essential information hits the trough zone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fortify-the-shortest-stave-in-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Reconstruction with Conditioned Diffusion Models for Unsupervised Anomaly Detection in Brain MRIs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guided-reconstruction-with-conditioned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using our proposed conditioning mechanism we can reduce the false-positive predictions and enable a more precise delineation of anomalies which significantly enhances the anomaly detection performance compared to established state-of-the-art approaches to unsupervised anomaly detection in brain MRI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guided-reconstruction-with-conditioned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Laws of Synthetic Images for Model Training ... for Now</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-laws-of-synthetic-images-for-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings also suggest that scaling synthetic data can be particularly effective in scenarios such as: (1) when there is a limited supply of real images for a supervised problem (e. g., fewer than 0. 5 million images in ImageNet), (2) when the evaluation dataset diverges significantly from the training data, indicating the out-of-distribution scenario, or (3) when synthetic data is used in conjunction with real images, as demonstrated in the training of CLIP models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-laws-of-synthetic-images-for-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLadder: A Benchmark to Assess Causal Reasoning Capabilities of Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cladder-a-benchmark-to-assess-causal-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Much of the existing work in natural language processing (NLP) focuses on evaluating commonsense causal reasoning in LLMs, thus failing to assess whether a model can perform causal inference in accordance with a set of well-defined formal rules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cladder-a-benchmark-to-assess-causal-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsyChat: A Client-Centric Dialogue System for Mental Health Support</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psychat-a-client-centric-dialogue-system-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dialogue systems are increasingly integrated into mental health support to help clients facilitate exploration, gain insight, take action, and ultimately heal themselves.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psychat-a-client-centric-dialogue-system-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIMo: A Multi-Modal Infant Model for Studying Cognitive Development</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimo-a-multi-modal-infant-model-for-studying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human intelligence and human consciousness emerge gradually during the process of cognitive development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimo-a-multi-modal-infant-model-for-studying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance Tracking in 3D Scenes from Egocentric Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-tracking-in-3d-scenes-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore this problem by first introducing a new benchmark dataset, consisting of RGB and depth videos, per-frame camera pose, and instance-level annotations in both 2D camera and 3D world coordinates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-tracking-in-3d-scenes-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Learning for Feature Shift Detection and Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-learning-for-feature-shift-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data shift is a phenomenon present in many real-world applications, and while there are multiple methods attempting to detect shifts, the task of localizing and correcting the features originating such shifts has not been studied in depth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-learning-for-feature-shift-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-scale Information Integration Framework for Infrared and Visible Image Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-scale-information-integration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a multi-scale dual attention (MDA) framework for infrared and visible image fusion, which is designed to measure and integrate complementary information in both structure and loss function at the image and patch level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-scale-information-integration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards 4D Human Video Stylization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-4d-human-video-stylization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, we leverage Neural Radiance Fields (NeRFs) to represent videos, conducting stylization in the rendered feature space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-4d-human-video-stylization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activity Grammars for Temporal Action Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activity-grammars-for-temporal-action-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sequence prediction on temporal data requires the ability to understand compositional structures of multi-level semantics beyond individual and contextual properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activity-grammars-for-temporal-action-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free3D: Consistent Novel View Synthesis without 3D Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free3d-consistent-novel-view-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Free3D, a simple approach designed for open-set novel view synthesis (NVS) from a single image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free3d-consistent-novel-view-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PrimDiffusion: Volumetric Primitives Diffusion for 3D Human Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/primdiffusion-volumetric-primitives-diffusion-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present PrimDiffusion, the first diffusion-based framework for 3D human generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/primdiffusion-volumetric-primitives-diffusion-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caregiver Talk Shapes Toddler Vision: A Computational Study of Dyadic Play</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caregiver-talk-shapes-toddler-vision-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this we propose a computational model of visual representation learning during dyadic play.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caregiver-talk-shapes-toddler-vision-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Surface: Probing LLaMA Across Scales and Layers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-surface-probing-llama-across-scales</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an in-depth analysis of Large Language Models (LLMs), focusing on LLaMA, a prominent open-source foundational model in natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-surface-probing-llama-across-scales</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constraint Model for the Satellite Image Mosaic Selection Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constraint-model-for-the-satellite-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More precisely, for this problem the input is an area of interest, several satellite images intersecting the area, a list of requirements relative to the image and the mosaic, such as cloud coverage percentage, image resolution, and a list of objectives to optimize.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constraint-model-for-the-satellite-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Area Estimation of Case Growths for Timely COVID-19 Outbreak Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/small-area-estimation-of-case-growths-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we conducted a case study based on outbreak case data from the state of Colorado and showed that the timely detection of outbreaks could have been improved by up to 224% using TLGRF when compared to the decisions made by Colorado's Department of Health and Environment (CDPHE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/small-area-estimation-of-case-growths-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Model Knowledge Distillation for Efficient Question Answering in Spanish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-model-knowledge-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in the development of pre-trained Spanish language models has led to significant progress in many Natural Language Processing (NLP) tasks, such as question answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-model-knowledge-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Registration of Images and LiDAR Point Clouds with VoxelPoint-to-Pixel Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-registration-of-images-and-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these problems, we propose to learn a structured cross-modality latent space to represent pixel features and 3D features via a differentiable probabilistic PnP solver.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-registration-of-images-and-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MuRF: Multi-Baseline Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/murf-multi-baseline-radiance-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Multi-Baseline Radiance Fields (MuRF), a general feed-forward approach to solving sparse view synthesis under multiple different baseline settings (small and large baselines, and different number of input views).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/murf-multi-baseline-radiance-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotional Speech-driven 3D Body Animation via Disentangled Latent Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotional-speech-driven-3d-body-animation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Once trained, AMUSE synthesizes 3D human gestures directly from speech with control over the expressed emotions and style by combining the content from the driving speech with the emotion and style of another speech sequence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotional-speech-driven-3d-body-animation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Knowledge-driven Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-knowledge-driven-autonomous-driving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the emerging knowledge-driven autonomous driving technologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-knowledge-driven-autonomous-driving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn to Unlearn for Deep Neural Networks: Minimizing Unlearning Interference with Gradient Projection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-to-unlearn-for-deep-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent data-privacy laws have sparked interest in machine unlearning, which involves removing the effect of specific training samples from a learnt model as if they were never present in the original training dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-to-unlearn-for-deep-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Scalar Fields for Molecular Docking with Fast Fourier Transforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-scalar-fields-for-molecular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The runtime of our approach can be amortized at several levels of abstraction, and is particularly favorable for virtual screening settings with a common binding pocket.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-scalar-fields-for-molecular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Series2Vec: Similarity-based Self-supervised Representation Learning for Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/series2vec-similarity-based-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our evaluation of Series2Vec on nine large real-world datasets, along with the UCR/UEA archive, shows enhanced performance compared to current state-of-the-art self-supervised techniques for time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/series2vec-similarity-based-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nerblackbox: A High-level Library for Named Entity Recognition in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerblackbox-a-high-level-library-for-named</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present nerblackbox, a python library to facilitate the use of state-of-the-art transformer-based models for named entity recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerblackbox-a-high-level-library-for-named</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Structural-Clustering Based Active Learning for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-structural-clustering-based-active-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we propose the Structural-Clustering PageRank method for improved Active learning (SPA) specifically designed for graph-structured data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-structural-clustering-based-active-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeanCut: A Greedy-Optimized Graph Clustering via Path-based Similarity and Degree Descent Criterion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meancut-a-greedy-optimized-graph-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the most typical graph clustering method, spectral clustering is popular and attractive due to the remarkable performance, easy implementation, and strong adaptability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meancut-a-greedy-optimized-graph-clustering</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
