<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 09:12:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Grimm -- Open-ended Visual Storytelling via Latent Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intelligent-grimm-open-ended-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative models have recently exhibited exceptional capabilities in various scenarios, for example, image generation based on text description.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intelligent-grimm-open-ended-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explanation Graph Generation via Generative Pre-training over Synthetic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanation-graph-generation-via-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The generation of explanation graphs is a significant task that aims to produce explanation graphs in response to user input, revealing the internal reasoning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanation-graph-generation-via-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Reinforcement Learning under Limited Visual Observability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-reinforcement-learning-under-limited</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This learnable reward is assigned by sensorimotor reward module, incentivizes the sensory policy to select observations that are optimal to infer its own motor action, inspired by the sensorimotor stage of humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-reinforcement-learning-under-limited</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepFake-Adapter: Dual-Level Adapter for DeepFake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepfake-adapter-dual-level-adapter-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike existing deepfake detection methods merely focusing on low-level forgery patterns, the forgery detection process of our model can be regularized by generalizable high-level semantics from a pre-trained ViT and adapted by global and local low-level forgeries of deepfake data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepfake-adapter-dual-level-adapter-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(Almost) Provable Error Bounds Under Distribution Shift via Disagreement Discrepancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/almost-provable-error-bounds-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimating the bound requires optimizing one multiclass classifier to disagree with another, for which some prior works have used sub-optimal proxy losses; we devise a "disagreement loss" which is theoretically justified and performs better in practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/almost-provable-error-bounds-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A big data approach towards sarcasm detection in Russian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-big-data-approach-towards-sarcasm-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a set of deterministic algorithms for Russian inflection and automated text synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-big-data-approach-towards-sarcasm-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TorchRL: A data-driven decision-making library for PyTorch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchrl-a-data-driven-decision-making-library</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Striking a balance between integration and modularity is crucial for a machine learning library to be versatile and user-friendly, especially in handling decision and control tasks that involve large development teams and complex, real-world data, and environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchrl-a-data-driven-decision-making-library</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleash the Potential of 3D Point Cloud Modeling with A Calibrated Local Geometry-driven Distance Metric</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleash-the-potential-of-3d-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By associating each reference point with two given point clouds through computing its directional distances to them, the difference in directional distances of an identical reference point characterizes the geometric difference between a typical local region of the two point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleash-the-potential-of-3d-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object pop-up: Can we infer 3D objects and their poses from human interactions alone?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-pop-up-can-we-infer-3d-objects-and-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The intimate entanglement between objects affordances and human poses is of large interest, among others, for behavioural sciences, cognitive psychology, and Computer Vision communities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-pop-up-can-we-infer-3d-objects-and-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vocabulary-free Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vocabulary-free-image-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We thus formalize a novel task, termed as Vocabulary-free Image Classification (VIC), where we aim to assign to an input image a class that resides in an unconstrained language-induced semantic space, without the prerequisite of a known vocabulary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vocabulary-free-image-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Test-time Adaptation through Weight Ensembling, Diversity Weighting, and Prior Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-test-time-adaptation-through-weight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since distribution shifts are likely to occur during test-time and can drastically decrease the model's performance, online test-time adaptation (TTA) continues to update the model after deployment, leveraging the current test data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-test-time-adaptation-through-weight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geo-Tiles for Semantic Segmentation of Earth Observation Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geo-tiles-for-semantic-segmentation-of-earth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For instance, the proposed tiling scheme shows flexible customization properties regarding tile granularity, tile stride and image boundary alignment, which allows us to perform a tile specific data augmentation during training and a substitution of pixel predictions with limited context information using data of overlapping tiles during inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geo-tiles-for-semantic-segmentation-of-earth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Failure Pattern Identification of Predictive Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-failure-pattern-identification-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recommendation algorithm is conceptualized as a stochastic sampler that, in each round, queries the annotators a subset of samples for their true labels and obtains the feedback information on whether the samples are misclassified.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-failure-pattern-identification-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S$^2$ME: Spatial-Spectral Mutual Teaching and Ensemble Learning for Scribble-supervised Polyp Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-2-me-spatial-spectral-mutual-teaching-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, to produce reliable mixed pseudo labels, which enhance the effectiveness of ensemble learning, we introduce a novel adaptive pixel-wise fusion technique based on the entropy guidance from the spatial and spectral branches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-2-me-spatial-spectral-mutual-teaching-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconstructing Graph Diffusion History from a Single Snapshot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructing-graph-diffusion-history-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[They are exclusively based on the maximum likelihood estimation (MLE) formulation and require to know true diffusion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructing-graph-diffusion-history-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affinity-based Attention in Self-supervised Transformers Predicts Dynamics of Object Grouping in Humans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affinity-based-attention-in-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We found that our models of affinity spread that were built on feature maps from the self-supervised Transformers showed significant improvement over baseline and CNN based models on predicting reaction time patterns of humans, despite not being trained on the task or with any other object labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affinity-based-attention-in-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of Multi-indicator And Multi-organ Medical Image Segmentation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-multi-indicator-and-multi-organ</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, MIMO offers detailed information on the segmentation of each organ in each sample, thereby aiding developers in analyzing and improving the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-multi-indicator-and-multi-organ</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSGD-CECA: Decentralized SGD with Communication-Optimal Exact Consensus Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsgd-ceca-decentralized-sgd-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Their communication, governed by the communication topology and gossip weight matrices, facilitates the exchange of model updates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsgd-ceca-decentralized-sgd-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decomposing Global Feature Effects Based on Feature Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decomposing-global-feature-effects-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We formally introduce generalized additive decomposition of global effects (GADGET), which is a new framework based on recursive partitioning to find interpretable regions in the feature space such that the interaction-related heterogeneity of local feature effects is minimized.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decomposing-global-feature-effects-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech Self-Supervised Representation Benchmarking: Are We Doing it Right?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-self-supervised-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning (SSL) has recently allowed leveraging large datasets of unlabeled speech signals to reach impressive performance on speech tasks using only small amounts of annotated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-self-supervised-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-end Knowledge Retrieval with Multi-modal Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-knowledge-retrieval-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate knowledge retrieval with multi-modal queries, i. e. queries containing information split across image and text inputs, a challenging task that differs from previous work on cross-modal retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-knowledge-retrieval-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label- and slide-free tissue histology using 3D epi-mode quantitative phase imaging and virtual H&amp;E staining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-and-slide-free-tissue-histology-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Histological staining of tissue biopsies, especially hematoxylin and eosin (H&E) staining, serves as the benchmark for disease diagnosis and comprehensive clinical assessment of tissue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-and-slide-free-tissue-histology-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unfair Utilities and First Steps Towards Improving Them</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unfair-utilities-and-first-steps-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many fairness criteria constrain the policy or choice of predictors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unfair-utilities-and-first-steps-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACT: Federated Adversarial Cross Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fact-federated-adversarial-cross-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Federated Adversarial Cross Training (FACT), which uses the implicit domain differences between source clients to identify domain shifts in the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fact-federated-adversarial-cross-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inserting Anybody in Diffusion Models via Celeb Basis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inserting-anybody-in-diffusion-models-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empowered by the proposed celeb basis, the new identity in our customized model showcases a better concept combination ability than previous personalization methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inserting-anybody-in-diffusion-models-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wuerstchen: Efficient Pretraining of Text-to-Image Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wuerstchen-efficient-pretraining-of-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Wuerstchen, a novel technique for text-to-image synthesis that unites competitive performance with unprecedented cost-effectiveness and ease of training on constrained hardware.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wuerstchen-efficient-pretraining-of-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuroGF: A Neural Representation for Fast Geodesic Distance and Path Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurogf-a-neural-representation-for-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, traditional algorithms for computing geodesic distances and paths on 3D mesh models are often inefficient and slow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurogf-a-neural-representation-for-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thought Cloning: Learning to Think while Acting by Imitating Human Thinking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thought-cloning-learning-to-think-while</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hypothesize one reason for such cognitive deficiencies is that they lack the benefits of thinking in language and that we can improve AI agents by training them to think like humans do.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thought-cloning-learning-to-think-while</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In or Out? Fixing ImageNet Out-of-Distribution Detection Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-or-out-fixing-imagenet-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The OOD detection performance when the in-distribution (ID) is ImageNet-1K is commonly being tested on a small range of test OOD datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-or-out-fixing-imagenet-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Interactive Image Inpainting via Sketch Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-interactive-image-inpainting-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we propose a two-stage image inpainting method termed SketchRefiner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-interactive-image-inpainting-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symmetric Uncertainty-Aware Feature Transmission for Depth Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetric-uncertainty-aware-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(2) For the cross-modality gap, we propose a novel Symmetric Uncertainty scheme to remove parts of RGB information harmful to the recovery of HR depth maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetric-uncertainty-aware-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning and Kalman Filtering for Nanomechanical Mass Spectrometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-and-kalman-filtering-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the pure learning based approach that discards the Kalman filter, the raw data from the sensor are used in training a model for both location and size prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-and-kalman-filtering-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interaction Measures, Partition Lattices and Kernel Tests for High-Order Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interaction-measures-partition-lattices-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Models that rely solely on pairwise relationships often fail to capture the complete statistical structure of the complex multivariate data found in diverse domains, such as socio-economic, ecological, or biomedical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interaction-measures-partition-lattices-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlothSpeech: Denial-of-service Attack Against Speech Recognition Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slothspeech-denial-of-service-attack-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that popular ASR models like Speech2Text model and Whisper model have dynamic computation based on different inputs, causing dynamic efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slothspeech-denial-of-service-attack-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TriSig: Assessing the statistical significance of triclusters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trisig-assessing-the-statistical-significance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work aims at proposing a statistical frame to assess the probability of patterns in tensor data to deviate from null expectations, extending well-established principles for assessing the statistical significance of patterns in matrix data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trisig-assessing-the-statistical-significance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Switching Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-switching-dynamical-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamical systems with complex behaviours, e. g. immune system cells interacting with a pathogen, are commonly modelled by splitting the behaviour into different regimes, or modes, each with simpler dynamics, and then learning the switching behaviour from one mode to another.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-switching-dynamical-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonicverse: A Multisensory Simulation Platform for Embodied Household Agents that See and Hear</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sonicverse-a-multisensory-simulation-platform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Sonicverse, a multisensory simulation platform with integrated audio-visual simulation for training household agents that can both see and hear.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sonicverse-a-multisensory-simulation-platform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Train Offline, Test Online: A Real Robot Learning Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/train-offline-test-online-a-real-robot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Three challenges limit the progress of robot learning research: robots are expensive (few labs can participate), everyone uses different robots (findings do not generalize across labs), and we lack internet-scale robotics data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/train-offline-test-online-a-real-robot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiera: A Hierarchical Vision Transformer without the Bells-and-Whistles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiera-a-hierarchical-vision-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern hierarchical vision transformers have added several vision-specific components in the pursuit of supervised classification performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiera-a-hierarchical-vision-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dilated Convolution with Learnable Spacings: beyond bilinear interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilated-convolution-with-learnable-spacings-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dilated Convolution with Learnable Spacings (DCLS) is a recently proposed variation of the dilated convolution in which the spacings between the non-zero elements in the kernel, or equivalently their positions, are learnable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilated-convolution-with-learnable-spacings-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Event Argument Extraction: Can EAE Models Learn Better When Being Aware of Event Co-occurrences?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-event-argument-extraction-can-eae</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under this framework, we experiment with 3 different training-inference schemes on 4 datasets (ACE05, RAMS, WikiEvents and MLEE) and discover that via training the model to extract all events in parallel, it can better distinguish the semantic boundary of each event and its ability to extract single event gets substantially improved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-event-argument-extraction-can-eae</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Anisotropy and Outliers in Multilingual Language Models for Cross-Lingual Semantic Sentence Similarity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-anisotropy-and-outliers-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate outlier dimensions and their relationship to anisotropy in multiple pre-trained multilingual language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-anisotropy-and-outliers-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hidden Language of Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-hidden-language-of-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applied over the state-of-the-art Stable Diffusion model, this decomposition reveals non-trivial and surprising structures in the representations of concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-hidden-language-of-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Autoencoders with Multi-Window Attention Are Better Audio Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-with-multi-window</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several recent works have adapted Masked Autoencoders (MAEs) for learning general-purpose audio representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-with-multi-window</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layout and Task Aware Instruction Prompt for Zero-shot Document Image Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layout-and-task-aware-instruction-prompt-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pre-training-fine-tuning paradigm based on layout-aware multimodal pre-trained models has achieved significant progress on document image question answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layout-and-task-aware-instruction-prompt-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRES: Generalized Referring Expression Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gres-generalized-referring-expression-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing classic RES datasets and methods commonly support single-target expressions only, i. e., one expression refers to one target object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gres-generalized-referring-expression-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Risks of Recourse in Binary Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-risks-of-recourse-in-binary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Algorithmic recourse provides explanations that help users overturn an unfavorable decision by a machine learning system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-risks-of-recourse-in-binary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShaRP: Shape-Regularized Multidimensional Projections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharp-shape-regularized-multidimensional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Projections, or dimensionality reduction methods, are techniques of choice for the visual exploration of high-dimensional data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharp-shape-regularized-multidimensional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pgMAP: a pipeline to enable guide RNA read mapping from dual-targeting CRISPR screens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgmap-a-pipeline-to-enable-guide-rna-read</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We developed pgMAP, an analysis pipeline to map gRNA sequencing reads from dual-targeting CRISPR screens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgmap-a-pipeline-to-enable-guide-rna-read</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EEL: Efficiently Encoding Lattices for Reranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eel-efficiently-encoding-lattices-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Standard decoding approaches for conditional text generation tasks typically search for an output hypothesis with high model probability, but this may not yield the best hypothesis according to human judgments of quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eel-efficiently-encoding-lattices-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
