<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 21:07:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Spurious Forgetting in Continual Learning of Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spurious-forgetting-in-continual-learning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) reveal a perplexing phenomenon in continual learning: despite extensive training, models experience significant performance declines, raising questions about task alignment and underlying knowledge retention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spurious-forgetting-in-continual-learning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Task Diversity: Provable Representation Transfer for Sequential Multi-Task Linear Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-task-diversity-provable-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present the first nontrivial result for sequential multi-task linear bandits without the task diversity assumption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-task-diversity-provable-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pix2Cap-COCO: Advancing Visual Comprehension via Pixel-Level Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pix2cap-coco-advancing-visual-comprehension</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results demonstrate that Pix2Cap-COCO is a particularly challenging dataset, as it requires models to excel in both fine-grained visual understanding and detailed language generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pix2cap-coco-advancing-visual-comprehension</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Efficient Diffusion-based Non-Autoregressive Solver for Traveling Salesman Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-diffusion-based-non</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enhance the solution quality while maintaining fast inference, we propose DEITSP, a diffusion model with efficient iterations tailored for TSP that operates in a NAR manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-diffusion-based-non</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Large Language Models Truly Understand Geometric Structures?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-large-language-models-truly-understand</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Geometric ability is a significant challenge for large language models (LLMs) due to the need for advanced spatial comprehension and abstract thinking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-large-language-models-truly-understand</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensuring Medical AI Safety: Explainable AI-Driven Detection and Mitigation of Spurious Model Behavior and Associated Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensuring-medical-ai-safety-explainable-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks are increasingly employed in high-stakes medical applications, despite their tendency for shortcut learning in the presence of spurious correlations, which can have potentially fatal consequences in practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensuring-medical-ai-safety-explainable-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HumorReject: Decoupling LLM Safety from Refusal Prefix via A Little Humor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humorreject-decoupling-llm-safety-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) commonly rely on explicit refusal prefixes for safety, making them vulnerable to prefix injection attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humorreject-decoupling-llm-safety-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoMINO: A Decomposable Multi-scale Iterative Neural Operator for Modeling Large Scale Engineering Simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domino-a-decomposable-multi-scale-iterative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerical simulations play a critical role in design and development of engineering products and processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domino-a-decomposable-multi-scale-iterative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedPref: Federated Learning Across Heterogeneous Multi-objective Preferences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedpref-federated-learning-across</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FL circumvents this constraint by carrying out model training in distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedpref-federated-learning-across</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WFCRL: A Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning Benchmark for Wind Farm Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wfcrl-a-multi-agent-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, we introduce WFCRL (Wind Farm Control with Reinforcement Learning), the first open suite of multi-agent reinforcement learning environments for the wind farm control problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wfcrl-a-multi-agent-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Prompt-One-Story: Free-Lunch Consistent Text-to-Image Generation Using a Single Prompt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-prompt-one-story-free-lunch-consistent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Drawing inspiration from the inherent context consistency, we propose a novel training-free method for consistent text-to-image (T2I) generation, termed "One-Prompt-One-Story" (1Prompt1Story).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-prompt-one-story-free-lunch-consistent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointOBB-v3: Expanding Performance Boundaries of Single Point-Supervised Oriented Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointobb-v3-expanding-performance-boundaries</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the views, a scale augmentation module and an angle acquisition module are constructed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointobb-v3-expanding-performance-boundaries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Multimodal Open-set Test-time Adaptation via Adaptive Entropy-aware Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-multimodal-open-set-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This task becomes more challenging when multiple modalities are involved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-multimodal-open-set-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MambaQuant: Quantizing the Mamba Family with Variance Aligned Rotation Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambaquant-quantizing-the-mamba-family-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To these ends, we propose MambaQuant, a post-training quantization (PTQ) framework consisting of: 1) Karhunen-Loeve Transformation (KLT) enhanced rotation, rendering the rotation matrix adaptable to diverse channel distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambaquant-quantizing-the-mamba-family-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can We Generate Images with CoT? Let's Verify and Reinforce Image Generation Step by Step</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-generate-images-with-cot-let-s-verify</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope our study provides unique insights and paves a new path for integrating CoT reasoning with autoregressive image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-generate-images-with-cot-let-s-verify</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularizing cross entropy loss via minimum entropy and K-L divergence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-cross-entropy-loss-via-minimum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The two loss functions extend standard cross entropy loss by regularizing it with minimum entropy and Kullback-Leibler (K-L) divergence terms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-cross-entropy-loss-via-minimum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio Map Estimation via Latent Domain Plug-and-Play Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radio-map-estimation-via-latent-domain-plug</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike conventional PnP methods that operate directly in the data domain, the proposed method exploits the underlying physical structure of radio maps and proposes an ADMM algorithm that denoises in a latent domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radio-map-estimation-via-latent-domain-plug</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring a Principled Framework For Deep Subspace Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-a-principled-framework-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subspace clustering is a classical unsupervised learning task, built on a basic assumption that high-dimensional data can be approximated by a union of subspaces (UoS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-a-principled-framework-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAMQA: A Unified Framework for Retrieval-Augmented Multi-Modal Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ramqa-a-unified-framework-for-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal retrieval-augmented Question Answering (MRAQA), integrating text and images, has gained significant attention in information retrieval (IR) and natural language processing (NLP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ramqa-a-unified-framework-for-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Controlled Differential Equations For Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-controlled-differential-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we argue that weight control is critical for neural ODE-based methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-controlled-differential-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A light-weight model to generate NDWI from Sentinel-1</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-light-weight-model-to-generate-ndwi-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The use of Sentinel-2 images to compute Normalized Difference Water Index (NDWI) has many applications, including water body area detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-light-weight-model-to-generate-ndwi-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M3PT: A Transformer for Multimodal, Multi-Party Social Signal Prediction with Person-aware Blockwise Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3pt-a-transformer-for-multimodal-multi-party</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding social signals in multi-party conversations is important for human-robot interaction and artificial social intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3pt-a-transformer-for-multimodal-multi-party</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EgoHand: Ego-centric Hand Pose Estimation and Gesture Recognition with Head-mounted Millimeter-wave Radar and IMUs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egohand-ego-centric-hand-pose-estimation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advanced Virtual Reality (VR) headsets, such as the Apple Vision Pro, employ bottom-facing cameras to detect hand gestures and inputs, which offers users significant convenience in VR interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egohand-ego-centric-hand-pose-estimation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Conformance Checking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-conformance-checking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We generate synthetic event logs for each organization as well as the complete process, and we apply our approach to identify and evaluate the cost of pre-injected miscommunications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-conformance-checking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Realistic Forehead-Creases for User Verification via Conditioned Piecewise Polynomial Curves</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-realistic-forehead-creases-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a trait-specific image generation method that models forehead creases geometrically using B-spline and B\'ezier curves.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-realistic-forehead-creases-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantized Spike-driven Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantized-spike-driven-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate this issue, we take inspiration from mutual information entropy and propose a bi-level optimization strategy to rectify the information distribution in Q-SDSA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantized-spike-driven-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watching the AI Watchdogs: A Fairness and Robustness Analysis of AI Safety Moderation Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watching-the-ai-watchdogs-a-fairness-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AI Safety Moderation (ASM) classifiers are designed to moderate content on social media platforms and to serve as guardrails that prevent Large Language Models (LLMs) from being fine-tuned on unsafe inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watching-the-ai-watchdogs-a-fairness-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NUDT4MSTAR: A New Dataset and Benchmark Towards SAR Target Recognition in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nudt4mstar-a-new-dataset-and-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces NUDT4MSTAR, a large-scale SAR dataset for vehicle target recognition in the wild, including 40 target types and a wide array of imaging conditions across 5 different scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nudt4mstar-a-new-dataset-and-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Video Understanding and Multi-round Interaction with Memory-enhanced Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-video-understanding-and-multi-round</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in Large Language Models (LLMs) have enabled the development of Video-LLMs, advancing multimodal learning by bridging video data with language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-video-understanding-and-multi-round</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unraveling Normal Anatomy via Fluid-Driven Anomaly Randomization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-normal-anatomy-via-fluid-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[UNA is trained on a combination of synthetic and real data, and can be applied directly to real images with potential pathology without the need for fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-normal-anatomy-via-fluid-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLO11-JDE: Fast and Accurate Multi-Object Tracking with Self-Supervised Re-ID</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo11-jde-fast-and-accurate-multi-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce YOLO11-JDE, a fast and accurate multi-object tracking (MOT) solution that combines real-time object detection with self-supervised Re-Identification (Re-ID).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo11-jde-fast-and-accurate-multi-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAA: Kolmogorov-Arnold Attention for Enhancing Attentive Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kaa-kolmogorov-arnold-attention-for-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) with attention mechanisms, often referred to as attentive GNNs, have emerged as a prominent paradigm in advanced GNN models in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kaa-kolmogorov-arnold-attention-for-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse identification of nonlinear dynamics and Koopman operators with Shallow Recurrent Decoder Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-identification-of-nonlinear-dynamics-6</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatiotemporal modeling of real-world data poses a challenging problem due to inherent high dimensionality, measurement noise, and expensive data collection procedures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-identification-of-nonlinear-dynamics-6</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do as We Do, Not as You Think: the Conformity of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-as-we-do-not-as-you-think-the-conformity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) revolutionize the field of intelligent agents, enabling collaborative multi-agent systems capable of tackling complex problems across various domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-as-we-do-not-as-you-think-the-conformity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable XR: Understanding User Behaviors of XR Environments using LLM-assisted Analytics Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-xr-understanding-user-behaviors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Explainable XR, an end-to-end framework for analyzing user behavior in diverse eXtended Reality (XR) environments by leveraging Large Language Models (LLMs) for data interpretation assistance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-xr-understanding-user-behaviors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LITE: Efficiently Estimating Gaussian Probability of Maximality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lite-efficiently-estimating-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of computing the probability of maximality (PoM) of a Gaussian random vector, i. e., the probability for each dimension to be maximal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lite-efficiently-estimating-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixRec: Individual and Collective Mixing Empowers Data Augmentation for Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixrec-individual-and-collective-mixing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, data sparsity caused by difficult-to-access interaction data severely limits the effectiveness of recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixrec-individual-and-collective-mixing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utilizing Evolution Strategies to Train Transformers in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilizing-evolution-strategies-to-train</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore a capability of evolution strategies to train an agent with its policy based on a transformer architecture in a reinforcement learning setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilizing-evolution-strategies-to-train</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-driven Online Action Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-driven-online-action-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting actions as they occur is essential for applications like video surveillance, autonomous driving, and human-robot interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-driven-online-action-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentRec: Agent Recommendation Using Sentence Embeddings Aligned to Human Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentrec-agent-recommendation-using-sentence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel architecture for recommending which LLM agent out of many should perform a task given a natural language prompt by extending the Sentence-BERT (SBERT) encoder model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentrec-agent-recommendation-using-sentence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Sample Relations for Few-Shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-sample-relations-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MGRCL categorizes sample relations into three types: intra-sample relation of the same sample under different transformations, intra-class relation of homogenous samples, and inter-class relation of inhomogeneous samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-sample-relations-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Disentangled Training for Nonlinear Transform in Learned Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-disentangled-training-for-nonlinear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On such basis, we propose a linear auxiliary transform (AuxT) to disentangle energy compaction in training nonlinear transforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-disentangled-training-for-nonlinear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Vision-Language Models for Knowledge-Grounded Data Annotation of Memes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-vision-language-models-for-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Memes have emerged as a powerful form of communication, integrating visual and textual elements to convey humor, satire, and cultural messages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-vision-language-models-for-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Transformer-based Autoregressive Decoder Architecture for Hierarchical Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transformer-based-autoregressive-decoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, unlike existing approaches for HTC, the encoder of RADAr has no explicit encoding of the label hierarchy and the decoder solely relies on the label sequences of the samples observed during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transformer-based-autoregressive-decoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantification via Gaussian Latent Space Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantification-via-gaussian-latent-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantification, or prevalence estimation, is the task of predicting the prevalence of each class within an unknown bag of examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantification-via-gaussian-latent-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning for Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, this survey aims to provide a comprehensive overview of PEFT techniques applied to diverse FMs and address critical gaps in understanding the techniques, trends, and applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoPixel: Pixel Grounding Large Multimodal Model in Remote Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geopixel-pixel-grounding-large-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GeoPixel supports up to 4K HD resolution in any aspect ratio, ideal for high-precision RS image analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geopixel-pixel-grounding-large-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exact Soft Analytical Side-Channel Attacks using Tractable Circuits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-soft-analytical-side-channel-attacks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By leveraging sparse belief messages, this performance is achieved with little more computational cost than SASCA, and about 3 orders of magnitude less than exact inference via exhaustive enumeration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-soft-analytical-side-channel-attacks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Robust Fairness via Confusional Spectral Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-robust-fairness-via-confusional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our analysis shows that the worst-class robust error is influenced by two main factors: the spectral norm of the empirical robust confusion matrix and the information embedded in the model and training set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-robust-fairness-via-confusional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Multi-tab Website Fingerprinting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-multi-tab-website</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art website fingerprinting (WF) attacks have demonstrated effectiveness even against Tor-protected network traffic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-multi-tab-website</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
