<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:17:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Batch Bayesian Optimization via Expected Subspace Improvement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batch-bayesian-optimization-via-expected</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most of current batch approaches use artificial functions to simulate the sequential Bayesian optimization algorithm's behavior to select a batch of points for parallel evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batch-bayesian-optimization-via-expected</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse patches adversarial attacks via extrapolating point-wise information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-patches-adversarial-attacks-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach enables simultaneous optimization of multiple sparse patches' locations and perturbations for any given number and shape.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-patches-adversarial-attacks-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreeFormer: Single-view Plant Skeleton Estimation via Tree-constrained Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treeformer-single-view-plant-skeleton</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While recent graph generation methods successfully infer thin structures from images, it is challenging to constrain the output graph strictly to a tree structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treeformer-single-view-plant-skeleton</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Driven Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-driven-occupancy-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate the inaccurate supervision, we propose a semantic transitive labeling pipeline to generate dense and finegrained 3D language occupancy ground truth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-driven-occupancy-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVGenMaster: Scaling Multi-View Generation from Any Image via 3D Priors Enhanced Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvgenmaster-scaling-multi-view-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce MVGenMaster, a multi-view diffusion model enhanced with 3D priors to address versatile Novel View Synthesis (NVS) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvgenmaster-scaling-multi-view-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Generation to Judgment: Opportunities and Challenges of LLM-as-a-judge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-generation-to-judgment-opportunities-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assessment and evaluation have long been critical challenges in artificial intelligence (AI) and natural language processing (NLP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-generation-to-judgment-opportunities-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIFeD: a Tiny Integer-based Federated learning algorithm with Direct feedback alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tifed-a-tiny-integer-based-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training machine and deep learning models directly on extremely resource-constrained devices is the next challenge in the field of tiny machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tifed-a-tiny-integer-based-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaussian Process Priors for Boundary Value Problems of Linear Partial Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-process-priors-for-boundary-value</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose Boundary Ehrenpreis-Palamodov Gaussian Processes (B-EPGPs), a novel framework for constructing GP priors that satisfy both general systems of linear PDEs with constant coefficients and linear boundary conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-process-priors-for-boundary-value</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Discrete Flow Matching for 3D De Novo Molecule Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-discrete-flow-matching-for-3d-de</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several discrete flow matching methods have been proposed recently to address this gap.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-discrete-flow-matching-for-3d-de</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ca2-VDM: Efficient Autoregressive Video Diffusion Model with Causal Generation and Cache Sharing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ca2-vdm-efficient-autoregressive-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For causal generation, it introduces unidirectional feature computation, which ensures that the cache of conditional frames can be precomputed in previous autoregression steps and reused in every subsequent step, eliminating redundant computations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ca2-vdm-efficient-autoregressive-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UltraSam: A Foundation Model for Ultrasound using Large Open-Access Segmentation Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultrasam-a-foundation-model-for-ultrasound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods: We compile US-43d, a large-scale collection of 43 open-access ultrasound datasets with over 280, 000 images and segmentation masks for more than 50 anatomical structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultrasam-a-foundation-model-for-ultrasound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnonyNoise: Anonymizing Event Data with Smart Noise to Outsmart Re-Identification and Preserve Privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anonynoise-anonymizing-event-data-with-smart</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing capabilities of deep neural networks for re-identification, combined with the rise in public surveillance in recent years, pose a substantial threat to individual privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anonynoise-anonymizing-event-data-with-smart</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM Augmentations to support Analytical Reasoning over Multiple Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-augmentations-to-support-analytical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on their demonstrated ability to perform a variety of tasks, we investigate the application of large language models (LLMs) to enhance in-depth analytical reasoning within the context of intelligence analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-augmentations-to-support-analytical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FUN-AD: Fully Unsupervised Learning for Anomaly Detection with Noisy Training Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fun-ad-fully-unsupervised-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method is motivated by two observations, that i) the pairwise feature distances between the normal samples are on average likely to be smaller than those between the anomaly samples or heterogeneous samples and ii) pairs of features mutually closest to each other are likely to be homogeneous pairs, which hold if the normal data has smaller variance than the anomaly data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fun-ad-fully-unsupervised-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O1 Replication Journey -- Part 2: Surpassing O1-preview through Simple Distillation, Big Progress or Bitter Lesson?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/o1-replication-journey-part-2-surpassing-o1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a critical examination of current approaches to replicating OpenAI's O1 model capabilities, with particular focus on the widespread but often undisclosed use of knowledge distillation techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/o1-replication-journey-part-2-surpassing-o1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Deep Reinforcement Learning with Task-Agnostic Policy Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-deep-reinforcement-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Central to the development of universal learning systems is the ability to solve multiple tasks without retraining from scratch when new data arrives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-deep-reinforcement-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soft-TransFormers for Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soft-transformers-for-continual-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by Well-initialized Lottery Ticket Hypothesis (WLTH), which provides suboptimal fine-tuning solutions, we propose a novel fully fine-tuned continual learning (CL) method referred to as Soft-TransFormers (Soft-TF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soft-transformers-for-continual-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Babies Teach Babies: Can student knowledge sharing outperform Teacher-Guided Distillation on small datasets?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-babies-teach-babies-can-student</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present our submission to the BabyLM challenge, aiming to push the boundaries of data-efficient language model pretraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-babies-teach-babies-can-student</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Generation Diversity Issues and How to Tame Them</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-generation-diversity-issues-and-how-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluation reveals that current diffusion models converge to limited subsets of the real distribution, with no current state-of-the-art models superpassing 77% of the diversity of the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-generation-diversity-issues-and-how-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deformable Mamba for Wide Field of View Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deformable-mamba-for-wide-field-of-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wide-FoV cameras, like fisheye and panoramic setups, are essential for broader perception but introduce significant distortions in 180{\deg} and 360{\deg} images, complicating dense prediction tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deformable-mamba-for-wide-field-of-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utilizing Uncertainty in 2D Pose Detectors for Probabilistic 3D Human Mesh Recovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilizing-uncertainty-in-2d-pose-detectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead, we propose to additionally supervise the learned distributions by minimizing the distance to distributions encoded in heatmaps of a 2D pose detector.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilizing-uncertainty-in-2d-pose-detectors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BayLing 2: A Multilingual Large Language Model with Efficient Language Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayling-2-a-multilingual-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce BayLing 2, which efficiently transfers generative capabilities and knowledge from high-resource languages to low-resource languages through language alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayling-2-a-multilingual-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensemble Learning via Knowledge Transfer for CTR Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-learning-via-knowledge-transfer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While many existing methods utilize ensemble learning to improve model performance, they typically limit the ensemble to two or three sub-networks, with little exploration of larger ensembles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-learning-via-knowledge-transfer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning for the Digital Typhoon Dataset: Extensions to Multiple Basins and New Developments in Representations and Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-for-the-digital-typhoon</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the Digital Typhoon Dataset V2, a new version of the longest typhoon satellite image dataset for 40+ years aimed at benchmarking machine learning models for long-term spatio-temporal data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-for-the-digital-typhoon</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cautious Optimizers: Improving Training with One Line of Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cautious-optimizers-improving-training-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a \textbf{single-line modification in Pytorch} to any momentum-based optimizer, which we rename Cautious Optimizer, e. g. C-AdamW and C-Lion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cautious-optimizers-improving-training-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edge Weight Prediction For Category-Agnostic Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge-weight-prediction-for-category-agnostic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Category-Agnostic Pose Estimation (CAPE) localizes keypoints across diverse object categories with a single model, using one or a few annotated support images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge-weight-prediction-for-category-agnostic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Spike-driven Transformer with Efficient Spike Firing Approximation Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-spike-driven-transformer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work enables SNNs to match ANN performance while maintaining the low-power advantage, marking a significant step towards SNNs as a general visual backbone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-spike-driven-transformer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Diffusion to Generate Them All</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-diffusion-to-generate-them-all</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results demonstrate competitive performance across tasks in both generation and prediction such as text-to-image, multiview generation, ID preservation, depth estimation and camera pose estimation despite relatively small training dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-diffusion-to-generate-them-all</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilevel semantic and adaptive actionness learning for weakly supervised temporal action localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilevel-semantic-and-adaptive-actionness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The AAL branch uses pseudo labels to learn class-agnostic action information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilevel-semantic-and-adaptive-actionness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable Single-view Object Pose Estimation by Two-side Generating and Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-single-view-object-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel generalizable object pose estimation method to determine the object pose using only one RGB image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-single-view-object-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LRSAA: Large-scale Remote Sensing Image Target Recognition and Automatic Annotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lrsaa-large-scale-remote-sensing-image-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a method for object recognition and automatic labeling in large-area remote sensing images called LRSAA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lrsaa-large-scale-remote-sensing-image-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highly Efficient and Unsupervised Framework for Moving Object Detection in Satellite Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/highly-efficient-and-unsupervised-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a generic unsupervised framework for SVMOD, in which pseudo labels generated by a traditional method can evolve with the training process to promote detection performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/highly-efficient-and-unsupervised-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Extensive Study on D2C: Overfitting Remediation in Deep Learning Using a Decentralized Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-extensive-study-on-d2c-overfitting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overfitting remains a significant challenge in deep learning, often arising from data outliers, noise, and limited training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-extensive-study-on-d2c-overfitting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lattice $φ^{4}$ field theory as a multi-agent system of financial markets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lattice-ph-4-field-theory-as-a-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a $\phi^{4}$ lattice field theory with frustrated dynamics as a multi-agent system to reproduce stylized facts of financial markets such as fat-tailed distributions of returns and clustered volatility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lattice-ph-4-field-theory-as-a-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantile deep learning models for multi-step ahead time series prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantile-deep-learning-models-for-multi-step</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Uncertainty quantification is crucial in time series prediction, and quantile regression offers a valuable mechanism for uncertainty quantification which is useful for extreme value forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantile-deep-learning-models-for-multi-step</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards RAW Object Detection in Diverse Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-raw-object-detection-in-diverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that sRGB pre-training constrains the potential of RAW object detection due to the domain gap between sRGB and RAW, prompting us to directly pre-train on the RAW domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-raw-object-detection-in-diverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROOT: VLM based System for Indoor Scene Understanding and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/root-vlm-based-system-for-indoor-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To train our SceneVLM, we collect over 610, 000 images from various public indoor datasets and implement a scene data generation pipeline with a semi-automated technique to establish relationships and estimate distances among indoor objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/root-vlm-based-system-for-indoor-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusion Matters: Learning Fusion in Deep Click-through Rate Prediction Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusion-matters-learning-fusion-in-deep-click</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce OptFusion, a method that automates the learning of fusion, encompassing both the connection learning and the operation selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusion-matters-learning-fusion-in-deep-click</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ResCLIP: Residual Attention for Training-free Dense Vision-language Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resclip-residual-attention-for-training-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works often attribute such deficiency in dense predictions to the self-attention layers in the final block, and have achieved commendable results by modifying the original query-key attention to self-correlation attention, (e. g., query-query and key-key attention).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resclip-residual-attention-for-training-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peritumoral Expansion Radiomics for Improved Lung Cancer Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peritumoral-expansion-radiomics-for-improved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Purpose: This study investigated how nodule segmentation and surrounding peritumoral regions influence radionics-based lung cancer classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peritumoral-expansion-radiomics-for-improved</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVTRv2: CTC Beats Encoder-Decoder Models in Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svtrv2-ctc-beats-encoder-decoder-models-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose SVTRv2, a CTC model that beats leading EDTRs in both accuracy and inference speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svtrv2-ctc-beats-encoder-decoder-models-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Training Data Quality or Quantity More Impactful to Small Language Model Performance?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-training-data-quality-or-quantity-more</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Minimal duplication positively impacted model accuracy (+0. 87% increase in accuracy at 25% duplication) without significantly increasing perplexity (+0. 52% increase going from 0% to 25% duplication) but excessive duplication led to pronounced performance degradation (-40% drop in accuracy at 100% duplication).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-training-data-quality-or-quantity-more</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Effect of Parametrization for Dimensionality Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-the-effect-of-parametrization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To explain this, we provide evidence that parameterized approaches lack the ability to repulse negative pairs, and the choice of loss function also has an impact.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-the-effect-of-parametrization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OccludeNet: A Causal Journey into Mixed-View Actor-Centric Video Action Recognition under Occlusions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occludenet-a-causal-journey-into-mixed-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We anticipate that the challenges posed by OccludeNet will stimulate further exploration of causal relations in occlusion scenarios and encourage a reevaluation of class correlations, ultimately promoting sustainable performance improvements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occludenet-a-causal-journey-into-mixed-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GSurf: 3D Reconstruction via Signed Distance Fields with Direct Gaussian Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gsurf-3d-reconstruction-via-signed-distance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these approaches often suffer from slow training and rendering speeds compared to 3D Gaussian splatting (3DGS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gsurf-3d-reconstruction-via-signed-distance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoding Urban Industrial Complexity: Enhancing Knowledge-Driven Insights via IndustryScopeGPT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-urban-industrial-complexity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Industrial parks are critical to urban economic growth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-urban-industrial-complexity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCDet: Object Center Detection via Bounding Box-Aware Heatmap Prediction on Edge Devices with NPUs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ocdet-object-center-detection-via-bounding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By integrating GC, BCFL, and CAS, OCDet establishes a new paradigm for efficient and robust object center detection on edge devices with NPUs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ocdet-object-center-detection-via-bounding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gotta Hear Them All: Sound Source Aware Vision to Audio Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gotta-hear-them-all-sound-source-aware-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is to our knowledge the first work to address V2A generation at the sound-source level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gotta-hear-them-all-sound-source-aware-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FG-CXR: A Radiologist-Aligned Gaze Dataset for Enhancing Interpretability in Chest X-Ray Report Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fg-cxr-a-radiologist-aligned-gaze-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike existing datasets that include a raw sequence of gaze alongside a report, with significant misalignment between gaze location and report content, our FG-CXR dataset offers a more grained alignment between gaze attention and diagnosis transcript.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fg-cxr-a-radiologist-aligned-gaze-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing person re-identification via Uncertainty Feature Fusion Method and Auto-weighted Measure Combination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-person-re-identification-via-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the Occluded-DukeMTMC dataset, our method increases Rank@1 by 22. 0% and mAP by 18. 4%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-person-re-identification-via-1</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
