<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 21:08:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>TeXBLEU: Automatic Metric for Evaluate LaTeX Format</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texbleu-automatic-metric-for-evaluate-latex</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LaTeX is highly suited to creating documents with special formatting, particularly in the fields of science, technology, mathematics, and computer science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texbleu-automatic-metric-for-evaluate-latex</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DACAT: Dual-stream Adaptive Clip-aware Time Modeling for Robust Online Surgical Phase Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dacat-dual-stream-adaptive-clip-aware-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the other stream, DACAT fine-tunes a new frame encoder to extract the frame-wise feature at the current moment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dacat-dual-stream-adaptive-clip-aware-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALSS-YOLO: An Adaptive Lightweight Channel Split and Shuffling Network for TIR Wildlife Detection in UAV Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alss-yolo-an-adaptive-lightweight-channel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This improves the extraction of blurry features, crucial for handling jitter-induced blur and overlapping targets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alss-yolo-an-adaptive-lightweight-channel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ferret: Federated Full-Parameter Tuning at Scale for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ferret-federated-full-parameter-tuning-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these limitations, we propose federated full-parameter tuning at scale for LLMs (Ferret), the first first-order method with shared randomness to enable scalable full-parameter tuning of LLMs across decentralized data sources while maintaining competitive model accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ferret-federated-full-parameter-tuning-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context Enhancement with Reconstruction as Sequence for Unified Unsupervised Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-enhancement-with-reconstruction-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating the RASFormer block, our RAS method achieves superior contextual awareness capabilities, leading to remarkable performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-enhancement-with-reconstruction-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loss Distillation via Gradient Matching for Point Cloud Completion with Weighted Chamfer Distance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loss-distillation-via-gradient-matching-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a search scheme, {\em Loss Distillation via Gradient Matching}, to find good candidate loss functions by mimicking the learning behavior in backpropagation between HyperCD and weighted CD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loss-distillation-via-gradient-matching-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Source Music Generation with Latent Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-music-generation-with-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The compressed source latent also facilitates more efficient generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-music-generation-with-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Performance Few-Shot Segmentation with Foundation Models: An Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-performance-few-shot-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the performance of these methods is often constrained by models pre-trained on classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-performance-few-shot-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTDA-HSED: Mutual-Assistance Tuning and Dual-Branch Aggregating for Heterogeneous Sound Event Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtda-hsed-mutual-assistance-tuning-and-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sound Event Detection (SED) plays a vital role in comprehending and perceiving acoustic scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtda-hsed-mutual-assistance-tuning-and-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoCalib: Learning Single-image Calibration with Geometric Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geocalib-learning-single-image-calibration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This single-image calibration can benefit various downstream applications like image editing and 3D mapping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geocalib-learning-single-image-calibration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RealisDance: Equip controllable character animation with realistic hands</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realisdance-equip-controllable-character</link>
      <description><![CDATA[2) The hands generated using the DWPose sequence are blurry and unrealistic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realisdance-equip-controllable-character</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Generative Interactive Environments By Trained Agent Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-generative-interactive-environments</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Genie, a recent model, excels at learning from visually diverse environments but relies on costly human-collected data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-generative-interactive-environments</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Weaknesses of Backdoor-based Model Watermarking: An Information-theoretic Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-weaknesses-of-backdoor-based-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this discovery, we propose a novel model watermarking scheme, In-distribution Watermark Embedding (IWE), to overcome the limitations of existing method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-weaknesses-of-backdoor-based-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larger Language Models Don't Care How You Think: Why Chain-of-Thought Prompting Fails in Subjective Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/larger-language-models-don-t-care-how-you</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ICL can be augmented by incorporating the reasoning process to arrive at the final label explicitly in the prompt, a technique called Chain-of-Thought (CoT) prompting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/larger-language-models-don-t-care-how-you</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQLucid: Grounding Natural Language Database Queries with Interactive Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sqlucid-grounding-natural-language-database</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though recent advances in machine learning have led to significant improvements in natural language interfaces for databases, the accuracy and reliability of these systems remain limited, especially in high-stakes domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sqlucid-grounding-natural-language-database</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HybridFC: A Hybrid Fact-Checking Approach for Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybridfc-a-hybrid-fact-checking-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider fact-checking approaches that aim to predict the veracity of assertions in knowledge graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybridfc-a-hybrid-fact-checking-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When to Extract ReID Features: A Selective Approach for Improved Multiple Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-extract-reid-features-a-selective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate a selective approach to minimize the overhead of feature extraction while preserving accuracy, modularity, and ease of implementation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-extract-reid-features-a-selective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EntAugment: Entropy-Driven Adaptive Data Augmentation Framework for Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entaugment-entropy-driven-adaptive-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, to further enhance the efficacy of EntAugment, we introduce a novel entropy regularization term, EntLoss, which complements the EntAugment approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entaugment-entropy-driven-adaptive-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mahalanobis k-NN: A Statistical Lens for Robust Point-Cloud Registrations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mahalanobis-k-nn-a-statistical-lens-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we discuss Mahalanobis k-NN: a statistical lens designed to address the challenges of feature matching in learning-based point cloud registration when confronted with an arbitrary density of point clouds, either in the source or target point cloud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mahalanobis-k-nn-a-statistical-lens-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt2Fashion: An automatically generated fashion dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt2fashion-an-automatically-generated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the provided fine-grained insights on the quality and relevance of generation, we extend the discussion on the importance of expert knowledge for the evaluation of artistic AI-generated datasets such as this one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt2fashion-an-automatically-generated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly-supervised Camera Localization by Ground-to-satellite Image Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-camera-localization-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate this issue, this paper proposes a weakly supervised learning strategy for ground-to-satellite image registration when only noisy pose labels for ground images are available for network training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-camera-localization-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniLearn: Enhancing Dynamic Facial Expression Recognition through Unified Pre-Training and Fine-Tuning on Images and Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unilearn-enhancing-dynamic-facial-expression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this, we introduce UniLearn, a novel unified learning paradigm that integrates static facial expression recognition (SFER) data to enhance DFER task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unilearn-enhancing-dynamic-facial-expression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaMA-Omni: Seamless Speech Interaction with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-omni-seamless-speech-interaction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We build our model based on the latest Llama-3. 1-8B-Instruct model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-omni-seamless-speech-interaction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sources of Uncertainty in 3D Scene Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sources-of-uncertainty-in-3d-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The process of 3D scene reconstruction can be affected by numerous uncertainty sources in real-world scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sources-of-uncertainty-in-3d-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MENSA: A Multi-Event Network for Survival Analysis under Informative Censoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mensa-a-multi-event-network-for-survival</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These events are not mutually exclusive and there are often statistical dependencies between them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mensa-a-multi-event-network-for-survival</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developing the Temporal Graph Convolutional Neural Network Model to Predict Hip Replacement using Electronic Health Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/developing-the-temporal-graph-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model, trained on 9, 187 cases and 9, 187 controls, predicts hip replacement one year in advance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/developing-the-temporal-graph-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EDADepth: Enhanced Data Augmentation for Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edadepth-enhanced-data-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We employ the BEiT pre-trained semantic segmentation model for better extraction of text embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edadepth-enhanced-data-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedBrain-Distill: Communication-Efficient Federated Brain Tumor Classification Using Ensemble Knowledge Distillation on Non-IID Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedbrain-distill-communication-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose FedBrain-Distill, an approach that leverages Knowledge Distillation (KD) in an FL setting that maintains the users privacy and ensures the independence of FL clients in terms of model architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedbrain-distill-communication-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Tree Probability Estimation with Stochastic Optimization and Variance Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-tree-probability-estimation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Probability estimation of tree topologies is one of the fundamental tasks in phylogenetic inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-tree-probability-estimation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Chinese Knowledge Rectification in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-chinese-knowledge-rectification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Large Language Models (LLMs) exhibit remarkable generative capabilities, they are not without flaws, particularly in the form of hallucinations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-chinese-knowledge-rectification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLoRA: Federated Fine-Tuning Large Language Models with Heterogeneous Low-Rank Adaptations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flora-federated-fine-tuning-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new approach called FLORA that enables federated fine-tuning on heterogeneous LoRA adapters across clients through a novel stacking-based aggregation method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flora-federated-fine-tuning-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrofitting Temporal Graph Neural Networks with Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrofitting-temporal-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also adapt Transformer codebase to train TF-TGN efficiently with multiple GPUs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrofitting-temporal-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MemoRAG: Moving towards Next-Gen RAG Via Memory-Inspired Knowledge Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memorag-moving-towards-next-gen-rag-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) leverages retrieval tools to access external databases, thereby enhancing the generation quality of large language models (LLMs) through optimized context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memorag-moving-towards-next-gen-rag-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IndicVoices-R: Unlocking a Massive Multilingual Multi-speaker Speech Corpus for Scaling Indian TTS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indicvoices-r-unlocking-a-massive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our pipeline leverages the cross-lingual generalization of denoising and speech enhancement models trained on English and applied to Indian languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indicvoices-r-unlocking-a-massive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SciAgents: Automating scientific discovery through multi-agent intelligent graph reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sciagents-automating-scientific-discovery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key challenge in artificial intelligence is the creation of systems capable of autonomously advancing scientific understanding by exploring novel domains, identifying complex patterns, and uncovering previously unseen connections in vast scientific data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sciagents-automating-scientific-discovery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting English Winogender Schemas for Consistency, Coverage, and Grammatical Case</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-english-winogender-schemas-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While measuring bias and robustness in coreference resolution are important goals, such measurements are only as good as the tools we use to measure them with.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-english-winogender-schemas-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extracting the U.S. building types from OpenStreetMap data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extracting-the-u-s-building-types-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A major result of this work is the resulting dataset of classifying 67, 705, 475 buildings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extracting-the-u-s-building-types-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatially-Aware Speaker for Vision-and-Language Navigation Instruction Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatially-aware-speaker-for-vision-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Embodied AI aims to develop robots that can \textit{understand} and execute human language instructions, as well as communicate in natural languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatially-aware-speaker-for-vision-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STLM Engineering Report: Dropout</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stlm-engineering-report-dropout</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we explore the relevance of dropout for modern language models, particularly in the context of models on the scale of <100M parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stlm-engineering-report-dropout</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Multiview Object Consistency in Humans and Image Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-multiview-object-consistency-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a benchmark to directly evaluate the alignment between human observers and vision models on a 3D shape inference task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-multiview-object-consistency-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Multitask Learning Using Gradient-based Estimation of Task Affinity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-multitask-learning-using-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key idea of Grad-TAG is to train a "base" model for all tasks and then use a linearization technique to estimate the loss of the model for a specific task combination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-multitask-learning-using-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Utility Models: General Policies for Zero-Shot Deployment in New Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robot-utility-models-general-policies-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Robot Utility Models (RUMs), a framework for training and deploying zero-shot robot policies that can directly generalize to new environments without any finetuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robot-utility-models-general-policies-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distribution Discrepancy and Feature Heterogeneity for Active 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-discrepancy-and-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel and effective active learning (AL) method called Distribution Discrepancy and Feature Heterogeneity (DDFH), which simultaneously considers geometric features and model embeddings, assessing information from both the instance-level and frame-level perspectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-discrepancy-and-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEROjD: Lidar Extended Radar-Only Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lerojd-lidar-extended-radar-only-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore two strategies to transfer knowledge from the lidar to the radar domain and radar-only object detectors: 1. multi-stage training with sequential lidar point cloud thin-out, and 2. cross-modal knowledge distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lerojd-lidar-extended-radar-only-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransformerRanker: A Tool for Efficiently Finding the Best-Suited Language Models for Downstream Classification Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformerranker-a-tool-for-efficiently</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Classification tasks in NLP are typically addressed by selecting a pre-trained language model (PLM) from a model hub, and fine-tuning it for the task at hand.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformerranker-a-tool-for-efficiently</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototype-Driven Multi-Feature Generation for Visible-Infrared Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-driven-multi-feature-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The primary challenges in visible-infrared person re-identification arise from the differences between visible (vis) and infrared (ir) images, including inter-modal and intra-modal variations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-driven-multi-feature-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoDiCast: Conditional Diffusion Model for Weather Prediction with Uncertainty Quantification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codicast-conditional-diffusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our conditional diffusion model, CoDiCast, can generate 3-day global weather forecasts, at 6-hour steps and $5. 625^\circ$ latitude-longitude resolution, for over 5 variables, in about 12 minutes on a commodity A100 GPU machine with 80GB memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codicast-conditional-diffusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRADLE-VAE: Enhancing Single-Cell Gene Perturbation Modeling with Counterfactual Reasoning-based Artifact Disentanglement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cradle-vae-enhancing-single-cell-gene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting cellular responses to various perturbations is a critical focus in drug discovery and personalized therapeutics, with deep learning models playing a significant role in this endeavor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cradle-vae-enhancing-single-cell-gene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeing Through the Mask: Rethinking Adversarial Examples for CAPTCHAs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seeing-through-the-mask-rethinking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these methods are model-specific and thus can not aid CAPTCHAs in fooling all models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seeing-through-the-mask-rethinking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAN-Based Fusion of Dual-Domain for Audio-Driven Facial Landmarks Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kan-based-fusion-of-dual-domain-for-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the KFusion of Dual-Domain model, a robust model that generates landmarks from audio.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kan-based-fusion-of-dual-domain-for-audio</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
