<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 09:18:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DLNet: Direction-Aware Feature Integration for Robust Lane Detection in Complex Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dlnet-direction-aware-feature-integration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of autonomous driving systems has created a pressing need for accurate and robust lane detection to ensure driving safety and reliability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dlnet-direction-aware-feature-integration-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Object Stitching for Unsupervised Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-object-stitching-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive learning for single object centric images has achieved remarkable progress on unsupervised representation, but suffering inferior performance on the widespread images with multiple objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-object-stitching-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Well Begun is Half Done: Low-resource Preference Alignment by Weak-to-Strong Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/well-begun-is-half-done-low-resource</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the observation that the difficulty of generating aligned responses is concentrated at the beginning of decoding, we propose a novel framework, Weak-to-Strong Decoding (WSD), to enhance the alignment ability of base models by the guidance of a small aligned model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/well-begun-is-half-done-low-resource</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flowing Datasets with Wasserstein over Wasserstein Gradient Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowing-datasets-with-wasserstein-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many applications in machine learning involve data represented as probability distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowing-datasets-with-wasserstein-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CausalPFN: Amortized Causal Effect Estimation via In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalpfn-amortized-causal-effect-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CausalPFN combines ideas from Bayesian causal inference with the large-scale training protocol of prior-fitted networks (PFNs), learning to map raw observations directly to causal effects without any task-specific adjustment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalpfn-amortized-causal-effect-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Compact Vision Tokens for Efficient Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-compact-vision-tokens-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a Spatial Token Fusion (STF) method to learn compact vision tokens for short vision token sequence, where spatial-adjacent tokens are fused into one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-compact-vision-tokens-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TissUnet: Improved Extracranial Tissue and Cranium Segmentation for Children through Adulthood</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tissunet-improved-extracranial-tissue-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a second validation using expert manual annotations, median Dice was 0. 83 [IQR: 0. 83-0. 84] in healthy individuals and 0. 81 [IQR: 0. 78-0. 83] in tumor cases, outperforming previous state-of-the-art method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tissunet-improved-extracranial-tissue-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMBER2024 -- A Benchmark Dataset for Holistic Evaluation of Malware Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ember2024-a-benchmark-dataset-for-holistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A lack of accessible data has historically restricted malware analysis research, and practitioners have relied heavily on datasets provided by industry sources to advance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ember2024-a-benchmark-dataset-for-holistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agentic AI for Intent-Based Industrial Automation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentic-ai-for-intent-based-industrial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent development of Agentic AI systems, empowered by autonomous large language models (LLMs) agents with planning and tool-usage capabilities, enables new possibilities for the evolution of industrial automation and reduces the complexity introduced by Industry 4. 0.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentic-ai-for-intent-based-industrial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMSU: A Massive Multi-task Spoken Language Understanding and Reasoning Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmsu-a-massive-multi-task-spoken-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we introduce MMSU, a comprehensive benchmark designed specifically for understanding and reasoning in spoken language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmsu-a-massive-multi-task-spoken-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time to Talk: LLM Agents for Asynchronous Group Communication in Mafia Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-to-talk-llm-agents-for-asynchronous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, in group chats, online team meetings, or social games, there is no inherent notion of turns; therefore, the decision of when to speak forms a crucial part of the participant's decision making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-to-talk-llm-agents-for-asynchronous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissecting Logical Reasoning in LLMs: A Fine-Grained Evaluation and Supervision Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dissecting-logical-reasoning-in-llms-a-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Logical reasoning is a core capability for many applications of large language models (LLMs), yet existing benchmarks often rely solely on final-answer accuracy, failing to capture the quality and structure of the reasoning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dissecting-logical-reasoning-in-llms-a-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Play to Replay: Composed Video Retrieval for Temporally Fine-Grained Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-play-to-replay-composed-video-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Composed Video Retrieval (CoVR) retrieves a target video given a query video and a modification text describing the intended change.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-play-to-replay-composed-video-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlashDMoE: Fast Distributed MoE in a Single Kernel</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashdmoe-fast-distributed-moe-in-a-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The computational sparsity of Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) models enables sub-linear growth in compute cost as model size increases, thus offering a scalable path to training massive neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashdmoe-fast-distributed-moe-in-a-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Appearance Codes and Bilateral Grids for Driving Scene Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-appearance-codes-and-bilateral-grids</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel multi-scale bilateral grid that unifies appearance codes and bilateral grids.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-appearance-codes-and-bilateral-grids</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLFer: Smaller LM-Generated Documents Hallucination Filter &amp; Combiner for Query Expansion in Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/golfer-smaller-lm-generated-documents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs)-based query expansion for information retrieval augments queries with generated hypothetical documents with LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/golfer-smaller-lm-generated-documents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Channel Allocation for IEEE 802.11be Multi-Link Operation: When MAB Meets LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intelligent-channel-allocation-for-ieee-802</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further reduce sample complexity and enhance generalizability across diverse network scenarios, we put forth LLM-BAI-MCTS, an intelligent algorithm for the dynamic channel allocation problem by integrating the Large Language Model (LLM) into the BAI-MCTS algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intelligent-channel-allocation-for-ieee-802</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MineInsight: A Multi-sensor Dataset for Humanitarian Demining Robotics in Off-Road Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mineinsight-a-multi-sensor-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MineInsight is, to the best of our knowledge, the first dataset to integrate dual-view sensor scans from both an Unmanned Ground Vehicle and its robotic arm, offering multiple viewpoints to mitigate occlusions and improve spatial awareness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mineinsight-a-multi-sensor-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Beyond Experience: Generalizing to Unseen State Space with Reservoir Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-beyond-experience-generalizing-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning techniques offer an effective approach to modeling dynamical systems solely from observed data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-beyond-experience-generalizing-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OGGSplat: Open Gaussian Growing for Generalizable Reconstruction with Expanded Field-of-View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oggsplat-open-gaussian-growing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate our method, we establish a Gaussian Outpainting (GO) benchmark that assesses both semantic and generative quality of reconstructed open-vocabulary scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oggsplat-open-gaussian-growing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exp4Fuse: A Rank Fusion Framework for Enhanced Sparse Retrieval using Large Language Model-based Query Expansion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exp4fuse-a-rank-fusion-framework-for-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the efficacy of this method is highly dependent on the quality of the generated documents, which often requires complex prompt strategies and the integration of advanced dense retrieval techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exp4fuse-a-rank-fusion-framework-for-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Tempering Sampler with Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-tempering-sampler-with-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also introduce a novel method to combine high-temperature diffusion models to generate approximate lower-temperature samples, which are minimally refined using MCMC and used to train the next diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-tempering-sampler-with-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tight analyses of first-order methods with error feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tight-analyses-of-first-order-methods-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Communication between agents often constitutes a major computational bottleneck in distributed learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tight-analyses-of-first-order-methods-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs for sensory-motor control: Combining in-context and iterative learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-for-sensory-motor-control-combining-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method that enables large language models (LLMs) to control embodied agents by directly mapping continuous observation vectors to continuous action vectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-for-sensory-motor-control-combining-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inference economics of language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-economics-of-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a theoretical model that addresses the economic trade-off between cost per token versus serial token generation speed when deploying LLMs for inference at scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-economics-of-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth in the Few: High-Value Data Selection for Efficient Multi-Modal Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truth-in-the-few-high-value-data-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While multi-modal large language models (MLLMs) have made significant progress in complex reasoning tasks via reinforcement learning, it is commonly believed that extensive training data is necessary for improving multi-modal reasoning ability, inevitably leading to data redundancy and substantial computational costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truth-in-the-few-high-value-data-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEAR: BGP Event Analysis and Reporting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bear-bgp-event-analysis-and-reporting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce BEAR (BGP Event Analysis and Reporting), a novel framework that leverages large language models (LLMs) to automatically generate comprehensive reports explaining detected BGP anomaly events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bear-bgp-event-analysis-and-reporting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient Inversion Attacks on Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-inversion-attacks-on-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate how the privacy of the fine-tuning data of the users can be compromised via a malicious design of the pretrained model and trainable adapter modules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-inversion-attacks-on-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic measures afford fair comparisons of AIWP and NWP model output</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-measures-afford-fair</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then we find PC as the mean continuous ranked probability score (CRPS) of the postprocessed probabilistic forecasts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-measures-afford-fair</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HtFLlib: A Comprehensive Heterogeneous Federated Learning Library and Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/htfllib-a-comprehensive-heterogeneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill this gap, we introduce the first Heterogeneous Federated Learning Library (HtFLlib), an easy-to-use and extensible framework that integrates multiple datasets and model heterogeneity scenarios, offering a robust benchmark for research and practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/htfllib-a-comprehensive-heterogeneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Far Are We from Predicting Missing Modalities with Foundation Models?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-are-we-from-predicting-missing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we introduce a \textit{self-refinement mechanism}, which iteratively verifies and enhances the quality of generated modalities through internal feedback.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-are-we-from-predicting-missing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pseudo-Simulation for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-simulation-for-autonomous-driving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method then assigns a higher importance to synthetic observations that best match the AV's likely behavior using a novel proximity-based weighting scheme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-simulation-for-autonomous-driving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think Like a Person Before Responding: A Multi-Faceted Evaluation of Persona-Guided LLMs for Countering Hate</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/think-like-a-person-before-responding-a-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated counter-narratives (CN) offer a promising strategy for mitigating online hate speech, yet concerns about their affective tone, accessibility, and ethical risks remain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/think-like-a-person-before-responding-a-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AmbiK: Dataset of Ambiguous Tasks in Kitchen Environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambik-dataset-of-ambiguous-tasks-in-kitchen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AmbiK was collected with the assistance of LLMs and is human-validated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambik-dataset-of-ambiguous-tasks-in-kitchen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SplArt: Articulation Estimation and Part-Level Reconstruction with 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/splart-articulation-estimation-and-part-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstructing articulated objects prevalent in daily environments is crucial for applications in augmented/virtual reality and robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/splart-articulation-estimation-and-part-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSIMBaD: Sigma Scaling with SSIM-Guided Balanced Diffusion for AnimeFace Colorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssimbad-sigma-scaling-with-ssim-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel diffusion-based framework for automatic colorization of Anime-style facial sketches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssimbad-sigma-scaling-with-ssim-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matter-of-Fact: A Benchmark for Verifying the Feasibility of Literature-Supported Claims in Materials Science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matter-of-fact-a-benchmark-for-verifying-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contemporary approaches to assisted scientific discovery use language models to automatically generate large numbers of potential hypothesis to test, while also automatically generating code-based experiments to test those hypotheses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matter-of-fact-a-benchmark-for-verifying-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Savage-Dickey density ratio estimation with normalizing flows for Bayesian model comparison</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/savage-dickey-density-ratio-estimation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a neural SDDR approach using normalizing flows that can scale to settings where the super model contains a large number of extra parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/savage-dickey-density-ratio-estimation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Adaptation Method and Modality Gap Impact in Audio-Text Models for Prototypical Sound Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptation-method-and-modality-gap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Audio-text models are widely used in zero-shot environmental sound classification as they alleviate the need for annotated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptation-method-and-modality-gap</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OWMM-Agent: Open World Mobile Manipulation With Multi-modal Agentic Data Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/owmm-agent-open-world-mobile-manipulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the open-world mobile manipulation (OWMM) task remains a challenge due to the need for generalization to open-ended instructions and environments, as well as the systematic complexity to integrate high-level decision making with low-level robot control based on both global scene understanding and current agent state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/owmm-agent-open-world-mobile-manipulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding signatures of low-dimensional geometric landscapes in high-dimensional cell fate transitions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-signatures-of-low-dimensional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model combines low-dimensional gradient-like dynamical systems and high-dimensional Hopfield networks to capture the interplay between cell fate, gene expression, and signaling pathways.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-signatures-of-low-dimensional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR: Learning Diverse Robot Skill Abstractions through Rotation-Augmented Vector Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/star-learning-diverse-robot-skill</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transforming complex actions into discrete skill abstractions has demonstrated strong potential for robotic manipulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/star-learning-diverse-robot-skill</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLARIS: A High-contrast Polarimetric Imaging Benchmark Dataset for Exoplanetary Disk Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polaris-a-high-contrast-polarimetric-imaging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With over 1, 000, 000 images from more than 10, 000 exposures using state-of-the-art high-contrast imagers (e. g., Gemini Planet Imager, VLT/SPHERE) in the search for exoplanets, can artificial intelligence (AI) serve as a transformative tool in imaging Earth-like exoplanets in the coming decade?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polaris-a-high-contrast-polarimetric-imaging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survey of Active Learning Hyperparameters: Insights from a Large-Scale Experimental Grid</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survey-of-active-learning-hyperparameters</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we first compiled a large hyperparameter grid of over 4. 6 million hyperparameter combinations, second, recorded the performance of all combinations in the so-far biggest conducted AL study, and third, analyzed the impact of each hyperparameter in the experiment results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survey-of-active-learning-hyperparameters</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GARG-AML against Smurfing: A Scalable and Interpretable Graph-Based Framework for Anti-Money Laundering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/garg-aml-against-smurfing-a-scalable-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Money laundering poses a significant challenge as it is estimated to account for 2%-5% of the global GDP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/garg-aml-against-smurfing-a-scalable-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial Appearance Capture at Home with Patch-Level Reflectance Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facial-appearance-capture-at-home-with-patch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the reconstruction quality is still far behind the ones based on studio recordings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facial-appearance-capture-at-home-with-patch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapt before Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapt-before-continual-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual Learning (CL) seeks to enable neural networks to incrementally acquire new knowledge (plasticity) while retaining existing knowledge (stability).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapt-before-continual-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Expansion-Based Approach for Quantified Integer Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-expansion-based-approach-for-quantified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, the inclusion of a linear objective function enables QIP to effectively model multistage robust discrete linear optimization problems, making it a powerful tool for tackling uncertainty in optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-expansion-based-approach-for-quantified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photoreal Scene Reconstruction from an Egocentric Device</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/photoreal-scene-reconstruction-from-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the challenges associated with using egocentric devices to photorealistic reconstruct the scene in high dynamic range.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/photoreal-scene-reconstruction-from-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextAtari: 100K Frames Game Playing with Language Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textatari-100k-frames-game-playing-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present TextAtari, a benchmark for evaluating language agents on very long-horizon decision-making tasks spanning up to 100, 000 steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textatari-100k-frames-game-playing-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
