<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 21:06:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>TrOMR:Transformer-Based Polyphonic Optical Music Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tromr-transformer-based-polyphonic-optical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optical Music Recognition (OMR) is an important technology in music and has been researched for a long time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tromr-transformer-based-polyphonic-optical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Few-shot Action Recognition with Graph-guided Hybrid Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-few-shot-action-recognition-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Class prototype construction and matching are core aspects of few-shot action recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-few-shot-action-recognition-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Image Forgery Detection via Contrastive Learning and Unsupervised Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-image-forgery-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To resolve this dilemma, we propose the FOrensic ContrAstive cLustering (FOCAL) method, a novel, simple yet very effective paradigm based on contrastive learning and unsupervised clustering for the image forgery detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-image-forgery-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-based Alignment and Uniformity for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-alignment-and-uniformity-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel approach, graph-based alignment and uniformity (GraphAU), that explicitly considers high-order connectivities in the user-item bipartite graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-alignment-and-uniformity-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MonoNeRD: NeRF-like Representations for Monocular 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mononerd-nerf-like-representations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this work is the first to introduce volume rendering for M3D, and demonstrates the potential of implicit reconstruction for image-based 3D perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mononerd-nerf-like-representations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Relation Transformer for Unbiased Scene Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-relation-transformer-for-unbiased</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have seen a growing interest in Scene Graph Generation (SGG), a comprehensive visual scene understanding task that aims to predict entity relationships using a relation encoder-decoder pipeline stacked on top of an object encoder-decoder backbone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-relation-transformer-for-unbiased</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single Frame Semantic Segmentation Using Multi-Modal Spherical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-frame-semantic-segmentation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the research community has shown a lot of interest to panoramic images that offer a 360-degree directional perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-frame-semantic-segmentation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GiGaMAE: Generalizable Graph Masked Autoencoder via Collaborative Latent Space Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gigamae-generalizable-graph-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By considering embeddings encompassing graph topology and attribute information as reconstruction targets, our model could capture more generalized and comprehensive knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gigamae-generalizable-graph-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferior Alveolar Nerve Segmentation in CBCT images using Connectivity-Based Selective Re-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferior-alveolar-nerve-segmentation-in-cbct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inferior Alveolar Nerve (IAN) canal detection in CBCT is an important step in many dental and maxillofacial surgery applications to prevent irreversible damage to the nerve during the procedure. The ToothFairy2023 Challenge aims to establish a 3D maxillofacial dataset consisting of all sparse labels and partial dense labels, and improve the ability of automatic IAN segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferior-alveolar-nerve-segmentation-in-cbct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RLIPv2: Fast Scaling of Relational Language-Image Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlipv2-fast-scaling-of-relational-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose RLIPv2, a fast converging model that enables the scaling of relational pre-training to large-scale pseudo-labelled scene graph data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlipv2-fast-scaling-of-relational-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAPA-VQ: Neighborhood Aware Prototype Augmentation with Vector Quantization for Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/napa-vq-neighborhood-aware-prototype</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to the lack of old data, NECIL methods struggle to discriminate between old and new classes causing their feature representations to overlap.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/napa-vq-neighborhood-aware-prototype</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSE: Music Recommender System with Shuffle Play Recommendation Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/muse-music-recommender-system-with-shuffle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommender systems have become indispensable in music streaming services, enhancing user experiences by personalizing playlists and facilitating the serendipitous discovery of new music.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/muse-music-recommender-system-with-shuffle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predictive Authoring for Brazilian Portuguese Augmentative and Alternative Communication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictive-authoring-for-brazilian-portuguese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We tested different approaches to representing a pictogram for prediction: as a word (using pictogram captions), as a concept (using a dictionary definition), and as a set of synonyms (using related terms).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictive-authoring-for-brazilian-portuguese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training with Product Digital Twins for AutoRetail Checkout</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-with-product-digital-twins-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because the digital twins individually mimic user bias, the resulting DT training set better reflects the characteristics of the target scenario and allows us to train more effective product detection and tracking models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-with-product-digital-twins-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReCon: Reducing Congestion in Job Recommendation using Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recon-reducing-congestion-in-job</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommenders are increasingly used in domains where items have limited availability, such as the job market, where congestion is especially problematic: Recommending a vacancy -- for which typically only one person will be hired -- to a large number of job seekers may lead to frustration for job seekers, as they may be applying for jobs where they are not hired.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recon-reducing-congestion-in-job</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DReg-NeRF: Deep Registration for Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreg-nerf-deep-registration-for-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although Neural Radiance Fields (NeRF) is popular in the computer vision community recently, registering multiple NeRFs has yet to gain much attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreg-nerf-deep-registration-for-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising diffusion-based MR to CT image translation enables whole spine vertebral segmentation in 2D and 3D without manual annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-based-mr-to-ct-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The 3D translation outperformed the 2D approach, resulting in improved Dice scores (0. 80) and anatomically accurate segmentations in a higher resolution than the original MR image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-based-mr-to-ct-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Skin Tone Fairness in Dermatological Lesion Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-skin-tone-fairness-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing fairness in lesion classification from dermatological images is crucial due to variations in how skin diseases manifest across skin tones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-skin-tone-fairness-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASAG: Building Strong One-Decoder-Layer Sparse Detectors via Adaptive Sparse Anchor Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asag-building-strong-one-decoder-layer-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the architecture discrepancy between dense and sparse detectors leads to feature conflict, hampering the performance of one-decoder-layer detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asag-building-strong-one-decoder-layer-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scope is all you need: Transforming LLMs for HPC Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scope-is-all-you-need-transforming-llms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With easier access to powerful compute resources, there is a growing trend in the field of AI for software development to develop larger and larger language models (LLMs) to address a variety of programming tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scope-is-all-you-need-transforming-llms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red-Teaming Large Language Models using Chain of Utterances for Safety-Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/red-teaming-large-language-models-using-chain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new safety evaluation benchmark RED-EVAL that carries out red-teaming.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/red-teaming-large-language-models-using-chain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Spatio-Temporal Structure Prediction for Self-supervised Learning on Point Cloud Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-spatio-temporal-structure-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Masked Spatio-Temporal Structure Prediction (MaST-Pre) method to capture the structure of point cloud videos without human annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-spatio-temporal-structure-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retro-FPN: Retrospective Feature Pyramid Network for Point Cloud Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retro-fpn-retrospective-feature-pyramid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this way, the categorization of each point is conditioned on its local semantic pattern.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retro-fpn-retrospective-feature-pyramid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A hybrid Decoder-DeepONet operator regression framework for unaligned observation data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-decoder-deeponet-operator-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results illustrate the advantages of Decoder-DeepONet and Multi-Decoder-DeepONet in handling unaligned observation data and showcase their potentials in improving prediction accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-decoder-deeponet-operator-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMCVR: Morphology-Guided Diffusion Model for 3D Cardiac Volume Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dmcvr-morphology-guided-diffusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, current cardiac MRI-based reconstruction technology used in clinical settings is 2D with limited through-plane resolution, resulting in low-quality reconstructed cardiac volumes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dmcvr-morphology-guided-diffusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-learning enhanced next POI recommendation by leveraging check-ins from auxiliary cities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-enhanced-next-poi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, a city-level correlation strategy is devised to attentively capture common patterns among cities, so as to transfer more relevant knowledge from more correlated cities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-enhanced-next-poi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audiovisual Moments in Time: A Large-Scale Annotated Dataset of Audiovisual Actions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audiovisual-moments-in-time-a-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also offer 2 sets of pre-computed audiovisual feature embeddings, using VGGish/YamNet for audio data and VGG16/EfficientNetB0 for visual data, thereby lowering the barrier to entry for audiovisual DNN research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audiovisual-moments-in-time-a-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progression-Guided Temporal Action Detection in Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progression-guided-temporal-action-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The framework locates actions in videos by detecting the action evolution process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progression-guided-temporal-action-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StableVideo: Text-driven Consistency-aware Diffusion Video Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stablevideo-text-driven-consistency-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we tackle this problem by introducing temporal dependency to existing text-driven diffusion models, which allows them to generate consistent appearance for the edited objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stablevideo-text-driven-consistency-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poison Dart Frog: A Clean-Label Attack with Low Poisoning Rate and High Attack Success Rate in the Absence of Training Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poison-dart-frog-a-clean-label-attack-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Poison Dart Frog does not require access to any training data; it only necessitates knowledge of the target class for the attack, such as 'frog'.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poison-dart-frog-a-clean-label-attack-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial LibriSpeech: An Augmented Dataset for Spatial Audio Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-librispeech-an-augmented-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Spatial LibriSpeech, a spatial audio dataset with over 650 hours of 19-channel audio, first-order ambisonics, and optional distractor noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-librispeech-an-augmented-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Object Detection via Coarse-to-fine Proposal Generation and Imitation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/small-object-detection-via-coarse-to-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The past few years have witnessed the immense success of object detection, while current excellent detectors struggle on tackling size-limited instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/small-object-detection-via-coarse-to-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning in Cooperative Multiagent Systems Using Cognitive and Machine Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-in-cooperative-multiagent-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Developing effective Multi-Agent Systems (MAS) is critical for many applications requiring collaboration and coordination with humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-in-cooperative-multiagent-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Audio Anti-Spoofing with Fusion-Reconstruction Learning on Multi-Order Spectrograms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-audio-anti-spoofing-with-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust audio anti-spoofing has been increasingly challenging due to the recent advancements on deepfake techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-audio-anti-spoofing-with-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WizardMath: Empowering Mathematical Reasoning for Large Language Models via Reinforced Evol-Instruct</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wizardmath-empowering-mathematical-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through extensive experiments on two mathematical reasoning benchmarks, namely GSM8k and MATH, we reveal the extraordinary capabilities of our model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wizardmath-empowering-mathematical-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoupled conditional contrastive learning with variable metadata for prostate lesion detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-conditional-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Early diagnosis of prostate cancer is crucial for efficient treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-conditional-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoSynDA: Multi-Hypothesis Pose Synthesis Domain Adaptation for Robust 3D Human Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posynda-multi-hypothesis-pose-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The current 3D human pose estimators face challenges in adapting to new datasets due to the scarcity of 2D-3D pose pairs in target domain training sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posynda-multi-hypothesis-pose-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph of Thoughts: Solving Elaborate Problems with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-of-thoughts-solving-elaborate-problems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Graph of Thoughts (GoT): a framework that advances prompting capabilities in large language models (LLMs) beyond those offered by paradigms such as Chain-ofThought or Tree of Thoughts (ToT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-of-thoughts-solving-elaborate-problems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transitivity-Preserving Graph Representation Learning for Bridging Local Connectivity and Role-based Similarity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transitivity-preserving-graph-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Unified Graph Transformer Networks (UGT) that effectively integrate local and global structural information into fixed-length vector representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transitivity-preserving-graph-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lightweight Transformer for Faster and Robust EBSD Data Collection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-transformer-for-faster-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Three dimensional electron back-scattered diffraction (EBSD) microscopy is a critical tool in many applications in materials science, yet its data quality can fluctuate greatly during the arduous collection process, particularly via serial-sectioning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-transformer-for-faster-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Processing and Machine Learning for Hyperspectral Unmixing: An Overview and the HySUPP Python Package</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-processing-and-machine-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we draw a critical comparison between advanced and conventional techniques from the three categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-processing-and-machine-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Attack-tolerant Federated Learning via Critical Parameter Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-attack-tolerant-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is used to train a shared model in a decentralized way without clients sharing private data with each other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-attack-tolerant-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatHaruhi: Reviving Anime Character in Reality via Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatharuhi-reviving-anime-character-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Role-playing chatbots built on large language models have drawn interest, but better techniques are needed to enable mimicking specific fictional characters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatharuhi-reviving-anime-character-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Calibrated Cross Attention Network for Few-Shot Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-calibrated-cross-attention-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, when calculating SCCA, we design a scaled-cosine mechanism to better utilize the support features for similarity calculation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-calibrated-cross-attention-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable Decision Boundaries: Dualistic Meta-Learning for Open Set Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-decision-boundaries-dualistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain generalization (DG) is proposed to deal with the issue of domain shift, which occurs when statistical differences exist between source and target domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-decision-boundaries-dualistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Effectiveness of LayerNorm Tuning for Continual Learning in Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-layernorm-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art rehearsal-free continual learning methods exploit the peculiarities of Vision Transformers to learn task-specific prompts, drastically reducing catastrophic forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-layernorm-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Class Incremental Learning on Stochastic Blurry Task Boundary via Mask and Visual Prompt Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-class-incremental-learning-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, to alleviate the class imbalance problem, we introduce a new gradient similarity-based focal loss and adaptive feature scaling to ease overfitting to the major classes and underfitting to the minor classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-class-incremental-learning-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>biquality-learn: a Python library for Biquality Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biquality-learn-a-python-library-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[That is why Biquality Learning has been proposed as a machine learning framework to design algorithms capable of handling multiple weaknesses of supervision and dataset shifts without assumptions on their nature and level by relying on the availability of a small trusted dataset composed of cleanly labeled and representative samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biquality-learn-a-python-library-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Uncertainty Quantification using Conformalised Monte Carlo Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-uncertainty-quantification-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deploying deep learning models in safety-critical applications remains a very challenging task, mandating the provision of assurances for the dependable operation of these models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-uncertainty-quantification-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-guided Human Motion Synthesis with Atomic Actions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-guided-human-motion-synthesis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose ATOM (ATomic mOtion Modeling) to mitigate this problem, by decomposing actions into atomic actions, and employing a curriculum learning strategy to learn atomic action composition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-guided-human-motion-synthesis-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
