<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 09:13:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>What a MESS: Multi-Domain Evaluation of Zero-Shot Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-a-mess-multi-domain-evaluation-of-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, zero-shot semantic segmentation makes use of large self-supervised vision-language models, allowing zero-shot transfer to unseen classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-a-mess-multi-domain-evaluation-of-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShuttleSet22: Benchmarking Stroke Forecasting with Stroke-Level Badminton Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shuttleset22-benchmarking-stroke-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also hold a challenge, Track 2: Forecasting Future Turn-Based Strokes in Badminton Rallies, at CoachAI Badminton Challenge 2023 to boost researchers to tackle this problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shuttleset22-benchmarking-stroke-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulating counterfactuals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-counterfactuals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterfactual inference considers a hypothetical intervention in a parallel world that shares some evidence with the factual world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-counterfactuals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC-RS: Elevate LiDAR Semantic Scene Completion with Representation Separation and BEV Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssc-rs-elevate-lidar-semantic-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, how to effectively exploit the relationships between the semantic context in semantic segmentation and geometric structure in scene completion remains under exploration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssc-rs-elevate-lidar-semantic-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transferability Metrics for Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferability-metrics-for-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our experiments, we compare TLogME to state-of-the-art metrics in the estimation of transfer performance of the Faster-RCNN object detector.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferability-metrics-for-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Pseudo Future Contexts for Emotion Recognition in Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-pseudo-future-contexts-for-emotion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, for an utterance, we generate its future context with pre-trained language models, potentially containing extra beneficial knowledge in a conversational form homogeneous with the historical ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-pseudo-future-contexts-for-emotion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Annotation of Direct Speech in Written French Narratives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-annotation-of-direct-speech-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The automatic annotation of direct speech (AADS) in written text has been often used in computational narrative understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-annotation-of-direct-speech-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDOL: Indicator-oriented Logic Pre-training for Logical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idol-indicator-oriented-logic-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[IDOL achieves state-of-the-art performance on ReClor and LogiQA, the two most representative benchmarks in logical reasoning MRC, and is proven to be capable of generalizing to different pre-trained models and other types of MRC benchmarks like RACE and SQuAD 2. 0 while keeping competitive general language understanding ability through testing on tasks in GLUE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idol-indicator-oriented-logic-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-class systems seamlessly fit in the forward-forward algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-class-systems-seamlessly-fit-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The forward-forward algorithm presents a new method of training neural networks by updating weights during an inference, performing parameter updates for each layer individually.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-class-systems-seamlessly-fit-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symphonize 3D Semantic Scene Completion with Contextual Instance Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symphonize-3d-semantic-scene-completion-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating the queries as the instance feature representations within the scene, Symphonies dynamically encodes the instance-centric semantics to interact with the image and volume features while avoiding the dense voxel-wise modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symphonize-3d-semantic-scene-completion-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyBADS: Fast and robust black-box optimization in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pybads-fast-and-robust-black-box-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PyBADS is a Python implementation of the Bayesian Adaptive Direct Search (BADS) algorithm for fast and robust black-box optimization (Acerbi and Ma 2017).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pybads-fast-and-robust-black-box-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Truss Design with Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-truss-design-with-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Directly applying end-to-end reinforcement learning (RL) methods to truss layout design is infeasible either, since only a tiny portion of the entire layout space is valid under the physical constraints, leading to particularly sparse rewards for RL training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-truss-design-with-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CellViT: Vision Transformers for Precise Cell Segmentation and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cellvit-vision-transformers-for-precise-cell</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nuclei detection and segmentation in hematoxylin and eosin-stained (H&E) tissue images are important clinical tasks and crucial for a wide range of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cellvit-vision-transformers-for-precise-cell</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Meta-analytical Comparison of Naive Bayes and Random Forest for Software Defect Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-meta-analytical-comparison-of-naive-bayes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conducted a systematic literature review by establishing criteria to search and choose papers, resulting in five studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-meta-analytical-comparison-of-naive-bayes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Client Reactions in Online Mental Health Counseling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-client-reactions-in-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Communication success relies heavily on reading participants' reactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-client-reactions-in-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCID: Deep Canonical Information Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcid-deep-canonical-information-decomposition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Canonical Correlation Analysis (CCA)-based methods have traditionally been used to identify shared variables, however, they were designed for multivariate targets and only offer trivial solutions for univariate cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcid-deep-canonical-information-decomposition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Inferential Structure in Neural Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-inferential-structure-in-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Processes (NPs) are appealing due to their ability to perform fast adaptation based on a context set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-inferential-structure-in-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KnowPrefix-Tuning: A Two-Stage Prefix-Tuning Framework for Knowledge-Grounded Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowprefix-tuning-a-two-stage-prefix-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Knowledgeable Prefix Tuning (KnowPrefix-Tuning), a two-stage tuning framework, bypassing the retrieval process in a knowledge-grounded conversation system by injecting prior knowledge into the lightweight knowledge prefix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowprefix-tuning-a-two-stage-prefix-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeanDojo: Theorem Proving with Retrieval-Augmented Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leandojo-theorem-proving-with-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using this data, we develop ReProver (Retrieval-Augmented Prover): the first LLM-based prover that is augmented with retrieval for selecting premises from a vast math library.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leandojo-theorem-proving-with-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Can Mask More For Extremely Low-Bitrate Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-can-mask-more-for-extremely-low-bitrate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments have demonstrated that our approach outperforms recent state-of-the-art methods in R-D performance, visual quality, and downstream applications, at very low bitrates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-can-mask-more-for-extremely-low-bitrate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIPA-v2: Scaling CLIP Training with 81.1% Zero-shot ImageNet Accuracy within a \$10,000 Budget; An Extra \$4,000 Unlocks 81.8% Accuracy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clipa-v2-scaling-clip-training-with-81-1-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent work CLIPA presents an inverse scaling law for CLIP training -- whereby the larger the image/text encoders used, the shorter the sequence length of image/text tokens that can be applied in training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clipa-v2-scaling-clip-training-with-81-1-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shikra: Unleashing Multimodal LLM's Referential Dialogue Magic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shikra-unleashing-multimodal-llm-s</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Referential dialogue is a superset of various vision-language (VL) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shikra-unleashing-multimodal-llm-s</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PANet: LiDAR Panoptic Segmentation with Sparse Instance Proposal and Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panet-lidar-panoptic-segmentation-with-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we propose a non-learning Sparse Instance Proposal (SIP) module with the ``sampling-shifting-grouping" scheme to directly group thing points into instances from the raw point cloud efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panet-lidar-panoptic-segmentation-with-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIMIC: Masked Image Modeling with Image Correspondences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimic-masked-image-modeling-with-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, the effective pretraining datasets are those with multi-view scenes and have only been curated using annotated 3D meshes, point clouds, and camera parameters from simulated environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimic-masked-image-modeling-with-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Annealed Importance Sampling with Constant Rate Progress</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-annealed-importance-sampling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This algorithm relies on a sequence of interpolating distributions bridging the target to an initial tractable distribution such as the well-known geometric mean path of unnormalized distributions which is assumed to be suboptimal in general.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-annealed-importance-sampling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Re] Double Sampling Randomized Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-double-sampling-randomized-smoothing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper is a contribution to the reproducibility challenge in the field of machine learning, specifically addressing the issue of certifying the robustness of neural networks (NNs) against adversarial perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-double-sampling-randomized-smoothing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly Detection in Networks via Score-Based Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomaly-detection-in-networks-via-score-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Node outlier detection in attributed graphs is a challenging problem for which there is no method that would work well across different datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomaly-detection-in-networks-via-score-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quality Issues in Machine Learning Software Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quality-issues-in-machine-learning-software-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We validate the identified quality issues via a survey with ML practitioners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quality-issues-in-machine-learning-software-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On-Device Evaluation Toolkit for Machine Learning on Heterogeneous Low-Power System-on-Chip</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-device-evaluation-toolkit-for-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide an open source implementation of U-TOE and we demonstrate its use to experimentally evaluate the performance of a wide variety of models, on a wide variety of low-power boards, based on popular microcontroller architectures (ARM Cortex-M and RISC-V).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-device-evaluation-toolkit-for-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faithful Synthesis of Low-dose Contrast-enhanced Brain MRI Scans using Noise-preserving Conditional GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithful-synthesis-of-low-dose-contrast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our numerical experiments show that conditional GANs are suitable for generating images at different GBCA dose levels and can be used to augment datasets for virtual contrast models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithful-synthesis-of-low-dose-contrast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SugarCrepe: Fixing Hackable Benchmarks for Vision-Language Compositionality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sugarcrepe-fixing-hackable-benchmarks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the last year alone, a surge of new benchmarks to measure compositional understanding of vision-language models have permeated the machine learning ecosystem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sugarcrepe-fixing-hackable-benchmarks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WinoQueer: A Community-in-the-Loop Benchmark for Anti-LGBTQ+ Bias in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/winoqueer-a-community-in-the-loop-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present WinoQueer: a benchmark specifically designed to measure whether large language models (LLMs) encode biases that are harmful to the LGBTQ+ community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/winoqueer-a-community-in-the-loop-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AME-CAM: Attentive Multiple-Exit CAM for Weakly Supervised Segmentation on MRI Brain Tumor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ame-cam-attentive-multiple-exit-cam-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) is commonly used for brain tumor segmentation, which is critical for patient evaluation and treatment planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ame-cam-attentive-multiple-exit-cam-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond AUROC &amp; co. for evaluating out-of-distribution detection performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-auroc-co-for-evaluating-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While there has been a growing research interest in developing out-of-distribution (OOD) detection methods, there has been comparably little discussion around how these methods should be evaluated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-auroc-co-for-evaluating-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongCoder: A Long-Range Pre-trained Language Model for Code Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longcoder-a-long-range-pre-trained-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a new task for code completion that focuses on handling long code input and propose a sparse Transformer model, called LongCoder, to address this task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longcoder-a-long-range-pre-trained-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedLSAM: Localize and Segment Anything Model for 3D Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medlsam-localize-and-segment-anything-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nevertheless, both the original SAM and its medical adaptations necessitate slice-by-slice annotations, which directly increase the annotation workload with the size of the dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medlsam-localize-and-segment-anything-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransERR: Translation-based Knowledge Graph Completion via Efficient Relation Rotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transerr-translation-based-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents translation-based knowledge graph completion method via efficient relation rotation (TransERR), a straightforward yet effective alternative to traditional translation-based knowledge graph completion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transerr-translation-based-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Federated Model with Mixture of Personalized and Sharing Components</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-federated-model-with-mixture-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comparing with 13 existing related methods, the proposed method successfully achieves the best model performance, and meanwhile up to 60% improvement of communication efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-federated-model-with-mixture-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off-Policy Evaluation of Ranking Policies under Diverse User Behavior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/off-policy-evaluation-of-ranking-policies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the resulting estimator, which we call Adaptive IPS (AIPS), can be unbiased under any complex user behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/off-policy-evaluation-of-ranking-policies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Driven Chance-Constrained Multiple-Choice Knapsack Problem: Model, Algorithms, and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-chance-constrained-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first present the problem formulation of DDCCMCKP, and then establish two benchmark sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-chance-constrained-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PTVD: A Large-Scale Plot-Oriented Multimodal Dataset Based on Television Dramas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptvd-a-large-scale-plot-oriented-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Art forms such as movies and television (TV) dramas are reflections of the real world, which have attracted much attention from the multimodal learning community recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptvd-a-large-scale-plot-oriented-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauno: The Italian Large Language Model that will leave you senza parole!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fauno-the-italian-large-language-model-that</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents Fauno, the first and largest open-source Italian conversational Large Language Model (LLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fauno-the-italian-large-language-model-that</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Solution to CVPR'2023 AQTC Challenge: Video Alignment for Multi-Step Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-solution-to-cvpr-2023-aqtc-challenge-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a solution for enhancing video alignment to improve multi-step inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-solution-to-cvpr-2023-aqtc-challenge-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>logLTN: Differentiable Fuzzy Logic in the Logarithm Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logltn-differentiable-fuzzy-logic-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A significant trend in the literature involves integrating axioms and facts in loss functions by grounding logical symbols with neural networks and operators with fuzzy semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logltn-differentiable-fuzzy-logic-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond dynamic programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-dynamic-programming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the effectiveness of our approach by applying it to nonlinear optimal control problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-dynamic-programming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Component Separation for Targeted Signal Recovery in Noisy Mixtures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-component-separation-for-targeted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the case of 1), we show that our method better recovers the descriptors of the target data than a standard denoising method in most situations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-component-separation-for-targeted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structured Dialogue Discourse Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-dialogue-discourse-parsing-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, unlike in previous work, we do not rely on hand-crafted features; this improves the model's robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-dialogue-discourse-parsing-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Large Multi-Modal Model with Robust Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-multi-modal-model-with-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our dataset consists of 120k visual instructions generated by GPT4, covering 16 vision-and-language tasks with open-ended instructions and answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-multi-modal-model-with-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNABERT-2: Efficient Foundation Model and Benchmark For Multi-Species Genome</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dnabert-2-efficient-foundation-model-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decoding the linguistic intricacies of the genome is a crucial problem in biology, and pre-trained foundational models such as DNABERT and Nucleotide Transformer have made significant strides in this area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dnabert-2-efficient-foundation-model-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design from Policies: Conservative Test-Time Adaptation for Offline Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/design-from-policies-conservative-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Naturally, such a paradigm raises three core questions that are \textit{not} fully answered by prior non-iterative offline RL counterparts like reward-conditioned policy: Q1) What information should we transfer from the inner-level to the outer-level?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/design-from-policies-conservative-test-time</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
