<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 09:14:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>X-Avatar: Expressive Human Avatars</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-avatar-expressive-human-avatars</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method models bodies, hands, facial expressions and appearance in a holistic fashion and can be learned from either full 3D scans or RGB-D data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-avatar-expressive-human-avatars</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAM: Texture Recognition through Randomized Aggregated Encoding of Deep Activation Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radam-texture-recognition-through-randomized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Texture analysis is a classical yet challenging task in computer vision for which deep neural networks are actively being applied.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radam-texture-recognition-through-randomized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost-Effective Hyperparameter Optimization for Large Language Model Generation Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-effective-hyperparameter-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) like GPT-3 have sparked significant interest in their generative capabilities, leading to the development of various commercial applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-effective-hyperparameter-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loss-Curvature Matching for Dataset Selection and Condensation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loss-curvature-matching-for-dataset-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training neural networks on a large dataset requires substantial computational costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loss-curvature-matching-for-dataset-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vector Quantized Time Series Generation with a Bidirectional Prior Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vector-quantized-time-series-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series generation (TSG) studies have mainly focused on the use of Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) combined with recurrent neural network (RNN) variants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vector-quantized-time-series-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unimodal Distributions for Ordinal Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unimodal-distributions-for-ordinal-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then propose a new architecture that imposes unimodal distributions and a new loss term that relies on the notion of projection in a set to promote unimodality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unimodal-distributions-for-ordinal-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Audio Representations Image Gan Generation from BriVL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-audio-representations-image-gan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, researchers have gradually realized that in some cases, the self-supervised pre-training on large-scale Internet data is better than that of high-quality/manually labeled data sets, and multimodal/large models are better than single or bimodal/small models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-audio-representations-image-gan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Message Passing Perspective on Learning Dynamics of Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-message-passing-perspective-on-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, contrastive learning achieves impressive results on self-supervised visual representation learning, but there still lacks a rigorous understanding of its learning dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-message-passing-perspective-on-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual ChatGPT: Talking, Drawing and Editing with Visual Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-chatgpt-talking-drawing-and-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, We build a system called \textbf{Visual ChatGPT}, incorporating different Visual Foundation Models, to enable the user to interact with ChatGPT by 1) sending and receiving not only languages but also images 2) providing complex visual questions or visual editing instructions that require the collaboration of multiple AI models with multi-steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-chatgpt-talking-drawing-and-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACCER: Towards Reachable and Certain Counterfactual Explanations for Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raccer-towards-reachable-and-certain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose RACCER, the first RL-specific approach to generating counterfactual explanations for the behaviour of RL agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raccer-towards-reachable-and-certain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Enhancement From Degradation: A Diffusion Model For Fundus Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-enhancement-from-degradation-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel diffusion model based framework, named Learning Enhancement from Degradation (LED), for enhancing fundus images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-enhancement-from-degradation-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SGDViT: Saliency-Guided Dynamic Vision Transformer for UAV Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgdvit-saliency-guided-dynamic-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method designs a new task-specific object saliency mining network to refine the cross-correlation operation and effectively discriminate foreground and background information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgdvit-saliency-guided-dynamic-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preference-Aware Delivery Planning for Last-Mile Logistics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preference-aware-delivery-planning-for-last</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, despite many decades of solid research on solving these VRP instances, we still see significant gaps between optimized routes and the routes that are actually preferred by the practitioners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preference-aware-delivery-planning-for-last</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Hybrid Interpretable Models: Theory, Taxonomy, and Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-hybrid-interpretable-models-theory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advantages of such models over classical ones are two-fold: 1) They grant users precise control over the level of transparency of the system and 2) They can potentially perform better than a standalone black box since redirecting some of the inputs to an interpretable model implicitly acts as regularization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-hybrid-interpretable-models-theory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Byzantine-Robust Loopless Stochastic Variance-Reduced Gradient</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/byzantine-robust-loopless-stochastic-variance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Distributed optimization with open collaboration is a popular field since it provides an opportunity for small groups/companies/universities, and individuals to jointly solve huge-scale problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/byzantine-robust-loopless-stochastic-variance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer-based Image Generation from Scene Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-image-generation-from-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show how employing multi-head attention to encode the graph information, as well as using a transformer-based model in the latent space for image generation can improve the quality of the sampled data, without the need to employ adversarial models with the subsequent advantage in terms of training stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-image-generation-from-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonlinear Kalman Filtering with Reparametrization Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonlinear-kalman-filtering-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The widely used parametric approximation is based on a jointly Gaussian assumption of the state-space model, which is in turn equivalent to minimizing an approximation to the Kullback-Leibler divergence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonlinear-kalman-filtering-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RM-Depth: Unsupervised Learning of Recurrent Monocular Depth in Dynamic Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rm-depth-unsupervised-learning-of-recurrent-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, an unsupervised learning framework is proposed to jointly predict monocular depth and complete 3D motion including the motions of moving objects and camera.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rm-depth-unsupervised-learning-of-recurrent-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point Cloud Classification Using Content-based Transformer via Clustering in Feature Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-cloud-classification-using-content</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome the limitation of local spatial attention, we propose a point content-based Transformer architecture, called PointConT for short.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-cloud-classification-using-content</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Light Weight Model for Active Speaker Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-light-weight-model-for-active-speaker</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results on the AVA-ActiveSpeaker dataset show that our framework achieves competitive mAP performance (94. 1% vs. 94. 2%), while the resource costs are significantly lower than the state-of-the-art method, especially in model parameters (1. 0M vs. 22. 5M, about 23x) and FLOPs (0. 6G vs. 2. 6G, about 4x).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-light-weight-model-for-active-speaker</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contribution of clinical course to outcome after traumatic brain injury: mining patient trajectories from European intensive care unit data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contribution-of-clinical-course-to-outcome</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aimed to develop a modelling strategy which integrates all data stored in medical records to produce an interpretable disease course for each TBI patient's ICU stay.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contribution-of-clinical-course-to-outcome</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Densely Connected $G$-invariant Deep Neural Networks with Signed Permutation Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/densely-connected-g-invariant-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce and investigate, for finite groups $G$, $G$-invariant deep neural network ($G$-DNN) architectures with ReLU activation that are densely connected -- i. e., include all possible skip connections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/densely-connected-g-invariant-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastFill: Efficient Compatible Model Update</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastfill-efficient-compatible-model-update</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of retrieving the most similar data from a gallery set to a given query data is performed through a similarity comparison on features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastfill-efficient-compatible-model-update</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M-EBM: Towards Understanding the Manifolds of Energy-Based Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-ebm-towards-understanding-the-manifolds-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite its simplicity, M-EBM significantly improves unconditional EBMs in training stability and speed on a host of benchmark datasets, such as CIFAR10, CIFAR100, CelebA-HQ, and ImageNet 32x32.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-ebm-towards-understanding-the-manifolds-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ElC-OIS: Ellipsoidal Clustering for Open-World Instance Segmentation on LiDAR Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elc-ois-ellipsoidal-clustering-for-open-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a flexible and effective OIS framework for LiDAR point cloud that can accurately segment both known and unknown instances (i. e., seen and unseen instance categories during training).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elc-ois-ellipsoidal-clustering-for-open-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuity-Aware Latent Interframe Information Mining for Reliable UAV Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuity-aware-latent-interframe</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above issues, this work proposes a novel framework with continuity-aware latent interframe information mining for reliable UAV tracking, i. e., ClimRT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuity-aware-latent-interframe</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAM: Texture Recognition through Randomized Aggregated Encoding of Deep Activation Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radam-texture-recognition-through-randomized-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Texture analysis is a classical yet challenging task in computer vision for which deep neural networks are actively being applied.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radam-texture-recognition-through-randomized-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robustness Evaluation in Hand Pose Estimation Models using Metamorphic Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-evaluation-in-hand-pose-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We found that on average more than 80\% of the hands could not be identified by BodyHands, and at least 50\% of hands could not be identified by MediaPipe hands when diagonal motion blur is introduced, while an average of more than 50\% of strongly underexposed hands could not be correctly estimated by NSRM hand.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-evaluation-in-hand-pose-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imbalanced Open Set Domain Adaptation via Moving-threshold Estimation and Gradual Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imbalanced-open-set-domain-adaptation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate the negative effects raised by label shift in OSDA, we propose Open-set Moving-threshold Estimation and Gradual Alignment (OMEGA) - a novel architecture that improves existing OSDA methods on class-imbalanced data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imbalanced-open-set-domain-adaptation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extrapolative Controlled Sequence Generation via Iterative Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extrapolative-controlled-sequence-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of extrapolative controlled generation, i. e., generating sequences with attribute values beyond the range seen in training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extrapolative-controlled-sequence-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically Auditing Large Language Models via Discrete Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatically-auditing-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Auditing large language models for unexpected behaviors is critical to preempt catastrophic deployments, yet remains challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatically-auditing-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GaussianMLR: Learning Implicit Class Significance via Calibrated Multi-Label Ranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussianmlr-learning-implicit-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that our method is able to accurately learn a representation of the incorporated positive rank order, which is not only consistent with the ground truth but also proportional to the underlying information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussianmlr-learning-implicit-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face: Fast, Accurate and Context-Aware Audio Annotation and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-fast-accurate-and-context-aware-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a context-aware framework for feature selection and classification procedures to realize a fast and accurate audio event annotation and classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-fast-accurate-and-context-aware-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlled Diversity with Preference : Towards Learning a Diverse Set of Desired Skills</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlled-diversity-with-preference-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomously learning diverse behaviors without an extrinsic reward signal has been a problem of interest in reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlled-diversity-with-preference-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zeroth-Order Optimization Meets Human Feedback: Provable Learning via Ranking Oracles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zeroth-order-optimization-meets-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on a novel optimization problem in which the objective function is a black-box and can only be evaluated through a ranking oracle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zeroth-order-optimization-meets-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DR-VIDAL -- Doubly Robust Variational Information-theoretic Deep Adversarial Learning for Counterfactual Prediction and Treatment Effect Estimation on Real World Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dr-vidal-doubly-robust-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DR-VIDAL integrates: (i) a variational autoencoder (VAE) to factorize confounders into latent variables according to causal assumptions; (ii) an information-theoretic generative adversarial network (Info-GAN) to generate counterfactuals; (iii) a doubly robust block incorporating treatment propensities for outcome predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dr-vidal-doubly-robust-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LORE: Logical Location Regression Network for Table Structure Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lore-logical-location-regression-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Table structure recognition (TSR) aims at extracting tables in images into machine-understandable formats.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lore-logical-location-regression-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SGDA: Towards 3D Universal Pulmonary Nodule Detection via Slice Grouped Domain Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgda-towards-3d-universal-pulmonary-nodule</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a slice grouped domain attention (SGDA) module to enhance the generalization capability of the pulmonary nodule detection networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgda-towards-3d-universal-pulmonary-nodule</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Hamiltonian Systems with Mono-Implicit Runge-Kutta Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-hamiltonian-systems-with-mono</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerical integrators could be used to form interpolation conditions when training neural networks to approximate the vector field of an ordinary differential equation (ODE) from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-hamiltonian-systems-with-mono</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Confidence Calibration for Failure Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-confidence-calibration-for-failure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate this problem and reveal that popular confidence calibration methods often lead to worse confidence separation between correct and incorrect samples, making it more difficult to decide whether to trust a prediction or not.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-confidence-calibration-for-failure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centroid Distance Distillation for Effective Rehearsal in Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centroid-distance-distillation-for-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rehearsal, retraining on a stored small data subset of old tasks, has been proven effective in solving catastrophic forgetting in continual learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centroid-distance-distillation-for-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Algebraic Perspective on Lipschitz Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-algebraic-perspective-on-lipschitz</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Important research efforts have focused on the design and training of neural networks with a controlled Lipschitz constant.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-algebraic-perspective-on-lipschitz</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Differentiable Causal Discovery via Adaptive Sample Reweighting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-differentiable-causal-discovery-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite great success in low-dimensional linear systems, it has been observed that these approaches overly exploit easier-to-fit samples, thus inevitably learning spurious edges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-differentiable-causal-discovery-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symbolic Synthesis of Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-synthesis-of-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks adapt very well to distributed and continuous representations, but struggle to learn and generalize from small amounts of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-synthesis-of-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SC-Block: Supervised Contrastive Blocking within Entity Resolution Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sc-block-supervised-contrastive-blocking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reduce these runtimes, entity resolution pipelines are constructed of two parts: a blocker that applies a computationally cheap method to select candidate record pairs, and a matcher that afterwards identifies matching pairs from this set using more expensive methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sc-block-supervised-contrastive-blocking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep symbolic regression for physics guided by units constraints: toward the automated discovery of physical laws</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-symbolic-regression-for-physics-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we present $\Phi$-SO, a Physical Symbolic Optimization framework for recovering analytical symbolic expressions from physics data using deep reinforcement learning techniques by learning units constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-symbolic-regression-for-physics-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Grained Self-Interpretable Symbolic-Neural Model For Single/Multi-Labeled Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-grained-self-interpretable-symbolic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the structured language model learns to predict constituency trees in a self-supervised manner, only raw texts and sentence-level labels are required as training data, which makes it essentially a general constituent-level self-interpretable classification model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-grained-self-interpretable-symbolic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeCap: Decoding CLIP Latents for Zero-Shot Captioning via Text-Only Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decap-decoding-clip-latents-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This decoder is both data-efficient and computation-efficient: 1) it only requires the text data for training, easing the burden on the collection of paired data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decap-decoding-clip-latents-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Parametric Outlier Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-parametric-outlier-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Importantly, our proposed synthesis approach does not make any distributional assumption on the ID embeddings, thereby offering strong flexibility and generality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-parametric-outlier-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Searching for Effective Neural Network Architectures for Heart Murmur Detection from Phonocardiogram</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/searching-for-effective-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aim: The George B. Moody PhysioNet Challenge 2022 raised problems of heart murmur detection and related abnormal cardiac function identification from phonocardiograms (PCGs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/searching-for-effective-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
