<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 09:12:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DePT: Decomposed Prompt Tuning for Parameter-Efficient Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dept-decomposed-prompt-tuning-for-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompt tuning (PT), where a small amount of trainable soft (continuous) prompt vectors is affixed to the input of language models (LM), has shown promising results across various tasks and models for parameter-efficient fine-tuning (PEFT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dept-decomposed-prompt-tuning-for-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panoptic Vision-Language Feature Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panoptic-vision-language-feature-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to our knowledge the first algorithm for open-vocabulary panoptic segmentation, simultaneously performing both semantic and instance segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panoptic-vision-language-feature-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Co-design Study for Multi-Stakeholder Job Recommender System Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-co-design-study-for-multi-stakeholder-job</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent legislation proposals have significantly increased the demand for eXplainable Artificial Intelligence (XAI) in many businesses, especially in so-called `high-risk' domains, such as recruitment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-co-design-study-for-multi-stakeholder-job</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive analysis of synthetic learning applied to neonatal brain MRI segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-analysis-of-synthetic-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then evaluate the synthetic learning approach and confirm its robustness to variations in image contrast by reporting the capacity of such a model to segment both T1- and T2-weighted images from the same individuals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-analysis-of-synthetic-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Formalizing Multimedia Recommendation through Multimodal Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/formalizing-multimedia-recommendation-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommender systems (RSs) offer personalized navigation experiences on online platforms, but recommendation remains a challenging task, particularly in specific scenarios and domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/formalizing-multimedia-recommendation-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Information Extraction on Business Documents with Specific Pre-Training Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-information-extraction-on-business</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These tasks force the model to learn better-contextualized representations of the scanned documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-information-extraction-on-business</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Objective-Specific Active Learning Strategies with Attentive Neural Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-objective-specific-active-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel LAL method for classification that exploits symmetry and independence properties of the active learning problem with an Attentive Conditional Neural Process model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-objective-specific-active-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Share Your Representation Only: Guaranteed Improvement of the Privacy-Utility Tradeoff in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/share-your-representation-only-guaranteed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Repeated parameter sharing in federated learning causes significant information leakage about private data, thus defeating its main purpose: data privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/share-your-representation-only-guaranteed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniKG: A Benchmark and Universal Embedding for Large-Scale Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unikg-a-benchmark-and-universal-embedding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To perform effective learning on the large-scale UniKG, two key measures are taken, including (i) the semantic alignment strategy for multi-attribute entities, which projects the feature description of multi-attribute nodes into a common embedding space to facilitate node aggregation in a large receptive field; (ii) proposing a novel plug-and-play anisotropy propagation module (APM) to learn effective multi-hop anisotropy propagation kernels, which extends methods of large-scale homogeneous graphs to heterogeneous graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unikg-a-benchmark-and-universal-embedding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoFuse: Automatic Fusion Networks for Deformable Medical Image Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autofuse-automatic-fusion-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, DNN-based registration needs to explore the spatial information of each image and fuse this information to characterize spatial correspondence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autofuse-automatic-fusion-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAT: Hybrid Attention Transformer for Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hat-hybrid-attention-transformer-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the training stage, we additionally adopt a same-task pre-training strategy to further exploit the potential of the model for further improvement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hat-hybrid-attention-transformer-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniSeg: A Unified Multi-Modal LiDAR Segmentation Network and the OpenPCSeg Codebase</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniseg-a-unified-multi-modal-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, we construct the OpenPCSeg codebase, which is the largest and most comprehensive outdoor LiDAR segmentation codebase.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniseg-a-unified-multi-modal-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenFashionCLIP: Vision-and-Language Contrastive Learning with Open-Source Fashion Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openfashionclip-vision-and-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The inexorable growth of online shopping and e-commerce demands scalable and robust machine learning-based solutions to accommodate customer requirements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openfashionclip-vision-and-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Better Data Exploitation In Self-Supervised Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-data-exploitation-in-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we introduce the detail-enhanced DepthNet with an extra full-scale branch in the encoder and a grid decoder to enhance the restoration of fine details in depth maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-data-exploitation-in-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the detection of Out-Of-Distribution samples in Multiple Instance Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-detection-of-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While significant efforts have been devoted to OOD detection in classical supervised settings, the context of weakly supervised learning, particularly the Multiple Instance Learning (MIL) framework, remains under-explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-detection-of-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distance-Aware eXplanation Based Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-aware-explanation-based-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[eXplanation Based Learning (XBL) is an interactive learning approach that provides a transparent method of training deep learning models by interacting with their explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-aware-explanation-based-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Content-based Pixel Retrieval in Revisited Oxford and Paris</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-content-based-pixel-retrieval-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose pixel retrieval benchmarks named PROxford and PRParis, which are based on the widely used image retrieval datasets, ROxford and RParis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-content-based-pixel-retrieval-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine learning the dimension of a Fano variety</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-the-dimension-of-a-fano</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is a sequence of integers which gives a numerical fingerprint for a Fano variety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-the-dimension-of-a-fano</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EDAC: Efficient Deployment of Audio Classification Models For COVID-19 Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edac-efficient-deployment-of-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Various researchers made use of machine learning methods in an attempt to detect COVID-19.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edac-efficient-deployment-of-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Latent Decomposition with Normalizing Flows for Face Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-latent-decomposition-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, SDFlow decomposes the original latent code into different irrelevant variables by jointly optimizing two components: (i) a semantic encoder to estimate semantic variables from input faces and (ii) a flow-based transformation module to map the latent code into a semantic-irrelevant variable in Gaussian distribution, conditioned on the learned semantic variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-latent-decomposition-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Natural Language Queries for More Effective Systematic Review Screening Prioritisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-natural-language-queries-for-more</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Screening prioritisation in medical systematic reviews aims to rank the set of documents retrieved by complex Boolean queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-natural-language-queries-for-more</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARE: Confidence-rich Autonomous Robot Exploration using Bayesian Kernel Inference and Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/care-confidence-rich-autonomous-robot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first utilize Gaussian process (GP) regression to learn a surrogate model to infer the confidence-rich mutual information (CRMI) of querying control actions, then adopt an objective function consisting of predicted CRMI values and prediction uncertainties to conduct Bayesian optimization (BO), i. e., GP-based BO (GPBO).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/care-confidence-rich-autonomous-robot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Action Localization with Enhanced Instant Discriminability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-action-localization-with-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal action detection (TAD) aims to detect all action boundaries and their corresponding categories in an untrimmed video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-action-localization-with-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimize Weight Rounding via Signed Gradient Descent for the Quantization of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimize-weight-rounding-via-signed-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the number of bits decreases, the quantization grid broadens, thus emphasizing the importance of up and down rounding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimize-weight-rounding-via-signed-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrete Denoising Diffusion Approach to Integer Factorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-denoising-diffusion-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Integer factorization is a famous computational problem unknown whether being solvable in the polynomial time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-denoising-diffusion-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSimAD: Zero-Shot 3D Domain Transfer for Autonomous Driving with Source Reconstruction and Target Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resimad-zero-shot-3d-domain-transfer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain shifts such as sensor type changes and geographical situation variations are prevalent in Autonomous Driving (AD), which poses a challenge since AD model relying on the previous-domain knowledge can be hardly directly deployed to a new domain without additional costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resimad-zero-shot-3d-domain-transfer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Koopman prior for data assimilation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-koopman-prior-for-data-assimilation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increasing availability of large scale datasets, computational power and tools like automatic differentiation and expressive neural network architectures, sequential data are now often treated in a data-driven way, with a dynamical model trained from the observation data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-koopman-prior-for-data-assimilation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeCUR: decoupling common &amp; unique representations for multimodal self-supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decur-decoupling-common-unique</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Decoupling Common and Unique Representations (DeCUR), a simple yet effective method for multimodal self-supervised learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decur-decoupling-common-unique</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Geometric Representations of Objects via Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-geometric-representations-of-objects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the problem of learning representations from observations of a scene involving an agent and an external object the agent interacts with.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-geometric-representations-of-objects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGent: A Novel Pipeline for Automatically Creating Unanswerable Questions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-a-novel-pipeline-for-automatically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we demonstrate the usefulness of this AGent pipeline by creating two sets of unanswerable questions from answerable questions in SQuAD and HotpotQA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-a-novel-pipeline-for-automatically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonlinear Granger Causality using Kernel Ridge Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonlinear-granger-causality-using-kernel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This novel algorithm uses a flexible plug-in architecture that enables researchers to employ any nonlinear regressor as the base prediction model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonlinear-granger-causality-using-kernel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Emotional Adaptation for Audio-Driven Talking-Head Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-emotional-adaptation-for-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Audio-driven talking-head synthesis is a popular research topic for virtual human-related applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-emotional-adaptation-for-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-modal Extreme Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-extreme-classification-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper develops the MUFIN technique for extreme classification (XC) tasks with millions of labels where datapoints and labels are endowed with visual and textual descriptors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-extreme-classification-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SdCT-GAN: Reconstructing CT from Biplanar X-Rays with Self-driven Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdct-gan-reconstructing-ct-from-biplanar-x</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computed Tomography (CT) is a medical imaging modality that can generate more informative 3D images than 2D X-rays.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdct-gan-reconstructing-ct-from-biplanar-x</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutation-based Fault Localization of Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutation-based-fault-localization-of-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNNs) are susceptible to bugs, just like other types of software systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutation-based-fault-localization-of-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformers in Small Object Detection: A Benchmark and Survey of State-of-the-Art</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-in-small-object-detection-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have rapidly gained popularity in computer vision, especially in the field of object recognition and detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-in-small-object-detection-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collecting Visually-Grounded Dialogue with A Game Of Sorts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collecting-visually-grounded-dialogue-with-a-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address these concerns by introducing a collaborative image ranking task, a grounded agreement game we call "A Game Of Sorts".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collecting-visually-grounded-dialogue-with-a-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive conformal classification with noisy labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-conformal-classification-with-noisy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper develops novel conformal prediction methods for classification tasks that can automatically adapt to random label contamination in the calibration sample, enabling more informative prediction sets with stronger coverage guarantees compared to state-of-the-art approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-conformal-classification-with-noisy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Self-supervised Disentanglement for General Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-self-supervised-disentanglement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is understandable as the model is designed to learn paired mapping (e. g. from a noisy image to its clean version).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-self-supervised-disentanglement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAD++: Improved Data-free Test Time Adversarial Defense</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dad-improved-data-free-test-time-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increasing deployment of deep neural networks in safety-critical applications such as self-driving cars, medical imaging, anomaly detection, etc., adversarial robustness has become a crucial concern in the reliability of these networks in real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dad-improved-data-free-test-time-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Skeleton-based Approach For Rock Crack Detection Towards A Climbing Robot Application</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-skeleton-based-approach-for-rock-crack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A new group of metrics, LineAcc, has been proposed for thin object segmentation such that the impact of the object width on the score is minimized.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-skeleton-based-approach-for-rock-crack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting CLIP for Zero-shot HOI Detection Requires Knowledge Distillation at Multiple Levels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-clip-for-zero-shot-hoi-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the task of zero-shot human-object interaction (HOI) detection, a novel paradigm for identifying HOIs without the need for task-specific annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-clip-for-zero-shot-hoi-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeMan: Towards Benchmarking 3D Human Pose Estimation in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freeman-towards-benchmarking-3d-human-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate the development of 3D pose estimation, we present FreeMan, the first large-scale, real-world multi-view dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freeman-towards-benchmarking-3d-human-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Implicit Transporter for Temporally Consistent Keypoint Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-implicit-transporter-for-temporally</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, the Transporter method was introduced for 2D data, which reconstructs the target frame from the source frame to incorporate both spatial and temporal information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-implicit-transporter-for-temporally</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RGAT: A Deeper Look into Syntactic Dependency Information for Coreference Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgat-a-deeper-look-into-syntactic-dependency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments on a public Gendered Ambiguous Pronouns (GAP) dataset show that with the supervision learning of the syntactic dependency graph and without fine-tuning the entire BERT, we increased the F1-score of the previous best model (RGCN-with-BERT) from 80. 3% to 82. 5%, compared to the F1-score by single BERT embeddings from 78. 5% to 82. 5%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgat-a-deeper-look-into-syntactic-dependency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outlier Robust Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-robust-adversarial-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Theoretically, we show that the learning objective of ORAT satisfies the $\mathcal{H}$-consistency in binary classification, which establishes it as a proper surrogate to adversarial 0/1 loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-robust-adversarial-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural-Hidden-CRF: A Robust Weakly-Supervised Sequence Labeler</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-hidden-crf-a-robust-weakly-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Neural-Hidden-CRF, we can capitalize on the powerful language model BERT or other deep models to provide rich contextual semantic knowledge to the latent ground truth sequence, and use the hidden CRF layer to capture the internal label dependencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-hidden-crf-a-robust-weakly-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gray Jedi MVDR Post-filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gray-jedi-mvdr-post-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatial filters can exploit deep-learning-based speech enhancement models to increase their reliability in scenarios with multiple speech sources scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gray-jedi-mvdr-post-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVARS -- Alleviating Unexpected Urban Road Traffic Congestion using UAVs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avars-alleviating-unexpected-urban-road</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we argue that Unmanned Aerial Vehicles (UAVs) can play a crucial role in dealing with unexpected traffic congestion because UAVs with onboard cameras can be economically deployed when and where unexpected congestion occurs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avars-alleviating-unexpected-urban-road</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Augmentation for Conversational AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-for-conversational-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This tutorial provides a comprehensive and up-to-date overview of DA approaches in the context of conversational systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-for-conversational-ai</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
