<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:08:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>AutoPET Challenge III: Testing the Robustness of Generalized Dice Focal Loss trained 3D Residual UNet for FDG and PSMA Lesion Segmentation from Whole-Body PET/CT Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopet-challenge-iii-testing-the-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, creating an effective segmentation model for routine PET/CT image analysis is challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopet-challenge-iii-testing-the-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2S-ODIS: Two-Stage Omni-Directional Image Synthesis by Geometric Distortion Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2s-odis-two-stage-omni-directional-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, two-stage structure was adopted to first create a global coarse image in ERP and then refine the image by integrating multiple local NFoV images in the higher resolution to compensate the distortions in ERP, both of which are based on the pre-trained VQGAN model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2s-odis-two-stage-omni-directional-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MusicLIME: Explainable Multimodal Music Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musiclime-explainable-multimodal-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal models are critical for music understanding tasks, as they capture the complex interplay between audio and lyrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musiclime-explainable-multimodal-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Centric Strategies for Overcoming PET/CT Heterogeneity: Insights from the AutoPET III Lesion Segmentation Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-centric-strategies-for-overcoming-pet-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The third autoPET challenge introduced a new data-centric task this year, shifting the focus from model development to improving metastatic lesion segmentation on PET/CT images through data quality and handling strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-centric-strategies-for-overcoming-pet-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep-Wide Learning Assistance for Insect Pest Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-wide-learning-assistance-for-insect-pest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate insect pest recognition plays a critical role in agriculture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-wide-learning-assistance-for-insect-pest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Efficacy of Instance Incremental vs. Batch Learning in Delayed Label Environments: An Empirical Study on Tabular Data Streaming for Fraud Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-efficacy-of-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In such a setting, most studies in the literature regarding supervised learning favor the use of instance incremental algorithms due to their ability to adapt to changes in the data distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-efficacy-of-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOST: MR reconstruction Optimization for multiple downStream Tasks via continual learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/most-mr-reconstruction-optimization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate this issue, downstream task-oriented reconstruction optimization has been proposed for a single downstream task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/most-mr-reconstruction-optimization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust image representations with counterfactual contrastive learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-image-representations-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, counterfactual contrastive learning achieves superior downstream performance on both in-distribution and on external datasets, especially for images acquired with scanners under-represented in the training set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-image-representations-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SelECT-SQL: Self-correcting ensemble Chain-of-Thought for Text-to-SQL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/select-sql-self-correcting-ensemble-chain-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, Text-to-SQL, the problem of automatically converting questions posed in natural language to formal SQL queries, has emerged as an important problem at the intersection of natural language processing and data management research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/select-sql-self-correcting-ensemble-chain-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AceParse: A Comprehensive Dataset with Diverse Structured Texts for Academic Literature Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aceparse-a-comprehensive-dataset-with-diverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the development of data-centric AI, the focus has shifted from model-driven approaches to improving data quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aceparse-a-comprehensive-dataset-with-diverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Large Language Model Uncertainty for Prompt Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-language-model-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompt optimization algorithms for Large Language Models (LLMs) excel in multi-step reasoning but still lack effective uncertainty estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-language-model-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trustworthiness in Retrieval-Augmented Generation Systems: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trustworthiness-in-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) has quickly grown into a pivotal paradigm in the development of Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trustworthiness-in-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Diagram of Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-diagram-of-thought</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Diagram of Thought (DoT), a framework that models iterative reasoning in large language models (LLMs) as the construction of a directed acyclic graph (DAG) within a single model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-diagram-of-thought</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Syllable Discovery Based on Speaker-Disentangled HuBERT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-syllable-discovery-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we observe that the information aggregated in the CLS token correlates more with speaker identity than with linguistic content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-syllable-discovery-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>beeFormer: Bridging the Gap Between Semantic and Interaction Similarity in Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beeformer-bridging-the-gap-between-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose beeFormer, a framework for training sentence Transformer models with interaction data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beeformer-bridging-the-gap-between-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Physically-Realizable Adversarial Attacks in Embodied Vision Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-physically-realizable-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results show our adversarial patches reduce navigation success rates by about 40%, outperforming previous methods in practicality, effectiveness, and naturalness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-physically-realizable-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Graph Anomaly Detection: A Survey and New Perspectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-graph-anomaly-detection-a-survey-and-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, in this work we aim to present a comprehensive review of deep learning approaches for GAD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-graph-anomaly-detection-a-survey-and-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anatomical Positional Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomical-positional-embeddings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We train our APE model on 8400 publicly available CT images of abdomen and chest regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomical-positional-embeddings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEAL: Towards Safe Autonomous Driving via Skill-Enabled Adversary Learning for Closed-Loop Scenario Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seal-towards-safe-autonomous-driving-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Verification and validation of autonomous driving (AD) systems and components is of increasing importance, as such technology increases in real-world prevalence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seal-towards-safe-autonomous-driving-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional sampling within generative diffusion models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-sampling-within-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative diffusions are a powerful class of Monte Carlo samplers that leverage bridging Markov processes to approximate complex, high-dimensional distributions, such as those found in image processing and language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-sampling-within-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famba-V: Fast Vision Mamba with Cross-Layer Token Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/famba-v-fast-vision-mamba-with-cross-layer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces Fast Mamba for Vision (Famba-V), a cross-layer token fusion technique to enhance the training efficiency of Vim models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/famba-v-fast-vision-mamba-with-cross-layer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stutter-Solver: End-to-end Multi-lingual Dysfluency Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stutter-solver-end-to-end-multi-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current de-facto dysfluency modeling methods utilize template matching algorithms which are not generalizable to out-of-domain real-world dysfluencies across languages, and are not scalable with increasing amounts of training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stutter-solver-end-to-end-multi-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SITSMamba for Crop Classification based on Satellite Image Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sitsmamba-for-crop-classification-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we proposed a Satellite Image Time Series Mamba (SITSMamba) method for crop classification based on remote sensing time series data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sitsmamba-for-crop-classification-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlpaPICO: Extraction of PICO Frames from Clinical Trial Documents Using LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpapico-extraction-of-pico-frames-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, there has been a surge in the publication of clinical trial reports, making it challenging to conduct systematic reviews.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpapico-extraction-of-pico-frames-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Lesion Segmentation in PET/CT Imaging with Deep Learning and Advanced Data Preprocessing Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-lesion-segmentation-in-pet-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The escalating global cancer burden underscores the critical need for precise diagnostic tools in oncology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-lesion-segmentation-in-pet-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SparX: A Sparse Cross-Layer Connection Mechanism for Hierarchical Vision Mamba and Transformer Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparx-a-sparse-cross-layer-connection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, such models are not capable of distilling features across layers through feature aggregation, interaction, and selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparx-a-sparse-cross-layer-connection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Lesion Segmentation in Whole-Body PET/CT in a multitracer setting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-lesion-segmentation-in-whole-body-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study explores a workflow for automated segmentation of lesions in FDG and PSMA PET/CT images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-lesion-segmentation-in-whole-body-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RandALO: Out-of-sample risk estimation in no time flat</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randalo-out-of-sample-risk-estimation-in-no</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimating out-of-sample risk for models trained on large high-dimensional datasets is an expensive but essential part of the machine learning process, enabling practitioners to optimally tune hyperparameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randalo-out-of-sample-risk-estimation-in-no</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Kinetic Manipulation of the Latent Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-kinetic-manipulation-of-the-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The latent space of many generative models are rich in unexplored valleys and mountains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-kinetic-manipulation-of-the-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reliable Multi-View Learning with Conformal Prediction for Aortic Stenosis Classification in Echocardiography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliable-multi-view-learning-with-conformal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The fundamental problem with ultrasound-guided diagnosis is that the acquired images are often 2-D cross-sections of a 3-D anatomy, potentially missing important anatomical details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliable-multi-view-learning-with-conformal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLCONet: Learning Multi-source Perception Representation for Camouflaged Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glconet-learning-multi-source-perception</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, biological perception has been a powerful tool for handling the camouflaged object detection (COD) task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glconet-learning-multi-source-perception</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Centrifugal Clutches in Two-Speed Automatic Transmissions with Deep Learning-Based Engagement Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-centrifugal-clutches-in-two-speed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a comprehensive numerical analysis of centrifugal clutch systems integrated with a two-speed automatic transmission, a key component in automotive torque transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-centrifugal-clutches-in-two-speed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Single-Lens Controllable Depth-of-Field Imaging via All-in-Focus Aberration Correction and Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-single-lens-controllable-depth-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A Depth-aware Controllable DoF Imaging (DCDI) framework is proposed equipped with All-in-Focus (AiF) aberration correction and monocular depth estimation, where the recovered image and corresponding depth map are utilized to produce imaging results under diverse DoFs of any high-end lens via patch-wise convolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-single-lens-controllable-depth-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REG: Refined Generalized Focal Loss for Road Asset Detection on Thai Highways Using Vision-Based Detection and Segmentation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reg-refined-generalized-focal-loss-for-road</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel framework for detecting and segmenting critical road assets on Thai highways using an advanced Refined Generalized Focal Loss (REG) formulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reg-refined-generalized-focal-loss-for-road</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synergistic Spotting and Recognition of Micro-Expression via Temporal State Transition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synergistic-spotting-and-recognition-of-micro</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The analysis of micro-expressions generally involves two main tasks: spotting micro-expression intervals in long videos and recognizing the emotions associated with these intervals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synergistic-spotting-and-recognition-of-micro</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COSCO: A Sharpness-Aware Training Framework for Few-shot Multivariate Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosco-a-sharpness-aware-training-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a new learning framework named COSCO consisting of a sharpness-aware minimization (SAM) optimization and a Prototypical loss function to improve the generalization ability of DNN for multivariate time series classification problems under few-shot setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosco-a-sharpness-aware-training-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constructing a Singing Style Caption Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-a-singing-style-caption-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Singing style captioning is a relative task to voice generation that generates text descriptions of vocal characteristics, which we first suggested.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-a-singing-style-caption-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Large Language Models Grasp Event Signals? Exploring Pure Zero-Shot Event-based Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-grasp-event-signals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these methods heavily depend on extensive training and are inherently constrained by the characteristics of CLIP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-grasp-event-signals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-Powered Ensemble Learning for Paper Source Tracing: A GPU-Free Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-powered-ensemble-learning-for-paper</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This competition tasked participants with identifying the reference sources (i. e., ref-sources, as referred to by the organizers of the competition) of given academic papers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-powered-ensemble-learning-for-paper</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VSFormer: Mining Correlations in Flexible View Set for Multi-view 3D Shape Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vsformer-mining-correlations-in-flexible-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we propose to incorporate different views of a 3D shape into a permutation-invariant set, referred to as \emph{View Set}, which removes rigid relation assumptions and facilitates adequate information exchange and fusion among views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vsformer-mining-correlations-in-flexible-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One missing piece in Vision and Language: A Survey on Comics Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-missing-piece-in-vision-and-language-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our contributions are fivefold: (1) We analyze the structure of the comics medium, detailing its distinctive compositional elements; (2) We survey the widely used datasets and tasks in comics research, emphasizing their role in advancing the field; (3) We introduce the Layer of Comics Understanding (LoCU) framework, a novel taxonomy that redefines vision-language tasks within comics and lays the foundation for future work; (4) We provide a detailed review and categorization of existing methods following the LoCU framework; (5) Finally, we highlight current research challenges and propose directions for future exploration, particularly in the context of vision-language models applied to comics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-missing-piece-in-vision-and-language-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeriGuru: A Peripheral Robotic Mobile App Operation Assistant based on GUI Image Understanding and Prompting with LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/periguru-a-peripheral-robotic-mobile-app</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With considerations for privacy, permissions, and cross-platform compatibility issues, we endeavor to devise and develop PeriGuru in this work, a peripheral robotic mobile app operation assistant based on GUI image understanding and prompting with Large Language Model (LLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/periguru-a-peripheral-robotic-mobile-app</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Vision-Language Survival Analysis with Ordinal Inductive Bias for Computational Pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-vision-language-survival</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our VLSA could pave a new way for SA in CPATH by offering weakly-supervised MIL an effective means to learn valuable prognostic clues from gigapixel WSIs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-vision-language-survival</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beta-Sigma VAE: Separating beta and decoder variance in Gaussian variational autoencoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beta-sigma-vae-separating-beta-and-decoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Variational autoencoder (VAE) is an established generative model but is notorious for its blurriness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beta-sigma-vae-separating-beta-and-decoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating Neural Orientation Distribution Fields on High Resolution Diffusion MRI Scans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-neural-orientation-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Orientation Distribution Function (ODF) characterizes key brain microstructural properties and plays an important role in understanding brain structural connectivity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-neural-orientation-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-OCTA2: Layer Sequence OCTA Segmentation with Fine-tuned Segment Anything Model 2</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-octa2-layer-sequence-octa-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segmentation of indicated targets aids in the precise analysis of optical coherence tomography angiography (OCTA) samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-octa2-layer-sequence-octa-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The T05 System for The VoiceMOS Challenge 2024: Transfer Learning from Deep Image Classifier to Naturalness MOS Prediction of High-Quality Synthetic Speech</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-t05-system-for-the-voicemos-challenge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present our system (denoted as T05) for the VoiceMOS Challenge (VMC) 2024.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-t05-system-for-the-voicemos-challenge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MHAD: Multimodal Home Activity Dataset with Multi-Angle Videos and Synchronized Physiological Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mhad-multimodal-home-activity-dataset-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This non-contact, real-time monitoring method holds great potential for home settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mhad-multimodal-home-activity-dataset-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETAGE: Enhanced Test Time Adaptation with Integrated Entropy and Gradient Norms for Robust Model Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/etage-enhanced-test-time-adaptation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on CIFAR-10-C and CIFAR-100-C datasets demonstrate that our approach outperforms existing TTA techniques, particularly in challenging and biased scenarios, leading to more robust and consistent model performance across diverse test scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/etage-enhanced-test-time-adaptation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProcessTBench: An LLM Plan Generation Dataset for Process Mining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/processtbench-an-llm-plan-generation-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have shown significant promise in plan generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/processtbench-an-llm-plan-generation-dataset</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
