<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 21:06:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Network Traffic Classification based on Single Flow Time Series Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-traffic-classification-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Network traffic monitoring using IP flows is used to handle the current challenge of analyzing encrypted network communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-traffic-classification-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Code Coverage without Execution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-code-coverage-without-execution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using Machine Learning to amortize this expensive process could lower the cost of code coverage by requiring only the source code context, and the task of code coverage prediction can be a novel benchmark for judging the ability of models to understand code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-code-coverage-without-execution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Mainstream Bias in Recommendation via Cost-sensitive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-mainstream-bias-in-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mainstream bias, where some users receive poor recommendations because their preferences are uncommon or simply because they are less active, is an important aspect to consider regarding fairness in recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-mainstream-bias-in-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optical Flow boosts Unsupervised Localization and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optical-flow-boosts-unsupervised-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our fine-tuning procedure outperforms state-of-the-art techniques for unsupervised semantic segmentation through linear probing, without the use of any labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optical-flow-boosts-unsupervised-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FacTool: Factuality Detection in Generative AI -- A Tool Augmented Framework for Multi-Task and Multi-Domain Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factool-factuality-detection-in-generative-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emergence of generative pre-trained models has facilitated the synthesis of high-quality text, but it has also posed challenges in identifying factual errors in the generated text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factool-factuality-detection-in-generative-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Submodular Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/submodular-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many important applications, such as coverage control, experiment design and informative path planning, rewards naturally have diminishing returns, i. e., their value decreases in light of similar states visited previously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/submodular-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empower Your Model with Longer and Better Context Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empower-your-model-with-longer-and-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, with the emergence of numerous Large Language Models (LLMs), the implementation of AI has entered a new era.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empower-your-model-with-longer-and-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the learning Dynamics of Attention Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-learning-dynamics-of-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Attention models are typically learned by optimizing one of three standard loss functions that are variously called -- soft attention, hard attention, and latent variable marginal likelihood (LVML) attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-learning-dynamics-of-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoSAS: Deep Semi-Supervised Anomaly Detection with Contamination-Resilient Continuous Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rosas-deep-semi-supervised-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[anomaly contamination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rosas-deep-semi-supervised-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Importance Measurement based on Decision Tree Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-importance-measurement-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Random forest is effective for prediction tasks but the randomness of tree generation hinders interpretability in feature importance analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-importance-measurement-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinterpreting survival analysis in the universal approximator age</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinterpreting-survival-analysis-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim to provide the tools needed to fully harness the potential of survival analysis in deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinterpreting-survival-analysis-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectrum-guided Multi-granularity Referring Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectrum-guided-multi-granularity-referring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the drift problem, we propose a Spectrum-guided Multi-granularity (SgMg) approach, which performs direct segmentation on the encoded features and employs visual details to further optimize the masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectrum-guided-multi-granularity-referring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Investigation into Glomeruli Detection in Kidney H&amp;E and PAS Images using YOLO</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-investigation-into-glomeruli-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conclusions: Automated glomeruli detection in human kidney images is possible using modern AI models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-investigation-into-glomeruli-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One for Multiple: Physics-informed Synthetic Data Boosts Generalizable Deep Learning for Fast MRI Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-for-multiple-physics-informed-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) is a principal radiological modality that provides radiation-free, abundant, and diverse information about the whole human body for medical diagnosis, but suffers from prolonged scan time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-for-multiple-physics-informed-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Segmentation Keras : Implementation of Segnet, FCN, UNet, PSPNet and other models in Keras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-segmentation-keras-implementation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation plays a vital role in computer vision tasks, enabling precise pixel-level understanding of images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-segmentation-keras-implementation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BotHawk: An Approach for Bots Detection in Open Source Software Projects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bothawk-an-approach-for-bots-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identifying bot accounts and behavior is a challenging task in the OSS project.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bothawk-an-approach-for-bots-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Granularity Prediction with Learnable Fusion for Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-prediction-with-learnable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, MGP-STR achieves an average recognition accuracy of $94\%$ on standard benchmarks for scene text recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-prediction-with-learnable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holistic Exploration on Universal Decompositional Semantic Parsing: Architecture, Data Augmentation, and LLM Paradigm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holistic-exploration-on-universal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we conduct a holistic exploration of the Universal Decompositional Semantic (UDS) Parsing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holistic-exploration-on-universal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Money Launderers Using Heterogeneous Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-money-launderers-using-heterogeneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we extend the homogeneous GNN method known as the Message Passing Neural Network (MPNN) to operate effectively on a heterogeneous graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-money-launderers-using-heterogeneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuickQual: Lightweight, convenient retinal image quality scoring with off-the-shelf pretrained models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quickqual-lightweight-convenient-retinal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this task, we present a second model, QuickQual MEga Minified Estimator (QuickQual-MEME), that consists of only 10 parameters on top of an off-the-shelf Densenet121 and can distinguish between gradable and ungradable images with an accuracy of 89. 18% (AUC: 0. 9537).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quickqual-lightweight-convenient-retinal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embedding Models for Supervised Automatic Extraction and Classification of Named Entities in Scientific Acknowledgements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embedding-models-for-supervised-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Flair Embeddings model trained on the medium corpus with the latest FLAIR version showed the best accuracy of 0. 79.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embedding-models-for-supervised-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scoring Cycling Environments Perceived Safety using Pairwise Image Comparisons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scoring-cycling-environments-perceived-safety</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, this approach facilitates the continuous assessment of changing cycling environments, allows for a short-term evaluation of measures, and is efficiently deployed in different locations or contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scoring-cycling-environments-perceived-safety</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Calibration in Dense Classification with Adaptive Label Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-calibration-in-dense-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve model calibration, we propose Adaptive Stochastic Label Perturbation (ASLP) which learns a unique label perturbation level for each training image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-calibration-in-dense-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Unifying Anatomy Segmentation: Automated Generation of a Full-body CT Dataset via Knowledge Aggregation and Anatomical Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-unifying-anatomy-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We examine its plausibility and usefulness using three complementary checks: Human expert evaluation which approved the dataset, a Deep Learning usefulness benchmark on the BTCV dataset in which we achieve 85% dice score without using its training dataset, and medical validity checks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-unifying-anatomy-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED CoMETS: An ensemble classifier for symbolically represented multivariate time series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/red-comets-an-ensemble-classifier-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multivariate time series classification is a rapidly growing research field with practical applications in finance, healthcare, engineering, and more.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/red-comets-an-ensemble-classifier-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuIP: 2-Bit Quantization of Large Language Models With Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quip-2-bit-quantization-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work studies post-training parameter quantization in large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quip-2-bit-quantization-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformal prediction for frequency-severity modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-prediction-for-frequency-severity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a nonparametric model-agnostic framework for building prediction intervals of insurance claims, with finite sample statistical guarantees, extending the technique of split conformal prediction to the domain of two-stage frequency-severity modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-prediction-for-frequency-severity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Explainable Geometric-Weighted Graph Attention Network for Identifying Functional Networks Associated with Gait Impairment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-explainable-geometric-weighted-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the hallmark symptoms of Parkinson's Disease (PD) is the progressive loss of postural reflexes, which eventually leads to gait difficulties and balance problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-explainable-geometric-weighted-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness Under Demographic Scarce Regime</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-under-demographic-scarce-regime</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Surprisingly, our framework outperforms models trained with constraints on the true sensitive attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-under-demographic-scarce-regime</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks For Mapping Variables Between Programs -- Extended Version</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-for-mapping-variables</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Typically, in order to compare two programs, a relation between both programs' sets of variables is required.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-for-mapping-variables</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COCO-O: A Benchmark for Object Detectors under Natural Distribution Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coco-o-a-benchmark-for-object-detectors-under-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To give a more comprehensive robustness assessment, we introduce COCO-O(ut-of-distribution), a test dataset based on COCO with 6 types of natural distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coco-o-a-benchmark-for-object-detectors-under-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Skeleton Meta-Prototype Contrastive Learning with Hard Skeleton Mining for Unsupervised Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-skeleton-meta-prototype</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then a hierarchical meta-prototype contrastive learning model is proposed to cluster and contrast the most typical skeleton features ("prototypes") from different-level skeletons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-skeleton-meta-prototype</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonparametric Linear Feature Learning in Regression Through Regularisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonparametric-linear-feature-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose a novel method for linear feature learning with non-parametric prediction, which simultaneously estimates the prediction function and the linear subspace.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonparametric-linear-feature-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost In Translation: Generating Adversarial Examples Robust to Round-Trip Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lost-in-translation-generating-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language Models today provide a high accuracy across a large number of downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lost-in-translation-generating-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Connection between One-Step Regularization and Critic Regularization in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-connection-between-one-step-regularization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One-step methods perform regularization by doing just a single step of policy improvement, while critic regularization methods do many steps of policy improvement with a regularized objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-connection-between-one-step-regularization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exposing the Troublemakers in Described Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposing-the-troublemakers-in-described</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we advance them to a more practical setting called Described Object Detection (DOD) by expanding category names to flexible language expressions for OVD and overcoming the limitation of REC to only grounding the pre-existing object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposing-the-troublemakers-in-described</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Client-Level Differential Privacy via Adaptive Intermediary in Federated Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/client-level-differential-privacy-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to optimize the trade-off under the context of client-level DP, which focuses on privacy during communications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/client-level-differential-privacy-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GridMM: Grid Memory Map for Vision-and-Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gridmm-grid-memory-map-for-vision-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-and-language navigation (VLN) enables the agent to navigate to a remote location following the natural language instruction in 3D environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gridmm-grid-memory-map-for-vision-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PG-RCNN: Semantic Surface Point Generation for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pg-rcnn-semantic-surface-point-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, we propose Point Generation R-CNN (PG-RCNN), a novel end-to-end detector that generates semantic surface points of foreground objects for accurate detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pg-rcnn-semantic-surface-point-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Provably Robust Estimators for Inverse Problems via Jittering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-provably-robust-estimators-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This raises the question of whether such networks can be trained efficiently to be worst-case robust.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-provably-robust-estimators-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extending Path-Dependent NJ-ODEs to Noisy Observations and a Dependent Observation Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-path-dependent-nj-odes-to-noisy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Path-Dependent Neural Jump ODE (PD-NJ-ODE) is a model for predicting continuous-time stochastic processes with irregular and incomplete observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-path-dependent-nj-odes-to-noisy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-View Vertebra Localization and Identification from CT Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-vertebra-localization-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we further propose a Sequence Loss to maintain the sequential structure embedded along the vertebrae.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-vertebra-localization-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use LLMs for Text Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-use-llms-for-text-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This guide introduces Large Language Models (LLM) as a highly versatile text analysis method within the social sciences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-use-llms-for-text-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Example-Based Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-example-based-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a method for offline, example-based control that learns an implicit model of multi-step transitions, rather than a reward function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-example-based-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptation of Whisper models to child speech recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptation-of-whisper-models-to-child-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that finetuning Whisper on child speech yields significant improvements in ASR performance on child speech, compared to non finetuned Whisper models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptation-of-whisper-models-to-child-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unbiased Delayed Feedback Label Correction for Conversion Rate Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-delayed-feedback-label-correction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To directly introduce the correct feedback label information, we propose an Unbiased delayed feedback Label Correction framework (ULC), which uses an auxiliary model to correct labels for observed negative feedback samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-delayed-feedback-label-correction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compact &amp; Capable: Harnessing Graph Neural Networks and Edge Convolution for Medical Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-capable-harnessing-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we investigate the potential of Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) for medical image classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-capable-harnessing-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Large Language Models with Human: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-language-models-with-human-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(2) Training methodologies: a detailed review of the prevailing training methods employed for LLM alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-language-models-with-human-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guidance in Radiology Report Summarization: An Empirical Evaluation and Error Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guidance-in-radiology-report-summarization-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatically summarizing radiology reports into a concise impression can reduce the manual burden of clinicians and improve the consistency of reporting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guidance-in-radiology-report-summarization-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rule By Example: Harnessing Logical Rules for Explainable Hate Speech Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rule-by-example-harnessing-logical-rules-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present Rule By Example (RBE): a novel exemplar-based contrastive learning approach for learning from logical rules for the task of textual content moderation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rule-by-example-harnessing-logical-rules-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
