<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 09:14:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>UDE: A Unified Driving Engine for Human Motion Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ude-a-unified-driving-engine-for-human-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating controllable and editable human motion sequences is a key challenge in 3D Avatar generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ude-a-unified-driving-engine-for-human-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Procedural Image Programs for Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procedural-image-programs-for-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning image representations using synthetic data allows training neural networks without some of the concerns associated with real images, such as privacy and bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procedural-image-programs-for-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Ensemble Averages: Leveraging Climate Model Ensembles for Subseasonal Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-ensemble-averages-leveraging-climate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper further includes an investigation of feature importance, trade-offs between using the full ensemble or only the ensemble average, and different modes of accounting for spatial variability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-ensemble-averages-leveraging-climate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling the Mechanisms Behind Implicit Regularization in SGD</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-the-mechanisms-behind-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A number of competing hypotheses have been proposed to explain why small-batch Stochastic Gradient Descent (SGD)leads to improved generalization over the full-batch regime, with recent work crediting the implicit regularization of various quantities throughout training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-the-mechanisms-behind-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks: A Powerful and Versatile Tool for Advancing Design, Reliability, and Security of ICs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-a-powerful-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) have pushed the state-of-the-art (SOTA) for performance in learning and predicting on large-scale data present in social networks, biology, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-a-powerful-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Commonsense in Vision-Language Models via Knowledge Graph Riddles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-commonsense-in-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through our analysis, we find one important reason is that existing large-scale VL datasets do not contain much commonsense knowledge, which motivates us to improve the commonsense of VL-models from the data perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-commonsense-in-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Neural Discourse Deixis Resolution in Dialogue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-neural-discourse-deixis-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We adapt Lee et al.'s (2018) span-based entity coreference model to the task of end-to-end discourse deixis resolution in dialogue, specifically by proposing extensions to their model that exploit task-specific characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-neural-discourse-deixis-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compressing Volumetric Radiance Fields to 1 MB</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compressing-volumetric-radiance-fields-to-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Approximating radiance fields with volumetric grids is one of promising directions for improving NeRF, represented by methods like Plenoxels and DVGO, which achieve super-fast training convergence and real-time rendering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compressing-volumetric-radiance-fields-to-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TyDiP: A Dataset for Politeness Classification in Nine Typologically Diverse Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tydip-a-dataset-for-politeness-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study politeness phenomena in nine typologically diverse languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tydip-a-dataset-for-politeness-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Opinion Summarization with GPT-3</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-opinion-summarization-with-gpt-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Very large language models such as GPT-3 have shown impressive performance across a wide variety of tasks, including text summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-opinion-summarization-with-gpt-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming a Generative Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-a-generative-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method can be used in the context of privacy, e. g., removing a specific person from the output of a model, and also in the context of de-biasing by forcing a model to output specific image categories according to a given target distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-a-generative-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifelong Person Re-Identification via Knowledge Refreshing and Consolidation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelong-person-re-identification-via-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lifelong person re-identification (LReID) is in significant demand for real-world development as a large amount of ReID data is captured from diverse locations over time and cannot be accessed at once inherently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelong-person-re-identification-via-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Simultaneous Factorization and Prediction Using Multi-Omic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-simultaneous-factorization-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show via simulation that BSFP is competitive in recovering latent variation structure, as well as the importance of propagating uncertainty from the estimated factorization to prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-simultaneous-factorization-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robustness Disparities in Face Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-disparities-in-face-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many existing algorithmic audits examine the performance of these systems on later stage elements of facial analysis systems like facial recognition and age, emotion, or perceived gender prediction; however, a core component to these systems has been vastly understudied from a fairness perspective: face detection, sometimes called face localization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-disparities-in-face-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PatchMatch-Stereo-Panorama, a fast dense reconstruction from 360° video images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchmatch-stereo-panorama-a-fast-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes a new method for real-time dense 3d reconstruction for common 360{\deg} action cams, which can be mounted on small scouting UAVs during USAR missions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchmatch-stereo-panorama-a-fast-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffG-RL: Leveraging Difference between State and Common Sense</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffg-rl-leveraging-difference-between-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel agent, DiffG-RL, which constructs a Difference Graph that organizes the environment states and common sense by means of interactive objects with a dedicated graph encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffg-rl-leveraging-difference-between-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear Causal Disentanglement via Interventions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-causal-disentanglement-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A representation is identifiable if both the latent model and the transformation from latent to observed variables are unique.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-causal-disentanglement-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kinematic-aware Hierarchical Attention Network for Human Pose Estimation in Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kinematic-aware-hierarchical-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous video-based human pose estimation methods have shown promising results by leveraging aggregated features of consecutive frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kinematic-aware-hierarchical-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable User Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-user-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Probabilistic user modeling is essential for building collaborative AI systems within probabilistic frameworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-user-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedalCare-XL: 16,900 healthy and pathological 12 lead ECGs obtained through electrophysiological simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medalcare-xl-16900-healthy-and-pathological</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mechanistic cardiac electrophysiology models allow for personalized simulations of the electrical activity in the heart and the ensuing electrocardiogram (ECG) on the body surface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medalcare-xl-16900-healthy-and-pathological</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Unsupervised Text Classification: Zero-shot and Similarity-based Approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-unsupervised-text-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text classification of unseen classes is a challenging Natural Language Processing task and is mainly attempted using two different types of approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-unsupervised-text-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offline Supervised Learning V.S. Online Direct Policy Optimization: A Comparative Study and A Unified Training Paradigm for Neural Network-Based Optimal Feedback Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-supervised-learning-v-s-online-direct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first conduct a comparative study of two mainstream approaches: offline supervised learning and online direct policy optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-supervised-learning-v-s-online-direct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifelong Embedding Learning and Transfer for Growing Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelong-embedding-learning-and-transfer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider knowledge transfer and retention of the learning on growing snapshots of a KG without having to learn embeddings from scratch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelong-embedding-learning-and-transfer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three-stage binarization of color document images based on discrete wavelet transform and generative adversarial networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/three-stage-binarization-of-color-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, a three-stage method is proposed for image enhancement and binarization of degraded color document images by using discrete wavelet transform (DWT) and generative adversarial network (GAN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/three-stage-binarization-of-color-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACE: Cooperative Multi-agent Q-learning with Bidirectional Action-Dependency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ace-cooperative-multi-agent-q-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the learning phase, each agent minimizes the TD error that is dependent on how the subsequent agents have reacted to their chosen action.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ace-cooperative-multi-agent-q-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Revenue Function for Comparison-Based Hierarchical Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-revenue-function-for-comparison-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comparison-based learning addresses the problem of learning when, instead of explicit features or pairwise similarities, one only has access to comparisons of the form: \emph{Object $A$ is more similar to $B$ than to $C$.}]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-revenue-function-for-comparison-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring the Measuring Tools: An Automatic Evaluation of Semantic Metrics for Text Corpora</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-the-measuring-tools-an-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to compare the semantic similarity between text corpora is important in a variety of natural language processing applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-the-measuring-tools-an-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extending the Subwording Model of Multilingual Pretrained Models for New Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-the-subwording-model-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multilingual pretrained models are effective for machine translation and cross-lingual processing because they contain multiple languages in one model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-the-subwording-model-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Front-Door Adjustment Sets in Linear Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-front-door-adjustment-sets-in-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advantage of this approach is that it uses observed mediators to identify causal effects, which is possible even in the presence of unobserved confounding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-front-door-adjustment-sets-in-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BotSIM: An End-to-End Bot Simulation Toolkit for Commercial Task-Oriented Dialog Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/botsim-an-end-to-end-bot-simulation-toolkit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BotSIM adopts a layered design comprising the infrastructure layer, the adaptor layer and the application layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/botsim-an-end-to-end-bot-simulation-toolkit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Extreme-Adaptive Time Series Prediction Model Based on Probability-Enhanced LSTM Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-extreme-adaptive-time-series-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Forecasting time series with extreme events has been a challenging and prevalent research topic, especially when the time series data are affected by complicated uncertain factors, such as is the case in hydrologic prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-extreme-adaptive-time-series-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guiding Neural Entity Alignment with Compatibility</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-neural-entity-alignment-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Making compatible predictions thus should be one of the goals of training an EA model along with fitting the labelled data: this aspect however is neglected in current methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-neural-entity-alignment-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring Attack Relations for Gradual Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-attack-relations-for-gradual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main contribution of our work is to demonstrate that the associated decision problem, i. e., whether a set of attacks can exist which allows the final acceptability degrees to occur for given initial weights, is NP-complete for the weighted h-categoriser and cardinality-based semantics, and is polynomial for the weighted max-based semantics, even for the complete version of the problem (where all initial weights and final acceptability degrees are known).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-attack-relations-for-gradual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One is All: Bridging the Gap Between Neural Radiance Fields Architectures with Progressive Volume Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-is-all-bridging-the-gap-between-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Progressive Volume Distillation (PVD), a systematic distillation method that allows any-to-any conversions between different architectures, including MLP, sparse or low-rank tensors, hashtables and their compositions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-is-all-bridging-the-gap-between-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dependency-aware Self-training for Entity Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dependency-aware-self-training-for-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entity Alignment (EA), which aims to detect entity mappings (i. e. equivalent entity pairs) in different Knowledge Graphs (KGs), is critical for KG fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dependency-aware-self-training-for-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-driven Open-Vocabulary 3D Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-driven-open-vocabulary-3d-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-vocabulary scene understanding aims to localize and recognize unseen categories beyond the annotated label space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-driven-open-vocabulary-3d-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intra-class Adaptive Augmentation with Neighbor Correction for Deep Metric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intra-class-adaptive-augmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[They have overlooked the wide characteristic changes of different classes and can not model abundant intra-class variations for generations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intra-class-adaptive-augmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Temperature for Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-temperature-for-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a simple curriculum-based technique, termed Curriculum Temperature for Knowledge Distillation (CTKD), which controls the task difficulty level during the student's learning career through a dynamic and learnable temperature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-temperature-for-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARTSmiles: Generative Masked Language Models for Molecular Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bartsmiles-generative-masked-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then quantitatively show that when applied to the molecular domain, the BART objective learns representations that implicitly encode our downstream tasks of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bartsmiles-generative-masked-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoCAD: Automatically Generating Counterfactuals for Mitigating Shortcut Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autocad-automatically-generating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies have shown the impressive efficacy of counterfactually augmented data (CAD) for reducing NLU models' reliance on spurious features and improving their generalizability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autocad-automatically-generating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards More Robust Interpretation via Local Gradient Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-more-robust-interpretation-via-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the lack of considering the normalization of the attributions, which is essential in their visualizations, has been an obstacle to understanding and improving the robustness of feature attribution methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-more-robust-interpretation-via-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Training Object Detection Models with Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-training-object-detection-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The downside of this technique is that the so-called domain gap between the real target images and synthetic training data leads to a decrease in performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-training-object-detection-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdsorbML: Accelerating Adsorption Energy Calculations with Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adsorbml-accelerating-adsorption-energy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computational catalysis is playing an increasingly significant role in the design of catalysts across a wide range of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adsorbml-accelerating-adsorption-energy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which Shortcut Solution Do Question Answering Models Prefer to Learn?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/which-shortcut-solution-do-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We assume that the learnability of shortcuts, i. e., how easy it is to learn a shortcut, is useful to mitigate the problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/which-shortcut-solution-do-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fourier-Net: Fast Image Registration with Band-limited Deformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fourier-net-fast-image-registration-with-band</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, instead of our Fourier-Net learning to output a full-resolution displacement field in the spatial domain, we learn its low-dimensional representation in a band-limited Fourier domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fourier-net-fast-image-registration-with-band</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Challenging the Universal Representation of Deep Models for 3D Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenging-the-universal-representation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning universal representations across different applications domain is an open research problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenging-the-universal-representation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Visual Active Search Framework for Geospatial Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-visual-active-search-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We model this class of problems in a visual active search (VAS) framework, which takes as input an image of a broad area, and aims to identify as many examples of a target object as possible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-visual-active-search-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyTorch Adapt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytorch-adapt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PyTorch Adapt is a library for domain adaptation, a type of machine learning algorithm that re-purposes existing models to work in new domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytorch-adapt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superpoint Transformer for 3D Scene Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superpoint-transformer-for-3d-scene-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key step in this framework is a novel query decoder with transformers that can capture the instance information through the superpoint cross-attention mechanism and generate the superpoint masks of the instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superpoint-transformer-for-3d-scene-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Découvrir de nouvelles classes dans des données tabulaires</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decouvrir-de-nouvelles-classes-dans-des</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Novel Class Discovery (NCD), the goal is to find new classes in an unlabeled set given a labeled set of known but different classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decouvrir-de-nouvelles-classes-dans-des</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
