<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 21:07:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Traffic state data imputation: An efficient generating method based on the graph aggregator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-state-data-imputation-an-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Road traffic state estimation is an essential component of intelligent transportation systems (ITSs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-state-data-imputation-an-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSUMNet: Unified Modality Part Streams are All You Need for Efficient Pose-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psumnet-unified-modality-part-streams-are-all</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the representation level, we propose a global frame based part stream approach as opposed to conventional modality based streams.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psumnet-unified-modality-part-streams-are-all</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TotalSegmentator: robust segmentation of 104 anatomical structures in CT images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/totalsegmentator-robust-segmentation-of-104</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we train a segmentation algorithm on this new dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/totalsegmentator-robust-segmentation-of-104</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-Guided Face Animation by Recurrent StyleGAN-based Generator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-guided-face-animation-by-recurrent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a recurrent motion generator to extract a series of semantic and motion information from the language and feed it along with visual information to a pre-trained StyleGAN to generate high-quality frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-guided-face-animation-by-recurrent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointTree: Transformation-Robust Point Cloud Encoder with Relaxed K-D Trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointtree-transformation-robust-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Being able to learn an effective semantic representation directly on raw point clouds has become a central topic in 3D understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointtree-transformation-robust-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>K-UNN: k-Space Interpolation With Untrained Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-unn-k-space-interpolation-with-untrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, untrained neural networks (UNNs) have shown satisfactory performances for MR image reconstruction on random sampling trajectories without using additional full-sampled training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-unn-k-space-interpolation-with-untrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Face Morphing Attack Detection via Self-paced Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-face-morphing-attack-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, given variations in the morphing attacks, the performance of supervised MAD solutions drops significantly due to the insufficient diversity and quantity of the existing MAD datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-face-morphing-attack-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Quantification of Sparse Travel Demand Prediction with Spatial-Temporal Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-of-sparse-travel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, spatial-temporal deep learning models demonstrate the tremendous potential to enhance prediction accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-of-sparse-travel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heatmap Regression for Lesion Detection using Pointwise Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heatmap-regression-for-lesion-detection-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many clinical contexts, detecting all lesions is imperative for evaluating disease activity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heatmap-regression-for-lesion-detection-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family based HLA imputation and optimization of haplo-identical transplants</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/family-based-hla-imputation-and-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use GRAMM to detect recombination events and show that the rate of falsely detected recombination events (False Positive Rate) in simulations is very low.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/family-based-hla-imputation-and-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROC: A New Paradigm for Lyric-to-Melody Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roc-a-new-paradigm-for-lyric-to-melody</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our paradigm has two stages: (1) creation stage, where a huge amount of music pieces are generated by a neural-based melody language model and indexed in a database through several key features (e. g., chords, tonality, rhythm, and structural information including chorus or verse); (2) re-creation stage, where melodies are recreated by retrieving music pieces from the database according to the key features from lyrics and concatenating best music pieces based on composition guidelines and melody language model scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roc-a-new-paradigm-for-lyric-to-melody</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixSKD: Self-Knowledge Distillation from Mixup for Image Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixskd-self-knowledge-distillation-from-mixup</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MixSKD mutually distills feature maps and probability distributions between the random pair of original images and their mixup images in a meaningful way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixskd-self-knowledge-distillation-from-mixup</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled Modeling of Domain and Relevance for Adaptable Dense Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-modeling-of-domain-and-relevance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By making the REM and DAMs disentangled, DDR enables a flexible training paradigm in which REM is trained with supervision once and DAMs are trained with unsupervised data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-modeling-of-domain-and-relevance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Sequence-Level Training for Visual Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-sequence-level-training-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the extensive adoption of machine learning on the task of visual object tracking, recent learning-based approaches have largely overlooked the fact that visual tracking is a sequence-level task in its nature; they rely heavily on frame-level training, which inevitably induces inconsistency between training and testing in terms of both data distributions and task objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-sequence-level-training-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive and Implicit Regularization for Matrix Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-and-implicit-regularization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Theoretically, we show that the adaptive regularization of \ReTwo{AIR} enhances the implicit regularization and vanishes at the end of training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-and-implicit-regularization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differencing based Self-supervised pretraining for Scene Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differencing-based-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SCD is challenging due to noisy changes in illumination, seasonal variations, and perspective differences across a pair of views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differencing-based-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empirical investigations on WVA structural issues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-investigations-on-wva-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we want to present the results of empirical verification of some issues concerning the methods for overcoming catastrophic forgetting in neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-investigations-on-wva-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Specific Text Generation for Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-specific-text-generation-for-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Preservation of domain knowledge from the source to target is crucial in any translation workflow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-specific-text-generation-for-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularizing Deep Neural Networks with Stochastic Estimators of Hessian Trace</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-deep-neural-networks-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we develop a novel regularization method for deep neural networks by penalizing the trace of Hessian.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-deep-neural-networks-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PPMN: Pixel-Phrase Matching Network for One-Stage Panoptic Narrative Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppmn-pixel-phrase-matching-network-for-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate these drawbacks, we propose a one-stage end-to-end Pixel-Phrase Matching Network (PPMN), which directly matches each phrase to its corresponding pixels instead of region proposals and outputs panoptic segmentation by simple combination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppmn-pixel-phrase-matching-network-for-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodness of Fit Metrics for Multi-class Predictor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goodness-of-fit-metrics-for-multi-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The multi-class prediction had gained popularity over recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goodness-of-fit-metrics-for-multi-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeing your sleep stage: cross-modal distillation from EEG to infrared video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seeing-your-sleep-stage-cross-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[$S^3VE$ is a large-scale dataset including synchronized infrared video and EEG signal for sleep stage classification, including 105 subjects and 154, 573 video clips that is more than 1100 hours long.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seeing-your-sleep-stage-cross-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech Enhancement and Dereverberation with Diffusion-based Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-enhancement-and-dereverberation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we show that the proposed method achieves remarkable state-of-the-art performance in single-channel speech dereverberation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-enhancement-and-dereverberation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable cytometry cell-type annotation with flow-based deep generative models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-cytometry-cell-type-annotation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cytometry enables precise single-cell phenotyping within heterogeneous populations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-cytometry-cell-type-annotation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PASS: De novo assembler for short peptide sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pass-de-novo-assembler-for-short-peptide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to characterize proteins at sequence-level resolution is vital to biological research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pass-de-novo-assembler-for-short-peptide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Transport Features for Morphometric Population Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-features-for-morphometric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the proposed optimal transport feature extraction step in the context of a volumetric morphometric analysis of the OASIS-1 study for Alzheimer's disease.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-features-for-morphometric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cine-AI: Generating Video Game Cutscenes in the Style of Human Directors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cine-ai-generating-video-game-cutscenes-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cutscenes form an integral part of many video games, but their creation is costly, time-consuming, and requires skills that many game developers lack.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cine-ai-generating-video-game-cutscenes-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Contrastive Self-Supervised Learning of Utterance-Level Speech Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-contrastive-self-supervised-learning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper applies a non-contrastive self-supervised learning method on an unlabeled speech corpus to learn utterance-level embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-contrastive-self-supervised-learning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DVR: Micro-Video Recommendation Optimizing Watch-Time-Gain under Duration Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dvr-micro-video-recommendation-optimizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommender systems are prone to be misled by biases in the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dvr-micro-video-recommendation-optimizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Diverse Chemical Reactions for Single-step Retrosynthesis via Discrete Latent Variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-diverse-chemical-reactions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of single-step retrosynthesis is to identify the possible reactants that lead to the synthesis of the target product in one reaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-diverse-chemical-reactions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patching open-vocabulary models by interpolating weights</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patching-open-vocabulary-models-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study model patching, where the goal is to improve accuracy on specific tasks without degrading accuracy on tasks where performance is already adequate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patching-open-vocabulary-models-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Reinforcement Learning using Offline Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-reinforcement-learning-using-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of robust reinforcement learning (RL) is to learn a policy that is robust against the uncertainty in model parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-reinforcement-learning-using-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Supervised Training for Skeleton-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-supervised-training-for-skeleton</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More specifically, we employ a large-scale language model as the knowledge engine to provide text descriptions for body parts movements of actions, and propose a multi-modal training scheme by utilizing the text encoder to generate feature vectors for different body parts and supervise the skeleton encoder for action representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-supervised-training-for-skeleton</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghost-free High Dynamic Range Imaging with Context-aware Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ghost-free-high-dynamic-range-imaging-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High dynamic range (HDR) deghosting algorithms aim to generate ghost-free HDR images with realistic details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ghost-free-high-dynamic-range-imaging-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Self-adaptation: Enhancing Generalization with a Single Sample</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-self-adaptation-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we challenge this premise with a self-adaptive approach for semantic segmentation that adjusts the inference process to each input sample.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-self-adaptation-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Degradation Representations for Image Deblurring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-degradation-representations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the integration, MSDI-Net can handle various and complicated blurry patterns adaptively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-degradation-representations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSInterpret: A unified framework for time series interpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsinterpret-a-unified-framework-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increasing application of deep learning algorithms to time series classification, especially in high-stake scenarios, the relevance of interpreting those algorithms becomes key.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsinterpret-a-unified-framework-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-supervised segmentation of tooth from 3D Scanned Dental Arches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-segmentation-of-tooth-from-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the dental field, the variability of input data is high and there are no publicly available 3D dental arch datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-segmentation-of-tooth-from-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Transfer Learning: Covid-19 Classification with a few Chest X-ray Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-transfer-learning-covid-19</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, interpreting imaging data is often time-consuming and requires a great deal of human expertise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-transfer-learning-covid-19</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Networks for Scalar Input and Functional Output</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-for-scalar-input-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The regression of a functional response on a set of scalar predictors can be a challenging task, especially if there is a large number of predictors, these predictors have interaction effects, or the relationship between those predictors and the response is nonlinear.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-for-scalar-input-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Point-BEV Fusion for 3D Point Cloud Object Tracking with Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-point-bev-fusion-for-3d-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a point cloud sequence, 3D object tracking aims to predict the location and orientation of an object in consecutive frames given an object template.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-point-bev-fusion-for-3d-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for a Needle in a Haystack: A Comprehensive Study of Hallucinations in Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-for-a-needle-in-a-haystack-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the problem of hallucinations in neural machine translation (NMT) has received some attention, research on this highly pathological phenomenon lacks solid ground.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-for-a-needle-in-a-haystack-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing Exploitability with Population Based Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-exploitability-with-population-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate this defense's robustness against new adversaries in two low-dimensional environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-exploitability-with-population-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Inference of Temporal Logic Formulas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-inference-of-temporal-logic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is great interest in learning formal specifications that characterize the ideal behavior of such systems -- that is, formulas in temporal logic that are satisfied by the system's output signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-inference-of-temporal-logic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Autonomous Atlas-based Ultrasound Acquisitions in Presence of Articulated Motion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-autonomous-atlas-based-ultrasound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robotic ultrasound (US) imaging aims at overcoming some of the limitations of free-hand US examinations, e. g. difficulty in guaranteeing intra- and inter-operator repeatability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-autonomous-atlas-based-ultrasound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Monitoring and Discovery Approach for Declarative Processes Based on Streams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-monitoring-and-discovery-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We validated the technique via quantitative and qualitative evaluations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-monitoring-and-discovery-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Prune-and-Select: Class-incremental learning with specialized subnetworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-prune-and-select-class-incremental</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, CP&S is capable of sequentially learning 10 tasks from ImageNet-1000 keeping an accuracy around 94% with negligible forgetting, a first-of-its-kind result in class-incremental learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-prune-and-select-class-incremental</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Evaluation for Decision Tree Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-evaluation-for-decision-tree-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We transfer distances on clusterings to the building process of decision trees, and as a consequence extend the classical ID3 algorithm to perform modifications based on the global distance of the tree to the ground truth--instead of considering single leaves.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-evaluation-for-decision-tree-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Video Analysis on Large-Scale Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sports-video-analysis-on-large-scale-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel large-scale NBA dataset for Sports Video Analysis (NSVA) with a focus on captioning, to address the above challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sports-video-analysis-on-large-scale-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra Lite Convolutional Neural Network for Automatic Modulation Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-lite-convolutional-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic modulation classification (AMC) is a key technique for desiging non-cooperative communication systems, and deep learning (DL) is applied effectively into AMC for improving the classification accuracy. However, most of the DL-based AMC methods have a large number of parameters and high computational complexity, and they cannot be directly applied into scenarios with limited computing power and storage space. In this paper, we propose a lightweight and low-complexity AMC method using ultra lite convolutional neural network (ULCNN), which is based on multiple tricks, including data augmentation, complex-valued convolution, separable convolution, channel attention, channel shuffle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-lite-convolutional-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
