<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 21:07:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>RDRec: Rationale Distillation for LLM-based Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdrec-rationale-distillation-for-llm-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language model (LLM)-based recommender models that bridge users and items through textual prompts for effective semantic reasoning have gained considerable attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdrec-rationale-distillation-for-llm-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CM-UNet: Hybrid CNN-Mamba UNet for Remote Sensing Image Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cm-unet-hybrid-cnn-mamba-unet-for-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose CM-UNet, comprising a CNN-based encoder for extracting local image features and a Mamba-based decoder for aggregating and integrating global information, facilitating efficient semantic segmentation of remote sensing images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cm-unet-hybrid-cnn-mamba-unet-for-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FA-Depth: Toward Fast and Accurate Self-supervised Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fa-depth-toward-fast-and-accurate-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing methods often rely on complex models to predict scene depth with high accuracy, resulting in slow inference that is not conducive to deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fa-depth-toward-fast-and-accurate-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Saliency Explanations in NLP by Crowdsourcing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-saliency-explanations-in-nlp-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of methods to explain models has become a key issue in the reliability of deep learning models in many important applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-saliency-explanations-in-nlp-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECR-Chain: Advancing Generative Language Models to Better Emotion-Cause Reasoners through Reasoning Chains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecr-chain-advancing-generative-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, inspired by the emotion generation process of "stimulus-appraisal-emotion" in the cognitive appraisal theory, we introduce a step-by-step reasoning method, Emotion-Cause Reasoning Chain (ECR-Chain), to infer the stimulus from the target emotional expressions in conversations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecr-chain-advancing-generative-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LighTDiff: Surgical Endoscopic Image Low-Light Enhancement with T-Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightdiff-surgical-endoscopic-image-low-light</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further introduce a Chroma Balancer (CB) to mitigate this issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightdiff-surgical-endoscopic-image-low-light</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneity-Informed Meta-Parameter Learning for Spatiotemporal Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneity-informed-meta-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatiotemporal time series forecasting plays a key role in a wide range of real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneity-informed-meta-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Know in AdVance: Linear-Complexity Forecasting of Ad Campaign Performance with Evolving User Interest</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/know-in-advance-linear-complexity-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further condition SSM's global predictions on the accumulation of local results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/know-in-advance-linear-complexity-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature-based Low-Rank Compression of Large Language Models via Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-based-low-rank-compression-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the challenges of low-rank compression in LLMs, we conduct empirical research on the low-rank characteristics of large models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-based-low-rank-compression-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBAAM! Eliminating Transcript Dependency in Automatic Subtitling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sbaam-eliminating-transcript-dependency-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subtitling plays a crucial role in enhancing the accessibility of audiovisual content and encompasses three primary subtasks: translating spoken dialogue, segmenting translations into concise textual units, and estimating timestamps that govern their on-screen duration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sbaam-eliminating-transcript-dependency-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Sora What We Can See: A Survey of Text-to-Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-sora-what-we-can-see-a-survey-of-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With impressive achievements made, artificial intelligence is on the path forward to artificial general intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-sora-what-we-can-see-a-survey-of-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Large Language Models with Multilingualism: Recent Advances and New Frontiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-large-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we provide a survey with multiple perspectives on the utilization of LLMs in the multilingual scenario.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-large-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackbox Adaptation for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blackbox-adaptation-for-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There have been some attempts in the literature to perform parameter-efficient finetuning of such foundation models for medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blackbox-adaptation-for-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Data Consistency: a Fast and Robust Diffusion Model-based Solver for Inverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-data-consistency-a-fast-and-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the challenges, we propose Deep Data Consistency (DDC) to update the data consistency step with a deep learning model when solving inverse problems with diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-data-consistency-a-fast-and-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature-Adaptive and Data-Scalable In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-adaptive-and-data-scalable-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a feature-adaptive and data-scalable in-context learning framework (FADS-ICL), which can leverage task-adaptive features to promote inference on the downstream task, with the supervision of beyond-context samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-adaptive-and-data-scalable-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What should be observed for optimal reward in POMDPs?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-should-be-observed-for-optimal-reward-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This raises the question of how one should select an agent's sensors cost-effectively such that it achieves the desired goals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-should-be-observed-for-optimal-reward-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not All Prompts Are Secure: A Switchable Backdoor Attack Against Pre-trained Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-prompts-are-secure-a-switchable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experiments on diverse visual recognition tasks confirm the success of our switchable backdoor attack, i. e., achieving 95%+ attack success rate, and also being hard to be detected and removed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-prompts-are-secure-a-switchable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic data sampler for cross-language transfer learning in large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-data-sampler-for-cross-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have gained significant attention in the field of natural language processing (NLP) due to their wide range of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-data-sampler-for-cross-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Expert System: Large Language Models as Text Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-expert-system-large-language-models-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text classification is a fundamental task in Natural Language Processing (NLP), and the advent of Large Language Models (LLMs) has revolutionized the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-expert-system-large-language-models-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Large Language Models on CFLUE -- A Chinese Financial Language Understanding Evaluation Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-language-models-on-cflue-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The datasets and scripts associated with CFLUE are openly accessible at https://github. com/aliyun/cflue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-language-models-on-cflue-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Training Data for Occupancy Map Prediction in Automated Driving Using Evidence Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-training-data-for-occupancy-map</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When converting the occupancy maps back to depth estimates and comparing them with the raw LiDAR measurements, our method yields a MAE improvement of 30% to 52% on nuScenes and 53% on Waymo over other occupancy ground-truth data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-training-data-for-occupancy-map</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepPavlov at SemEval-2024 Task 8: Leveraging Transfer Learning for Detecting Boundaries of Machine-Generated Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deeppavlov-at-semeval-2024-task-8-leveraging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Multigenerator, Multidomain, and Multilingual Black-Box Machine-Generated Text Detection shared task in the SemEval-2024 competition aims to tackle the problem of misusing collaborative human-AI writing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deeppavlov-at-semeval-2024-task-8-leveraging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hi-GMAE: Hierarchical Graph Masked Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hi-gmae-hierarchical-graph-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To ensure masking uniformity of subgraphs across these scales, we propose a novel coarse-to-fine strategy that initiates masking at the coarsest scale and progressively back-projects the mask to the finer scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hi-gmae-hierarchical-graph-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOR: A Comprehensive and Practical Evaluation Method for Compositional Generalization in Data-to-Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spor-a-comprehensive-and-practical-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work shows the necessity for comprehensive research on different manifestations of compositional generalization in data-to-text generation and provides a framework for evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spor-a-comprehensive-and-practical-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis, Modeling and Design of Personalized Digital Learning Environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-modeling-and-design-of-personalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We seek ways to establish a foundation for the seamless integration of FL into learning systems, offering a transformative approach to personalized learning in digital environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-modeling-and-design-of-personalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Multimodal Large Language Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multimodal-large-language-models-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the past year, Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) have demonstrated remarkable performance in tasks such as visual question answering, visual understanding and reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multimodal-large-language-models-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reduced storage direct tensor ring decomposition for convolutional neural networks compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduced-storage-direct-tensor-ring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experiments, performed on the CIFAR-10 and ImageNet datasets, clearly demonstrate the efficiency of RSDTR in comparison to other state-of-the-art CNNs compression approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduced-storage-direct-tensor-ring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tailoring Vaccine Messaging with Common-Ground Opinions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-vaccine-messaging-with-common</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We define the task of tailoring vaccine interventions to a Common-Ground Opinion (CGO).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-vaccine-messaging-with-common</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models can Evaluate Themselves via Probability Discrepancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-can-evaluate-themselves-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we initiate our discussion by demonstrating how Large Language Models (LLMs), when tasked with responding to queries, display a more even probability distribution in their answers if they are more adept, as opposed to their less skilled counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-can-evaluate-themselves-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Aggregation of Prediction Intervals under Unsupervised Domain Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-aggregation-of-prediction-intervals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose methodologies for aggregating prediction intervals to obtain one with minimal width and adequate coverage on the target domain under unsupervised domain shift, under which we have labeled samples from a related source domain and unlabeled covariates from the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-aggregation-of-prediction-intervals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffAM: Diffusion-based Adversarial Makeup Transfer for Facial Privacy Protection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffam-diffusion-based-adversarial-makeup</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel face protection approach, dubbed DiffAM, which leverages the powerful generative ability of diffusion models to generate high-quality protected face images with adversarial makeup transferred from reference images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffam-diffusion-based-adversarial-makeup</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LFED: A Literary Fiction Evaluation Dataset for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lfed-a-literary-fiction-evaluation-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid evolution of large language models (LLMs) has ushered in the need for comprehensive assessments of their performance across various dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lfed-a-literary-fiction-evaluation-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Algorithmic Bias in Models for Predicting Academic Performance of Filipino Students</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-algorithmic-bias-in-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The best-performing model reached AUC of 0. 75 and weighted F1-score of 0. 79.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-algorithmic-bias-in-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Federated Learning via Informed Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-federated-learning-via-informed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, its application on edge devices is hindered by limited computational capabilities and data communication challenges, compounded by the inherent complexity of Deep Learning (DL) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-federated-learning-via-informed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIR: Remote Sensing Image-Text Retrieval with Prior Instruction Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pir-remote-sensing-image-text-retrieval-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continuing with the above, we propose PIR-CLIP, a domain-specific CLIP-based framework for remote sensing image-text retrieval, to address semantic noise in remote sensing vision-language representations and further improve open-domain retrieval performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pir-remote-sensing-image-text-retrieval-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Size-invariance Matters: Rethinking Metrics and Losses for Imbalanced Multi-object Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/size-invariance-matters-rethinking-metrics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the size-invariance of evaluation metrics in Salient Object Detection (SOD), especially when multiple targets of diverse sizes co-exist in the same image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/size-invariance-matters-rethinking-metrics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CatCMA : Stochastic Optimization for Mixed-Category Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/catcma-stochastic-optimization-for-mixed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CatCMA updates the parameters of the joint probability distribution in the natural gradient direction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/catcma-stochastic-optimization-for-mixed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whole-Song Hierarchical Generation of Symbolic Music Using Cascaded Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whole-song-hierarchical-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A cascaded diffusion model is trained to model the hierarchical language, where each level is conditioned on its upper levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whole-song-hierarchical-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Deep Audio-Text Retrieval Through the Lens of Transportation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-deep-audio-text-retrieval-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Learning-to-match (LTM) framework proves to be an effective inverse optimal transport approach for learning the underlying ground metric between two sources of data, facilitating subsequent matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-deep-audio-text-retrieval-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Vision Transformers for Quark-Gluon Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-vision-transformers-for-quark-gluon</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a hybrid quantum-classical vision transformer architecture, notable for its integration of variational quantum circuits within both the attention mechanism and the multi-layer perceptrons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-vision-transformers-for-quark-gluon</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMLP: Symbolic Machine Learning Prover (User Manual)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smlp-symbolic-machine-learning-prover-user</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SMLP: Symbolic Machine Learning Prover an open source tool for exploration and optimization of systems represented by machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smlp-symbolic-machine-learning-prover-user</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iDRAMA-Scored-2024: A Dataset of the Scored Social Media Platform from 2020 to 2023</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idrama-scored-2024-a-dataset-of-the-scored</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online web communities often face bans for violating platform policies, encouraging their migration to alternative platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idrama-scored-2024-a-dataset-of-the-scored</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MarkLLM: An Open-Source Toolkit for LLM Watermarking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/markllm-an-open-source-toolkit-for-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the abundance of LLM watermarking algorithms, their intricate mechanisms, and the complex evaluation procedures and perspectives pose challenges for researchers and the community to easily experiment with, understand, and assess the latest advancements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/markllm-an-open-source-toolkit-for-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many-Shot In-Context Learning in Multimodal Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/many-shot-in-context-learning-in-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that batching up to 50 queries can lead to performance improvements under zero-shot and many-shot ICL, with substantial gains in the zero-shot setting on multiple datasets, while drastically reducing per-query cost and latency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/many-shot-in-context-learning-in-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Learning with Fully Bayesian Neural Networks for Discontinuous and Nonstationary Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-with-fully-bayesian-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we assess the suitability and performance of FBNNs with the No-U-Turn Sampler for active learning tasks in the 'small data' regime, highlighting their potential to enhance predictive accuracy and reliability on test functions relevant to problems in physical sciences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-with-fully-bayesian-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Gesticulator: Semantics-Aware Co-Speech Gesture Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-gesticulator-semantics-aware-co</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Semantic Gesticulator, a novel framework designed to synthesize realistic gestures accompanying speech with strong semantic correspondence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-gesticulator-semantics-aware-co</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grounding DINO 1.5: Advance the "Edge" of Open-Set Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-dino-1-5-advance-the-edge-of-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirical results demonstrate the effectiveness of Grounding DINO 1. 5, with the Grounding DINO 1. 5 Pro model attaining a 54. 3 AP on the COCO detection benchmark and a 55. 7 AP on the LVIS-minival zero-shot transfer benchmark, setting new records for open-set object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-dino-1-5-advance-the-edge-of-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influence Maximization in Hypergraphs using Multi-Objective Evolutionary Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/influence-maximization-in-hypergraphs-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Among the various methods for solving the IM problem, evolutionary algorithms (EAs) have been shown to be particularly effective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/influence-maximization-in-hypergraphs-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-Oriented Semantic Latent Representation for Image Transmission</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-oriented-semantic-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the new paradigm of semantic communication (SC), the focus is on delivering meanings behind bits by extracting semantic information from raw data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-oriented-semantic-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bilateral Event Mining and Complementary for Event Stream Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilateral-event-mining-and-complementary-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a bilateral event mining and complementary network (BMCNet) to fully leverage the potential of each event and capture the shared information to complement each other simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilateral-event-mining-and-complementary-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
