<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:13:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Constant in HATE: Analyzing Toxicity in Reddit across Topics and Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-constant-in-hate-analyzing-toxicity-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Toxic language remains an ongoing challenge on social media platforms, presenting significant issues for users and communities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-constant-in-hate-analyzing-toxicity-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Semantic Change through Lexical Replacements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-semantic-change-through-lexical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we leverage the replacement schema as a basis for a novel \textit{interpretable} model for semantic change.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-semantic-change-through-lexical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficiency-Effectiveness Tradeoff of Probabilistic Structured Queries for Cross-Language Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiency-effectiveness-tradeoff-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Probabilistic Structured Queries (PSQ) is a cross-language information retrieval (CLIR) method that uses translation probabilities statistically derived from aligned corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiency-effectiveness-tradeoff-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More RLHF, More Trust? On The Impact of Human Preference Alignment On Language Model Trustworthiness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-rlhf-more-trust-on-the-impact-of-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The surge in Large Language Models (LLMs) development has led to improved performance on cognitive tasks as well as an urgent need to align these models with human values in order to safely exploit their power.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-rlhf-more-trust-on-the-impact-of-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Inverted Indexes for Approximate Retrieval over Learned Sparse Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-inverted-indexes-for-approximate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel organization of the inverted index that enables fast yet effective approximate retrieval over learned sparse embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-inverted-indexes-for-approximate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSCaMa: Remote Sensing Image Change Captioning with State Space Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rscama-remote-sensing-image-change-captioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results validate the effectiveness of CaMa layers and demonstrate the superior performance of RSCaMa, as well as the potential of Mamba in the RSICC task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rscama-remote-sensing-image-change-captioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Boundary Segmentation for Topological Accuracy with Skeleton-based Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-boundary-segmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topological consistency plays a crucial role in the task of boundary segmentation for reticular images, such as cell membrane segmentation in neuron electron microscopic images, grain boundary segmentation in material microscopic images and road segmentation in aerial images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-boundary-segmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIDBench: A Python Framework for Reliably Assessing Synthetic Image Detection Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sidbench-a-python-framework-for-reliably</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The generative AI technology offers an increasing variety of tools for generating entirely synthetic images that are increasingly indistinguishable from real ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sidbench-a-python-framework-for-reliably</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3AM: An Ambiguity-Aware Multi-Modal Machine Translation Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3am-an-ambiguity-aware-multi-modal-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results show that MMT models trained on our dataset exhibit a greater ability to exploit visual information than those trained on other MMT datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3am-an-ambiguity-aware-multi-modal-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BMRetriever: Tuning Large Language Models as Better Biomedical Text Retrievers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bmretriever-tuning-large-language-models-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Developing effective biomedical retrieval models is important for excelling at knowledge-intensive biomedical tasks but still challenging due to the deficiency of sufficient publicly annotated biomedical data and computational resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bmretriever-tuning-large-language-models-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Benchmark Leakage in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-benchmark-leakage-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By analyzing 31 LLMs under the context of mathematical reasoning, we reveal substantial instances of training even test set misuse, resulting in potentially unfair comparisons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-benchmark-leakage-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-boosted Robust Video Activity Anticipation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-boosted-robust-video-activity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video activity anticipation aims to predict what will happen in the future, embracing a broad application prospect ranging from robot vision and autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-boosted-robust-video-activity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Line Combination Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-line-combination-detector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A novel algorithm, called semantic line combination detector (SLCD), to find an optimal combination of semantic lines is proposed in this paper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-line-combination-detector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going Beyond Popularity and Positivity Bias: Correcting for Multifactorial Bias in Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/going-beyond-popularity-and-positivity-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Debiasing methods aim to mitigate the effect of selection bias on the evaluation and optimization of RSs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/going-beyond-popularity-and-positivity-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlexiFilm: Long Video Generation with Flexible Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexifilm-long-video-generation-with-flexible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating long and consistent videos has emerged as a significant yet challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexifilm-long-video-generation-with-flexible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptReps: Prompting Large Language Models to Generate Dense and Sparse Representations for Zero-Shot Document Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptreps-prompting-large-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The current use of large language models (LLMs) for zero-shot document ranking follows one of two ways: 1) prompt-based re-ranking methods, which require no further training but are feasible for only re-ranking a handful of candidate documents due to the associated computational costs; and 2) unsupervised contrastive trained dense retrieval methods, which can retrieve relevant documents from the entire corpus but require a large amount of paired text data for contrastive training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptreps-prompting-large-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised learning for classifying paranasal anomalies in the maxillary sinus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-for-classifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lastly, we fine-tune the encoder part of the 3D CNN on a labelled dataset of normal and anomalous MS images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-for-classifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Systematic Evaluation of Adversarial Attacks against Speech Emotion Recognition Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-evaluation-of-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In summary, this work contributes to the understanding of the robustness of CNN-LSTM models, particularly in SER scenarios, and the impact of AEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-evaluation-of-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M3oE: Multi-Domain Multi-Task Mixture-of Experts Recommendation Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3oe-multi-domain-multi-task-mixture-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[M3oE integrates multi-domain information, maps knowledge across domains and tasks, and optimizes multiple objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3oe-multi-domain-multi-task-mixture-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-hoc and manifold explanations analysis of facial expression data based on deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-hoc-and-manifold-explanations-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study not only advances the application of AI technology in the field of psychology but also provides a new psychological theoretical understanding the information processing of the AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-hoc-and-manifold-explanations-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hallucination of Multimodal Large Language Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallucination-of-multimodal-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By drawing the granular classification and landscapes of hallucination causes, evaluation benchmarks, and mitigation methods, this survey aims to deepen the understanding of hallucinations in MLLMs and inspire further advancements in the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallucination-of-multimodal-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-SR: Scientific Equation Discovery via Programming with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-sr-scientific-equation-discovery-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mathematical equations have been unreasonably effective in describing complex natural phenomena across various scientific disciplines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-sr-scientific-equation-discovery-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenStreetView-5M: The Many Roads to Global Visual Geolocation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openstreetview-5m-the-many-roads-to-global</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Determining the location of an image anywhere on Earth is a complex visual task, which makes it particularly relevant for evaluating computer vision algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openstreetview-5m-the-many-roads-to-global</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Vision Mamba: Models, Applications and Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-vision-mamba-models-applications</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To help keep pace with the rapid advancements in computer vision, this paper aims to provide a comprehensive review of visual Mamba approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-vision-mamba-models-applications</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Safety Misbehaviours in Autonomous Driving Systems using Uncertainty Quantification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-safety-misbehaviours-in-autonomous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The automated real-time recognition of unexpected situations plays a crucial role in the safety of autonomous vehicles, especially in unsupported and unpredictable scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-safety-misbehaviours-in-autonomous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-in-the-Loop Synthetic Text Data Inspection with Provenance Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-in-the-loop-synthetic-text-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[INSPECTOR allows users to group related texts by their transformation provenance, i. e., the transformations applied to the original text, or feature provenance, the linguistic features of the original text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-in-the-loop-synthetic-text-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PECC: Problem Extraction and Coding Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pecc-problem-extraction-and-coding-challenges</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) have showcased their exceptional abilities across various tasks, such as code generation, problem-solving and reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pecc-problem-extraction-and-coding-challenges</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WorldGPT: Empowering LLM as Multimodal World Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/worldgpt-empowering-llm-as-multimodal-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As for evaluation, we build WorldNet, a multimodal state transition prediction benchmark encompassing varied real-life scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/worldgpt-empowering-llm-as-multimodal-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Boosting Learning: A Brand-new Cooperative Approach for Image-Text Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-boosting-learning-a-brand-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a brand-new Deep Boosting Learning (DBL) algorithm, where an anchor branch is first trained to provide insights into the data properties, with a target branch gaining more advanced knowledge to develop optimal features and distance metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-boosting-learning-a-brand-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake with Shifted Window: Learning to Adapt Vessel Pattern for OCTA Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snake-with-shifted-window-learning-to-adapt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we thus study how to use OCTA images with projection vascular layers to segment retinal structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snake-with-shifted-window-learning-to-adapt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ComposerX: Multi-Agent Symbolic Music Composition with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composerx-multi-agent-symbolic-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Music composition represents the creative side of humanity, and itself is a complex task that requires abilities to understand and generate information with long dependency and harmony constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composerx-multi-agent-symbolic-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing Image Quality Using a Simple Generative Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-image-quality-using-a-simple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Perceptual image quality assessment (IQA) is the task of predicting the visual quality of an image as perceived by a human observer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-image-quality-using-a-simple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Robustness of In-Context Learning with Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-robustness-of-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, inspired by prior research that studies ICL ability using simple function classes, we take a closer look at this problem by investigating the robustness of Transformers against noisy labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-robustness-of-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUL: Unlocking the Power of Second-Order Optimization for LLM Unlearning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soul-unlocking-the-power-of-second-order</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have highlighted the necessity of effective unlearning mechanisms to comply with data regulations and ethical AI practices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soul-unlocking-the-power-of-second-order</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4DBInfer: A 4D Benchmarking Toolbox for Graph-Centric Predictive Modeling on Relational DBs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4dbinfer-a-4d-benchmarking-toolbox-for-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although RDBs store vast amounts of rich, informative data spread across interconnected tables, the progress of predictive machine learning models as applied to such tasks arguably falls well behind advances in other domains such as computer vision or natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4dbinfer-a-4d-benchmarking-toolbox-for-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Customization for Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-customization-for-continual-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to conventional methods that employ hard prompt selection, PGM assigns different coefficients to prompts from a fixed-sized pool of prompts and generates tailored prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-customization-for-continual-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMEX-Reg: Implicit-Explicit Regularization in the Function Space for Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imex-reg-implicit-explicit-regularization-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further leverage the global relationship between representations learned using CRL, we propose a regularization strategy to guide the classifier toward the activation correlations in the unit hypersphere of the CRL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imex-reg-implicit-explicit-regularization-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAFE-RL: Saliency-Aware Counterfactual Explainer for Deep Reinforcement Learning Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-rl-saliency-aware-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate the effectiveness of our framework in diverse domains, including ADS, Atari Pong, Pacman and space-invaders games, using traditional performance metrics such as validity, proximity and sparsity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-rl-saliency-aware-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L3Cube-MahaNews: News-based Short Text and Long Document Classification Datasets in Marathi</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l3cube-mahanews-news-based-short-text-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct a comparative analysis between monolingual and multilingual BERT models, including MahaBERT, IndicBERT, and MuRIL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l3cube-mahanews-news-based-short-text-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Supervised Learning with the Wave Loss Function: A Robust and Smooth Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-supervised-learning-with-the-wave</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To empirically showcase the effectiveness of the proposed Wave-SVM and Wave-TSVM, we evaluate them on benchmark UCI and KEEL datasets (with and without feature noise) from diverse domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-supervised-learning-with-the-wave</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mamba-FETrack: Frame-Event Tracking via State Space Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-fetrack-frame-event-tracking-via-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our Mamba-based tracker achieves 43. 5/55. 6 on the SR/PR metric, while the ViT-S based tracker (OSTrack) obtains 40. 0/50. 9.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-fetrack-frame-event-tracking-via-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Remote Sensing with Harmonized Transfer Learning and Modality Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-remote-sensing-with-harmonized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope this method can facilitate the efficient application of large models to a wide range of downstream tasks while significantly reducing the resource consumption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-remote-sensing-with-harmonized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ranked List Truncation for Large Language Model-based Re-Ranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ranked-list-truncation-for-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RLT is crucial for re-ranking as it can improve re-ranking efficiency by sending variable-length candidate lists to a re-ranker on a per-query basis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ranked-list-truncation-for-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBMAP: Clustering-based manifold approximation and projection for dimensionality reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbmap-clustering-based-manifold-approximation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dimensionality reduction methods are employed to decrease data dimensionality, either to enhance machine learning performance or to facilitate data visualization in two or three-dimensional spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbmap-clustering-based-manifold-approximation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Stream Cellular Test-Time Adaptation of Real-Time Models Evolving in Dynamic Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stream-cellular-test-time-adaptation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the era of the Internet of Things (IoT), objects connect through a dynamic network, empowered by technologies like 5G, enabling real-time data sharing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stream-cellular-test-time-adaptation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Random Walk on Pixel Manifolds for Anomaly Segmentation of Complex Driving Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-walk-on-pixel-manifolds-for-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In anomaly segmentation for complex driving scenes, state-of-the-art approaches utilize anomaly scoring functions to calculate anomaly scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-walk-on-pixel-manifolds-for-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Cross-Modal Neighbor Representation for Improved CLIP Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-cross-modal-neighbor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite this, some studies have directly used CLIP's image encoder for tasks like few-shot classification, introducing a misalignment between its pre-training objectives and feature extraction methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-cross-modal-neighbor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLFT: Camera-LiDAR Fusion Transformer for Semantic Segmentation in Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clft-camera-lidar-fusion-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposal uses the novel progressive-assemble strategy of vision transformers on a double-direction network and then integrates the results in a cross-fusion strategy over the transformer decoder layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clft-camera-lidar-fusion-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Watermarks Bugs for Deepfake Detectors? Rethinking Proactive Forensics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-watermarks-bugs-for-deepfake-detectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AI-generated content has accelerated the topic of media synthesis, particularly Deepfake, which can manipulate our portraits for positive or malicious purposes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-watermarks-bugs-for-deepfake-detectors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bounding the Expected Robustness of Graph Neural Networks Subject to Node Feature Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bounding-the-expected-robustness-of-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we theoretically define the concept of expected robustness in the context of attributed graphs and relate it to the classical definition of adversarial robustness in the graph representation learning literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bounding-the-expected-robustness-of-graph</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
