<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 09:14:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Reasoning in Object-Centric Deep Neural Networks: A Comparative Cognition Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-reasoning-in-object-centric-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, these models use several kinds of attention mechanisms to segregate the individual objects in a scene from the background and from other objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-reasoning-in-object-centric-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TorchCP: A Library for Conformal Prediction based on PyTorch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchcp-a-library-for-conformal-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TorchCP is a Python toolbox for conformal prediction research on deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchcp-a-library-for-conformal-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-stage Rainfall-Forecasting Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stage-rainfall-forecasting-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of the second stage is to reconstruct the low-resolution images generated in the first stage into high-resolution images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stage-rainfall-forecasting-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TofuEval: Evaluating Hallucinations of LLMs on Topic-Focused Dialogue Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tofueval-evaluating-hallucinations-of-llms-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that there are diverse errors and error distributions in model-generated summaries and that non-LLM based metrics can capture all error types better than LLM-based evaluators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tofueval-evaluating-hallucinations-of-llms-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAP: Targeted Random Adversarial Prompt Honeypot for Black-Box Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trap-targeted-random-adversarial-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Model (LLM) services and models often come with legal rules on who can use them and how they must use them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trap-targeted-random-adversarial-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Network Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The autoencoder extracts latent representations of a subset of the trained network parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SiLLM: Large Language Models for Simultaneous Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sillm-large-language-models-for-simultaneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose SiLLM, which delegates the two sub-tasks to separate agents, thereby incorporating LLM into SiMT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sillm-large-language-models-for-simultaneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoCode: A Dataset for Measuring Code Intelligence from Problem Definitions in Romanian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rocode-a-dataset-for-measuring-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, large language models (LLMs) have become increasingly powerful and have become capable of solving a plethora of tasks through proper instructions in natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rocode-a-dataset-for-measuring-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ArabicMMLU: Assessing Massive Multitask Language Understanding in Arabic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arabicmmlu-assessing-massive-multitask</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The focus of language model evaluation has transitioned towards reasoning and knowledge-intensive tasks, driven by advancements in pretraining large models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arabicmmlu-assessing-massive-multitask</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Check: Unleashing Potentials for Self-Correction in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-check-unleashing-potentials-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After integrating the original CoT data and checking-correction data for training, we observe that models could improve their self-checking capabilities, thereby enhancing their self-correction capacity and eliminating the need for external feedback or ground truth labels to ascertain the endpoint of correction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-check-unleashing-potentials-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Robustness for Joint Optimization of Camera Poses and Decomposed Low-Rank Tensorial Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-robustness-for-joint-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an algorithm that allows joint refinement of camera pose and scene geometry represented by decomposed low-rank tensor, using only 2D images as supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-robustness-for-joint-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE-3S:Multimodal-based Offline Reinforcement Learning with Shared Semantic Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-3s-multimodal-based-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Drawing upon the intuition that aligning different modalities to the same semantic embedding space would allow models to understand states and actions more easily, we propose a new perspective to the offline reinforcement learning (RL) challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-3s-multimodal-based-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreeEval: Benchmark-Free Evaluation of Large Language Models through Tree Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treeeval-benchmark-free-evaluation-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, numerous new benchmarks have been established to evaluate the performance of large language models (LLMs) via either computing a holistic score or employing another LLM as a judge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treeeval-benchmark-free-evaluation-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Worst-case Attacks: Robust RL with Adaptive Defense via Non-dominated Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-worst-case-attacks-robust-rl-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In light of the burgeoning success of reinforcement learning (RL) in diverse real-world applications, considerable focus has been directed towards ensuring RL policies are robust to adversarial attacks during test time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-worst-case-attacks-robust-rl-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guarantee Regions for Local Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guarantee-regions-for-local-explanations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interpretability methods that utilise local surrogate models (e. g. LIME) are very good at describing the behaviour of the predictive model at a point of interest, but they are not guaranteed to extrapolate to the local region surrounding the point.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guarantee-regions-for-local-explanations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAFFORD: A Benchmark Dataset for Testing the Knowledge of Object Affordances of Language and Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grafford-a-benchmark-dataset-for-testing-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the knowledge of object affordances in pre-trained language models (LMs) and pre-trained Vision-Language models (VLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grafford-a-benchmark-dataset-for-testing-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Reinforcement Learning for Quadruped Locomotion using Decision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiny-reinforcement-learning-for-quadruped</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that quantization (down to 4 bits) and pruning reduce model size by around 30\% while maintaining a competitive reward, making the model deployable in a resource-constrained system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiny-reinforcement-learning-for-quadruped</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Knowledge Distillation of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-knowledge-distillation-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This survey presents an in-depth exploration of knowledge distillation (KD) techniques within the realm of Large Language Models (LLMs), spotlighting the pivotal role of KD in transferring sophisticated capabilities from proprietary giants such as GPT-4 to accessible, open-source models like LLaMA and Mistral.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-knowledge-distillation-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model-based Human-Agent Collaboration for Complex Task Solving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-based-human-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We construct a human-agent collaboration dataset to train this policy model in an offline reinforcement learning environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-based-human-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A User-Friendly Framework for Generating Model-Preferred Prompts in Text-to-Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-user-friendly-framework-for-generating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge the distribution gap between user input behavior and model training datasets, we first construct a novel Coarse-Fine Granularity Prompts dataset (CFP) and propose a novel User-Friendly Fine-Grained Text Generation framework (UF-FGTG) for automated prompt optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-user-friendly-framework-for-generating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soft Self-Consistency Improves Language Model Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soft-self-consistency-improves-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current "sample and select" methods such as self-consistency (SC) rely on majority voting to score answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soft-self-consistency-improves-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Discriminative Sentence Embeddings via Semantic Graph Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-discriminative-sentence-embeddings-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores an empirical approach to learn more discriminantive sentence representations in an unsupervised fashion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-discriminative-sentence-embeddings-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing Calibration in Subquadratic Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testing-calibration-in-subquadratic-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by [BGHN23], which proposed a rigorous framework for measuring distances to calibration, we initiate the algorithmic study of calibration through the lens of property testing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testing-calibration-in-subquadratic-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Causal Discovery from Heterogeneous Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-causal-discovery-from-heterogeneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This discrepancy has motivated the development of federated causal discovery (FCD) approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-causal-discovery-from-heterogeneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cell Graph Transformer for Nuclei Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cell-graph-transformer-for-nuclei</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nuclei classification is a critical step in computer-aided diagnosis with histopathology images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cell-graph-transformer-for-nuclei</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>exploreCOSMOS: Interactive Exploration of Conditional Statistical Shape Models in the Web-Browser</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explorecosmos-interactive-exploration-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Statistical Shape Models of faces and various body parts are heavily used in medical image analysis, computer vision and visualization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explorecosmos-interactive-exploration-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind the Exit Pupil Gap: Revisiting the Intrinsics of a Standard Plenoptic Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-the-exit-pupil-gap-revisiting-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work addresses the often-overlooked role of the main lens exit pupil in these models and specifically in the decoding process of standard plenoptic camera (SPC) images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-the-exit-pupil-gap-revisiting-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniCell: Universal Cell Nucleus Classification via Prompt Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unicell-universal-cell-nucleus-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recognition of multi-class cell nuclei can significantly facilitate the process of histopathological diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unicell-universal-cell-nucleus-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FormulaQA: A Question Answering Dataset for Formula-Based Numerical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/formulaqa-a-question-answering-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The application of formulas is a fundamental ability of humans when addressing numerical reasoning problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/formulaqa-a-question-answering-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Graph Reasoning for Fact Checking over Texts and Tables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-reasoning-for-fact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose a novel word-level Heterogeneous-graph-based model for Fact Checking over unstructured and structured information, namely HeterFC.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-reasoning-for-fact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLO-Ant: A Lightweight Detector via Depthwise Separable Convolutional and Large Kernel Design for Antenna Interference Source Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo-ant-a-lightweight-detector-via-depthwise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, an antenna dataset is created to address important antenna interference source detection issues and serves as the basis for subsequent research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo-ant-a-lightweight-detector-via-depthwise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhythmFormer: Extracting rPPG Signals Based on Hierarchical Temporal Periodic Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rhythmformer-extracting-rppg-signals-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the periodicity nature of rPPG, the long-range dependency capturing capacity of the Transformer was assumed to be advantageous for such signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rhythmformer-extracting-rppg-signals-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Mapper For Topological Optimization Of Data Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-mapper-for-topological</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While highly generic and applicable, its use has been hampered so far by the manual tuning of its many parameters-among these, a crucial one is the so-called filter: it is a continuous function whose variations on the data set are the main ingredient for both building the Mapper representation and assessing the presence and sizes of its topological structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-mapper-for-topological</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event-level Knowledge Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-level-knowledge-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, natural knowledge updates in the real world come from the occurrences of new events rather than direct changes in factual triplets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-level-knowledge-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperMoE: Towards Better Mixture of Experts via Transferring Among Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypermoe-towards-better-mixture-of-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Mixture of Experts (MoE) for language models has been proven effective in augmenting the capacity of models by dynamically routing each input token to a specific subset of experts for processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypermoe-towards-better-mixture-of-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Guided Molecule Generation with Diffusion Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-molecule-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose the Text-Guided Molecule Generation with Diffusion Language Model (TGM-DLM), a novel approach that leverages diffusion models to address the limitations of autoregressive methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-molecule-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Cultural Alignment of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-cultural-alignment-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The intricate relationship between language and culture has long been a subject of exploration within the realm of linguistic anthropology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-cultural-alignment-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICON: Improving Inter-Report Consistency of Radiology Report Generation via Lesion-aware Mix-up Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icon-improving-inter-report-consistency-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous research on radiology report generation has made significant progress in terms of increasing the clinical accuracy of generated reports.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icon-improving-inter-report-consistency-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RealCompo: Dynamic Equilibrium between Realism and Compositionality Improves Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realcompo-dynamic-equilibrium-between-realism</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new training-free and transferred-friendly text-to-image generation framework, namely RealCompo, which aims to leverage the advantages of text-to-image and layout-to-image models to enhance both realism and compositionality of the generated images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realcompo-dynamic-equilibrium-between-realism</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Softmax Probabilities (Mostly) Predict Large Language Model Correctness on Multiple-Choice Q&amp;A</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softmax-probabilities-mostly-predict-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although large language models (LLMs) perform impressively on many tasks, overconfidence remains a problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softmax-probabilities-mostly-predict-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHILI: Chemically-Informed Large-scale Inorganic Nanomaterials Dataset for Advancing Graph Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chili-chemically-informed-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We invite the graph ML community to address these open challenges by presenting two new chemically-informed large-scale inorganic (CHILI) nanomaterials datasets: A medium-scale dataset (with overall >6M nodes, >49M edges) of mono-metallic oxide nanomaterials generated from 12 selected crystal types (CHILI-3K) and a large-scale dataset (with overall >183M nodes, >1. 2B edges) of nanomaterials generated from experimentally determined crystal structures (CHILI-100K).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chili-chemically-informed-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improve Cross-Architecture Generalization on Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improve-cross-architecture-generalization-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dataset distillation, a pragmatic approach in machine learning, aims to create a smaller synthetic dataset from a larger existing dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improve-cross-architecture-generalization-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object-level Geometric Structure Preserving for Natural Image Stitching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-level-geometric-structure-preserving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current methodologies exhibit the ability to preserve local geometric structures, yet fall short in maintaining relationships between these geometric structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-level-geometric-structure-preserving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MuLan: Multimodal-LLM Agent for Progressive Multi-Object Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mulan-multimodal-llm-agent-for-progressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, MuLan adopts a vision-language model (VLM) to provide feedback to the image generated in each sub-task and control the diffusion model to re-generate the image if it violates the original prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mulan-multimodal-llm-agent-for-progressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Microstructure-based Graph Neural Network for Accelerating Multiscale Simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-microstructure-based-graph-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We achieve this for an elasto-plastic material by predicting full-field microscopic strains using a graph neural network (GNN) while retaining the microscopic constitutive material model to obtain the stresses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-microstructure-based-graph-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiMediX: Bilingual Medical Mixture of Experts LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bimedix-bilingual-medical-mixture-of-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce BiMediX, the first bilingual medical mixture of experts LLM designed for seamless interaction in both English and Arabic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bimedix-bilingual-medical-mixture-of-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical Kernel Tests of Conditional Independence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-kernel-tests-of-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe a data-efficient, kernel-based approach to statistical testing of conditional independence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-kernel-tests-of-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributionally Robust Graph-based Recommendation System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributionally-robust-graph-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DR-GNN addresses two core challenges: 1) To enable DRO to cater to graph data intertwined with GNN, we reinterpret GNN as a graph smoothing regularizer, thereby facilitating the nuanced application of DRO; 2) Given the typically sparse nature of recommendation data, which might impede robust optimization, we introduce slight perturbations in the training distribution to expand its support.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributionally-robust-graph-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuanTest: Entanglement-Guided Testing of Quantum Neural Network Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantest-entanglement-guided-testing-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, QuanTest formulates the problem of generating test inputs that maximize the quantum entanglement sufficiency and capture incorrect behaviors of the QNN system as a joint optimization problem and solves it in a gradient-based manner to generate quantum adversarial examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantest-entanglement-guided-testing-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Geometric Algorithm for Tubular Shape Reconstruction from Skeletal Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-geometric-algorithm-for-tubular-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel approach for the reconstruction of tubular shapes from skeletal representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-geometric-algorithm-for-tubular-shape</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
