<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 09:12:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ViLaM: A Vision-Language Model with Enhanced Visual Grounding and Generalization Capability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vilam-a-vision-language-model-with-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach enables us to optimally utilize the knowledge and reasoning capacities of large pre-trained language models for an array of tasks encompassing both language and vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vilam-a-vision-language-model-with-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>minimax: Efficient Baselines for Autocurricula in JAX</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimax-efficient-baselines-for-autocurricula</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This compute requirement is a major obstacle to rapid innovation for the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimax-efficient-baselines-for-autocurricula</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShareGPT4V: Improving Large Multi-Modal Models with Better Captions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharegpt4v-improving-large-multi-modal-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of large multi-modal models (LMMs), efficient modality alignment is crucial yet often constrained by the scarcity of high-quality image-text data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharegpt4v-improving-large-multi-modal-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LowResource at BLP-2023 Task 2: Leveraging BanglaBert for Low Resource Sentiment Analysis of Bangla Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lowresource-at-blp-2023-task-2-leveraging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes the system of the LowResource Team for Task 2 of BLP-2023, which involves conducting sentiment analysis on a dataset composed of public posts and comments from diverse social media platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lowresource-at-blp-2023-task-2-leveraging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Home Staging: Inverse Rendering and Editing an Indoor Panorama under Natural Illumination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virtual-home-staging-inverse-rendering-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel inverse rendering method that enables the transformation of existing indoor panoramas with new indoor furniture layouts under natural illumination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virtual-home-staging-inverse-rendering-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-resolution Image-based Malware Classification using Multiple Instance Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-image-based-malware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel method of classifying malware into families using high-resolution greyscale images and multiple instance learning to overcome adversarial binary enlargement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-image-based-malware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Audio-visual Zero-shot Learning with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-audio-visual-zero-shot-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Audio-visual zero-shot learning aims to recognize unseen categories based on paired audio-visual sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-audio-visual-zero-shot-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair Text Classification with Wasserstein Independence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-text-classification-with-wasserstein</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is more suitable for real-life scenarios compared to existing methods that require annotations of sensitive attributes at train time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-text-classification-with-wasserstein</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSVEP-DAN: A Data Alignment Network for SSVEP-based Brain Computer Interfaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssvep-dan-a-data-alignment-network-for-ssvep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Steady-state visual-evoked potential (SSVEP)-based brain-computer interfaces (BCIs) offer a non-invasive means of communication through high-speed speller systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssvep-dan-a-data-alignment-network-for-ssvep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming Pathology Image Data Deficiency: Generating Images from Pathological Transformation Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-pathology-image-data-deficiency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ADBD is effective for overcoming pathological image data deficiency and supportable for further pathology-related research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-pathology-image-data-deficiency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Transformer Architecture in Long-Context Large Language Models: A Comprehensive Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-transformer-architecture-in-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the bomb ignited by ChatGPT, Transformer-based Large Language Models (LLMs) have paved a revolutionary path toward Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) and have been applied in diverse areas as knowledge bases, human interfaces, and dynamic agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-transformer-architecture-in-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Time Granularity on Temporal Graphs for Dynamic Link Prediction in Real-world Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-time-granularity-on-temporal-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic Graph Neural Networks (DGNNs) have emerged as the predominant approach for processing dynamic graph-structured data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-time-granularity-on-temporal-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Multimodal Large Language Models for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-multimodal-large-language-models-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first introduce the background of Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs), the multimodal models development using LLMs, and the history of autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-multimodal-large-language-models-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Random Linear Projections Loss for Hyperplane-Based Optimization in Regression Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-linear-projections-loss-for-hyperplane</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their popularity across a wide range of domains, regression neural networks are prone to overfitting complex datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-linear-projections-loss-for-hyperplane</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SelfOcc: Self-Supervised Vision-Based 3D Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selfocc-self-supervised-vision-based-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our SelfOcc outperforms the previous best method SceneRF by 58. 7% using a single frame as input on SemanticKITTI and is the first self-supervised work that produces reasonable 3D occupancy for surround cameras on Occ3D.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selfocc-self-supervised-vision-based-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The limitation of neural nets for approximation and optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-limitation-of-neural-nets-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We are interested in assessing the use of neural networks as surrogate models to approximate and minimize objective functions in optimization problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-limitation-of-neural-nets-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine-Guided Discovery of a Real-World Rogue Wave Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-guided-discovery-of-a-real-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, it is still not clear how we can use the superior pattern matching abilities of machine learning models for scientific discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-guided-discovery-of-a-real-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orthogonally weighted $\ell_{2,1}$ regularization for rank-aware joint sparse recovery: algorithm and analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orthogonally-weighted-ell-21-regularization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose and analyze an efficient algorithm for solving the joint sparse recovery problem using a new regularization-based method, named orthogonally weighted $\ell_{2, 1}$ ($\mathit{ow}\ell_{2, 1}$), which is specifically designed to take into account the rank of the solution matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orthogonally-weighted-ell-21-regularization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Challenges in Video-Based Infant Action Recognition: A Critical Examination of the State of the Art</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenges-in-video-based-infant-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated human action recognition, a burgeoning field within computer vision, boasts diverse applications spanning surveillance, security, human-computer interaction, tele-health, and sports analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenges-in-video-based-infant-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSMeD: Bridging the Dataset Gap in Automated Citation Screening for Systematic Literature Reviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csmed-bridging-the-dataset-gap-in-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Systematic literature reviews (SLRs) play an essential role in summarising, synthesising and validating scientific evidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csmed-bridging-the-dataset-gap-in-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a more inductive world for drug repurposing approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-more-inductive-world-for-drug</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we first perform an in-depth evaluation of current DTI datasets and prediction models through a robust benchmarking process, and show that DTI prediction methods based on transductive models lack generalization and lead to inflated performance when evaluated as previously done in the literature, hence not being suited for drug repurposing approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-more-inductive-world-for-drug</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIP-RTVE: An Audiovisual Database for Continuous Spanish in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lip-rtve-an-audiovisual-database-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speech is considered as a multi-modal process where hearing and vision are two fundamentals pillars.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lip-rtve-an-audiovisual-database-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HierSpeech++: Bridging the Gap between Semantic and Acoustic Representation of Speech by Hierarchical Variational Inference for Zero-shot Speech Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierspeech-bridging-the-gap-between-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we significantly improve the naturalness and speaker similarity of synthetic speech even in zero-shot speech synthesis scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierspeech-bridging-the-gap-between-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning based on Decomposition: A taxonomy and framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-reinforcement-learning-based-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, a clear categorization based on both RL and MOO/D is lacking in the existing literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-reinforcement-learning-based-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content Augmented Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/content-augmented-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More precisely, we propose models wherein a structural embedding using a GNN and a content embedding are computed for each node.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/content-augmented-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Context Learning Functions with Varying Number of Minima</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-learning-functions-with-varying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our study, we use a formal framework to explore ICL and propose a new task of approximating functions with varying number of minima.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-learning-functions-with-varying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying Impairment and Disease Severity Using AI Models Trained on Healthy Subjects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-impairment-and-disease-severity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We applied the COBRA score to address a key limitation of current clinical evaluation of upper-body impairment in stroke patients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-impairment-and-disease-severity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Weight-Perturbed Deep Neural Networks With Application in Iris Presentation Attack Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-weight-perturbed-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we assess the sensitivity of DNNs against perturbations to their weight and bias parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-weight-perturbed-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lung cancer detection from thoracic CT scans using an ensemble of deep learning models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lung-cancer-detection-from-thoracic-ct-scans</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach leverages deep transfer learning and adopts an ensemble learning approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lung-cancer-detection-from-thoracic-ct-scans</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swift Parameter-free Attention Network for Efficient Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swift-parameter-free-attention-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose the Swift Parameter-free Attention Network (SPAN), a highly efficient SISR model that balances parameter count, inference speed, and image quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swift-parameter-free-attention-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mapping "Brain Coral" Regions on Mars using Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-brain-coral-regions-on-mars-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we use convolutional neural networks to detect surface regions containing "Brain Coral" terrain, a landform on Mars whose similarity in morphology and scale to sorted stone circles on Earth suggests that it may have formed as a consequence of freeze/thaw cycles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-brain-coral-regions-on-mars-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning via Consensus Mechanism on Heterogeneous Data: A New Perspective on Convergence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-via-consensus-mechanism-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We theoretically show that the consensus mechanism can guarantee the convergence of the global objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-via-consensus-mechanism-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"HoVer-UNet": Accelerating HoVerNet with UNet-based multi-class nuclei segmentation via knowledge distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hover-unet-accelerating-hovernet-with-unet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present "HoVer-UNet", an approach to distill the knowledge of the multi-branch HoVerNet framework for nuclei instance segmentation and classification in histopathology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hover-unet-accelerating-hovernet-with-unet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLAD: Global-Local View Alignment and Background Debiasing for Unsupervised Video Domain Adaptation with Large Domain Gap</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glad-global-local-view-alignment-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We specifically focus on scenarios with a substantial domain gap, in contrast to existing works primarily deal with small domain gaps between labeled source domains and unlabeled target domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glad-global-local-view-alignment-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEND: Benchmarking DNA Language Models on biologically meaningful tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bend-benchmarking-dna-language-models-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The genome sequence contains the blueprint for governing cellular processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bend-benchmarking-dna-language-models-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-aware Neural Machine Translation for English-Japanese Business Scene Dialogues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-neural-machine-translation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We make use of Conditional Cross-Mutual Information (CXMI) to explore how much of the context the model uses and generalise CXMI to study the impact of the extra-sentential context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-neural-machine-translation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can we infer the presence of Differential Privacy in Deep Learning models' weights? Towards more secure Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-infer-the-presence-of-differential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we face the challenge of determining whether a DL model has been trained with DP, according to the title question: Can we infer the presence of Differential Privacy in Deep Learning models' weights?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-infer-the-presence-of-differential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILA: Memory-Based Instance-Level Adaptation for Cross-Domain Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mila-memory-based-instance-level-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A source sample is considered suitable if it differs from the target sample only in domain, without differences in unimportant characteristics such as orientation and color, which can hinder the model’s focus on aligning the domain difference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mila-memory-based-instance-level-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Node classification in random trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/node-classification-in-random-trees</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our aim is to model a distribution over the node label assignments in settings where the tree data structure is associated with node attributes (typically high dimensional embeddings).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/node-classification-in-random-trees</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LogLead -- Fast and Integrated Log Loader, Enhancer, and Anomaly Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loglead-fast-and-integrated-log-loader</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The tool leverages Polars, a high-speed DataFrame library.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loglead-fast-and-integrated-log-loader</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiDAR-HMR: 3D Human Mesh Recovery from LiDAR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidar-hmr-3d-human-mesh-recovery-from-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, point cloud perception tasks have been garnering increasing attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidar-hmr-3d-human-mesh-recovery-from-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGCT: Mutual-Guided Cross-Modality Transformer for Survival Outcome Prediction using Integrative Histopathology-Genomic Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgct-mutual-guided-cross-modality-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapidly emerging field of deep learning-based computational pathology has shown promising results in utilizing whole slide images (WSIs) to objectively prognosticate cancer patients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgct-mutual-guided-cross-modality-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filling the Image Information Gap for VQA: Prompting Large Language Models to Proactively Ask Questions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filling-the-image-information-gap-for-vqa</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) demonstrate impressive reasoning ability and the maintenance of world knowledge not only in natural language tasks, but also in some vision-language tasks such as open-domain knowledge-based visual question answering (OK-VQA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filling-the-image-information-gap-for-vqa</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concept Sliders: LoRA Adaptors for Precise Control in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-sliders-lora-adaptors-for-precise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a method to create interpretable concept sliders that enable precise control over attributes in image generations from diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-sliders-lora-adaptors-for-precise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SA-Med2D-20M Dataset: Segment Anything in 2D Medical Imaging with 20 Million masks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-med2d-20m-dataset-segment-anything-in-2d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segment Anything Model (SAM) has achieved impressive results for natural image segmentation with input prompts such as points and bounding boxes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-med2d-20m-dataset-segment-anything-in-2d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Surface-to-Air Missile Engagement Zone Prediction Using Simulation and Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-surface-to-air-missile-engagement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Surface-to-Air Missiles (SAMs) are crucial in modern air defense systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-surface-to-air-missile-engagement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Structure Learning Supervised by Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-structure-learning-supervised-by-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal discovery from observational data is pivotal for deciphering complex relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-structure-learning-supervised-by-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChemScraper: Graphics Extraction, Molecular Diagram Parsing, and Annotated Data Generation for PDF Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chemscraper-graphics-extraction-molecular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing visual parsers for molecule diagrams translate pixel-based raster images such as PNGs to chemical structure representations (e. g., SMILES).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chemscraper-graphics-extraction-molecular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPQA: A Graduate-Level Google-Proof Q&amp;A Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpqa-a-graduate-level-google-proof-q-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present GPQA, a challenging dataset of 448 multiple-choice questions written by domain experts in biology, physics, and chemistry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpqa-a-graduate-level-google-proof-q-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Establishing Central Sensitization Inventory Cut-off Values in patients with Chronic Low Back Pain by Unsupervised Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/establishing-central-sensitization-inventory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Central Sensitization Inventory (CSI) was developed to evaluate the presence of HACS, with a cut-off value of 40/100 based on patients with chronic pain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/establishing-central-sensitization-inventory</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
