<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 21:07:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colour and Brush Stroke Pattern Recognition in Abstract Art using Modified Deep Convolutional Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colour-and-brush-stroke-pattern-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further this paper explores the generated latent space by performing random walks to understand vector relationships between brush strokes and colours in the abstract art space and a statistical analysis of unstable outputs after a certain period of GAN training and compare its significant difference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colour-and-brush-stroke-pattern-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Algorithms for Regularized Nonnegative Scale-invariant Low-rank Approximation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-algorithms-for-regularized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, from a practical perspective, the choice of regularizers and regularization coefficients, as well as the design of efficient algorithms, is challenging because of the multifactor nature of these models and the lack of theory to back these choices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-algorithms-for-regularized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoBOS: Constraint-Based Online Scheduler for Human-Robot Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cobos-constraint-based-online-scheduler-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The user will experience less stress as the robotic coworkers adapt their behavior to best complement the human-selected activities to complete the common task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cobos-constraint-based-online-scheduler-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-Informed Graph Neural Networks for Water Distribution Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-graph-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this realm, we propose a novel and efficient machine learning emulator, more precisely, a physics-informed deep learning (DL) model, for hydraulic state estimation in WDS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-graph-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Language Beat Numerical Regression? Language-Based Multimodal Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-language-beat-numerical-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, to guide the language model in understanding and reasoning high-level knowledge, such as scene context and social relationships between pedestrians, we introduce an auxiliary multi-task question and answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-language-beat-numerical-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ship in Sight: Diffusion Models for Ship-Image Super Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ship-in-sight-diffusion-models-for-ship-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this context, our method explores in depth the problem of ship image super resolution, which is crucial for coastal and port surveillance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ship-in-sight-diffusion-models-for-ship-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Optimizing Hyperparameters for Quantum Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-optimizing-hyperparameters-for-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing capabilities of Machine Learning (ML) models go hand in hand with an immense amount of data and computational power required for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-optimizing-hyperparameters-for-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Two-Dimensional to Three-Dimensional Environment with Q-Learning: Modeling Autonomous Navigation with Reinforcement Learning and no Libraries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-two-dimensional-to-three-dimensional-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study explores the performance of RL agents in both two-dimensional (2D) and three-dimensional (3D) environments, aiming to research the dynamics of learning across different spatial dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-two-dimensional-to-three-dimensional-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Medical Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-medical-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, GMS employs a robust pre-trained Variational Autoencoder (VAE) to derive latent representations of both images and masks, followed by a mapping model that learns the transition from image to mask in the latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-medical-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing the Potential of SAM for Medical Adaptation via Hierarchical Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-potential-of-sam-for-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces H-SAM: a prompt-free adaptation of SAM tailored for efficient fine-tuning of medical images via a two-stage hierarchical decoding procedure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-potential-of-sam-for-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>skscope: Fast Sparsity-Constrained Optimization in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skscope-fast-sparsity-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applying iterative solvers on sparsity-constrained optimization (SCO) requires tedious mathematical deduction and careful programming/debugging that hinders these solvers' broad impact.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skscope-fast-sparsity-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theoretical Bound-Guided Hierarchical VAE for Neural Image Codecs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theoretical-bound-guided-hierarchical-vae-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies reveal a significant theoretical link between variational autoencoders (VAEs) and rate-distortion theory, notably in utilizing VAEs to estimate the theoretical upper bound of the information rate-distortion function of images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theoretical-bound-guided-hierarchical-vae-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NL-ITI: Optimizing Probing and Intervention for Improvement of ITI Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nl-iti-optimizing-probing-and-intervention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLM) are prone to returning false information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nl-iti-optimizing-probing-and-intervention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object Pose Estimation via the Aggregation of Diffusion Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-pose-estimation-via-the-aggregation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this, we propose three distinct architectures that can effectively capture and aggregate diffusion features of different granularity, greatly improving the generalizability of object pose estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-pose-estimation-via-the-aggregation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Image Grid Can Be Worth a Video: Zero-shot Video Question Answering Using a VLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-image-grid-can-be-worth-a-video-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, an alternative strategy has surfaced, employing readily available foundation models, such as VideoLMs and LLMs, across multiple stages for modality bridging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-image-grid-can-be-worth-a-video-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CYCLE: Learning to Self-Refine the Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cycle-learning-to-self-refine-the-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained code language models have achieved promising performance in code generation and improved the programming efficiency of human developers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cycle-learning-to-self-refine-the-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SingularTrajectory: Universal Trajectory Predictor Using Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/singulartrajectory-universal-trajectory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose SingularTrajectory, a diffusion-based universal trajectory prediction framework to reduce the performance gap across the five tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/singulartrajectory-universal-trajectory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlendX: Complex Multi-Intent Detection with Blended Patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blendx-complex-multi-intent-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Task-oriented dialogue (TOD) systems are commonly designed with the presumption that each utterance represents a single intent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blendx-complex-multi-intent-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identification and Uses of Deep Learning Backbones via Pattern Mining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identification-and-uses-of-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we explore the notion of identifying a backbone of deep learning for a given group of instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identification-and-uses-of-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fact Checking Beyond Training Set</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fact-checking-beyond-training-set</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then focus on the reader component and propose to train it such that it is insensitive towards the order of claims and evidence documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fact-checking-beyond-training-set</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models Need Consultants for Reasoning: Becoming an Expert in a Complex Human System Through Behavior Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-need-consultants-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the MEOW framework, simulated data are utilized to train an expert model concentrating ``experience'' about a specific task in each independent time of simulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-need-consultants-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Multi-modal Models are Good Class-Incremental Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-multi-modal-models-are-good-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In class-incremental learning (CIL) scenarios, the phenomenon of catastrophic forgetting caused by the classifier's bias towards the current task has long posed a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-multi-modal-models-are-good-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECoDepth: Effective Conditioning of Diffusion Models for Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecodepth-effective-conditioning-of-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that the embedding vector from a ViT model, pre-trained on a large dataset, captures greater relevant information for SIDE than the usual route of generating pseudo image captions, followed by CLIP based text embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecodepth-effective-conditioning-of-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ParCo: Part-Coordinating Text-to-Motion Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parco-part-coordinating-text-to-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these methods encounter challenges such as the lack of coordination between different part motions and difficulties for networks to understand part concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parco-part-coordinating-text-to-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimax Optimal Fair Classification with Bounded Demographic Disparity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimax-optimal-fair-classification-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mitigating the disparate impact of statistical machine learning methods is crucial for ensuring fairness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimax-optimal-fair-classification-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSF-GAN: DownStream Feedback Generative Adversarial Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsf-gan-downstream-feedback-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, DSF-GAN utilizes a downstream prediction task to enhance the utility of synthetic samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsf-gan-downstream-feedback-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffusionFace: Towards a Comprehensive Dataset for Diffusion-Based Face Forgery Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusionface-towards-a-comprehensive-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid progress in deep learning has given rise to hyper-realistic facial forgery methods, leading to concerns related to misinformation and security risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusionface-towards-a-comprehensive-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensor-based Graph Learning with Consistency and Specificity for Multi-view Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensor-based-graph-learning-with-consistency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By making an assumption that the learned neighbor graph of each view comprises both a consistent graph and a view-specific graph, we formulate a new tensor-based target graph learning paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensor-based-graph-learning-with-consistency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Neural Protoform Reconstruction via Reflex Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-neural-protoform-reconstruction-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Protolanguage reconstruction is central to historical linguistics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-neural-protoform-reconstruction-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Embeddings: The Promise of Visual Table in Multi-Modal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-embeddings-the-promise-of-visual-table</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When visual tables serve as standalone visual representations, our model can closely match or even beat the SOTA MLLMs that are built on CLIP visual embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-embeddings-the-promise-of-visual-table</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ImageNet-D: Benchmarking Neural Network Robustness on Diffusion Synthetic Object</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagenet-d-benchmarking-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce generative model as a data source for synthesizing hard images that benchmark deep models' robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagenet-d-benchmarking-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ModaLink: Unifying Modalities for Efficient Image-to-PointCloud Place Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modalink-unifying-modalities-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results on the KITTI dataset show that our proposed methods achieve state-of-the-art performance while running in real time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modalink-unifying-modalities-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention Calibration for Disentangled Text-to-Image Personalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-calibration-for-disentangled-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, an intriguing problem persists: Is it possible to capture multiple, novel concepts from one single reference image?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-calibration-for-disentangled-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Object Detectors with COCO: A New Path Forward</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-object-detectors-with-coco-a-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With these findings, we advocate using COCO-ReM for future object detection research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-object-detectors-with-coco-a-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Multiple Kernel Learning approaches for multi-omics data integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-multiple-kernel-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advances in high-throughput technologies have originated an ever-increasing availability of omics datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-multiple-kernel-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Semi-supervised Nighttime Dehazing Baseline with Spatial-Frequency Aware and Realistic Brightness Constraint</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semi-supervised-nighttime-dehazing-baseline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are two distinctions between nighttime and daytime haze.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semi-supervised-nighttime-dehazing-baseline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many-Objective Evolutionary Influence Maximization: Balancing Spread, Budget, Fairness, and Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/many-objective-evolutionary-influence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Influence Maximization (IM) problem seeks to discover the set of nodes in a graph that can spread the information propagation at most.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/many-objective-evolutionary-influence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Heatmap-Guided 6-Dof Grasp Detection in Cluttered Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-heatmap-guided-6-dof-grasp-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, Gaussian encoding and the grid-based strategy are applied to predict grasp heatmaps as guidance to aggregate local points into graspable regions and provide global semantic information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-heatmap-guided-6-dof-grasp-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster Convergence for Transformer Fine-tuning with Line Search Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-convergence-for-transformer-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works have shown that line search methods greatly increase performance of traditional stochastic gradient descent methods on a variety of datasets and architectures [1], [2].]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-convergence-for-transformer-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Spectrogram Analysis in a Multiple Classifier Fusion Framework for Power Grid Classification Using Electric Network Frequency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-spectrogram-analysis-in-a-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Electric Network Frequency (ENF) serves as a unique signature inherent to power distribution systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-spectrogram-analysis-in-a-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemRoDe: Macro Adversarial Training to Learn Representations That are Robust to Word-Level Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semrode-macro-adversarial-training-to-learn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models (LMs) are indispensable tools for natural language processing tasks, but their vulnerability to adversarial attacks remains a concern.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semrode-macro-adversarial-training-to-learn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clustering Change Sign Detection by Fusing Mixture Complexity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clustering-change-sign-detection-by-fusing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose MC fusion as an extension of MC to handle situations in which multiple mixture numbers are possible in a finite mixture model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clustering-change-sign-detection-by-fusing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequential Recommendation with Latent Relations based on Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-recommendation-with-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from previous relation-aware models that rely on predefined rules, we propose to leverage the Large Language Model (LLM) to provide new types of relations and connections between items.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-recommendation-with-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HandBooster: Boosting 3D Hand-Mesh Reconstruction by Conditional Synthesis and Sampling of Hand-Object Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handbooster-boosting-3d-hand-mesh</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstructing 3D hand mesh robustly from a single image is very challenging, due to the lack of diversity in existing real-world datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handbooster-boosting-3d-hand-mesh</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mini-Gemini: Mining the Potential of Multi-modality Vision Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-gemini-mining-the-potential-of-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We try to narrow the gap by mining the potential of VLMs for better performance and any-to-any workflow from three aspects, i. e., high-resolution visual tokens, high-quality data, and VLM-guided generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-gemini-mining-the-potential-of-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TriviaHG: A Dataset for Automatic Hint Generation from Factoid Questions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triviahg-a-dataset-for-automatic-hint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the TriviaHG dataset and the proposed evaluation method, we enlisted 10 individuals to annotate 2, 791 hints and tasked 6 humans with answering questions using the provided hints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triviahg-a-dataset-for-automatic-hint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homogeneous Tokenizer Matters: Homogeneous Visual Tokenizer for Remote Sensing Image Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/homogeneous-tokenizer-matters-homogeneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to Patch Embed, which requires more than one hundred tokens for one image, HOOK requires only 6 and 8 tokens for sparse and dense tasks, respectively, resulting in efficiency improvements of 1. 5 to 2. 8 times.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/homogeneous-tokenizer-matters-homogeneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-form factuality in large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-form-factuality-in-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirically, we demonstrate that LLM agents can achieve superhuman rating performance - on a set of ~16k individual facts, SAFE agrees with crowdsourced human annotators 72% of the time, and on a random subset of 100 disagreement cases, SAFE wins 76% of the time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-form-factuality-in-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Impact of Uniform Inputs on Activation Sparsity and Energy-Latency Attacks in Computer Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-impact-of-uniform-inputs-on-activation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We empirically examine our findings in a comprehensive evaluation with multiple image classification models and show that our attack achieves the same sparsity effect as prior sponge-example methods, but at a fraction of computation effort.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-impact-of-uniform-inputs-on-activation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H2ASeg: Hierarchical Adaptive Interaction and Weighting Network for Tumor Segmentation in PET/CT Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h2aseg-hierarchical-adaptive-interaction-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, modality-specific encoders used in these methods operate independently, inadequately leveraging the synergistic relationships inherent in PET and CT modalities, for example, the complementarity between semantics and structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h2aseg-hierarchical-adaptive-interaction-and</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
