<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 21:09:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>vGamba: Attentive State Space Bottleneck for efficient Long-range Dependencies in Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vgamba-attentive-state-space-bottleneck-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The interplay of these components ensures that vGamba leverages the low computational demands of SSMs while maintaining the accuracy of attention mechanisms for modeling long-range dependencies in vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vgamba-attentive-state-space-bottleneck-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWI: Speaking with Intent in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swi-speaking-with-intent-in-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intent, typically clearly formulated and planned, functions as a cognitive framework for reasoning and problem-solving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swi-speaking-with-intent-in-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VADMamba: Exploring State Space Models for Fast Video Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vadmamba-exploring-state-space-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video anomaly detection (VAD) methods are mostly CNN-based or Transformer-based, achieving impressive results, but the focus on detection accuracy often comes at the expense of inference speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vadmamba-exploring-state-space-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompting Vision-Language Model for Nuclei Instance Segmentation and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompting-vision-language-model-for-nuclei</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nuclei instance segmentation and classification are a fundamental and challenging task in whole slide Imaging (WSI) analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompting-vision-language-model-for-nuclei</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riemannian Optimization on Relaxed Indicator Matrix Manifold</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/riemannian-optimization-on-relaxed-indicator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new relaxation of the indicator matrix and prove that this relaxation forms a manifold, which we call the Relaxed Indicator Matrix Manifold (RIM manifold).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/riemannian-optimization-on-relaxed-indicator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TerraTorch: The Geospatial Foundation Models Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/terratorch-the-geospatial-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TerraTorch is a fine-tuning and benchmarking toolkit for Geospatial Foundation Models built on PyTorch Lightning and tailored for satellite, weather, and climate data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/terratorch-the-geospatial-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Local Clustering over Attributed Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-local-clustering-over-attributed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, this paper resorts to leveraging the complementary nature of graph topology and node attributes to enhance local clustering quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-local-clustering-over-attributed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Context Autoregressive Video Modeling with Next-Frame Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-context-autoregressive-video-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing RoPE lacks effective temporal decay for remote context and fails to extrapolate well to long video sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-context-autoregressive-video-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Federated Learning Against Poisoning Attacks: A GAN-Based Defense Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-federated-learning-against-poisoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) enables collaborative model training across decentralized devices without sharing raw data, but it remains vulnerable to poisoning attacks that compromise model integrity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-federated-learning-against-poisoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Multimodal Discrete Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-multimodal-discrete-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Discrete diffusion models offer several advantages over AR models, including improved control over quality versus diversity of generated samples, the ability to perform joint multimodal inpainting (across both text and image domains), and greater controllability in generation through guidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-multimodal-discrete-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic-to-Real Self-supervised Robust Depth Estimation via Learning with Motion and Structure Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-to-real-self-supervised-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the synthetic adaptation, we transfer motion-structure knowledge inside cost volumes for better robust representation, using a frozen daytime model to train a depth estimator in synthetic adverse conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-to-real-self-supervised-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BASKET: A Large-Scale Video Dataset for Fine-Grained Skill Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/basket-a-large-scale-video-dataset-for-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BASKET includes 20 fine-grained basketball skills, challenging modern video recognition models to capture the intricate nuances of player skill through in-depth video analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/basket-a-large-scale-video-dataset-for-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADS-Edit: A Multimodal Knowledge Editing Dataset for Autonomous Driving Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ads-edit-a-multimodal-knowledge-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose the use of Knowledge Editing, which enables targeted modifications to a model's behavior without the need for full retraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ads-edit-a-multimodal-knowledge-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InsViE-1M: Effective Instruction-based Video Editing with Elaborate Dataset Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insvie-1m-effective-instruction-based-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The edited first frame is propagated to subsequent frames to produce the edited video, followed by another round of filtering for frame quality and motion evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insvie-1m-effective-instruction-based-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Depression Detection via Question-wise Modality Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-depression-detection-via-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of our framework is comparable to the current state-of-the-art models on the E-DAIC dataset and enhances interpretability by predicting scores for each question.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-depression-detection-via-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Deep Search: Democratizing Search with Open-source Reasoning Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-deep-search-democratizing-search-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open Search Tool is a novel web search tool that outperforms proprietary counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-deep-search-democratizing-search-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VPO: Aligning Text-to-Video Generation Models with Prompt Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vpo-aligning-text-to-video-generation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we construct and refine a supervised fine-tuning (SFT) dataset based on principles of safety and alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vpo-aligning-text-to-video-generation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate Parallelizable Reasoning via Parallel Decoding within One Sequence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerate-parallelizable-reasoning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in reasoning models have demonstrated significant improvements in accuracy, particularly for complex tasks such as mathematical reasoning, by employing detailed and comprehensive reasoning processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerate-parallelizable-reasoning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wan: Open and Advanced Large-Scale Video Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wan-open-and-advanced-large-scale-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Openness: We open-source the entire series of Wan, including source code and all models, with the goal of fostering the growth of the video generation community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wan-open-and-advanced-large-scale-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Efficient Long-to-Short LLM Reasoning with Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-efficient-long-to-short-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model merging, on the other hand, offers a cost-effective and robust alternative by integrating the quick-thinking capabilities of System 1 models with the methodical reasoning of System 2 models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-efficient-long-to-short-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EditCLIP: Representation Learning for Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editclip-representation-learning-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce EditCLIP, a novel representation-learning approach for image editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editclip-representation-learning-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Statistics with Uncertainty Help Adversarial Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-statistics-with-uncertainty-help</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this theoretical finding, we propose a robustness enhancement module called Feature Statistics with Uncertainty (FSU).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-statistics-with-uncertainty-help</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IAP: Improving Continual Learning of Vision-Language Models via Instance-Aware Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iap-improving-continual-learning-of-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent pre-trained vision-language models (PT-VLMs) often face a Multi-Domain Class-Incremental Learning (MCIL) scenario in practice, where several classes and domains of multi-modal tasks are incrementally arrived.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iap-improving-continual-learning-of-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free4D: Tuning-free 4D Scene Generation with Spatial-Temporal Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free4d-tuning-free-4d-scene-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Free4D, a novel tuning-free framework for 4D scene generation from a single image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free4d-tuning-free-4d-scene-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile-MMLU: A Mobile Intelligence Language Understanding Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobile-mmlu-a-mobile-intelligence-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rapid advancements in large language models (LLMs) have increased interest in deploying them on mobile devices for on-device AI applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobile-mmlu-a-mobile-intelligence-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryoSAMU: Enhancing 3D Cryo-EM Density Maps of Protein Structures at Intermediate Resolution with Structure-Aware Multimodal U-Nets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cryosamu-enhancing-3d-cryo-em-density-maps-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Enhancing cryogenic electron microscopy (cryo-EM) 3D density maps at intermediate resolution (4-8 {\AA}) is crucial in protein structure determination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cryosamu-enhancing-3d-cryo-em-density-maps-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphin: A Large-Scale Automatic Speech Recognition Model for Eastern Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dolphin-a-large-scale-automatic-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report introduces Dolphin, a large-scale multilingual automatic speech recognition (ASR) model that extends the Whisper architecture to support a wider range of languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dolphin-a-large-scale-automatic-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pluggable Style Representation Learning for Multi-Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pluggable-style-representation-learning-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, for style modeling, we propose a style representation learning scheme to encode the style information into a compact representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pluggable-style-representation-learning-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SaViD: Spectravista Aesthetic Vision Integration for Robust and Discerning 3D Object Detection in Challenging Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/savid-spectravista-aesthetic-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The fusion of LiDAR and camera sensors has demonstrated significant effectiveness in achieving accurate detection for short-range tasks in autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/savid-spectravista-aesthetic-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modality-Independent Brain Lesion Segmentation with Privacy-aware Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modality-independent-brain-lesion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional brain lesion segmentation models for multi-modal MRI are typically tailored to specific pathologies, relying on datasets with predefined modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modality-independent-brain-lesion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PVLens: Enhancing Pharmacovigilance Through Automated Label Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pvlens-enhancing-pharmacovigilance-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reliable drug safety reference databases are essential for pharmacovigilance, yet existing resources like SIDER are outdated and static.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pvlens-enhancing-pharmacovigilance-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast, Modular, and Differentiable Framework for Machine Learning-Enhanced Molecular Simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-modular-and-differentiable-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an end-to-end differentiable molecular simulation framework (DIMOS) for molecular dynamics and Monte Carlo simulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-modular-and-differentiable-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underwater Image Enhancement by Convolutional Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/underwater-image-enhancement-by-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our algorithm performs on par with its non-spiking counterpart methods in terms of PSNR and structural similarity index (SSIM) at reduced timesteps ($T=5$) and energy consumption of $85\%$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/underwater-image-enhancement-by-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EGVD: Event-Guided Video Diffusion Model for Physically Realistic Large-Motion Frame Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egvd-event-guided-video-diffusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video frame interpolation (VFI) in scenarios with large motion remains challenging due to motion ambiguity between frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egvd-event-guided-video-diffusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisit Time Series Classification Benchmark: The Impact of Temporal Information for Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisit-time-series-classification-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose UCR Augmented, a benchmark based on the UCR time series classification archive designed to evaluate classifiers' ability to extract and utilize temporal information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisit-time-series-classification-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TC-GS: Tri-plane based compression for 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tc-gs-tri-plane-based-compression-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, 3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) has emerged as a prominent framework for novel view synthesis, providing high fidelity and rapid rendering speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tc-gs-tri-plane-based-compression-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inductive Link Prediction on N-ary Relational Facts via Semantic Hypergraph Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inductive-link-prediction-on-n-ary-relational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results highlight the superiority of the n-ary subgraph reasoning framework and the exceptional inductive ability of NS-HART.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inductive-link-prediction-on-n-ary-relational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TraNCE: Transformative Non-linear Concept Explainer for CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trance-transformative-non-linear-concept</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(iii) A new metric, the Faith score, integrates both Coherence and Fidelity for a comprehensive evaluation of explainer faithfulness and consistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trance-transformative-non-linear-concept</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siformer: Feature-isolated Transformer for Efficient Skeleton-based Sign Language Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siformer-feature-isolated-transformer-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For LSA64, we achieve a top-1 accuracy of 99. 84%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siformer-feature-isolated-transformer-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RecTable: Fast Modeling Tabular Data with Rectified Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rectable-fast-modeling-tabular-data-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Score-based or diffusion models generate high-quality tabular data, surpassing GAN-based and VAE-based models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rectable-fast-modeling-tabular-data-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Implicit Sentiments: Enhancing Reliability and Validity in Psychological Trait Evaluation of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-implicit-sentiments-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through extensive experiments, we demonstrate that: 1) CSI effectively captures nuanced emotional patterns, revealing significant variation in LLMs across languages and contexts; 2) Compared to current approaches, CSI significantly improves reliability, yielding more consistent results; and 3) The correlation between CSI scores and the sentiment of LLM's real-world outputs exceeds 0. 85, demonstrating its strong validity in predicting LLM behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-implicit-sentiments-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning and Learning a Perceptual Metric for Self-Training of Reflective Objects in Bin-Picking with a Low-cost Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-and-learning-a-perceptual-metric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bin-picking of metal objects using low-cost RGB-D cameras often suffers from sparse depth information and reflective surface textures, leading to errors and the need for manual labeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-and-learning-a-perceptual-metric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Counterfactuals for Image Regressors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-counterfactuals-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present two methods to create counterfactual explanations for image regression tasks using diffusion-based generative models to address challenges in sparsity and quality: 1) one based on a Denoising Diffusion Probabilistic Model that operates directly in pixel-space and 2) another based on a Diffusion Autoencoder operating in latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-counterfactuals-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Evolutionary Multiobjective Optimization and GPU Acceleration via Tensorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-evolutionary-multiobjective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge the gap, we propose to parallelize EMO algorithms on GPUs via the \emph{tensorization} methodology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-evolutionary-multiobjective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding R1-Zero-Like Training: A Critical Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-r1-zero-like-training-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DeepSeek-R1-Zero has shown that reinforcement learning (RL) at scale can directly enhance the reasoning capabilities of LLMs without supervised fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-r1-zero-like-training-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Med3DVLM: An Efficient Vision-Language Model for 3D Medical Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/med3dvlm-an-efficient-vision-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Med3DVLM, a 3D VLM designed to address these challenges through three key innovations: (1) DCFormer, an efficient encoder that uses decomposed 3D convolutions to capture fine-grained spatial features at scale; (2) SigLIP, a contrastive learning strategy with pairwise sigmoid loss that improves image-text alignment without relying on large negative batches; and (3) a dual-stream MLP-Mixer projector that fuses low- and high-level image features with text embeddings for richer multi-modal representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/med3dvlm-an-efficient-vision-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-SD: Semi-Supervised Metric Depth Estimation via Surrounding Cameras for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-sd-semi-supervised-metric-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Semi-SD, a novel metric depth estimation framework tailored for surrounding cameras equipment in autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-sd-semi-supervised-metric-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Context Autoregressive Video Modeling with Next-Frame Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-context-autoregressive-video-modeling-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing RoPE lacks effective temporal decay for remote context and fails to extrapolate well to long video sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-context-autoregressive-video-modeling-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP-VMUNet: Atrous Shifted Parallel Vision Mamba U-Net for Skin Lesion Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asp-vmunet-atrous-shifted-parallel-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel skin lesion segmentation framework, the Atrous Shifted Parallel Vision Mamba UNet (ASP-VMUNet), which integrates the efficient and scalable Mamba architecture to overcome limitations in traditional CNNs and computationally demanding Transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asp-vmunet-atrous-shifted-parallel-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correcting Deviations from Normality: A Reformulated Diffusion Model for Multi-Class Unsupervised Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correcting-deviations-from-normality-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This leads to potential degradation of normal regions during reconstruction, hampering the effectiveness of anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correcting-deviations-from-normality-a</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
