<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 21:06:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Latent Multi-view Subspace Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-latent-multi-view-subspace</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we stack the data matrices from various views into the block-diagonal locations of the augmented matrix to exploit the complementary information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-latent-multi-view-subspace</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study on Compliance with Ranking Transparency in the Software Documentation of EU Online Platforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-compliance-with-ranking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compliance with the European Union's Platform-to-Business (P2B) Regulation is challenging for online platforms, and assessing their compliance can be difficult for public authorities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-compliance-with-ranking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inverse Transfer Multiobjective Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverse-transfer-multiobjective-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel concept of inverse transfer in multiobjective optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverse-transfer-multiobjective-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PC-Conv: Unifying Homophily and Heterophily with Two-fold Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pc-conv-unifying-homophily-and-heterophily</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is attributed to their neglect of homophily in heterophilic graphs, and vice versa.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pc-conv-unifying-homophily-and-heterophily</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViStripformer: A Token-Efficient Transformer for Versatile Video Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vistripformer-a-token-efficient-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, ViStripformer is an effective and efficient transformer architecture with much lower memory usage than the vanilla transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vistripformer-a-token-efficient-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacking Byzantine Robust Aggregation in High Dimensions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attacking-byzantine-robust-aggregation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing such aggregators is challenging when dealing with high dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attacking-byzantine-robust-aggregation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharp error estimates for target measure diffusion maps with applications to the committor problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharp-error-estimates-for-target-measure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remarkably, we find that the TMDmap algorithm is particularly suited as a meshless solver to the committor problem due to the cancellation of several error terms in the prefactor formula.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharp-error-estimates-for-target-measure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Diffusion Models for Visual Perception with Meta Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-diffusion-models-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our key insight is to introduce learnable embeddings (meta prompts) to the pre-trained diffusion models to extract proper features for perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-diffusion-models-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuaLight: Enhancing Traffic Signal Control by Leveraging Scenario-Specific and Scenario-Shared Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dualight-enhancing-traffic-signal-control-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we implement a scenario-shared Co-Train module to facilitate the learning of generalizable dynamics information across different scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dualight-enhancing-traffic-signal-control-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from higher-order statistics, efficiently: hypothesis tests, random features, and neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-higher-order-statistics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that neural networks extract information from higher-order correlations in the spiked cumulant model efficiently, and reveal a large gap in the amount of data required by neural networks and random features to learn from higher-order cumulants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-higher-order-statistics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards more sustainable enterprise data and application management with cross silo Federated Learning and Analytics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-more-sustainable-enterprise-data-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To comply with new legal requirements and policies committed to privacy protection, more and more companies start to deploy cross-silo Federated Learning at global scale, where several clients/silos collaboratively train a global model under the coordination of a central server.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-more-sustainable-enterprise-data-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balancing the Style-Content Trade-Off in Sentiment Transfer Using Polarity-Aware Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-the-style-content-trade-off-in-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text sentiment transfer aims to flip the sentiment polarity of a sentence (positive to negative or vice versa) while preserving its sentiment-independent content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-the-style-content-trade-off-in-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Learning Neuronal Skeleton and Brain Circuit Topology with Permutation Invariant Encoders for Neuron Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-learning-neuronal-skeleton-and-brain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Skeleton Encoder integrates the local information of neurons in a bottom-up manner, with a one-dimensional convolution in neural skeleton's point data; Connectome Encoder uses a graph neural network to capture the topological information of neural circuit; finally, Readout Layer fuses the above two information and outputs classification results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-learning-neuronal-skeleton-and-brain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part to Whole: Collaborative Prompting for Surgical Instrument Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/part-to-whole-collaborative-prompting-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, in this paper, we investigate text promptable surgical instrument segmentation and propose SP-SAM (SurgicalPart-SAM), a novel efficient-tuning approach that integrates surgical instrument structure knowledge with the generic segmentation knowledge of SAM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/part-to-whole-collaborative-prompting-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating the Design of Multigrid Methods with Evolutionary Program Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-the-design-of-multigrid-methods</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this purpose, we develop a novel context-free grammar that enables the automated generation of multigrid methods in a symbolically-manipulable formal language, based on which we can apply the same multigrid-based solver to problems of different sizes without having to adapt its internal structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-the-design-of-multigrid-methods</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TACO: Topics in Algorithmic COde generation dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taco-topics-in-algorithmic-code-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, each TACO problem includes several fine-grained labels such as task topics, algorithms, programming skills, and difficulty levels, providing a more precise reference for the training and evaluation of code generation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taco-topics-in-algorithmic-code-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUMA: Efficient Continual Graph Learning with Graph Condensation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puma-efficient-continual-graph-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our prior work, CaT is a replay-based framework with a balanced continual learning procedure, which designs a small yet effective memory bank for replaying data by condensing incoming graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puma-efficient-continual-graph-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasons to Reject? Aligning Language Models with Judgments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasons-to-reject-aligning-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As humans, we consistently engage in interactions with our peers and receive feedback in the form of natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasons-to-reject-aligning-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCUNet++: Assessment of Pulmonary Embolism CT Image Segmentation Leveraging Swin-UNet and CNN Bottleneck Hybrid Architecture with Multi-Fusion Dense Skip Connection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scunet-assessment-of-pulmonary-embolism-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These findings demonstrate that our method exhibits strong performance in PE segmentation tasks, potentially enhancing the accuracy of automatic segmentation of PE and providing a powerful diagnostic tool for clinical physicians.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scunet-assessment-of-pulmonary-embolism-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning via Input-Output Collaborative Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-via-input-output</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) is a machine learning paradigm in which distributed local nodes collaboratively train a central model without sharing individually held private data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-via-input-output</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Effectiveness of Unlearning in Session-Based Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-unlearning-in-session</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the one hand, these approaches cannot achieve satisfying unlearning effects due to the collaborative correlations and sequential connections between the unlearning item and the remaining items in the session.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-unlearning-in-session</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Token-Level Contrastive Learning with Modality-Aware Prompting for Multimodal Intent Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-level-contrastive-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To establish an optimal multimodal semantic environment for text modality, we develop a modality-aware prompting module (MAP), which effectively aligns and fuses features from text, video and audio modalities with similarity-based modality alignment and cross-modality attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-level-contrastive-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAST: Feature Aware Similarity Thresholding for Weak Unlearning in Black-Box Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-feature-aware-similarity-thresholding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The heightened emphasis on the regulation of deep generative models, propelled by escalating concerns pertaining to privacy and compliance with regulatory frameworks, underscores the imperative need for precise control mechanisms over these models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-feature-aware-similarity-thresholding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Synthesis of Patient Records through Multi-Visit Health State Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-synthesis-of-patient-records</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose to generate medical reports to add textual descriptions for each medical event, providing broader applications for synthesized EHR data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-synthesis-of-patient-records</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Stage Adaptive Feature Fusion Neural Network for Multimodal Gait Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-stage-adaptive-feature-fusion-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, by considering the temporal and spatial characteristics of gait data, we propose a multi-stage feature fusion strategy (MSFFS), which performs multimodal fusions at different stages in the feature extraction process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-stage-adaptive-feature-fusion-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Covariate Gait Recognition: A Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-covariate-gait-recognition-a-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to existing datasets, CCGR has both population and individual-level diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-covariate-gait-recognition-a-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAVAE: Leveraging the variational Bayes autoencoder for survival analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/savae-leveraging-the-variational-bayes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As in many fields of medical research, survival analysis has witnessed a growing interest in the application of deep learning techniques to model complex, high-dimensional, heterogeneous, incomplete, and censored medical data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/savae-leveraging-the-variational-bayes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Language-based solution to enable Metaverse Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-language-based-solution-to-enable-metaverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, the Metaverse is becoming increasingly attractive, with millions of users accessing the many available virtual worlds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-language-based-solution-to-enable-metaverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An effective and efficient green federated learning method for one-layer neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-effective-and-efficient-green-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) is one of the most active research lines in machine learning, as it allows the training of collaborative models in a distributed way, an interesting option in many real-world environments, such as the Internet of Things, allowing the use of these models in edge computing devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-effective-and-efficient-green-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Differential Evolution with Diversification: Addressing Optimization Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-differential-evolution-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The existing variants of the Differential Evolution (DE) algorithm come with certain limitations, such as poor local search and susceptibility to premature convergence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-differential-evolution-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Occlusion-Aware Transformer for Robust Stereo Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-occlusion-aware-transformer-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the remarkable progress facilitated by learning-based stereo-matching algorithms, the performance in the ill-conditioned regions, such as the occluded regions, remains a bottleneck.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-occlusion-aware-transformer-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Images in Discrete Choice Modeling: Addressing Data Isomorphism in Multi-Modality Inputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/images-in-discrete-choice-modeling-addressing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose and benchmark two methodologies to address this challenge: architectural design adjustments to segregate redundant information, and isomorphic information mitigation through source information masking and inpainting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/images-in-discrete-choice-modeling-addressing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSAP: Analyzing Bias Through Demographic Comparison of Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsap-analyzing-bias-through-demographic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Often, these biases can be traced back to the data used for training, where large uncurated datasets have become the norm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsap-analyzing-bias-through-demographic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quality-Diversity Generative Sampling for Learning with Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quality-diversity-generative-sampling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[QDGS is a model-agnostic framework that uses prompt guidance to optimize a quality objective across measures of diversity for synthetically generated data, without fine-tuning the generative model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quality-diversity-generative-sampling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aurora:Activating Chinese chat capability for Mistral-8x7B sparse Mixture-of-Experts through Instruction-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aurora-activating-chinese-chat-capability-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work is pioneering in the execution of instruction fine-tuning on a sparse expert-mixed model, marking a significant breakthrough in enhancing the capabilities of this model architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aurora-activating-chinese-chat-capability-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhysRFANet: Physics-Guided Neural Network for Real-Time Prediction of Thermal Effect During Radiofrequency Ablation Treatment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physrfanet-physics-guided-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Radiofrequency ablation (RFA) is a widely used minimally invasive technique for ablating solid tumors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physrfanet-physics-guided-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upper Bounding Barlow Twins: A Novel Filter for Multi-Relational Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/upper-bounding-barlow-twins-a-novel-filter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this drawback, we propose to learn a graph filter motivated by the theoretical analysis of Barlow Twins.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/upper-bounding-barlow-twins-a-novel-filter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ElasticTrainer: Speeding Up On-Device Training with Runtime Elastic Tensor Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elastictrainer-speeding-up-on-device-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To speed up on-device training, existing schemes select trainable NN portion offline or conduct unrecoverable selection at runtime, but the evolution of trainable NN portion is constrained and cannot adapt to the current need for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elastictrainer-speeding-up-on-device-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DP-AdamBC: Your DP-Adam Is Actually DP-SGD (Unless You Apply Bias Correction)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dp-adambc-your-dp-adam-is-actually-dp-sgd</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Adam optimizer is a popular choice in contemporary deep learning, due to its strong empirical performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dp-adambc-your-dp-adam-is-actually-dp-sgd</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation for Driving Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-semantic-segmentation-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, the proposed method achieves 51. 8\% mIoU on the Cityscapes test dataset, showcasing its potential as a strong WSSS baseline on driving scene datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-semantic-segmentation-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Noise Annotation: Unveiling the Impact of Noisy annotation on Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-noise-annotation-unveiling-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For object detection task with noisy labels, it is important to consider not only categorization noise, as in image classification, but also localization noise, missing annotations, and bogus bounding boxes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-noise-annotation-unveiling-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Semantic Space is Worth 256 Language Descriptions: Make Stronger Segmentation Models with Descriptive Properties</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semantic-space-is-worth-256-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of relying solely on category-specific annotations, ProLab uses descriptive properties grounded in common sense knowledge for supervising segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semantic-space-is-worth-256-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-tuning Graph Neural Networks by Preserving Graph Generative Patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-graph-neural-networks-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we identify the fundamental cause of structural divergence as the discrepancy of generative patterns between the pre-training and downstream graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-graph-neural-networks-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VCoder: Versatile Vision Encoders for Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vcoder-versatile-vision-encoders-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, we leverage the images from COCO and outputs from off-the-shelf vision perception models to create our COCO Segmentation Text (COST) dataset for training and evaluating MLLMs on the object perception task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vcoder-versatile-vision-encoders-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinySAM: Pushing the Envelope for Efficient Segment Anything Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinysam-pushing-the-envelope-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first propose a full-stage knowledge distillation method with online hard prompt sampling strategy to distill a lightweight student model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinysam-pushing-the-envelope-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HD-Painter: High-Resolution and Prompt-Faithful Text-Guided Image Inpainting with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hd-painter-high-resolution-and-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in text-guided image inpainting, based on the unprecedented success of text-to-image diffusion models, has led to exceptionally realistic and visually plausible results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hd-painter-high-resolution-and-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Front stability of infinitely steep travelling waves in population biology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/front-stability-of-infinitely-steep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We establish the existence of travelling wave solutions for these two extensions, and then consider stability of the travelling wave solutions by introducing a lateral perturbation of the travelling wavefront.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/front-stability-of-infinitely-steep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geo2SigMap: High-Fidelity RF Signal Mapping Using Geographic Databases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geo2sigmap-high-fidelity-rf-signal-mapping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we develop an automated framework that seamlessly integrates three open-source tools: OpenStreetMap (geographic databases), Blender (computer graphics), and Sionna (ray tracing), enabling the efficient generation of large-scale 3D building maps and ray tracing models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geo2sigmap-high-fidelity-rf-signal-mapping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-Eval: Evaluating the Tool Utilization Capability Step by Step</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-eval-evaluating-the-tool-utilization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to previous works that evaluate models holistically, we comprehensively decompose the tool utilization into multiple sub-processes, including instruction following, planning, reasoning, retrieval, understanding, and review.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-eval-evaluating-the-tool-utilization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Point Cloud Diffusion for Disentangled 3D Shape and Appearance Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-point-cloud-diffusion-for-disentangled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, none of the existing models enable disentangled generation to control the shape and appearance separately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-point-cloud-diffusion-for-disentangled</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
