<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 21:07:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Dataset for Evaluating Complex Compositional Knowledge for Natural Language Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-dataset-for-evaluating-complex</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we modify the original texts using a set of phrases - modifiers that correspond to universal quantifiers, existential quantifiers, negation, and other concept modifiers in Natural Logic (NL) (MacCartney, 2009).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-dataset-for-evaluating-complex</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Deep Dive into Perturbations as Evaluation Technique for Time Series XAI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-dive-into-perturbations-as-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper provides an in-depth analysis of using perturbations to evaluate attributions extracted from time series models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-dive-into-perturbations-as-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Need for a Language Describing Distribution Shifts: Illustrations on Tabular Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-need-for-a-language-describing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different distribution shifts require different algorithmic and operational interventions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-need-for-a-language-describing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Understanding In-Context Learning with Contrastive Demonstrations and Saliency Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-understanding-in-context-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the role of various demonstration components in the in-context learning (ICL) performance of large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-understanding-in-context-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OntoChatGPT Information System: Ontology-Driven Structured Prompts for ChatGPT Meta-Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontochatgpt-information-system-ontology</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The resulting productive triad comprises the methodological foundations, advanced information technology, and the OntoChatGPT system, which collectively enhance the effectiveness and performance of chatbot systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontochatgpt-information-system-ontology</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Agnostic Neural Architecture for Class Incremental Continual Learning in Document Processing Platform</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-agnostic-neural-architecture-for-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Production deployments in complex systems require ML architectures to be highly efficient and usable against multiple tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-agnostic-neural-architecture-for-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISLTranslate: Dataset for Translating Indian Sign Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isltranslate-dataset-for-translating-indian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, it is the largest translation dataset for continuous Indian Sign Language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isltranslate-dataset-for-translating-indian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-Attention Gated Vision-Language Embedding for Visual Question Localized-Answering in Robotic Surgery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-attention-gated-vision-language-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, a surgical Visual Question Localized-Answering (VQLA) system would be helpful for medical students and junior surgeons to learn and understand from recorded surgical videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-attention-gated-vision-language-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing Cognitive Synergy in Large Language Models: A Task-Solving Agent through Multi-Persona Self-Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-cognitive-synergy-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human intelligence thrives on the concept of cognitive synergy, where collaboration and information integration among different cognitive processes yield superior outcomes compared to individual cognitive processes in isolation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-cognitive-synergy-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U-CREAT: Unsupervised Case Retrieval using Events extrAcTion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-creat-unsupervised-case-retrieval-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further promote research in PCR, in this paper, we propose a new large benchmark (in English) for the PCR task: IL-PCR (Indian Legal Prior Case Retrieval) corpus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-creat-unsupervised-case-retrieval-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Versus-Others Attention: Scalable Multimodal Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-versus-others-attention-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal learning models have become increasingly important as they surpass single-modality approaches on diverse tasks ranging from question-answering to autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-versus-others-attention-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIAM -- A Metric for Evaluating Alignment in Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiam-a-metric-for-evaluating-alignment-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While several metrics have been proposed to assess the rendering of images, it is crucial for Text-to-Image (T2I) models, which generate images based on a prompt, to consider additional aspects such as to which extent the generated image matches the important content of the prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiam-a-metric-for-evaluating-alignment-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural-Symbolic Recommendation with Graph-Enhanced Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-symbolic-recommendation-with-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some researchers use user behavior for logic reasoning to achieve recommendation prediction from the perspective of cognitive reasoning, but this kind of reasoning is a local one and ignores implicit information on a global scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-symbolic-recommendation-with-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Feedback Efficiency of Interactive Reinforcement Learning by Adaptive Learning from Scores</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-feedback-efficiency-of-interactive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new method that uses scores provided by humans, instead of pairwise preferences, to improve the feedback efficiency of interactive reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-feedback-efficiency-of-interactive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting small molecules solubilities on endpoint devices using deep ensemble neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-small-molecules-solubilities-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, ease of use remains a concern for any computational technique, resulting in the sustained popularity of group-based contribution methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-small-molecules-solubilities-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Membership Inference Attacks on DNNs using Adversarial Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membership-inference-attacks-on-dnns-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, we utilize the framework to propose two novel attacks: (1) Adversarial Membership Inference Attack (AMIA) efficiently utilizes the membership and the non-membership information of the subjects while adversarially minimizing a novel loss function, achieving 6% TPR on both Fashion-MNIST and MNIST datasets; and (2) Enhanced AMIA (E-AMIA) combines EMIA and AMIA to achieve 8% and 4% TPRs on Fashion-MNIST and MNIST datasets respectively, at 1% FPR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membership-inference-attacks-on-dnns-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Modular Multimodal Architecture for Gaze Target Prediction: Application to Privacy-Sensitive Settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modular-multimodal-architecture-for-gaze-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[to detect obstructions in the line of sight or apply attention priors that humans typically have when observing others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modular-multimodal-architecture-for-gaze-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFR: Depth from Rotation by Uncalibrated Image Rectification with Latitudinal Motion Assumption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfr-depth-from-rotation-by-uncalibrated-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the increasing prevalence of rotating-style capture (e. g., surveillance cameras), conventional stereo rectification techniques frequently fail due to the rotation-dominant motion and small baseline between views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfr-depth-from-rotation-by-uncalibrated-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Anytime Optical Flow Estimation with Event Cameras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-anytime-optical-flow-estimation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then propose EVA-Flow, an EVent-based Anytime Flow estimation network to produce high-frame-rate event optical flow with only low-frame-rate optical flow ground truth for supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-anytime-optical-flow-estimation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PKU-GoodsAD: A Supermarket Goods Dataset for Unsupervised Anomaly Detection and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pku-goodsad-a-supermarket-goods-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It follows the unsupervised setting and only normal (defect-free) images are used for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pku-goodsad-a-supermarket-goods-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compact Twice Fusion Network for Edge Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-twice-fusion-network-for-edge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a Compact Twice Fusion Network (CTFN) to fully integrate multi-scale features while maintaining the compactness of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-twice-fusion-network-for-edge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Uncertainty: The Role of Short-Term Trajectory Prediction in Autonomous Vehicle Safety</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-uncertainty-the-role-of-short-term</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we have developed a synthetic dataset for short-term trajectory prediction tasks using the CARLA simulator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-uncertainty-the-role-of-short-term</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised adversarial masking for 3D point cloud representation learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-adversarial-masking-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce PointCAM, a novel adversarial method for learning a masking function for point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-adversarial-masking-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Cross-lingual Behavioral Testing of NLP Models with Typological Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-cross-lingual-behavioral-testing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A challenge towards developing NLP systems for the world's languages is understanding how they generalize to typological differences relevant for real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-cross-lingual-behavioral-testing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Pretraining in Multimodality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-pretraining-in-multimodality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Emu, a Transformer-based multimodal foundation model, which can seamlessly generate images and texts in multimodal context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-pretraining-in-multimodality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of RLHF in Large Language Models Part I: PPO</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secrets-of-rlhf-in-large-language-models-part</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we explore the PPO-max, an advanced version of PPO algorithm, to efficiently improve the training stability of the policy model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secrets-of-rlhf-in-large-language-models-part</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epidemic Modeling with Generative Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epidemic-modeling-with-generative-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study offers a new paradigm of individual-level modeling to address the grand challenge of incorporating human behavior in epidemic models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epidemic-modeling-with-generative-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duncode Characters Shorter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/duncode-characters-shorter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It discusses local encoders such as ASCII and GB-2312, which encode specific characters into shorter bytes, and universal encoders like UTF-8 and UTF-16, which can encode the complete Unicode set with greater space requirements and are gaining widespread acceptance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/duncode-characters-shorter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Contrastive Graph Learning for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-contrastive-graph-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, feature augmentation imposes the same scale noise augmentation on each node, which neglects the unique characteristics of nodes on the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-contrastive-graph-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mao-Zedong At SemEval-2023 Task 4: Label Represention Multi-Head Attention Model With Contrastive Learning-Enhanced Nearest Neighbor Mechanism For Multi-Label Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mao-zedong-at-semeval-2023-task-4-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The study of human values is essential in both practical and theoretical domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mao-zedong-at-semeval-2023-task-4-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Quantification of the Virial Black Hole Mass with Conformal Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-of-the-virial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to baseline approaches for prediction interval estimation, we show that the CQR method provides prediction intervals that adjust to the black hole mass and its related properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-of-the-virial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A stochastic optimization approach to minimize robust density power-based divergences for general parametric density models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stochastic-optimization-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Density power divergence (DPD) [Basu et al. (1998), Biometrika], designed to estimate the underlying distribution of the observations robustly, comprises an integral term of the power of the parametric density models to be estimated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stochastic-optimization-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering recommender systems using automatically generated Knowledge Graphs and Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-recommender-systems-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized recommendations have a growing importance in direct marketing, which motivates research to enhance customer experiences by knowledge graph (KG) applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-recommender-systems-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geometric Neural Diffusion Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-neural-diffusion-processes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we extend the framework of diffusion models to incorporate a series of geometric priors in infinite-dimension modelling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-neural-diffusion-processes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Algorithms for Federated Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-algorithms-for-federated-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then apply our methodology to evaluate 13 Federated DG methods, which include centralized DG methods adapted to the FL context, FL methods that handle client heterogeneity, and methods designed specifically for Federated DG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-algorithms-for-federated-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLUEX: A benchmark based on Brazilian Leading Universities Entrance eXams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bluex-a-benchmark-based-on-brazilian-leading</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One common trend in recent studies of language models (LMs) is the use of standardized tests for evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bluex-a-benchmark-based-on-brazilian-leading</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differential Analysis of Triggers and Benign Features for Black-Box DNN Backdoor Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-analysis-of-triggers-and-benign</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Having the computed five metrics, five novelty detectors are trained from the validation dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-analysis-of-triggers-and-benign</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformalization of Sparse Generalized Linear Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformalization-of-sparse-generalized-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a sequence of observable variables $\{(x_1, y_1), \ldots, (x_n, y_n)\}$, the conformal prediction method estimates a confidence set for $y_{n+1}$ given $x_{n+1}$ that is valid for any finite sample size by merely assuming that the joint distribution of the data is permutation invariant.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformalization-of-sparse-generalized-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly-supervised positional contrastive learning: application to cirrhosis classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-positional-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large medical imaging datasets can be cheaply and quickly annotated with low-confidence, weak labels (e. g., radiological scores).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-positional-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparison of Point Cloud and Image-based Models for Calorimeter Fast Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-of-point-cloud-and-image-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Score based generative models are a new class of generative models that have been shown to accurately generate high dimensional calorimeter datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-of-point-cloud-and-image-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partial Vessels Annotation-based Coronary Artery Segmentation with Self-training and Prototype Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-vessels-annotation-based-coronary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose partial vessels annotation (PVA) based on the challenges of coronary artery segmentation and clinical diagnostic characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-vessels-annotation-based-coronary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customizing Synthetic Data for Data-Free Student Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/customizing-synthetic-data-for-data-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing works generally synthesize data from the pre-trained teacher model to replace the original training data for student learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/customizing-synthetic-data-for-data-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINFA: a Python library for variational inference with normalizing flow and annealing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linfa-a-python-library-for-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Variational inference is an increasingly popular method in statistics and machine learning for approximating probability distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linfa-a-python-library-for-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handling Group Fairness in Federated Learning Using Augmented Lagrangian Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handling-group-fairness-in-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) has garnered considerable attention due to its privacy-preserving feature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handling-group-fairness-in-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recent Advancements in End-to-End Autonomous Driving using Deep Learning: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recent-advancements-in-end-to-end-autonomous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[End-to-End driving is a promising paradigm as it circumvents the drawbacks associated with modular systems, such as their overwhelming complexity and propensity for error propagation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recent-advancements-in-end-to-end-autonomous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Piano Transcription with Hierarchical Frequency-Time Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-piano-transcription-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is especially helpful when determining the precise onset and offset for each note in the polyphonic piano content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-piano-transcription-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnimateDiff: Animate Your Personalized Text-to-Image Diffusion Models without Specific Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animatediff-animate-your-personalized-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advance of text-to-image models (e. g., Stable Diffusion) and corresponding personalization techniques such as DreamBooth and LoRA, everyone can manifest their imagination into high-quality images at an affordable cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animatediff-animate-your-personalized-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wearable to detect electromyographic changes in the trapezius muscle due to improper posture while sitting for long periods of time.</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wearable-to-detect-electromyographic-changes-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The trapezius muscle, located in the back, plays an important role in maintaining upright posture and is involved in movements such as lateral flexion and rotation of the head, as well as shoulder elevation and depression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wearable-to-detect-electromyographic-changes-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early diagnosis of carpal tunnel syndrome using electromyogram signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-diagnosis-of-carpal-tunnel-syndrome</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The present investigation proposes to use electromyographic signals for the diagnosis of carpal tunnel with the aim of helping to reduce the number of false positives and negatives that are obtained with the criteria currently used.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-diagnosis-of-carpal-tunnel-syndrome</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of EEG signals of blinking patterns in order to control a wheelchair for people with ALS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-eeg-signals-of-blinking-patterns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS) is a progressive neurodegenerative disease with no cure, emphasizing the need for innovative approaches to improve patients' quality of life.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-eeg-signals-of-blinking-patterns</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
