<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 09:15:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Monitoring and Discovery Approach for Declarative Processes Based on Streams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-monitoring-and-discovery-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We validated the technique via quantitative and qualitative evaluations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-monitoring-and-discovery-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Point-BEV Fusion for 3D Point Cloud Object Tracking with Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-point-bev-fusion-for-3d-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a point cloud sequence, 3D object tracking aims to predict the location and orientation of an object in consecutive frames given an object template.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-point-bev-fusion-for-3d-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Degradation Representations for Image Deblurring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-degradation-representations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the integration, MSDI-Net can handle various and complicated blurry patterns adaptively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-degradation-representations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Autonomous Atlas-based Ultrasound Acquisitions in Presence of Articulated Motion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-autonomous-atlas-based-ultrasound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robotic ultrasound (US) imaging aims at overcoming some of the limitations of free-hand US examinations, e. g. difficulty in guaranteeing intra- and inter-operator repeatability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-autonomous-atlas-based-ultrasound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing Exploitability with Population Based Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-exploitability-with-population-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate this defense's robustness against new adversaries in two low-dimensional environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-exploitability-with-population-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Transfer Learning: Covid-19 Classification with a few Chest X-ray Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-transfer-learning-covid-19</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, interpreting imaging data is often time-consuming and requires a great deal of human expertise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-transfer-learning-covid-19</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Contrastive Self-Supervised Learning of Utterance-Level Speech Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-contrastive-self-supervised-learning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper applies a non-contrastive self-supervised learning method on an unlabeled speech corpus to learn utterance-level embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-contrastive-self-supervised-learning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Supervised Training for Skeleton-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-supervised-training-for-skeleton</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More specifically, we employ a large-scale language model as the knowledge engine to provide text descriptions for body parts movements of actions, and propose a multi-modal training scheme by utilizing the text encoder to generate feature vectors for different body parts and supervise the skeleton encoder for action representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-supervised-training-for-skeleton</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghost-free High Dynamic Range Imaging with Context-aware Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ghost-free-high-dynamic-range-imaging-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High dynamic range (HDR) deghosting algorithms aim to generate ghost-free HDR images with realistic details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ghost-free-high-dynamic-range-imaging-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for a Needle in a Haystack: A Comprehensive Study of Hallucinations in Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-for-a-needle-in-a-haystack-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the problem of hallucinations in neural machine translation (NMT) has received some attention, research on this highly pathological phenomenon lacks solid ground.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-for-a-needle-in-a-haystack-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Inference of Temporal Logic Formulas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-inference-of-temporal-logic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is great interest in learning formal specifications that characterize the ideal behavior of such systems -- that is, formulas in temporal logic that are satisfied by the system's output signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-inference-of-temporal-logic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DVR: Micro-Video Recommendation Optimizing Watch-Time-Gain under Duration Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dvr-micro-video-recommendation-optimizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommender systems are prone to be misled by biases in the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dvr-micro-video-recommendation-optimizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSInterpret: A unified framework for time series interpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsinterpret-a-unified-framework-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increasing application of deep learning algorithms to time series classification, especially in high-stake scenarios, the relevance of interpreting those algorithms becomes key.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsinterpret-a-unified-framework-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Reinforcement Learning using Offline Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-reinforcement-learning-using-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of robust reinforcement learning (RL) is to learn a policy that is robust against the uncertainty in model parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-reinforcement-learning-using-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Out-of-Distribution Detection of Melanoma with Wavelet-based Normalizing Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-out-of-distribution-detection-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we aim at using these biases with domain-level knowledge of melanoma, to improve likelihood-based OOD detection of malignant images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-out-of-distribution-detection-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Mean-Field Control for Delayed Information Load Balancing in Large Queuing Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-mean-field-control-for-delayed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we consider a multi-agent load balancing system, with delayed information, consisting of many clients (load balancers) and many parallel queues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-mean-field-control-for-delayed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Sentence Embeddings and Semantic Similarity for Seeking Consensus when Assessing Trustworthy AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-sentence-embeddings-and-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, a core challenge of the assessment process is to identify when experts from different disciplines talk about the same problem but use different terminologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-sentence-embeddings-and-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Hate Speech Detection with HateXplain and BERT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-hate-speech-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We tune BERT to perform this task in the form of rationales and class prediction, and compare our performance on different metrics spanning across accuracy, explainability and bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-hate-speech-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra Lite Convolutional Neural Network for Automatic Modulation Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-lite-convolutional-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic modulation classification (AMC) is a key technique for desiging non-cooperative communication systems, and deep learning (DL) is applied effectively into AMC for improving the classification accuracy. However, most of the DL-based AMC methods have a large number of parameters and high computational complexity, and they cannot be directly applied into scenarios with limited computing power and storage space. In this paper, we propose a lightweight and low-complexity AMC method using ultra lite convolutional neural network (ULCNN), which is based on multiple tricks, including data augmentation, complex-valued convolution, separable convolution, channel attention, channel shuffle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-lite-convolutional-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Well Do Vision Transformers (VTs) Transfer To The Non-Natural Image Domain? An Empirical Study Involving Art Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-well-do-vision-transformers-vts-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision Transformers (VTs) are becoming a valuable alternative to Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) when it comes to problems involving high-dimensional and spatially organized inputs such as images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-well-do-vision-transformers-vts-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating DBSCAN via Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-dbscan-via-deep-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DBSCAN is widely used in many scientific and engineering fields because of its simplicity and practicality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-dbscan-via-deep-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Embarrassingly Easy but Strong Baseline for Nested Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-embarrassingly-easy-but-strong-baseline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose using Convolutional Neural Network (CNN) to model these spatial relations in the score matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-embarrassingly-easy-but-strong-baseline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Zeroth-Order Optimisation of Nonconvex Composite Objectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-zeroth-order-optimisation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose and analyze algorithms for zeroth-order optimization of non-convex composite objectives, focusing on reducing the complexity dependence on dimensionality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-zeroth-order-optimisation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motif-based Graph Representation Learning with Application to Chemical Molecules</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motif-based-graph-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MCM builds a motif vocabulary in an unsupervised way and deploys a novel motif convolution operation to extract the local structural context of individual nodes, which is then used to learn higher-level node representations via multilayer perceptron and/or message passing in graph neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motif-based-graph-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RDA: Reciprocal Distribution Alignment for Robust SSL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rda-reciprocal-distribution-alignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose Reciprocal Distribution Alignment (RDA) to address semi-supervised learning (SSL), which is a hyperparameter-free framework that is independent of confidence threshold and works with both the matched (conventionally) and the mismatched class distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rda-reciprocal-distribution-alignment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning-Based Objective and Reproducible Osteosarcoma Chemotherapy Response Assessment and Outcome Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-objective-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Necrosis is routinely assessed post-chemotherapy from histology slides on resection specimens where necrosis ratio is defined as the ratio of necrotic tumor to overall tumor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-objective-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-term Causal Effects Estimation via Latent Surrogates Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-term-causal-effects-estimation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimating long-term causal effects based on short-term surrogates is a significant but challenging problem in many real-world applications, e. g., marketing and medicine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-term-causal-effects-estimation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotion Detection From Tweets Using a BERT and SVM Ensemble Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotion-detection-from-tweets-using-a-bert</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic identification of emotions expressed in Twitter data has a wide range of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotion-detection-from-tweets-using-a-bert</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Comparison of User Modeling Techniques for Predicting Data Interaction and Detecting Exploration Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-comparison-of-user-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our paper seeks to fill in this missing gap by comparing and ranking eight user modeling algorithms based on their performance on a diverse set of four user study datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-comparison-of-user-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extending GCC-PHAT using Shift Equivariant Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-gcc-phat-using-shift-equivariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker localization using microphone arrays depends on accurate time delay estimation techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-gcc-phat-using-shift-equivariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoViT: Real-time phylogenetics for the SARS-CoV-2 pandemic using Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covit-real-time-phylogenetics-for-the-sars</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-time viral genome detection, taxonomic classification and phylogenetic analysis are critical for efficient tracking and control of viral pandemics such as Covid-19.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covit-real-time-phylogenetics-for-the-sars</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplified State Space Layers for Sequence Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplified-state-space-layers-for-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The S4 layer combines linear state space models (SSMs) with deep learning techniques and leverages the HiPPO framework for online function approximation to achieve high performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplified-state-space-layers-for-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAMDA-SSL: Semi-Supervised Learning in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lamda-ssl-semi-supervised-learning-in-python</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The second part shows the usage of LAMDA-SSL by abundant examples in detail.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lamda-ssl-semi-supervised-learning-in-python</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A functional connectivity atlas of $\textit{C. elegans}$ measured by neural activation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-functional-connectivity-atlas-of-textit-c</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural processing and dynamics are governed by the details of how neural signals propagate from one neuron to the next through the brain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-functional-connectivity-atlas-of-textit-c</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compositional Evaluation on Japanese Textual Entailment and Similarity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-evaluation-on-japanese-textual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also present a stress-test dataset for compositional inference, created by transforming syntactic structures of sentences in JSICK to investigate whether language models are sensitive to word order and case particles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-evaluation-on-japanese-textual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OptEmbed: Learning Optimal Embedding Table for Click-through Rate Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optembed-learning-optimal-embedding-table-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose an optimal embedding table learning framework OptEmbed, which provides a practical and general method to find an optimal embedding table for various base CTR models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optembed-learning-optimal-embedding-table-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Basis for Intentions: Efficient Inverse Reinforcement Learning using Past Experience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/basis-for-intentions-efficient-inverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[IRL can provide a generalizable and compact representation for apprenticeship learning, and enable accurately inferring the preferences of a human in order to assist them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/basis-for-intentions-efficient-inverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Evaluation for Decision Tree Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-evaluation-for-decision-tree-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We transfer distances on clusterings to the building process of decision trees, and as a consequence extend the classical ID3 algorithm to perform modifications based on the global distance of the tree to the ground truth--instead of considering single leaves.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-evaluation-for-decision-tree-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Video Analysis on Large-Scale Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sports-video-analysis-on-large-scale-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel large-scale NBA dataset for Sports Video Analysis (NSVA) with a focus on captioning, to address the above challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sports-video-analysis-on-large-scale-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Diverse Document Representations with Deep Query Interactions for Dense Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-diverse-document-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new dense retrieval model which learns diverse document representations with deep query interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-diverse-document-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRIT-VLP: Grouped Mini-batch Sampling for Efficient Vision and Language Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grit-vlp-grouped-mini-batch-sampling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to the mainstream VLP methods, we highlight that two routinely applied steps during pre-training have crucial impact on the performance of the pre-trained model: in-batch hard negative sampling for image-text matching (ITM) and assigning the large masking probability for the masked language modeling (MLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grit-vlp-grouped-mini-batch-sampling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrast-Phys: Unsupervised Video-based Remote Physiological Measurement via Spatiotemporal Contrast</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrast-phys-unsupervised-video-based-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, supervised rPPG methods require face videos and ground truth physiological signals for model training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrast-phys-unsupervised-video-based-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Map of Diverse Synthetic Stable Roommates Instances</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-map-of-diverse-synthetic-stable-roommates</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Focusing on Stable Roommates (SR) instances, we contribute to the toolbox for conducting experiments for stable matching problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-map-of-diverse-synthetic-stable-roommates</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPB-REC: Non-parametric Assessment of Uncertainty in Deep-learning-based MRI Reconstruction from Undersampled Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/npb-rec-non-parametric-assessment-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrated the added-value of our approach on the multi-coil brain MRI dataset, from the fastmri challenge, in comparison to the baseline E2E-VarNet with and without inference-time dropout.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/npb-rec-non-parametric-assessment-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Occlusion-Aware Instance Segmentation via BiLayer Network Architectures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occlusion-aware-instance-segmentation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike previous instance segmentation methods, we model image formation as a composition of two overlapping layers, and propose Bilayer Convolutional Network (BCNet), where the top layer detects occluding objects (occluders) and the bottom layer infers partially occluded instances (occludees).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occlusion-aware-instance-segmentation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Message Passing for Visual Relationship Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-message-passing-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual relationship detection aims to detect the interactions between objects in an image; however, this task suffers from combinatorial explosion due to the variety of objects and interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-message-passing-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LWGNet: Learned Wirtinger Gradients for Fourier Ptychographic Phase Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lwgnet-learned-wirtinger-gradients-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fourier Ptychographic Microscopy (FPM) is an imaging procedure that overcomes the traditional limit on Space-Bandwidth Product (SBP) of conventional microscopes through computational means.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lwgnet-learned-wirtinger-gradients-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKDCGN: Source-free Knowledge Distillation of Counterfactual Generative Networks using cGANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skdcgn-source-free-knowledge-distillation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, as an additional contribution, our paper conducts a thorough study on the composition mechanism of the CGNs, to gain a better understanding of how each mechanism influences the classification accuracy of an invariant classifier.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skdcgn-source-free-knowledge-distillation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CheXRelNet: An Anatomy-Aware Model for Tracking Longitudinal Relationships between Chest X-Rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chexrelnet-an-anatomy-aware-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the progress in utilizing deep learning to automate chest radiograph interpretation and disease diagnosis tasks, change between sequential Chest X-rays (CXRs) has received limited attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chexrelnet-an-anatomy-aware-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Plain Vision Transformer Towards Remote Sensing Foundation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-plain-vision-transformer-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we resort to plain vision transformers with about 100 million parameters and make the first attempt to propose large vision models customized for RS tasks and explore how such large models perform.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-plain-vision-transformer-towards</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
