<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 09:13:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Affordance Grounding from Demonstration Video to Target Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affordance-grounding-from-demonstration-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Humans excel at learning from expert demonstrations and solving their own problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affordance-grounding-from-demonstration-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intersection over Union with smoothing for bounding box regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intersection-over-union-with-smoothing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main principle is adding a smoothing part to the original IoU, where the smoothing part is given by a linear space with values that increases from the ground truth bounding box to the border of the input image, and thus covers the whole spatial search space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intersection-over-union-with-smoothing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning a Deep Color Difference Metric for Photographic Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-deep-color-difference-metric-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most well-established and widely used color difference (CD) metrics are handcrafted and subject-calibrated against uniformly colored patches, which do not generalize well to photographic images characterized by natural scene complexities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-deep-color-difference-metric-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A large-scale dataset for end-to-end table recognition in the wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-dataset-for-end-to-end-table</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a new large-scale dataset named Table Recognition Set (TabRecSet) with diverse table forms sourcing from multiple scenarios in the wild, providing complete annotation dedicated to end-to-end TR research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-dataset-for-end-to-end-table</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniDistill: A Universal Cross-Modality Knowledge Distillation Framework for 3D Object Detection in Bird's-Eye View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidistill-a-universal-cross-modality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of 3D object detection for autonomous driving, the sensor portfolio including multi-modality and single-modality is diverse and complex.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidistill-a-universal-cross-modality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIDiM: Contrastive Learning for Image Denoising in Microscopy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clidim-contrastive-learning-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Microscopy images often suffer from high levels of noise, which can hinder further analysis and interpretation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clidim-contrastive-learning-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label-Free Liver Tumor Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-free-liver-tumor-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that AI models can accurately segment liver tumors without the need for manual annotation by using synthetic tumors in CT scans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-free-liver-tumor-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Describing and Organizing Semantic Web and Machine Learning Systems in the SWeMLS-KG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/describing-and-organizing-semantic-web-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In line with the general trend in artificial intelligence research to create intelligent systems that combine learning and symbolic components, a new sub-area has emerged that focuses on combining machine learning (ML) components with techniques developed by the Semantic Web (SW) community - Semantic Web Machine Learning (SWeML for short).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/describing-and-organizing-semantic-web-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Federated Learning on Long-Tailed Data via Adversarial Feature Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-federated-learning-on-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized Federated Learning (PFL) aims to learn personalized models for each client based on the knowledge across all clients in a privacy-preserving manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-federated-learning-on-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Survey on Test-Time Adaptation under Distribution Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-survey-on-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Test-time adaptation (TTA), an emerging paradigm, has the potential to adapt a pre-trained model to unlabeled data during testing, before making predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-survey-on-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Few-shot Learning of Dense Prediction Tasks with Visual Token Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-few-shot-learning-of-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Visual Token Matching (VTM), a universal few-shot learner for arbitrary dense prediction tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-few-shot-learning-of-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Neural Topic Models with Wasserstein Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-neural-topic-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topic modeling is a dominant method for exploring document collections on the web and in digital libraries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-neural-topic-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-Based Reinforcement Learning with Isolated Imaginations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-based-reinforcement-learning-with-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On top of our previous work, we further consider the sparse dependencies between controllable and noncontrollable states, address the training collapse problem of state decoupling, and validate our approach in transfer learning setups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-based-reinforcement-learning-with-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffTAD: Temporal Action Detection with Proposal Denoising Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difftad-temporal-action-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, we establish the denoising process in the Transformer decoder (e. g., DETR) by introducing a temporal location query design with faster convergence in training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difftad-temporal-action-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVA-CLIP: Improved Training Techniques for CLIP at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eva-clip-improved-training-techniques-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach incorporates new techniques for representation learning, optimization, and augmentation, enabling EVA-CLIP to achieve superior performance compared to previous CLIP models with the same number of parameters but significantly smaller training costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eva-clip-improved-training-techniques-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Video Object Detection with Learnable Object-Centric Global Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-video-object-detection-with-learnable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore long-term temporal visual correspondence-based optimization for 3D video object detection in this work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-video-object-detection-with-learnable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnable Graph Matching: A Practical Paradigm for Data Association</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-graph-matching-a-practical-paradigm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For image matching, our method outperforms state-of-the-art methods with half training data and iterations on a popular indoor dataset, ScanNet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-graph-matching-a-practical-paradigm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuralPCI: Spatio-temporal Neural Field for 3D Point Cloud Multi-frame Non-linear Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralpci-spatio-temporal-neural-field-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In light of these issues, we present NeuralPCI: an end-to-end 4D spatio-temporal Neural field for 3D Point Cloud Interpolation, which implicitly integrates multi-frame information to handle nonlinear large motions for both indoor and outdoor scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralpci-spatio-temporal-neural-field-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimpleNet: A Simple Network for Image Anomaly Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplenet-a-simple-network-for-image-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SimpleNet consists of four components: (1) a pre-trained Feature Extractor that generates local features, (2) a shallow Feature Adapter that transfo local features towards target domain, (3) a simple Anomaly Feature Generator that counterfeits anomaly features by adding Gaussian noise to normal features, and (4) a binary Anomaly Discriminator that distinguishes anomaly features from normal features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplenet-a-simple-network-for-image-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoCon: A Data Set on Combined Contextualized Research Artifact Use</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cocon-a-data-set-on-combined-contextualized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enable more holistic analyses and systems dealing with academic publications and their content, we propose CoCon, a large scholarly data set reflecting the combined use of research artifacts, contextualized in academic publications' full-text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cocon-a-data-set-on-combined-contextualized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Composed Image Retrieval with Textual Inversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-composed-image-retrieval-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Composed Image Retrieval (CIR) aims to retrieve a target image based on a query composed of a reference image and a relative caption that describes the difference between the two images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-composed-image-retrieval-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable Local Feature Pre-training for Deformable Shape Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-local-feature-pre-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that with proper training, learned features can be useful in such tasks, but, crucially, only with an appropriate choice of the receptive field size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-local-feature-pre-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learned Image Compression with Mixed Transformer-CNN Architectures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learned-image-compression-with-mixed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing LIC methods are Convolutional Neural Networks-based (CNN-based) or Transformer-based, which have different advantages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learned-image-compression-with-mixed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architecturing Binarized Neural Networks for Traffic Sign Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/architecturing-binarized-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traffic signs support road safety and managing the flow of traffic, hence are an integral part of any vision system for autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/architecturing-binarized-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Granularity Archaeological Dating of Chinese Bronze Dings Based on a Knowledge-Guided Relation Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-archaeological-dating-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The archaeological dating of bronze dings has played a critical role in the study of ancient Chinese history.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-archaeological-dating-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>unarXive 2022: All arXiv Publications Pre-Processed for NLP, Including Structured Full-Text and Citation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unarxive-2022-all-arxiv-publications-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale data sets on scholarly publications are the basis for a variety of bibliometric analyses and natural language processing (NLP) applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unarxive-2022-all-arxiv-publications-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambiguity-Resistant Semi-Supervised Learning for Dense Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambiguity-resistant-semi-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It employs a "divide-and-conquer" strategy and separately exploits positives for the classification and localization task, which is more robust to the assignment ambiguity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambiguity-resistant-semi-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatially Adaptive Self-Supervised Learning for Real-World Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatially-adaptive-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[And we extend the blind-spot network to a blind-neighborhood network (BNN) for providing supervision on flat areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatially-adaptive-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Hidden Positives for Unsupervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-hidden-positives-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we add the loss propagating to local hidden positives, semantically similar nearby patches, in proportion to the predefined similarity scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-hidden-positives-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blind Image Quality Assessment via Vision-Language Correspondence: A Multitask Learning Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-image-quality-assessment-via-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim at advancing blind image quality assessment (BIQA), which predicts the human perception of image quality without any reference information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-image-quality-assessment-via-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Error-mitigated Quantum Approximate Optimization via Learning-based Adaptive Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/error-mitigated-quantum-approximate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantum approximate optimization algorithm (QAOA), one of the most representative quantum-classical hybrid algorithms, is designed to solve certain combinatorial optimization problems by transforming a discrete optimization problem into a classical optimization problem over a continuous circuit parameter domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/error-mitigated-quantum-approximate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Video Multi-Frame Interpolation and Deblurring under Unknown Exposure Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-video-multi-frame-interpolation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, on the seemingly implausible x16 interpolation task, our method outperforms existing methods by more than 1. 5 dB in terms of PSNR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-video-multi-frame-interpolation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MD-VQA: Multi-Dimensional Quality Assessment for UGC Live Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/md-vqa-multi-dimensional-quality-assessment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[User-generated content (UGC) live videos are often bothered by various distortions during capture procedures and thus exhibit diverse visual qualities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/md-vqa-multi-dimensional-quality-assessment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manifold Learning by Mixture Models of VAEs for Inverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manifold-learning-by-mixture-models-of-vaes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representing a manifold of very high-dimensional data with generative models has been shown to be computationally efficient in practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manifold-learning-by-mixture-models-of-vaes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Action Changes by Measuring Verb-Adverb Textual Relationships</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-action-changes-by-measuring-verb</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of this work is to understand the way actions are performed in videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-action-changes-by-measuring-verb</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Ranking Ensembles for Hyperparameter Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-ranking-ensembles-for-hyperparameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatically optimizing the hyperparameters of Machine Learning algorithms is one of the primary open questions in AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-ranking-ensembles-for-hyperparameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Semantic-Visual Mutual Adaption for Generalized Zero-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-semantic-visual-mutual-adaption</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalized Zero-Shot Learning (GZSL) identifies unseen categories by knowledge transferred from the seen domain, relying on the intrinsic interactions between visual and semantic information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-semantic-visual-mutual-adaption</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recovering 3D Hand Mesh Sequence from a Single Blurry Image: A New Dataset and Temporal Unfolding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recovering-3d-hand-mesh-sequence-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to the new dataset, we propose BlurHandNet, a baseline network for accurate 3D hand mesh recovery from a blurry hand image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recovering-3d-hand-mesh-sequence-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Adaptation from Repeated Traversals for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-adaptation-from-repeated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For a self-driving car to operate reliably, its perceptual system must generalize to the end-user's environment -- ideally without additional annotation efforts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-adaptation-from-repeated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScarceNet: Animal Pose Estimation with Scarce Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scarcenet-animal-pose-estimation-with-scarce</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose the ScarceNet, a pseudo label-based approach to generate artificial labels for the unlabeled images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scarcenet-animal-pose-estimation-with-scarce</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-DreamBooth: Protecting users from personalized text-to-image synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anti-dreambooth-protecting-users-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the complicated formulation of DreamBooth and Diffusion-based text-to-image models, our methods effectively defend users from the malicious use of those models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anti-dreambooth-protecting-users-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SwiftFormer: Efficient Additive Attention for Transformer-based Real-time Mobile Vision Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swiftformer-efficient-additive-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using our proposed efficient additive attention, we build a series of models called "SwiftFormer" which achieves state-of-the-art performance in terms of both accuracy and mobile inference speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swiftformer-efficient-additive-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Multi-Model Fitting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-multi-model-fitting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Geometric model fitting is a challenging but fundamental computer vision problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-multi-model-fitting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-PINN: Generative Pre-Trained Physics-Informed Neural Networks toward non-intrusive Meta-learning of parametric PDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-pinn-generative-pre-trained-physics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The meta-network adaptively ``learns'' the parametric dependence of the system and ``grows'' this hidden layer one neuron at a time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-pinn-generative-pre-trained-physics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Attention as Disentangler for Compositional Zero-shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-attention-as-disentangler-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key to CZSL is learning the disentanglement of the attribute-object composition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-attention-as-disentangler-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANI-Net: Uncalibrated Photometric Stereo by Differentiable Shadow Handling, Anisotropic Reflectance Modeling, and Neural Inverse Rendering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dani-net-uncalibrated-photometric-stereo-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the ambiguity is alleviated on non-Lambertian objects, the problem is still difficult to solve for more general objects with complex shapes introducing irregular shadows and general materials with complex reflectance like anisotropic reflectance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dani-net-uncalibrated-photometric-stereo-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D-Aware Multi-Class Image-to-Image Translation with NeRFs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-aware-multi-class-image-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the second step, based on the well-trained multi-class 3D-aware GAN architecture, that preserves view-consistency, we construct a 3D-aware I2I translation system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-aware-multi-class-image-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dimensionality Collapse: Optimal Measurement Selection for Low-Error Infinite-Horizon Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dimensionality-collapse-optimal-measurement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implementations of both an approximate dynamic programming formulation and the proposed alternative are illustrated using an extended Kalman filter for state estimation, with results on simulated systems with limit cycles and chaotic behavior demonstrating a linear improvement in the CRLB as a function of the number of collapsing dimensions of the system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dimensionality-collapse-optimal-measurement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Contextualized Topic Models with Negative Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-contextualized-topic-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topic modeling has emerged as a dominant method for exploring large document collections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-contextualized-topic-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Artistic Image Aesthetics Assessment: a Large-scale Dataset and a New Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-artistic-image-aesthetics-assessment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill the gap in the field of artistic image aesthetics assessment (AIAA), we first introduce a large-scale AIAA dataset: Boldbrush Artistic Image Dataset (BAID), which consists of 60, 337 artistic images covering various art forms, with more than 360, 000 votes from online users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-artistic-image-aesthetics-assessment</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
