<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 11:21:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Object Masks with Transformers for Unsupervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-object-masks-with-transformers-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents MaskDistill: a novel framework for unsupervised semantic segmentation based on three key ideas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-object-masks-with-transformers-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Understanding Sharpness-Aware Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-understanding-sharpness-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further study the properties of the implicit bias on non-linear networks empirically, where we show that fine-tuning a standard model with SAM can lead to significant generalization improvements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-understanding-sharpness-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cumulative culture spontaneously emerges in artificial navigators who are social and memory-guided</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cumulative-culture-spontaneously-emerges-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This subtly biased pairs' routes, and the resulting efficiency improvement is thus regression to the goal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cumulative-culture-spontaneously-emerges-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singular Value Fine-tuning: Few-shot Segmentation requires Few-parameters Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/singular-value-fine-tuning-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we rethink the paradigm and explore a new regime: {\em fine-tuning a small part of parameters in the backbone}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/singular-value-fine-tuning-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A universal synthetic dataset for machine learning on spectroscopic data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-universal-synthetic-dataset-for-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To assist in the development of machine learning methods for automated classification of spectroscopic data, we have generated a universal synthetic dataset that can be used for model validation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-universal-synthetic-dataset-for-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biologically Inspired Neural Path Finding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biologically-inspired-neural-path-finding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The human brain can be considered to be a graphical structure comprising of tens of billions of biological neurons connected by synapses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biologically-inspired-neural-path-finding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IGN : Implicit Generative Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ign-implicit-generative-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we build recent advances in distributional reinforcement learning to give a state-of-art distributional variant of the model based on the IQN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ign-implicit-generative-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Object Masks with Transformers for Unsupervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-object-masks-with-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents MaskDistill: a novel framework for unsupervised semantic segmentation based on three key ideas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-object-masks-with-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Convolutional Networks on Untrusted Platforms Using 2D Holographic Reduced Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deploying-convolutional-networks-on-untrusted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the computational cost of running inference for a neural network, the need to deploy the inferential steps on a third party's compute environment or hardware is common.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deploying-convolutional-networks-on-untrusted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Universal Sequence Representation Learning for Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-universal-sequence-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to develop effective sequential recommenders, a series of sequence representation learning (SRL) methods are proposed to model historical user behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-universal-sequence-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markov Decision Processes under Model Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/markov-decision-processes-under-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a general framework for Markov decision problems under model uncertainty in a discrete-time infinite horizon setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/markov-decision-processes-under-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Graph Generative Models with Contrastively Learned Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-graph-generative-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A wide range of models have been proposed for Graph Generative Models, necessitating effective methods to evaluate their quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-graph-generative-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singular Value Fine-tuning: Few-shot Segmentation requires Few-parameters Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/singular-value-fine-tuning-few-shot-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we rethink the paradigm and explore a new regime: {\em fine-tuning a small part of parameters in the backbone}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/singular-value-fine-tuning-few-shot-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributed Adversarial Training to Robustify Deep Neural Networks at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributed-adversarial-training-to-robustify-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spurred by that, we propose distributed adversarial training (DAT), a large-batch adversarial training framework implemented over multiple machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributed-adversarial-training-to-robustify-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markov Chain Score Ascent: A Unifying Framework of Variational Inference with Markovian Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/markov-chain-score-ascent-a-unifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Minimizing the inclusive Kullback-Leibler (KL) divergence with stochastic gradient descent (SGD) is challenging since its gradient is defined as an integral over the posterior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/markov-chain-score-ascent-a-unifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EmProx: Neural Network Performance Estimation For Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emprox-neural-network-performance-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The effectiveness of such strategies varies in terms of accuracy and fit and query time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emprox-neural-network-performance-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Inference-Based Root Cause Analysis for Online Service Systems with Intervention Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-inference-based-root-cause-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fault diagnosis is critical in many domains, as faults may lead to safety threats or economic losses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-inference-based-root-cause-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Structure-aware Transformer over Interaction Proposals for Human-Object Interaction Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-structure-aware-transformer-over-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such design decomposes the process of HOI set prediction into two subsequent phases, i. e., an interaction proposal generation is first performed, and then followed by transforming the non-parametric interaction proposals into HOI predictions via a structure-aware Transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-structure-aware-transformer-over-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPLHR-CT Dataset and Transformer Baseline for Volumetric Super-Resolution from CT Scans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rplhr-ct-dataset-and-transformer-baseline-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In clinical practice, anisotropic volumetric medical images with low through-plane resolution are commonly used due to short acquisition time and lower storage cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rplhr-ct-dataset-and-transformer-baseline-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning-based Placement of Charging Stations in Urban Road Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-based-placement-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We formulate the Placement of Charging Stations problem as a non-linear integer optimisation problem that seeks the optimal positions for charging stations and the optimal number of charging piles of different charging types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-based-placement-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning a Degradation-Adaptive Network for Light Field Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-degradation-adaptive-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing DNN-based LF image SR methods are developed on a single fixed degradation (e. g., bicubic downsampling), and thus cannot be applied to super-resolve real LF images with diverse degradations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-degradation-adaptive-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Domain Adaptive Object Detection with Probabilistic Teacher</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-domain-adaptive-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we conduct anchor adaptation in parallel with localization adaptation, since anchor can be regarded as a learnable parameter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-domain-adaptive-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Diffusion Energy-Based Model for Interpretable Text Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-diffusion-energy-based-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Latent space Energy-Based Models (EBMs), also known as energy-based priors, have drawn growing interests in generative modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-diffusion-energy-based-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Classification of Optical Galaxy Morphology Using Unsupervised Learning Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-classification-of-optical-galaxy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results were compared to the volunteer classifications of the Galaxy Zoo DECaLS dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-classification-of-optical-galaxy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Learning for Unsupervised Domain Adaptation of Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-for-unsupervised-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our framework, we further capture semantic variation between source and target domain via nearest-neighbor contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-for-unsupervised-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMMNA-Net for Overall Survival Time Prediction of Brain Tumor Patients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmmna-net-for-overall-survival-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several deep learning-based methods are proposed for the OS time prediction on multi-modal MRI problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmmna-net-for-overall-survival-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constraint Guided Gradient Descent: Guided Training with Inequality Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constraint-guided-gradient-descent-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to other neuro-symbolic approaches, the proposed method converges to a model that satisfies any inequality constraint on the training data and does not require to first transform the constraints into some ad-hoc term that is added to the learning (optimisation) objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constraint-guided-gradient-descent-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Legal Text Summarization: A Text Normalisation-based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indian-legal-text-summarization-a-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The authors experimented with two state-of-the-art domain-independent models for legal text summarization, namely BART and PEGASUS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indian-legal-text-summarization-a-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Polyp Segmentation with Multiple Kernel Dilated Convolution Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-polyp-segmentation-with-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The detection and removal of precancerous polyps through colonoscopy is the primary technique for the prevention of colorectal cancer worldwide.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-polyp-segmentation-with-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Featurized Query R-CNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/featurized-query-r-cnn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The query mechanism introduced in the DETR method is changing the paradigm of object detection and recently there are many query-based methods have obtained strong object detection performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/featurized-query-r-cnn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iCITRIS: Causal Representation Learning for Instantaneous Temporal Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icitris-causal-representation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work has shown that one can reconstruct the causal variables from temporal sequences of observations under the assumption that there are no instantaneous causal relations between them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icitris-causal-representation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Uncertainty with Artificial Neural Networks for Improved Predictive Process Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-uncertainty-with-artificial-neural-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The inability of artificial neural networks to assess the uncertainty of their predictions is an impediment to their widespread use.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-uncertainty-with-artificial-neural-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silver-Bullet-3D at ManiSkill 2021: Learning-from-Demonstrations and Heuristic Rule-based Methods for Object Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/silver-bullet-3d-at-maniskill-2021-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an overview and comparative analysis of our systems designed for the following two tracks in SAPIEN ManiSkill Challenge 2021: No Interaction Track: The No Interaction track targets for learning policies from pre-collected demonstration trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/silver-bullet-3d-at-maniskill-2021-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STD-NET: Search of Image Steganalytic Deep-learning Architecture via Hierarchical Tensor Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/std-net-search-of-image-steganalytic-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a normalized distortion threshold to evaluate the sensitivity of each involved convolutional layer of the base model to guide STD-NET to compress target network in an efficient and unsupervised approach, and obtain two network structures of different shapes with low computation cost and similar performance compared with the original one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/std-net-search-of-image-steganalytic-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Generalized Specialist Approach To Train Quality Resilient Snapshot Ensemble</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-generalized-specialist-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During each training cycle of G-Specialist, a model is fine-tuned on the synthetic images generated by RQMixup, intermixing clean and distorted images of a particular distortion at a randomly chosen level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-generalized-specialist-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human Mobility Prediction with Causal and Spatial-constrained Multi-task Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-mobility-prediction-with-causal-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next location prediction is one decisive task in individual human mobility modeling and is usually viewed as sequence modeling, solved with Markov or RNN-based methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-mobility-prediction-with-causal-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLIPv2: Unifying Localization and Vision-Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glipv2-unifying-localization-and-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present GLIPv2, a grounded VL understanding model, that serves both localization tasks (e. g., object detection, instance segmentation) and Vision-Language (VL) understanding tasks (e. g., VQA, image captioning).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glipv2-unifying-localization-and-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Narrowing the Gap: Improved Detector Training with Noisy Location Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/narrowing-the-gap-improved-detector-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments for both synthesized and real-world scenarios consistently demonstrate the effectiveness of our approach, e. g., our method increases the degraded performance of the FCOS detector from 33. 6% AP to 35. 6% AP on COCO.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/narrowing-the-gap-improved-detector-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Case-Based Inverse Reinforcement Learning Using Temporal Coherence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/case-based-inverse-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a prior, we assume that the higher-level strategy is to reach an unknown target state area, which we hypothesize is a valid prior for many domains in Reinforcement Learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/case-based-inverse-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic Gradient Descent without Full Data Shuffle</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-gradient-descent-without-full-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we first conduct a systematic empirical study on existing data shuffling strategies, which reveals that all existing strategies have room for improvement -- they all suffer in terms of I/O performance or convergence rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-gradient-descent-without-full-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-based Spatial Transformer with Memory Replay for Multi-future Pedestrian Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-spatial-transformer-with-memory-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pedestrian trajectory prediction is an essential and challenging task for a variety of real-life applications such as autonomous driving and robotic motion planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-spatial-transformer-with-memory-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balancing Bias and Variance for Active Weakly Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-bias-and-variance-for-active-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose to conduct novel active deep multiple instance learning that samples a small subset of informative instances for annotation, aiming to significantly boost the instance-level prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-bias-and-variance-for-active-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Functional Information Perspective on Model Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-functional-information-perspective-on-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work suggests a theoretical framework for model interpretability by measuring the contribution of relevant features to the functional entropy of the network with respect to the input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-functional-information-perspective-on-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Context-Aware Deviations in Process Executions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-context-aware-deviations-in-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We have implemented the proposed framework as a web service that can be extended to various contexts and deviation detection methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-context-aware-deviations-in-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning-Based MR Image Re-parameterization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-mr-image-re</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, using MR image re-parameterization to predict and estimate the contrast in these imaging scans can be an effective alternative.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-mr-image-re</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Selection using e-values</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-selection-using-e-values</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of supervised parametric models, we introduce the concept of e-values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-selection-using-e-values</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>gDDIM: Generalized denoising diffusion implicit models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gddim-generalized-denoising-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our goal is to extend the denoising diffusion implicit model (DDIM) to general diffusion models~(DMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gddim-generalized-denoising-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Imbalanced Datasets with Maximum Margin Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-imbalanced-datasets-with-maximum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A learning algorithm referred to as Maximum Margin (MM) is proposed for considering the class-imbalance data learning issue: the trained model tends to predict the majority of classes rather than the minority ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-imbalanced-datasets-with-maximum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convergence and Recovery Guarantees of the K-Subspaces Method for Subspace Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convergence-and-recovery-guarantees-of-the-k</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The K-subspaces (KSS) method is a generalization of the K-means method for subspace clustering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convergence-and-recovery-guarantees-of-the-k</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Defense Against Free-rider Attack From the Perspective of Model Weight Evolving Frequency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-defense-against-free-rider</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we reconsider the defense from a novel perspective, i. e., model weight evolving frequency. Empirically, we gain a novel insight that during the FL's training, the model weight evolving frequency of free-riders and that of benign clients are significantly different.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-defense-against-free-rider</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
