<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 09:12:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bidirectional Generative Framework for Cross-domain Aspect-based Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-generative-framework-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-domain aspect-based sentiment analysis (ABSA) aims to perform various fine-grained sentiment analysis tasks on a target domain by transferring knowledge from a source domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-generative-framework-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamics of niche construction in adaptable populations evolving in diverse environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamics-of-niche-construction-in-adaptable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study NC in simulation environments that consist of multiple, diverse niches and populations that evolve their plasticity, evolvability and niche-constructing behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamics-of-niche-construction-in-adaptable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tailoring Instructions to Student's Learning Levels Boosts Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-instructions-to-student-s-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It has been commonly observed that a teacher model with superior performance does not necessarily result in a stronger student, highlighting a discrepancy between current teacher training practices and effective knowledge transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-instructions-to-student-s-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Implicit Bias Using SHAP Feature Importance and Fuzzy Cognitive Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-implicit-bias-using-shap-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we integrate the concepts of feature importance with implicit bias in the context of pattern classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-implicit-bias-using-shap-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content-Adaptive Downsampling in Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/content-adaptive-downsampling-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many convolutional neural networks (CNNs) rely on progressive downsampling of their feature maps to increase the network's receptive field and decrease computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/content-adaptive-downsampling-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPI-rical: Data-Driven MPI Distributed Parallelism Assistance with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpi-rical-data-driven-mpi-distributed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic source-to-source parallelization of serial code for shared and distributed memory systems is a challenging task in high-performance computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpi-rical-data-driven-mpi-distributed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view MERA Subspace Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-mera-subspace-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Benefiting from multiple interactions among orthogonal/semi-orthogonal (low-rank) factors, the low-rank MERA has a strong representation power to capture the complex inter/intra-view information in the self-representation tensor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-mera-subspace-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Self-Knowledge Distillation with Multi-source Information Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-self-knowledge-distillation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce a Distillation with Reverse Guidance (DRG) method that considers different levels of information extracted by the model, including edge, shape, and detail of the input data, to construct a more informative teacher.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-self-knowledge-distillation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Global Interaction and Local Alignment for Audio-Visual Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-global-interaction-and-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most existing AVSR approaches simply fuse the audio and visual features by concatenation, without explicit interactions to capture the deep correlations between them, which results in sub-optimal multimodal representations for downstream speech recognition task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-global-interaction-and-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Optimal Strategies for Wordle and General Guessing Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-optimal-strategies-for-wordle-and-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent popularity of Wordle has revived interest in guessing games.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-optimal-strategies-for-wordle-and-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Alignment Pre-training for Cross-lingual Sentence Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-alignment-pre-training-for-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies have shown that dual encoder models trained with the sentence-level translation ranking task are effective methods for cross-lingual sentence embedding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-alignment-pre-training-for-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Continual Learning Without the Storage Constraint</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-continual-learning-without-the-storage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online continual learning (OCL) research has primarily focused on mitigating catastrophic forgetting with fixed and limited storage allocation throughout the agent's lifetime.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-continual-learning-without-the-storage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blind Image Quality Assessment via Transformer Predicted Error Map and Perceptual Quality Token</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-image-quality-assessment-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we firstly generate the predicted error map by pre-training one model consisting of a Transformer encoder and decoder, in which the objective difference between the distorted and the reference images is used as supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-image-quality-assessment-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-Training to Learn in Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-to-learn-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In-context learning, where pre-trained language models learn to perform tasks from task examples and instructions in their contexts, has attracted much attention in the NLP community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-to-learn-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satisfiability-Aided Language Models Using Declarative Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/satisfiability-aided-language-models-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new satisfiability-aided language modeling approach for improving the reasoning capabilities of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/satisfiability-aided-language-models-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concurrent Misclassification and Out-of-Distribution Detection for Semantic Segmentation via Energy-Based Normalizing Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concurrent-misclassification-and-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FlowEneDet achieves promising results on Cityscapes, Cityscapes-C, FishyScapes and SegmentMeIfYouCan benchmarks in IDM/OOD detection when applied to pretrained DeepLabV3+ and SegFormer semantic segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concurrent-misclassification-and-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Establishing Shared Query Understanding in an Open Multi-Agent System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/establishing-shared-query-understanding-in-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we demonstrate a use-case where our method can be applied for the task of cooperative query answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/establishing-shared-query-understanding-in-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid and Collaborative Passage Reranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-and-collaborative-passage-reranking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In passage retrieval system, the initial passage retrieval results may be unsatisfactory, which can be refined by a reranking scheme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-and-collaborative-passage-reranking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OmniSafe: An Infrastructure for Accelerating Safe Reinforcement Learning Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnisafe-an-infrastructure-for-accelerating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AI systems empowered by reinforcement learning (RL) algorithms harbor the immense potential to catalyze societal advancement, yet their deployment is often impeded by significant safety concerns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnisafe-an-infrastructure-for-accelerating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models are Built-in Autoregressive Search Engines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-built-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this limitation, recent autoregressive search engines replace the dual-encoder architecture by directly generating identifiers for relevant documents in the candidate pool.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-built-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Reinforcement Learning for Network Control via Bi-Level Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-reinforcement-learning-for-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimization problems over dynamic networks have been extensively studied and widely used in the past decades to formulate numerous real-world problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-reinforcement-learning-for-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xPQA: Cross-Lingual Product Question Answering across 12 Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xpqa-cross-lingual-product-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To study this practical industrial task, we present xPQA, a large-scale annotated cross-lingual PQA dataset in 12 languages across 9 branches, and report results in (1) candidate ranking, to select the best English candidate containing the information to answer a non-English question; and (2) answer generation, to generate a natural-sounding non-English answer based on the selected English candidate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xpqa-cross-lingual-product-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Translation: Improving Domain Robustness of Neural Machine Translation with Intermediate Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-translation-improving-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we introduce a full-permutation multi-task learning to alleviate the spurious causal relations from intermediate sequences to the target, which results from exposure bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-translation-improving-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAMario: Experimental Approach to Reptile Algorithm -- Reinforcement Learning for Mario</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ramario-experimental-approach-to-reptile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research paper presents an experimental approach to using the Reptile algorithm for reinforcement learning to train a neural network to play Super Mario Bros. We implement the Reptile algorithm using the Super Mario Bros Gym library and TensorFlow in Python, creating a neural network model with a single convolutional layer, a flatten layer, and a dense layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ramario-experimental-approach-to-reptile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUG: Single-dataset Unified Generalization for 3D Point Cloud Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sug-single-dataset-unified-generalization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, different from previous 2D DG works, we focus on the 3D DG problem and propose a Single-dataset Unified Generalization (SUG) framework that only leverages a single source dataset to alleviate the unforeseen domain differences faced by a well-trained source model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sug-single-dataset-unified-generalization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study on Google Research Football Multi-agent Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-google-research</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few multi-agent reinforcement learning (MARL) research on Google Research Football (GRF) focus on the 11v11 multi-agent full-game scenario and to the best of our knowledge, no open benchmark on this scenario has been released to the public.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-google-research</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wavelet-based Unsupervised Label-to-Image Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavelet-based-unsupervised-label-to-image-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic Image Synthesis (SIS) is a subclass of image-to-image translation where a semantic layout is used to generate a photorealistic image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavelet-based-unsupervised-label-to-image-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Level Global Context Cross Consistency Model for Semi-Supervised Ultrasound Image Segmentation with Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-global-context-cross-consistency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach enables the effective transfer of probability distribution knowledge to the segmentation network, resulting in improved segmentation accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-global-context-cross-consistency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Semantic Variation Prediction using the Distribution of Sibling Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-semantic-variation-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, some of the previously associated meanings of a target word can become obsolete over time (e. g. meaning of gay as happy), while novel usages of existing words are observed (e. g. meaning of cell as a mobile phone).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-semantic-variation-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal Extractive Summarization of U.S. Court Opinions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/legal-extractive-summarization-of-u-s-court</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper tackles the task of legal extractive summarization using a dataset of 430K U. S. court opinions with key passages annotated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/legal-extractive-summarization-of-u-s-court</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inverse Rendering of Translucent Objects using Physical and Neural Renderers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverse-rendering-of-translucent-objects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enhance the supervision of the proposed neural renderer, we also propose an augmented loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverse-rendering-of-translucent-objects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMBRACE: Evaluation and Modifications for Boosting RACE</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embrace-evaluation-and-modifications-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When training and evaluating machine reading comprehension models, it is very important to work with high-quality datasets that are also representative of real-world reading comprehension tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embrace-evaluation-and-modifications-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global and Local Mixture Consistency Cumulative Learning for Long-tailed Visual Recognitions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-and-local-mixture-consistency-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, our goal is to design a simple learning paradigm for long-tail visual recognition, which not only improves the robustness of the feature extractor but also alleviates the bias of the classifier towards head classes while reducing the training skills and overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-and-local-mixture-consistency-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Ensemble Approach for Automated Theorem Proving Based on Efficient Name Invariant Graph Neural Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ensemble-approach-for-automated-theorem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NIAGRA addresses this problem by using 1) improved Graph Neural Networks for learning name-invariant formula representations that is tailored for their unique characteristics and 2) an efficient ensemble approach for automated theorem proving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ensemble-approach-for-automated-theorem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DopUS-Net: Quality-Aware Robotic Ultrasound Imaging based on Doppler Signal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dopus-net-quality-aware-robotic-ultrasound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results demonstrate that the proposed approach with the re-identification process can significantly improve the accuracy and robustness of the segmentation results (dice score: from 0:54 to 0:86; intersection over union: from 0:47 to 0:78).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dopus-net-quality-aware-robotic-ultrasound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FeatFSDA: Towards Few-shot Domain Adaptation for Video-based Activity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/featfsda-towards-few-shot-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address few-shot domain adaptation for video-based activity recognition (FSDA-AR), which leverages a very small amount of labeled target videos to achieve effective adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/featfsda-towards-few-shot-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marsellus: A Heterogeneous RISC-V AI-IoT End-Node SoC with 2-to-8b DNN Acceleration and 30%-Boost Adaptive Body Biasing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marsellus-a-heterogeneous-risc-v-ai-iot-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Marsellus, an all-digital heterogeneous SoC for AI-IoT end-nodes fabricated in GlobalFoundries 22nm FDX that combines 1) a general-purpose cluster of 16 RISC-V Digital Signal Processing (DSP) cores attuned for the execution of a diverse range of workloads exploiting 4-bit and 2-bit arithmetic extensions (XpulpNN), combined with fused MAC&LOAD operations and floating-point support; 2) a 2-8bit Reconfigurable Binary Engine (RBE) to accelerate 3x3 and 1x1 (pointwise) convolutions in DNNs; 3) a set of On-Chip Monitoring (OCM) blocks connected to an Adaptive Body Biasing (ABB) generator and a hardware control loop, enabling on-the-fly adaptation of transistor threshold voltages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marsellus-a-heterogeneous-risc-v-ai-iot-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NLG Evaluation Metrics Beyond Correlation Analysis: An Empirical Metric Preference Checklist</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlg-evaluation-metrics-beyond-correlation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we analyze NLG automatic metrics based on whether human evaluation aspect is used as context or objective to compute the metrics: (i) Task-agnostic and (ii) Human-aligned.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlg-evaluation-metrics-beyond-correlation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEPR: Knowledge Enhancement and Plausibility Ranking for Generative Commonsense Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kepr-knowledge-enhancement-and-plausibility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within the experimental models, the T5-based GenCQA with KEPR obtains the best performance, which is up to 60. 91% at the primary canonical metric Inc@3.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kepr-knowledge-enhancement-and-plausibility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Consistency in Text-based Financial Forecasting Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-consistency-in-text-based-financial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using FinTrust, we show that the consistency of state-of-the-art NLP models for financial forecasting is poor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-consistency-in-text-based-financial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion Question Answering via Modular Motion Programs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-question-answering-via-modular-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to build artificial intelligence systems that can perceive and reason with human behavior in the real world, we must first design models that conduct complex spatio-temporal reasoning over motion sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-question-answering-via-modular-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coreference-aware Double-channel Attention Network for Multi-party Dialogue Reading Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coreference-aware-double-channel-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The corresponding solutions contribute to the answer-oriented reasoning on a series of well-organized and thread-aware conversational contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coreference-aware-double-channel-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mode Approximation Makes Good Vision-Language Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mode-approximation-makes-good-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advance of large-scale model technologies, parameter-efficient transfer learning (PETL) has swept across various fields of Artificial Intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mode-approximation-makes-good-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SRRM: Semantic Region Relation Model for Indoor Scene Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srrm-semantic-region-relation-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the remarkable success of convolutional neural networks in various computer vision tasks, recognizing indoor scenes still presents a significant challenge due to their complex composition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srrm-semantic-region-relation-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CQE: A Comprehensive Quantity Extractor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cqe-a-comprehensive-quantity-extractor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to other information extraction approaches, interestingly only a few works exist that describe methods for a proper extraction and representation of quantities in text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cqe-a-comprehensive-quantity-extractor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back Translation for Speech-to-text Translation Without Transcripts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/back-translation-for-speech-to-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the remarkable success of back translation in MT, we develop a back translation algorithm for ST (BT4ST) to synthesize pseudo ST data from monolingual target data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/back-translation-for-speech-to-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Boltzmann Machines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-boltzmann-machines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conditional generative models are capable of using contextual information as input to create new imaginative outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-boltzmann-machines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising Diffusion Models for Plug-and-Play Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-models-for-plug-and-play</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although diffusion models have shown impressive performance for high-quality image synthesis, their potential to serve as a generative denoiser prior to the plug-and-play IR methods remains to be further explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-models-for-plug-and-play</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLIP: Language-Image Pre-training for Person Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plip-language-image-pre-training-for-person</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate that our model not only significantly improves existing methods on all these tasks, but also shows great ability in the few-shot and domain generalization settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plip-language-image-pre-training-for-person</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning with Layer Pruning on Medical Report Summarization and Medical Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-with-layer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing size of language models raises great research interests in parameter-efficient fine-tuning (e. g. Adapter, LoRA and prompt tuning) that freezes the pre-trained model, and injects small-scale trainable parameters for multiple downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-with-layer</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
