<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 09:12:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Textron: Weakly Supervised Multilingual Text Detection Through Data Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textron-weakly-supervised-multilingual-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to solve this problem, we propose TEXTRON, a Data Programming-based approach, where users can plug various text detection methods into a weak supervision-based learning framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textron-weakly-supervised-multilingual-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ODTrack: Online Dense Temporal Token Learning for Visual Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odtrack-online-dense-temporal-token-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate the above problem, we propose a simple, flexible and effective video-level tracking pipeline, named \textbf{ODTrack}, which densely associates the contextual relationships of video frames in an online token propagation manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odtrack-online-dense-temporal-token-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototypical Information Bottlenecking and Disentangling for Multimodal Cancer Survival Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-information-bottlenecking-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite advantages of multimodal learning for cancer survival prediction, massive redundancy in multimodal data prevents it from extracting discriminative and compact information: (1) An extensive amount of intra-modal task-unrelated information blurs discriminability, especially for gigapixel whole slide images (WSIs) with many patches in pathology and thousands of pathways in genomic data, leading to an ``intra-modal redundancy" issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-information-bottlenecking-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-Aware Interaction Network for RGB-T Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-interaction-network-for-rgb-t</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a Context-Aware Complementary Reasoning (CACR) module aimed at establishing the complementary relationship between multimodal features with the long-term context in both spatial and channel dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-interaction-network-for-rgb-t</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poisoning Attacks against Recommender Systems: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poisoning-attacks-against-recommender-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This survey paper provides a systematic and up-to-date review of the research landscape on Poisoning Attacks against Recommendation (PAR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poisoning-attacks-against-recommender-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model Capabilities in Perioperative Risk Prediction and Prognostication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-capabilities-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We achieve F1 scores of 0. 50 for ASA Physical Status Classification, 0. 81 for ICU admission, and 0. 86 for hospital mortality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-capabilities-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting of Implicit Neural Representation-based Image Denoiser</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-of-implicit-neural-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implicit Neural Representation (INR) has emerged as an effective method for unsupervised image denoising.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-of-implicit-neural-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks for Surfactant Multi-Property Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-for-surfactant-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key factor in the predictive ability of QSPR and GNN models is the data available for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-for-surfactant-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S$^{2}$-DMs:Skip-Step Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-2-dms-skip-step-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the CIFAR10 dataset, models trained using our algorithm showed an improvement of 3. 27% to 14. 06% over models trained with traditional methods across various sampling algorithms (DDIMs, PNDMs, DEIS) and different numbers of sampling steps (10, 20, ..., 1000).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-2-dms-skip-step-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the Suitability of Concept Drift Detection for Detecting Leakages in Water Distribution Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-suitability-of-concept</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore the potential of model-loss-based and distribution-based drift detection methods to tackle leakage detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-suitability-of-concept</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedSumm: A Multimodal Approach to Summarizing Code-Mixed Hindi-English Clinical Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medsumm-a-multimodal-approach-to-summarizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces the task of multimodal medical question summarization for codemixed input in a low-resource setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medsumm-a-multimodal-approach-to-summarizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Act as You Learn: Adaptive Decision-Making in Non-Stationary Markov Decision Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/act-as-you-learn-adaptive-decision-making-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing approaches for decision-making in NSMDPs have two major shortcomings: first, they assume that the updated environmental dynamics at the current time are known (although future dynamics can change); and second, planning is largely pessimistic, i. e., the agent acts ``safely'' to account for the non-stationary evolution of the environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/act-as-you-learn-adaptive-decision-making-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-Guided Spatio-Temporal Video Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-guided-spatio-temporal-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key of CG-STVG lies in two specially designed modules, including instance context generation (ICG), which focuses on discovering visual context information (in both appearance and motion) of the instance, and instance context refinement (ICR), which aims to improve the instance context from ICG by eliminating irrelevant or even harmful information from the context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-guided-spatio-temporal-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glance and Focus: Memory Prompting for Multi-Event Video Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glance-and-focus-memory-prompting-for-multi-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of that, we train an Encoder-Decoder to generate a set of dynamic event memories at the glancing stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glance-and-focus-memory-prompting-for-multi-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-4V(ision) is a Generalist Web Agent, if Grounded</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-4v-ision-is-a-generalist-web-agent-if</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent development on large multimodal models (LMMs), especially GPT-4V(ision) and Gemini, has been quickly expanding the capability boundaries of multimodal models beyond traditional tasks like image captioning and visual question answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-4v-ision-is-a-generalist-web-agent-if</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Large Language Models in Semantic Parsing for Conversational Question Answering over Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-large-language-models-in-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational question answering systems often rely on semantic parsing to enable interactive information retrieval, which involves the generation of structured database queries from a natural language input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-large-language-models-in-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonshot: Towards Controllable Video Generation and Editing with Multimodal Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moonshot-towards-controllable-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents Moonshot, a new video generation model that conditions simultaneously on multimodal inputs of image and text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moonshot-towards-controllable-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Prompt with Distribution-Based Feature Replay for Few-Shot Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-prompt-with-distribution-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When progressing to a new session, pseudo-features are sampled from old-class distributions combined with training images of the current session to optimize the prompt, thus enabling the model to learn new knowledge while retaining old knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-prompt-with-distribution-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Foundation Purchasing Model: Pretrained Generative Autoregression on Transaction Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-foundation-purchasing-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning models underpin many modern financial systems for use cases such as fraud detection and churn prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-foundation-purchasing-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Regularized Evidential Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-regularized-evidential-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Evidential Regression Network (ERN) represents a novel approach that integrates deep learning with Dempster-Shafer's theory to predict a target and quantify the associated uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-regularized-evidential-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Invariant Information Geometric Method for High-Dimensional Online Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-invariant-information-geometric-method-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a full invariance oriented evolution strategies algorithm, derived from its corresponding framework, that effectively rivals the leading Bayesian optimization method in tasks with dimensions at the upper limit of Bayesian capability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-invariant-information-geometric-method-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concurrent Brainstorming &amp; Hypothesis Satisfying: An Iterative Framework for Enhanced Retrieval-Augmented Generation (R2CBR3H-SR)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concurrent-brainstorming-hypothesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing the complexity of comprehensive information retrieval, this study introduces an innovative, iterative retrieval-augmented generation system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concurrent-brainstorming-hypothesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A First Look at Information Highlighting in Stack Overflow Answers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-first-look-at-information-highlighting-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For training recommendation models, we choose CNN and BERT models for each type of formatting (i. e., Bold, Italic, Code, and Heading) using the information highlighting dataset we collected from SO answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-first-look-at-information-highlighting-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRA-PCN: Point Cloud Completion with Intra- and Inter-level Cross-Resolution Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cra-pcn-point-cloud-completion-with-intra-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Point cloud completion is an indispensable task for recovering complete point clouds due to incompleteness caused by occlusion, limited sensor resolution, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cra-pcn-point-cloud-completion-with-intra-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Structured Data as Graph for Data-to-Text Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-structured-data-as-graph-for-data-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we unify different types of structured data (i. e., table, key-value data, knowledge graph) into the graph format and cast different data-to-text generation tasks as graph-to-text generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-structured-data-as-graph-for-data-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Continual Anomaly Detection with Contrastively-learned Prompt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-continual-anomaly-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised Anomaly Detection (UAD) with incremental training is crucial in industrial manufacturing, as unpredictable defects make obtaining sufficient labeled data infeasible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-continual-anomaly-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable network reconstruction in subquadratic time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-network-reconstruction-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Network reconstruction consists in determining the unobserved pairwise couplings between $N$ nodes given only observational data on the resulting behavior that is conditioned on those couplings -- typically a time-series or independent samples from a graphical model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-network-reconstruction-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motif-aware Riemannian Graph Neural Network with Generative-Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motif-aware-riemannian-graph-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In light of the issues above, we propose the problem of \emph{Motif-aware Riemannian Graph Representation Learning}, seeking a numerically stable encoder to capture motif regularity in a diverse-curvature manifold without labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motif-aware-riemannian-graph-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$f$-Divergence Based Classification: Beyond the Use of Cross-Entropy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/f-divergence-based-classification-beyond-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, driven by the challenge of improving the state-of-the-art approach, we propose a bottom-up method that leads us to the formulation of a new objective function (and posterior probability estimator) corresponding to a novel $f$-divergence referred to as shifted log (SL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/f-divergence-based-classification-beyond-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quokka: An Open-source Large Language Model ChatBot for Material Science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quokka-an-open-source-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the development of a specialized chatbot for materials science, leveraging the Llama-2 language model, and continuing pre-training on the expansive research articles in the materials science domain from the S2ORC dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quokka-an-open-source-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holistic Autonomous Driving Understanding by Bird's-Eye-View Injected Multi-Modal Large Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holistic-autonomous-driving-understanding-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BEV-InMLLM integrates multi-view, spatial awareness, and temporal semantics to enhance MLLMs' capabilities on NuInstruct tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holistic-autonomous-driving-understanding-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnamese Poem Generation &amp; The Prospect Of Cross-Language Poem-To-Poem Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vietnamese-poem-generation-the-prospect-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Poetry generation has been a challenging task in the field of Natural Language Processing, as it requires the model to understand the nuances of language, sentiment, and style.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vietnamese-poem-generation-the-prospect-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable manifold learning by uniform landmark sampling and constrained locally linear embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-manifold-learning-by-uniform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a pivotal approach in machine learning and data science, manifold learning aims to uncover the intrinsic low-dimensional structure within complex nonlinear manifolds in high-dimensional space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-manifold-learning-by-uniform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DTBS: Dual-Teacher Bi-directional Self-training for Domain Adaptation in Nighttime Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dtbs-dual-teacher-bi-directional-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because the one-directional knowledge transfer from a single teacher is insufficient to adapt to a large domain shift.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dtbs-dual-teacher-bi-directional-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off-Road LiDAR Intensity Based Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/off-road-lidar-intensity-based-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LiDAR is used in autonomous driving to provide 3D spatial information and enable accurate perception in off-road environments, aiding in obstacle detection, mapping, and path planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/off-road-lidar-intensity-based-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Study of Knowledge Editing for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-study-of-knowledge-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we first define the knowledge editing problem and then provide a comprehensive review of cutting-edge approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-study-of-knowledge-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JMA: a General Algorithm to Craft Nearly Optimal Targeted Adversarial Example</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jma-a-general-algorithm-to-craft-nearly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most of the approaches proposed so far to craft targeted adversarial examples against Deep Learning classifiers are highly suboptimal and typically rely on increasing the likelihood of the target class, thus implicitly focusing on one-hot encoding settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jma-a-general-algorithm-to-craft-nearly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IdentiFace : A VGG Based Multimodal Facial Biometric System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identiface-a-vgg-based-multimodal-facial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce "IdentiFace" which is a multimodal facial biometric system that combines the core of facial recognition with some of the most important soft biometric traits such as gender, face shape, and emotion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identiface-a-vgg-based-multimodal-facial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indoor Obstacle Discovery on Reflective Ground via Monocular Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indoor-obstacle-discovery-on-reflective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Note that obstacle and reflection can be separated by the ground plane in 3D space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indoor-obstacle-discovery-on-reflective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auffusion: Leveraging the Power of Diffusion and Large Language Models for Text-to-Audio Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auffusion-leveraging-the-power-of-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Drawing inspiration from state-of-the-art Text-to-Image (T2I) diffusion models, we introduce Auffusion, a TTA system adapting T2I model frameworks to TTA task, by effectively leveraging their inherent generative strengths and precise cross-modal alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auffusion-leveraging-the-power-of-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Families of costs with zero and nonnegative MTW tensor in optimal transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/families-of-costs-with-zero-and-nonnegative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compute explicitly the MTW tensor (or cross curvature) for the optimal transport problem on $\mathbb{R}^n$ with a cost function of form $\mathsf{c}(x, y) = \mathsf{u}(x^{\mathfrak{t}}y)$, where $\mathsf{u}$ is a scalar function with inverse $\mathsf{s}$, $x^{\ft}y$ is a nondegenerate bilinear pairing of vectors $x, y$ belonging to an open subset of $\mathbb{R}^n$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/families-of-costs-with-zero-and-nonnegative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astraios: Parameter-Efficient Instruction Tuning Code Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/astraios-parameter-efficient-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through investigations across 5 tasks and 8 different datasets encompassing both code comprehension and code generation tasks, we find that FFT generally leads to the best downstream performance across all scales, and PEFT methods differ significantly in their efficacy based on the model scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/astraios-parameter-efficient-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring community structure in attributed hypergraphs using stochastic block models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-community-structure-in-attributed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hypergraphs are a representation of complex systems involving interactions among more than two entities and allow to investigation of higher-order structure and dynamics in real-world complex systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-community-structure-in-attributed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recent Advances in Text Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recent-advances-in-text-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we propose a new statistical model for ranking the citation impacts of $11$ topics, and we also build a cross-topic citation graph to illustrate how research results on different topics spread to one another.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recent-advances-in-text-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Computational Framework for Behavioral Assessment of LLM Therapists</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-computational-framework-for-behavioral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, we compare the behavior of LLM therapists against that of high- and low-quality human therapy, and study how their behavior can be modulated to better reflect behaviors observed in high-quality therapy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-computational-framework-for-behavioral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ToolEyes: Fine-Grained Evaluation for Tool Learning Capabilities of Large Language Models in Real-world Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tooleyes-fine-grained-evaluation-for-tool</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, a sole emphasis on outcomes disregards the intricate capabilities essential for LLMs to effectively utilize tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tooleyes-fine-grained-evaluation-for-tool</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Translation Testing via Syntactic Tree Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-translation-testing-via-syntactic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results show that STP can accurately find 5, 073 unique erroneous translations in Google Translate and 5, 100 unique erroneous translations in Bing Microsoft Translator (400% more than state-of-the-art techniques), with 64. 5% and 65. 4% precision, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-translation-testing-via-syntactic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Large Language Models on Controllable Generation under Diversified Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-language-models-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While large language models (LLMs) have exhibited impressive instruction-following capabilities, it is still unclear whether and to what extent they can respond to explicit constraints that might be entailed in various instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-language-models-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An attempt to generate new bridge types from latent space of generative adversarial network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attempt-to-generate-new-bridge-types-from-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative adversarial network can create new bridge types by organically combining different structural components on the basis of human original bridge types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attempt-to-generate-new-bridge-types-from-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking RAFT for Efficient Optical Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-raft-for-efficient-optical-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these problems, this paper proposes a novel approach based on the RAFT framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-raft-for-efficient-optical-flow</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
