<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 09:12:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Put Your Money Where Your Mouth Is: Evaluating Strategic Planning and Execution of LLM Agents in an Auction Arena</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/put-your-money-where-your-mouth-is-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, even our most advanced models (GPT-4) are occasionally surpassed by heuristic baselines and human agents, highlighting the potential for further improvements in the design of LLM agents and the important role that our simulation environment can play in further testing and refining agent architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/put-your-money-where-your-mouth-is-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sentence-level Prompts Benefit Composed Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentence-level-prompts-benefit-composed-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Composed image retrieval (CIR) is the task of retrieving specific images by using a query that involves both a reference image and a relative caption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentence-level-prompts-benefit-composed-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query and Response Augmentation Cannot Help Out-of-domain Math Reasoning Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-and-response-augmentation-cannot-help</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we conduct an investigation for such data augmentation in math reasoning and are intended to answer: (1) What strategies of data augmentation are more effective; (2) What is the scaling relationship between the amount of augmented data and model performance; and (3) Can data augmentation incentivize generalization to out-of-domain mathematical reasoning tasks?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-and-response-augmentation-cannot-help</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphLLM: Boosting Graph Reasoning Ability of Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphllm-boosting-graph-reasoning-ability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This synergy equips LLMs with the ability to proficiently interpret and reason on graph data, harnessing the superior expressive power of graph learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphllm-boosting-graph-reasoning-ability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-grained Audio-Visual Joint Representations for Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-audio-visual-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Audio-visual large language models (LLM) have drawn significant attention, yet the fine-grained combination of both input streams is rather under-explored, which is challenging but necessary for LLMs to understand general video inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-audio-visual-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humanoid Agents: Platform for Simulating Human-like Generative Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humanoid-agents-platform-for-simulating-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Just as computational simulations of atoms, molecules and cells have shaped the way we study the sciences, true-to-life simulations of human-like agents can be valuable tools for studying human behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humanoid-agents-platform-for-simulating-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Multi-modal Entity Alignment via Iteratively Fusing Modality Similarity Paths</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-multi-modal-entity-alignment-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The objective of Entity Alignment (EA) is to identify equivalent entity pairs from multiple Knowledge Graphs (KGs) and create a more comprehensive and unified KG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-multi-modal-entity-alignment-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Judge for Evaluating Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-judge-for-evaluating-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of Large Language Models (LLMs) has substantially expanded the range of tasks they can address.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-judge-for-evaluating-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ParFam -- Symbolic Regression Based on Continuous Global Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parfam-symbolic-regression-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present our new method ParFam that utilizes parametric families of suitable symbolic functions to translate the discrete symbolic regression problem into a continuous one, resulting in a more straightforward setup compared to current state-of-the-art methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parfam-symbolic-regression-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Optimal Timing Strategies for Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-optimal-timing-strategies-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deciding the best future execution time is a critical task in many business activities while evolving time series forecasting, and optimal timing strategy provides such a solution, which is driven by observed data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-optimal-timing-strategies-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffCPS: Diffusion Model based Constrained Policy Search for Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffcps-diffusion-model-based-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Constrained policy search (CPS) is a fundamental problem in offline reinforcement learning, which is generally solved by advantage weighted regression (AWR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffcps-diffusion-model-based-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Language Models with Human Preferences via a Bayesian Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-language-models-with-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this alignment, current popular methods leverage a reinforcement learning (RL) approach with a reward model trained on feedback from humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-language-models-with-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look into Automatic Evaluation Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-into-automatic-evaluation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we analyze LLM evaluation (Chiang and Lee, 2023) and G-Eval (Liu et al., 2023), and we discuss how those details in the evaluation process change how well the ratings given by LLMs correlate with human ratings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-into-automatic-evaluation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Robust Early-Exiting Framework for Autoregressive Language Models with Synchronized Parallel Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-robust-early-exiting-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle the high inference latency exhibited by autoregressive language models, previous studies have proposed an early-exiting framework that allocates adaptive computation paths for each token based on the complexity of generating the subsequent token.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-robust-early-exiting-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uni3DETR: Unified 3D Detection Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni3detr-unified-3d-detection-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Uni3DETR, a unified 3D detector that addresses indoor and outdoor 3D detection within the same framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni3detr-unified-3d-detection-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple and Robust Framework for Cross-Modality Medical Image Segmentation applied to Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-and-robust-framework-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a simple framework to achieve fair image segmentation of multiple modalities using a single conditional model that adapts its normalization layers based on the input type, trained with non-registered interleaved mixed data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-and-robust-framework-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problem-Solving Guide: Predicting the Algorithm Tags and Difficulty for Competitive Programming Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/problem-solving-guide-predicting-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we also consider predicting the difficulty levels of algorithm problems, which can be used as useful guidance to calculate the required time to solve that problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/problem-solving-guide-predicting-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Full-Convolutional Siamese Tracker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-full-convolutional-siamese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, existing lightweight trackers only achieve balance between 2-3 points in terms of parameters, performance, Flops and FPS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-full-convolutional-siamese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XAL: EXplainable Active Learning Makes Classifiers Better Low-resource Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xal-explainable-active-learning-makes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During the selection of unlabeled data, we combine the predictive uncertainty of the encoder and the explanation score of the decoder to acquire informative data for annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xal-explainable-active-learning-makes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SocialCircle: Learning the Angle-based Social Interaction Representation for Pedestrian Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/socialcircle-learning-the-angle-based-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analyzing and forecasting trajectories of agents like pedestrians and cars in complex scenes has become more and more significant in many intelligent systems and applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/socialcircle-learning-the-angle-based-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larth: Dataset and Machine Translation for Etruscan</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/larth-dataset-and-machine-translation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Etruscan is an ancient language spoken in Italy from the 7th century BC to the 1st century AD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/larth-dataset-and-machine-translation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Care3D: An Active 3D Object Detection Dataset of Real Robotic-Care Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/care3d-an-active-3d-object-detection-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As labor shortage increases in the health sector, the demand for assistive robotics grows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/care3d-an-active-3d-object-detection-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchor-Intermediate Detector: Decoupling and Coupling Bounding Boxes for Accurate Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anchor-intermediate-detector-decoupling-and-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The corner-aware head is able to score the corners of each bounding box to facilitate the coupling between corner points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anchor-intermediate-detector-decoupling-and-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mBBC: Exploring the Multilingual Maze</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbbc-exploring-the-multilingual-maze</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using the self-supervised task of next token prediction, we assess their performance across a diverse set of languages, with a focus on understanding the impact of resource availability, word order, language family, and script type on model accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbbc-exploring-the-multilingual-maze</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-bayesian-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Various BO algorithms have been theoretically shown to enjoy upper bounds on their cumulative regret which are sub-linear in the number T of iterations, and a regret lower bound of Omega(sqrt(T)) has been derived which represents the unavoidable regrets for any classical BO algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-bayesian-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiIns: A High-Quality Dataset for Controlled Text Editing by Natural Language Instruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikiins-a-high-quality-dataset-for-controlled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the problem of controlled text editing by natural language instruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikiins-a-high-quality-dataset-for-controlled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hieros: Hierarchical Imagination on Structured State Space Sequence World Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hieros-hierarchical-imagination-on-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the special properties of S5 layers, our method can train in parallel and predict next world states iteratively during imagination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hieros-hierarchical-imagination-on-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toolink: Linking Toolkit Creation and Using through Chain-of-Solving on Open-Source Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toolink-linking-toolkit-creation-and-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first validate the efficacy of Toolink in harnessing the model's creativity and CoS ability on ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toolink-linking-toolkit-creation-and-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast-DetectGPT: Efficient Zero-Shot Detection of Machine-Generated Text via Conditional Probability Curvature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-detectgpt-efficient-zero-shot-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown the ability to produce fluent and cogent content, presenting both productivity opportunities and societal risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-detectgpt-efficient-zero-shot-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepQTest: Testing Autonomous Driving Systems with Reinforcement Learning and Real-world Weather Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepqtest-testing-autonomous-driving-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, existing ADS testing techniques have limited effectiveness in ensuring the realism of test scenarios, especially the realism of weather conditions and their changes over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepqtest-testing-autonomous-driving-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZooPFL: Exploring Black-box Foundation Models for Personalized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zoopfl-exploring-black-box-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When personalized federated learning (FL) meets large foundation models, new challenges arise from various limitations in resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zoopfl-exploring-black-box-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GSLB: The Graph Structure Learning Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gslb-the-graph-structure-learning-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill this gap, we systematically analyze the performance of GSL in different scenarios and develop a comprehensive Graph Structure Learning Benchmark (GSLB) curated from 20 diverse graph datasets and 16 distinct GSL algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gslb-the-graph-structure-learning-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Data to Dialogue: Leveraging the Structure of Knowledge Graphs for Conversational Exploratory Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-data-to-dialogue-leveraging-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Exploratory search is an open-ended information retrieval process that aims at discovering knowledge about a topic or domain rather than searching for a specific answer or piece of information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-data-to-dialogue-leveraging-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEAR: A GPU-Centric Experience Replay System for Large Reinforcement Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gear-a-gpu-centric-experience-replay-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a distributed, GPU-centric experience replay system, GEAR, designed to perform scalable reinforcement learning (RL) with large sequence models (such as transformers).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gear-a-gpu-centric-experience-replay-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tailoring Self-Attention for Graph via Rooted Subtrees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-self-attention-for-graph-via-rooted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Attention mechanisms have made significant strides in graph learning, yet they still exhibit notable limitations: local attention faces challenges in capturing long-range information due to the inherent problems of the message-passing scheme, while global attention cannot reflect the hierarchical neighborhood structure and fails to capture fine-grained local information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-self-attention-for-graph-via-rooted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLatS: Principled Out-of-Distribution Detection with Feature-Based Likelihood Ratio Score</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flats-principled-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Backed by theoretical analysis, this paper advocates for the measurement of the "OOD-ness" of a test case $\boldsymbol{x}$ through the likelihood ratio between out-distribution $\mathcal P_{\textit{out}}$ and in-distribution $\mathcal P_{\textit{in}}$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flats-principled-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructDET: Diversifying Referring Object Detection with Generalized Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructdet-diversifying-referring-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to encompass common detection expressions, we involve emerging vision-language model (VLM) and large language model (LLM) to generate instructions guided by text prompts and object bbxs, as the generalizations of foundation models are effective to produce human-like expressions (e. g., describing object property, category, and relationship).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructdet-diversifying-referring-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UReader: Universal OCR-free Visually-situated Language Understanding with Multimodal Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ureader-universal-ocr-free-visually-situated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text is ubiquitous in our visual world, conveying crucial information, such as in documents, websites, and everyday photographs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ureader-universal-ocr-free-visually-situated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distantly-Supervised Joint Entity and Relation Extraction with Noise-Robust Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distantly-supervised-joint-entity-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing research primarily addresses only one type of noise, thereby limiting the effectiveness of noise reduction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distantly-supervised-joint-entity-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persis: A Persian Font Recognition Pipeline Using Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persis-a-persian-font-recognition-pipeline-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[What happens if we encounter a suitable font for our design work but do not know its name?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persis-a-persian-font-recognition-pipeline-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DialCoT Meets PPO: Decomposing and Exploring Reasoning Paths in Smaller Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialcot-meets-ppo-decomposing-and-exploring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chain-of-Thought (CoT) prompting has proven to be effective in enhancing the reasoning capabilities of Large Language Models (LLMs) with at least 100 billion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialcot-meets-ppo-decomposing-and-exploring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building an Open-Vocabulary Video CLIP Model with Better Architectures, Optimization and Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-an-open-vocabulary-video-clip-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant results achieved by Contrastive Language-Image Pretraining (CLIP) in zero-shot image recognition, limited effort has been made exploring its potential for zero-shot video recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-an-open-vocabulary-video-clip-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OV-PARTS: Towards Open-Vocabulary Part Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ov-parts-towards-open-vocabulary-part</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, part segmentation introduces an open granularity challenge due to the diverse and often ambiguous definitions of parts in the open world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ov-parts-towards-open-vocabulary-part</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Corrected Expected Improvement Acquisition Function Under Noisy Observations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-corrected-expected-improvement-acquisition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sequential maximization of expected improvement (EI) is one of the most widely used policies in Bayesian optimization because of its simplicity and ability to handle noisy observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-corrected-expected-improvement-acquisition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying GNN Performance with Low Rank Kernel Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-gnn-performance-with-low-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We posit that many of the current GNN architectures may be over-engineered.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-gnn-performance-with-low-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Investigation of LLMs' Inefficacy in Understanding Converse Relations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-investigation-of-llms-inefficacy-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our ConvRE features two tasks, Re2Text and Text2Re, which are formulated as multi-choice question answering to evaluate LLMs' ability to determine the matching between relations and associated text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-investigation-of-llms-inefficacy-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOD: A Benchmark Dataset for Harmful Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hod-a-benchmark-dataset-for-harmful-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new benchmark dataset for harmful object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hod-a-benchmark-dataset-for-harmful-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AANet: Aggregation and Alignment Network with Semi-hard Positive Sample Mining for Hierarchical Place Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aanet-aggregation-and-alignment-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we propose a Dynamically Aligning Local Features (DALF) algorithm to align the local features under spatial constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aanet-aggregation-and-alignment-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symmetrical Linguistic Feature Distillation with CLIP for Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetrical-linguistic-feature-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore the potential of the Contrastive Language-Image Pretraining (CLIP) model in scene text recognition (STR), and establish a novel Symmetrical Linguistic Feature Distillation framework (named CLIP-OCR) to leverage both visual and linguistic knowledge in CLIP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetrical-linguistic-feature-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering hidden geometry in Transformers via disentangling position and context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-hidden-geometry-in-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given embedding vector $\boldsymbol{h}_{c, t} \in \mathbb{R}^d$ at sequence position $t \le T$ in a sequence (or context) $c \le C$, extracting the mean effects yields the decomposition \[ \boldsymbol{h}_{c, t} = \boldsymbol{\mu} + \mathbf{pos}_t + \mathbf{ctx}_c + \mathbf{resid}_{c, t} \] where $\boldsymbol{\mu}$ is the global mean vector, $\mathbf{pos}_t$ and $\mathbf{ctx}_c$ are the mean vectors across contexts and across positions respectively, and $\mathbf{resid}_{c, t}$ is the residual vector.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-hidden-geometry-in-transformers</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
