<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 21:06:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Deformable Model Driven Neural Rendering for High-fidelity 3D Reconstruction of Human Heads Under Low-View Settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deformable-model-driven-neural-rendering-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We represent 3D human heads as the zero level-set of a composed signed distance field that consists of a smooth template, a non-rigid deformation, and a high-frequency displacement field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deformable-model-driven-neural-rendering-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GP-VTON: Towards General Purpose Virtual Try-on via Collaborative Local-Flow Global-Parsing Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gp-vton-towards-general-purpose-virtual-try</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, compared with the previous global warping mechanism, LFGP employs local flows to warp garments parts individually, and assembles the local warped results via the global garment parsing, resulting in reasonable warped parts and a semantic-correct intact garment even with challenging inputs. On the other hand, our DGT training strategy dynamically truncates the gradient in the overlap area and the warped garment is no more required to meet the boundary constraint, which effectively avoids the texture squeezing problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gp-vton-towards-general-purpose-virtual-try</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Adversarial Training Through Adaptive Instance-wise Loss Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-adversarial-training-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that during training an overall reduction of adversarial loss is achieved by sacrificing a considerable proportion of training samples to be more vulnerable to adversarial attack, which results in an uneven distribution of adversarial vulnerability among data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-adversarial-training-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Vision-Language Pretraining with Free Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-vision-language-pretraining-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FLM successfully frees the prediction rate from the tie-up with the corruption rate while allowing the corruption spans to be customized for each token to be predicted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-vision-language-pretraining-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Error Analysis Prompting Enables Human-Like Translation Evaluation in Large Language Models: A Case Study on ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/error-analysis-prompting-enables-human-like</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results indicate that by combining Chain-of-Thoughts and Error Analysis, a new prompting method called \textbf{\texttt{Error Analysis Prompting}}, LLMs like ChatGPT can \textit{generate human-like MT evaluations at both the system and segment level}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/error-analysis-prompting-enables-human-like</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniTS: A Universal Time Series Analysis Framework with Self-supervised Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/units-a-universal-time-series-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning has emerged as a powerful tool for time series analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/units-a-universal-time-series-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2PCNet: Two-Phase Consistency Training for Day-to-Night Unsupervised Domain Adaptive Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2pcnet-two-phase-consistency-training-for-day</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object detection at night is a challenging problem due to the absence of night image annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2pcnet-two-phase-consistency-training-for-day</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard Sample Matters a Lot in Zero-Shot Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-sample-matters-a-lot-in-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nonetheless, we find that the synthetic samples constructed in existing ZSQ methods can be easily fitted by models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-sample-matters-a-lot-in-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Particle Mean Field Variational Bayes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/particle-mean-field-variational-bayes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Mean Field Variational Bayes (MFVB) method is one of the most computationally efficient techniques for Bayesian inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/particle-mean-field-variational-bayes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Expert Language Models with Unsupervised Domain Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-expert-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models are typically trained densely: all parameters are updated with respect to all inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-expert-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zolly: Zoom Focal Length Correctly for Perspective-Distorted Human Mesh Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zolly-zoom-focal-length-correctly-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As it is hard to calibrate single-view RGB images in the wild, existing 3D human mesh reconstruction (3DHMR) methods either use a constant large focal length or estimate one based on the background environment context, which can not tackle the problem of the torso, limb, hand or face distortion caused by perspective camera projection when the camera is close to the human body.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zolly-zoom-focal-length-correctly-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>marl-jax: Multi-agent Reinforcement Leaning framework for Social Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marl-jax-multi-agent-reinforcement-leaning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present marl-jax, a multi-agent reinforcement learning software package for training and evaluating social generalization of the agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marl-jax-multi-agent-reinforcement-leaning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remind of the Past: Incremental Learning with Analogical Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remind-of-the-past-incremental-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It mimics the feature distribution of the target old class on the old model using only samples of new classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remind-of-the-past-incremental-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FishDreamer: Towards Fisheye Semantic Completion via Unified Image Outpainting and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fishdreamer-towards-fisheye-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper raises the new task of Fisheye Semantic Completion (FSC), where dense texture, structure, and semantics of a fisheye image are inferred even beyond the sensor field-of-view (FoV).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fishdreamer-towards-fisheye-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make-It-3D: High-Fidelity 3D Creation from A Single Image with Diffusion Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-it-3d-high-fidelity-3d-creation-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate the problem of creating high-fidelity 3D content from only a single image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-it-3d-high-fidelity-3d-creation-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Transport for Offline Imitation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-for-offline-imitation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Optimal Transport Reward labeling (OTR), an algorithm that assigns rewards to offline trajectories, with a few high-quality demonstrations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-for-offline-imitation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Scene Contrast: A Scalable Framework for Unsupervised 3D Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-scene-contrast-a-scalable-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a pioneering work, PointContrast conducts unsupervised 3D representation learning via leveraging contrastive learning over raw RGB-D frames and proves its effectiveness on various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-scene-contrast-a-scalable-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HRDoc: Dataset and Baseline Method Toward Hierarchical Reconstruction of Document Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrdoc-dataset-and-baseline-method-toward</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we proposed an encoder-decoder-based hierarchical document structure parsing system (DSPS) to tackle this problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrdoc-dataset-and-baseline-method-toward</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional Image-to-Video Generation with Latent Flow Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-image-to-video-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an approach for cI2V using novel latent flow diffusion models (LFDM) that synthesize an optical flow sequence in the latent space based on the given condition to warp the given image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-image-to-video-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StereoScene: BEV-Assisted Stereo Matching Empowers 3D Semantic Scene Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stereoscene-bev-assisted-stereo-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On top of the stereo and BEV representations, a mutual interactive aggregation (MIA) module is carefully devised to fully unleash their power.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stereoscene-bev-assisted-stereo-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Multiple Reliability Measures via Nuisance-extended Information Bottleneck</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-multiple-reliability-measures-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In practical scenarios where training data is limited, many predictive signals in the data can be rather from some biases in data acquisition (i. e., less generalizable), so that one cannot prevent a model from co-adapting on such (so-called) "shortcut" signals: this makes the model fragile in various distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-multiple-reliability-measures-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ImSPOC snapshot imaging spectrometer: image formation model and device characterization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-imspoc-snapshot-imaging-spectrometer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the demand for capturing spectral information with finer detail has increased, requiring hyperspectral imaging devices capable of acquiring the required information with increased temporal, spatial and spectral resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-imspoc-snapshot-imaging-spectrometer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalist: Decoupling Natural and Robust Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalist-decoupling-natural-and-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The parameters of base learners are collected and combined to form a global learner at intervals during the training process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalist-decoupling-natural-and-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Making the Most of ChatGPT for Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-making-the-most-of-chatgpt-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that: 1) The performance of ChatGPT depends largely on temperature, and a lower temperature usually can achieve better performance; 2) Emphasizing the task information further improves ChatGPT's performance, particularly in complex MT tasks; 3) Introducing domain information can elicit ChatGPT's generalization ability and improve its performance in the specific domain; 4) ChatGPT tends to generate hallucinations for non-English-centric MT tasks, which can be partially addressed by our proposed prompts but still need to be highlighted for the MT/NLP community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-making-the-most-of-chatgpt-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$k$NN Prompting: Beyond-Context Learning with Calibration-Free Nearest Neighbor Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-nn-prompting-beyond-context-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In-Context Learning (ICL), which formulates target tasks as prompt completion conditioned on in-context demonstrations, has become the prevailing utilization of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-nn-prompting-beyond-context-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CF-Font: Content Fusion for Few-shot Font Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cf-font-content-fusion-for-few-shot-font</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Content and style disentanglement is an effective way to achieve few-shot font generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cf-font-content-fusion-for-few-shot-font</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeing Through the Glass: Neural 3D Reconstruction of Object Inside a Transparent Container</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seeing-through-the-glass-neural-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we define a new problem of recovering the 3D geometry of an object confined in a transparent enclosure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seeing-through-the-glass-neural-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINe: Out-of-Distribution Detection by Leveraging Important Neurons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/line-out-of-distribution-detection-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, from the perspective of neurons in the deep layer of the model representing high-level features, we introduce a new aspect for analyzing the difference in model outputs between in-distribution data and OOD data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/line-out-of-distribution-detection-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Euler Characteristic Tools For Topological Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/euler-characteristic-tools-for-topological</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, we study Euler characteristic techniques in topological data analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/euler-characteristic-tools-for-topological</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatDoctor: A Medical Chat Model Fine-tuned on LLaMA Model using Medical Domain Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatdoctor-a-medical-chat-model-fine-tuned-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent large language models (LLMs) in the general domain, such as ChatGPT, have shown remarkable success in following instructions and producing human-like responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatdoctor-a-medical-chat-model-fine-tuned-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Principles of Forgetting in Domain-Incremental Semantic Segmentation in Adverse Weather Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/principles-of-forgetting-in-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks for scene perception in automated vehicles achieve excellent results for the domains they were trained on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/principles-of-forgetting-in-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Old Knowledge to Continually Learn New Classes in Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-old-knowledge-to-continually-learn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Class-incremental continual learning is a core step towards developing artificial intelligence systems that can continuously adapt to changes in the environment by learning new concepts without forgetting those previously learned.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-old-knowledge-to-continually-learn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best of Both Worlds: Multimodal Contrastive Learning with Tabular and Imaging Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/best-of-both-worlds-multimodal-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical datasets and especially biobanks, often contain extensive tabular data with rich clinical information in addition to images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/best-of-both-worlds-multimodal-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABLE-NeRF: Attention-Based Rendering with Learnable Embeddings for Neural Radiance Field</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/able-nerf-attention-based-rendering-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method, which we call ABLE-NeRF, significantly reduces `blurry' glossy surfaces in rendering and produces realistic translucent surfaces which lack in prior art.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/able-nerf-attention-based-rendering-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCL: Continual Contrastive Learning for LiDAR Place Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccl-continual-contrastive-learning-for-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results show that our CCL consistently improves the performance of different methods in different environments outperforming the state-of-the-art continual learning method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccl-continual-contrastive-learning-for-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transthoracic super-resolution ultrasound localization microscopy of myocardial vasculature in patients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transthoracic-super-resolution-ultrasound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Micro-vascular flow in the myocardium is of significant importance clinically but remains poorly understood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transthoracic-super-resolution-ultrasound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Get ready for a party": Exploring smarter smart spaces with help from large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/get-ready-for-a-party-exploring-smarter-smart</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first explore the feasibility of a system that places an LLM at the center of command inference and action planning, showing that LLMs have the capacity to infer intent behind vague, context-dependent commands like "get ready for a party" and respond with concrete, machine-parseable instructions that can be used to control smart devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/get-ready-for-a-party-exploring-smarter-smart</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoupled Multimodal Distilling for Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-multimodal-distilling-for-emotion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specially, the representation of each modality is decoupled into two parts, i. e., modality-irrelevant/-exclusive spaces, in a self-regression manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-multimodal-distilling-for-emotion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Double Descent Demystified: Identifying, Interpreting &amp; Ablating the Sources of a Deep Learning Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/double-descent-demystified-identifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Double descent is a surprising phenomenon in machine learning, in which as the number of model parameters grows relative to the number of data, test error drops as models grow ever larger into the highly overparameterized (data undersampled) regime.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/double-descent-demystified-identifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query-Dependent Video Representation for Moment Retrieval and Highlight Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-dependent-video-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As we observe the insignificant role of a given query in transformer architectures, our encoding module starts with cross-attention layers to explicitly inject the context of text query into video representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-dependent-video-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paraphrase Detection: Human vs. Machine Content</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paraphrase-detection-human-vs-machine-content</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we identify four datasets as the most diverse and challenging for paraphrase detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paraphrase-detection-human-vs-machine-content</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReCOGS: How Incidental Details of a Logical Form Overshadow an Evaluation of Semantic Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recogs-how-incidental-details-of-a-logical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that this concern is realized for the COGS benchmark (Kim and Linzen, 2020).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recogs-how-incidental-details-of-a-logical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2D Floor Plan Segmentation Based on Down-sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2d-floor-plan-segmentation-based-on-down</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, floor plan segmentation has gained significant attention due to its wide range of applications in floor plan reconstruction and robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2d-floor-plan-segmentation-based-on-down</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuFace: Realistic 3D Neural Face Rendering from Multi-view Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuface-realistic-3d-neural-face-rendering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Realistic face rendering from multi-view images is beneficial to various computer vision and graphics applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuface-realistic-3d-neural-face-rendering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Learning for the Random Feature Model in the Student-Teacher Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-learning-for-the-random-feature-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Only when the student's hidden layer size is exponentially larger than the input dimension, an approach to perfect generalization is possible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-learning-for-the-random-feature-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAK: Attributing Model Behavior at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trak-attributing-model-behavior-at-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[That is, computationally tractable methods can struggle with accurately attributing model predictions in non-convex settings (e. g., in the context of deep neural networks), while methods that are effective in such regimes require training thousands of models, which makes them impractical for large models or datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trak-attributing-model-behavior-at-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantasia3D: Disentangling Geometry and Appearance for High-quality Text-to-3D Content Creation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fantasia3d-disentangling-geometry-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Key to Fantasia3D is the disentangled modeling and learning of geometry and appearance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fantasia3d-disentangling-geometry-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inherent Consistent Learning for Accurate Semi-supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inherent-consistent-learning-for-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-supervised medical image segmentation has attracted much attention in recent years because of the high cost of medical image annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inherent-consistent-learning-for-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PanoVPR: Towards Unified Perspective-to-Equirectangular Visual Place Recognition via Sliding Windows across the Panoramic View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panovpr-towards-unified-perspective-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual place recognition has received increasing attention in recent years as a key technology in autonomous driving and robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panovpr-towards-unified-perspective-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUG: A General Meeting Understanding and Generation Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mug-a-general-meeting-understanding-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To prompt SLP advancement, we establish a large-scale general Meeting Understanding and Generation Benchmark (MUG) to benchmark the performance of a wide range of SLP tasks, including topic segmentation, topic-level and session-level extractive summarization and topic title generation, keyphrase extraction, and action item detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mug-a-general-meeting-understanding-and</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
