<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 09:12:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>3D Diffuser Actor: Policy Diffusion with 3D Scene Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-diffuser-actor-policy-diffusion-with-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We marry diffusion policies and 3D scene representations for robot manipulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-diffuser-actor-policy-diffusion-with-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedKit: Enabling Cross-Platform Federated Learning for Android and iOS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedkit-enabling-cross-platform-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present FedKit, a federated learning (FL) system tailored for cross-platform FL research on Android and iOS devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedkit-enabling-cross-platform-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steering Conversational Large Language Models for Long Emotional Support Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steering-conversational-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we address the challenge of consistently following emotional support strategies in long conversations by large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steering-conversational-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compact and De-biased Negative Instance Embedding for Multi-Instance Learning on Whole-Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-and-de-biased-negative-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using this free annotation, we introduce a semi-supervision signal to de-bias the inter-slide variability and to capture the common factors of variation within normal patches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-and-de-biased-negative-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic Localization via Iterative Posterior Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-localization-via-iterative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon score-based learning, new interest in stochastic localization techniques has recently emerged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-localization-via-iterative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalised Drug Identifier for Cancer Treatment with Transformers using Auxiliary Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalised-drug-identifier-for-cancer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cancer remains a global challenge due to its growing clinical and economic burden.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalised-drug-identifier-for-cancer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodaMal: Contrastive Domain Adaptation for Malaria Detection in Low-Cost Microscopes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codamal-contrastive-domain-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Annotating images from LCM significantly increases the burden on medical experts compared to annotating images from high-cost microscopes (HCM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codamal-contrastive-domain-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ToolSword: Unveiling Safety Issues of Large Language Models in Tool Learning Across Three Stages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toolsword-unveiling-safety-issues-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tool learning is widely acknowledged as a foundational approach or deploying large language models (LLMs) in real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toolsword-unveiling-safety-issues-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Class-Imbalanced Diffusion Model Via Overlap Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-class-imbalanced-diffusion-model-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the observed appearance overlap between synthesized images of rare classes and tail classes, we propose a method based on contrastive learning to minimize the overlap between distributions of synthetic images for different classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-class-imbalanced-diffusion-model-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FairSync: Ensuring Amortized Group Exposure in Distributed Recommendation Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairsync-ensuring-amortized-group-exposure-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, FairSync resolves the issue by moving it to the dual space, where a central node aggregates historical fairness data into a vector and distributes it to all servers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairsync-ensuring-amortized-group-exposure-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/10438484</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/https-ieeexplore-ieee-org-document-10438484</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) can capture local context information well but cannot model the global dependencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/https-ieeexplore-ieee-org-document-10438484</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Cohesion-Fairness Harmony: Contrastive Regularization in Individual Fair Graph Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-cohesion-fairness-harmony-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional fair graph clustering methods face two primary challenges: i) They prioritize balanced clusters at the expense of cluster cohesion by imposing rigid constraints, ii) Existing methods of both individual and group-level fairness in graph partitioning mostly rely on eigen decompositions and thus, generally lack interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-cohesion-fairness-harmony-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modelling crypto markets by multi-agent reinforcement learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelling-crypto-markets-by-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on a previous foundation work (Lussange et al. 2020), this study introduces a multi-agent reinforcement learning (MARL) model simulating crypto markets, which is calibrated to the Binance's daily closing prices of $153$ cryptocurrencies that were continuously traded between 2018 and 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelling-crypto-markets-by-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear Transformers with Learnable Kernel Functions are Better In-Context Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-transformers-with-learnable-kernel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advancing the frontier of subquadratic architectures for Language Models (LMs) is crucial in the rapidly evolving field of natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-transformers-with-learnable-kernel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitness-based Linkage Learning and Maximum-Clique Conditional Linkage Modelling for Gray-box Optimization with RV-GOMEA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fitness-based-linkage-learning-and-maximum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we propose a new way to model overlapping dependencies in conditional linkage models to maximize the joint sampling of fully interdependent groups of variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fitness-based-linkage-learning-and-maximum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DataDreamer: A Tool for Synthetic Data Generation and Reproducible LLM Workflows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/datadreamer-a-tool-for-synthetic-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid rise to prominence of these models and these unique challenges has had immediate adverse impacts on open science and on the reproducibility of work that uses them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/datadreamer-a-tool-for-synthetic-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformalized Credal Set Predictors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformalized-credal-set-predictors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Credal sets are sets of probability distributions that are considered as candidates for an imprecisely known ground-truth distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformalized-credal-set-predictors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weak-Mamba-UNet: Visual Mamba Makes CNN and ViT Work Better for Scribble-based Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weak-mamba-unet-visual-mamba-makes-cnn-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image segmentation is increasingly reliant on deep learning techniques, yet the promising performance often come with high annotation costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weak-mamba-unet-visual-mamba-makes-cnn-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlackJAX: Composable Bayesian inference in JAX</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blackjax-composable-bayesian-inference-in-jax</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BlackJAX is a library implementing sampling and variational inference algorithms commonly used in Bayesian computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blackjax-composable-bayesian-inference-in-jax</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance Gaps in Multi-view Clustering under the Nested Matrix-Tensor Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-gaps-in-multi-view-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the estimation of a planted signal hidden in a recently introduced nested matrix-tensor model, which is an extension of the classical spiked rank-one tensor model, motivated by multi-view clustering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-gaps-in-multi-view-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitDistiller: Unleashing the Potential of Sub-4-Bit LLMs via Self-Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitdistiller-unleashing-the-potential-of-sub</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The upscaling of Large Language Models (LLMs) has yielded impressive advances in natural language processing, yet it also poses significant deployment challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitdistiller-unleashing-the-potential-of-sub</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Llamas Work in English? On the Latent Language of Multilingual Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-llamas-work-in-english-on-the-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tracking intermediate embeddings through their high-dimensional space reveals three distinct phases, whereby intermediate embeddings (1) start far away from output token embeddings; (2) already allow for decoding a semantically correct next token in the middle layers, but give higher probability to its version in English than in the input language; (3) finally move into an input-language-specific region of the embedding space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-llamas-work-in-english-on-the-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's Learn Step by Step: Enhancing In-Context Learning Ability with Curriculum Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-s-learn-step-by-step-enhancing-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We advocate the few-shot in-context curriculum learning (ICCL), a simple but effective demonstration ordering method for ICL, which implies gradually increasing the complexity of prompt demonstrations during the inference process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-s-learn-step-by-step-enhancing-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genome-AC-GAN: Enhancing Synthetic Genotype Generation through Auxiliary Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genome-ac-gan-enhancing-synthetic-genotype</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conducted experiments to evaluate the performance of the Genome-AC-GAN and compare the AGs it generates with real genomic data as well as with AGs generated by previously published methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genome-ac-gan-enhancing-synthetic-genotype</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smaller Language Models are capable of selecting Instruction-Tuning Training Data for Larger Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smaller-language-models-are-capable-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel training data selection based on the learning percentage of the samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smaller-language-models-are-capable-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pushing the Limits of Zero-shot End-to-End Speech Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pushing-the-limits-of-zero-shot-end-to-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The speech encoder seamlessly integrates with the MT model at inference, enabling direct translation from speech to text, across all languages supported by the MT model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pushing-the-limits-of-zero-shot-end-to-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpreting CLIP with Sparse Linear Concept Embeddings (SpLiCE)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-clip-with-sparse-linear-concept</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CLIP embeddings have demonstrated remarkable performance across a wide range of computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-clip-with-sparse-linear-concept</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theoretical Understanding of Learning from Adversarial Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theoretical-understanding-of-learning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we provide a theoretical framework for understanding learning from perturbations using a one-hidden-layer network trained on mutually orthogonal samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theoretical-understanding-of-learning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STF: Spatio-Temporal Fusion Module for Improving Video Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stf-spatio-temporal-fusion-module-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The objective of our work is to leverage this complementary information to improve detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stf-spatio-temporal-fusion-module-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Textual Localization: Decomposing Multi-concept Images for Subject-Driven Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textual-localization-decomposing-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subject-driven text-to-image diffusion models empower users to tailor the model to new concepts absent in the pre-training dataset using a few sample images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textual-localization-decomposing-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Point: Multi-View Information-Enhanced Multi-Modal Self-Supervised 3D Point Cloud Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-point-multi-view-information-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In perception, multiple sensory information is integrated to map visual information from 2D views onto 3D objects, which is beneficial for understanding in 3D environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-point-multi-view-information-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoEval: Benchmark for Evaluating LLMs and Multi-Modal Models on Geometry Problem-Solving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geoeval-benchmark-for-evaluating-llms-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, their proficiency in tackling geometry math problems, which necessitates an integrated understanding of both textual and visual information, has not been thoroughly evaluated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geoeval-benchmark-for-evaluating-llms-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuRating: Selecting High-Quality Data for Training Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qurating-selecting-high-quality-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Selecting high-quality pre-training data is important for creating capable language models, but existing methods rely on simple heuristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qurating-selecting-high-quality-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Potential of Transformers in Time Series Forecasting with Sharpness-Aware Minimization and Channel-Wise Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-potential-of-transformers-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based architectures achieved breakthrough performance in natural language processing and computer vision, yet they remain inferior to simpler linear baselines in multivariate long-term forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-potential-of-transformers-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MC-DBN: A Deep Belief Network-Based Model for Modality Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mc-dbn-a-deep-belief-network-based-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in multi-modal artificial intelligence (AI) have revolutionized the fields of stock market forecasting and heart rate monitoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mc-dbn-a-deep-belief-network-based-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-maps: Direct Depth Lookup for Event-based Structured Light Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-maps-direct-depth-lookup-for-event-based-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new approach to direct depth estimation for Spatial Augmented Reality (SAR) applications using event cameras.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-maps-direct-depth-lookup-for-event-based-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIM-Refiner: A Contrastive Learning Boost from Intermediate Pre-Trained Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mim-refiner-a-contrastive-learning-boost-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The motivation behind MIM-Refiner is rooted in the insight that optimal representations within MIM models generally reside in intermediate layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mim-refiner-a-contrastive-learning-boost-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVIDHealth: A Benchmark Twitter Dataset and Machine Learning based Web Application for Classifying COVID-19 Discussions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covidhealth-a-benchmark-twitter-dataset-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, our primary objective is to develop a machine learning-based web application for automatically classifying COVID-19-related discussions on social media.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covidhealth-a-benchmark-twitter-dataset-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performative Reinforcement Learning in Gradually Shifting Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performative-reinforcement-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike PRL, our framework allows to model scenarios where the environment gradually adjusts to a deployed policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performative-reinforcement-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Representational Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-representational-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, we find that GRIT matches training on only generative or embedding data, thus we can unify both at no performance loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-representational-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedLion: Faster Adaptive Federated Optimization with Fewer Communication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedlion-faster-adaptive-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Federated Learning (FL), a framework to train machine learning models across distributed data, well-known algorithms like FedAvg tend to have slow convergence rates, resulting in high communication costs during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedlion-faster-adaptive-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Trembling House of Cards? Mapping Adversarial Attacks against Language Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-trembling-house-of-cards-mapping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a surprisingly large gap between the speed and scale of their development and deployment and our understanding of their safety risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-trembling-house-of-cards-mapping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DE-COP: Detecting Copyrighted Content in Language Models Training Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/de-cop-detecting-copyrighted-content-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We are motivated by the premise that a language model is likely to identify verbatim excerpts from its training text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/de-cop-detecting-copyrighted-content-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUICK: Quantization-aware Interleaving and Conflict-free Kernel for efficient LLM inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quick-quantization-aware-interleaving-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce QUICK, a group of novel optimized CUDA kernels for the efficient inference of quantized Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quick-quantization-aware-interleaving-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ControlLM: Crafting Diverse Personalities for Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllm-crafting-diverse-personalities-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This heightens the need to control model behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllm-crafting-diverse-personalities-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criterion collapse and loss distribution control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/criterion-collapse-and-loss-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we consider the notion of "criterion collapse," in which optimization of one metric implies optimality in another, with a particular focus on conditions for collapse into error probability minimizers under a wide variety of learning criteria, ranging from DRO and OCE risks (CVaR, tilted ERM) to non-monotonic criteria underlying recent ascent-descent algorithms explored in the literature (Flooding, SoftAD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/criterion-collapse-and-loss-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DreamMatcher: Appearance Matching Self-Attention for Semantically-Consistent Text-to-Image Personalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreammatcher-appearance-matching-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The objective of text-to-image (T2I) personalization is to customize a diffusion model to a user-provided reference concept, generating diverse images of the concept aligned with the target prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreammatcher-appearance-matching-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViGEO: an Assessment of Vision GNNs in Earth Observation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vigeo-an-assessment-of-vision-gnns-in-earth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Satellite missions and Earth Observation (EO) systems represent fundamental assets for environmental monitoring and the timely identification of catastrophic events, long-term monitoring of both natural resources and human-made assets, such as vegetation, water bodies, forests as well as buildings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vigeo-an-assessment-of-vision-gnns-in-earth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to validate average calibration for machine learning regression tasks ?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-validate-average-calibration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Average calibration of the uncertainties of machine learning regression tasks can be tested in two ways.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-validate-average-calibration-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting CSV File Dialects by Table Uniformity Measurement and Data Type Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-csv-file-dialects-by-table</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The human-readable simplicity with which the CSV format was devised, together with the absence of a standard that strictly defines this format, has allowed the proliferation of several variants in the dialects with which these files are written.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-csv-file-dialects-by-table</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
