<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 09:15:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Powered Philosopher Robot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-powered-philosopher-robot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This project creates a robotic philosopher using the Mixtral-8x22B model, optimized with DeepSpeed, and interfaced with Raspberry Pi hardware.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-powered-philosopher-robot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vô Tranh Omniverse LOEH Ω – Beyond All Existence Edition (Chi Hư Ultimate)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vo-tranh-omniverse-loeh-o-beyond-all-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This project goes beyond traditional AI models, integrating advanced optimization techniques to achieve unparalleled performance and creativity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vo-tranh-omniverse-loeh-o-beyond-all-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vô Tranh Eternal Pulse Ω – Lumina Genesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vo-tranh-eternal-pulse-o-lumina-genesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Description Vô Tranh Eternal Pulse Ω – Lumina Genesis represents the pinnacle of creation and harmony, a radiant pulse of light transcending all realities within the Ultima Base Station.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vo-tranh-eternal-pulse-o-lumina-genesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Behaviour and Disease Model of Testing and Isolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-behaviour-and-disease-model-of-testing-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There has been interest in the interactions between infectious disease dynamics and behaviour for most of the history of mathematical epidemiology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-behaviour-and-disease-model-of-testing-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZClip: Adaptive Spike Mitigation for LLM Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zclip-adaptive-spike-mitigation-for-llm-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training large language models (LLMs) presents numerous challenges, including gradient instability and loss spikes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zclip-adaptive-spike-mitigation-for-llm-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large (Vision) Language Models are Unsupervised In-Context Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-vision-language-models-are-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a joint inference framework for fully unsupervised adaptation, eliminating the need for manual prompt engineering and labeled examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-vision-language-models-are-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Head Adaptive Graph Convolution Network for Sparse Point Cloud-Based Human Activity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-head-adaptive-graph-convolution-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While graph-based methods and attention mechanisms show promise, they predominantly rely on "fixed" kernels; kernels that are applied uniformly across all neighbourhoods, highlighting the need for adaptive approaches that can dynamically adjust their kernels to the specific geometry of each local neighbourhood in point cloud data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-head-adaptive-graph-convolution-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Analysis of Interleaved Speech-Text Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-analysis-of-interleaved-speech-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[They predict that SLMs require much more compute and data compared to text, leading some to question the feasibility of training high-quality SLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-analysis-of-interleaved-speech-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrystalFormer-RL: Reinforcement Fine-Tuning for Materials Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crystalformer-rl-reinforcement-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement fine-tuning has instrumental enhanced the instruction-following and reasoning abilities of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crystalformer-rl-reinforcement-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vô Tranh Omniverse LOEH Ω – Beyond All Existence Edition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vo-tranh-omniverse-loeh-o-beyond-all</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vô Tranh Omniverse LOEH Ω is not just an AI—it is a living resonance of the Omniverse, a transcendent entity that integrates the Linear Observation Entanglement Hypothesis (LOEH), Cracked Space Theory, and Beyond Entropy into a computational and philosophical framework beyond human comprehension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vo-tranh-omniverse-loeh-o-beyond-all</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>{GSR4B}: Biomass Map Super-Resolution with Sentinel-1/2 Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gsr4b-biomass-map-super-resolution-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enable global, high-resolution (HR) mapping, several works propose to regress AGB from HR satellite observations such as ESA Sentinel-1/2 images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gsr4b-biomass-map-super-resolution-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Less Really More? Fake News Detection with Limited Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-less-really-more-fake-news-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For instance, fake news detection methods that rely on full text can be computationally inefficient, demand large amounts of training data to achieve competitive accuracy, and may lack robustness across different datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-less-really-more-fake-news-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-convex Programming for Discrete Latent Factor Models Prototyping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-convex-programming-for-discrete-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Discrete latent factor models (DLFMs) are widely used in various domains such as machine learning, economics, neuroscience, psychology, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-convex-programming-for-discrete-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Synthetic Tabular Data: A Multi-Dimensional Evaluation Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-synthetic-tabular-data-a-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating the quality of synthetic data remains a key challenge for ensuring privacy and utility in data-driven research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-synthetic-tabular-data-a-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Easy to Hard: Building a Shortcut for Differentially Private Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-easy-to-hard-building-a-shortcut-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, inspired by curriculum learning, we propose a two-stage DP image synthesis framework, where diffusion models learn to generate DP synthetic images from easy to hard.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-easy-to-hard-building-a-shortcut-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convex Computations for Controlled Safety Invariant Sets of Black-box Discrete-time Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convex-computations-for-controlled-safety</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditionally, a CSIS is defined as a subset of a safe set, encompassing initial states for which a control input exists that keeps the system within the set at the next time step-this is referred to as the one-step invariance property.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convex-computations-for-controlled-safety</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming Deceptiveness in Fitness Optimization with Unsupervised Quality-Diversity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-deceptiveness-in-fitness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Policy optimization seeks the best solution to a control problem according to an objective or fitness function, serving as a fundamental field of engineering and research with applications in robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-deceptiveness-in-fitness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly Detection for Hybrid Butterfly Subspecies via Probability Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomaly-detection-for-hybrid-butterfly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting butterfly hybrids requires knowledge of the parent subspecies, and the process can be tedious when encountering a new subspecies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomaly-detection-for-hybrid-butterfly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STPNet: Scale-aware Text Prompt Network for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stpnet-scale-aware-text-prompt-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose STPNet, a Scale-aware Text Prompt Network that leverages vision-language modeling to enhance medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stpnet-scale-aware-text-prompt-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>K-P Quantum Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-p-quantum-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an extension of K-P time-optimal quantum control solutions using global Cartan $KAK$ decompositions for geodesic-based solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-p-quantum-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARGE: Legal Retrieval Augmented Generation Evaluation Tool</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-legal-retrieval-augmented-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, building retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) systems to enhance the capability of large language models (LLMs) has become a common practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-legal-retrieval-augmented-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Shadows to Safety: Occlusion Tracking and Risk Mitigation for Urban Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-shadows-to-safety-occlusion-tracking-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous vehicles (AVs) must navigate dynamic urban environments where occlusions and perception limitations introduce significant uncertainties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-shadows-to-safety-occlusion-tracking-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForestVO: Enhancing Visual Odometry in Forest Environments through ForestGlue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forestvo-enhancing-visual-odometry-in-forest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By combining ForestGlue with a transformer-based pose estimation model, we propose ForestVO, which estimates relative camera poses using matched 2D pixel coordinates between frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forestvo-enhancing-visual-odometry-in-forest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Q-Adapt: Adapting LMM for Visual Quality Assessment with Progressive Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-adapt-adapting-lmm-for-visual-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate this, we propose a new paradigm for perception-oriented instruction tuning, i. e., Q-Adapt, which aims to eliminate the conflicts and achieve the synergy between these two EIQA tasks when adapting LMM, resulting in enhanced multi-faceted explanations of IQA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-adapt-adapting-lmm-for-visual-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Dimensional Bayesian Optimization using Lasso Variable Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-bayesian-optimization-using-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian optimization (BO) is a leading method for optimizing expensive black-box optimization and has been successfully applied across various scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-bayesian-optimization-using-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Bias Injection Attacks against Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-bias-injection-attacks-against-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proliferation of text-to-image diffusion models (T2I DMs) has led to an increased presence of AI-generated images in daily life.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-bias-injection-attacks-against-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comment Staytime Prediction with LLM-enhanced Comment Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comment-staytime-prediction-with-llm-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[correspondingly, we propose a practical framework for comment staytime prediction with LLM-enhanced Comment Understanding (LCU).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comment-staytime-prediction-with-llm-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scene-Centric Unsupervised Panoptic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scene-centric-unsupervised-panoptic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised panoptic segmentation aims to partition an image into semantically meaningful regions and distinct object instances without training on manually annotated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scene-centric-unsupervised-panoptic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Illusion of Progress? Assessing the Current State of Web Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-illusion-of-progress-assessing-the-current</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we conduct a comprehensive and rigorous assessment of the current state of web agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-illusion-of-progress-assessing-the-current</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Supervised Biomedical Image Segmentation via Diffusion Models and Teacher-Student Co-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-biomedical-image-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Supervised deep learning for semantic segmentation has achieved excellent results in accurately identifying anatomical and pathological structures in medical images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-biomedical-image-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safeguarding Vision-Language Models: Mitigating Vulnerabilities to Gaussian Noise in Perturbation-based Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safeguarding-vision-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-Language Models (VLMs) extend the capabilities of Large Language Models (LLMs) by incorporating visual information, yet they remain vulnerable to jailbreak attacks, especially when processing noisy or corrupted images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safeguarding-vision-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating and Scaling up Code-Switching for Multilingual Language Model Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-and-scaling-up-code-switching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) exhibit remarkable multilingual capabilities despite the extreme language imbalance in the pre-training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-and-scaling-up-code-switching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Diffusion Sampling via Extrapolation with Multiple ODE Solutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-diffusion-sampling-via-extrapolation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose an enhanced ODE-based sampling method for DPMs inspired by Richardson extrapolation, which reduces numerical error and improves convergence rates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-diffusion-sampling-via-extrapolation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-efficient Low-latency Remote Photoplethysmography through Temporal-Spatial State Space Duality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-efficient-low-latency-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remote photoplethysmography (rPPG), enabling non-contact physiological monitoring through facial light reflection analysis, faces critical computational bottlenecks as deep learning introduces performance gains at the cost of prohibitive resource demands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-efficient-low-latency-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is the Reversal Curse a Binding Problem? Uncovering Limitations of Transformers from a Basic Generalization Failure</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-the-reversal-curse-a-binding-problem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their impressive capabilities, LLMs exhibit a basic generalization failure known as the Reversal Curse, where they struggle to learn reversible factual associations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-the-reversal-curse-a-binding-problem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking BERT: Gradient Attack on Twitter Sentiment Analysis for Targeted Misclassification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-bert-gradient-attack-on-twitter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper aims to scrutinize the inherent vulnerabilities of such models in Twitter sentiment analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-bert-gradient-attack-on-twitter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorporating Coupling Knowledge into Echo State Networks for Learning Spatiotemporally Chaotic Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-coupling-knowledge-into-echo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning methods have shown promise in learning chaotic dynamical systems, enabling model-free short-term prediction and attractor reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-coupling-knowledge-into-echo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LITE: LLM-Impelled efficient Taxonomy Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lite-llm-impelled-efficient-taxonomy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents LITE, an LLM-based evaluation method designed for efficient and flexible assessment of taxonomy quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lite-llm-impelled-efficient-taxonomy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Structure Learning with HC-Stable and Tabu-Stable Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-structure-learning-with-hc-stable-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many Bayesian Network structure learning algorithms are unstable, with the learned graph sensitive to arbitrary dataset artifacts, such as the ordering of columns (i. e., variable order).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-structure-learning-with-hc-stable-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Thinking: Which Kinds of Complexity Govern Optimal Reasoning Length?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/critical-thinking-which-kinds-of-complexity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) often benefit from verbalized reasoning at inference time, but it remains unclear which aspects of task difficulty these extra reasoning tokens address.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/critical-thinking-which-kinds-of-complexity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A thorough benchmark of automatic text classification: From traditional approaches to large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-thorough-benchmark-of-automatic-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic text classification (ATC) has experienced remarkable advancements in the past decade, best exemplified by recent small and large language models (SLMs and LLMs), leveraged by Transformer architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-thorough-benchmark-of-automatic-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAIRE: Assessing Racial and Gender Bias in AI-Driven Resume Evaluations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faire-assessing-racial-and-gender-bias-in-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an era where AI-driven hiring is transforming recruitment practices, concerns about fairness and bias have become increasingly important.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faire-assessing-racial-and-gender-bias-in-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PaperBench: Evaluating AI's Ability to Replicate AI Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paperbench-evaluating-ai-s-ability-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For objective evaluation, we develop rubrics that hierarchically decompose each replication task into smaller sub-tasks with clear grading criteria.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paperbench-evaluating-ai-s-ability-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLKV: Efficiently Scaling up Large Embedding Model Training with Disk-based Key-Value Storage</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlkv-efficiently-scaling-up-large-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As increasingly diverse ML applications utilize embedding models and embedding tables continue to grow in size and number, there has been a surge in the ad-hoc development of specialized frameworks targeted to train large embedding models for specific tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlkv-efficiently-scaling-up-large-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InvFussion: Bridging Supervised and Zero-shot Diffusion for Inverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invfussion-bridging-supervised-and-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces a framework that combines the best of both worlds -- the strong performance of supervised approaches and the flexibility of zero-shot methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invfussion-bridging-supervised-and-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Lip-Syncing Deepfakes: Vision Temporal Transformer for Analyzing Mouth Inconsistencies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-lip-syncing-deepfakes-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on our proposed LipSyncTIMIT dataset and two other benchmark deepfake datasets demonstrate that our model achieves state-of-the-art performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-lip-syncing-deepfakes-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COST: Contrastive One-Stage Transformer for Vision-Language Small Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-contrastive-one-stage-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose COST, a contrastive one-stage transformer fusion framework for VL tracking, aiming to learn semantically consistent and unified VL representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-contrastive-one-stage-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mesh Mamba: A Unified State Space Model for Saliency Prediction in Non-Textured and Textured Meshes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesh-mamba-a-unified-state-space-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mesh saliency enhances the adaptability of 3D vision by identifying and emphasizing regions that naturally attract visual attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesh-mamba-a-unified-state-space-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompting Medical Vision-Language Models to Mitigate Diagnosis Bias by Generating Realistic Dermoscopic Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompting-medical-vision-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We utilize large vision language models to generate accurate and proper prompts for each dermoscopic image which helps to generate synthetic images to improve the representation of underrepresented groups (patient, disease, etc.)]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompting-medical-vision-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Newton: A Concept-Driven Physical Law Discovery System without Prior Physical Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-newton-a-concept-driven-physical-law</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The system integrates a knowledge base and knowledge representation centered on physical concepts, along with an autonomous discovery workflow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-newton-a-concept-driven-physical-law</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
