<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 21:07:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>For Learning in Symmetric Teams, Local Optima are Global Nash Equilibria</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/for-learning-in-symmetric-teams-local-optima</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show that any locally optimal symmetric strategy profile is also a (global) Nash equilibrium.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/for-learning-in-symmetric-teams-local-optima</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards the Practical Utility of Federated Learning in the Medical Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-practical-utility-of-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) is an active area of research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-practical-utility-of-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Gap between Object and Image-level Representations for Open-Vocabulary Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-object-and-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two popular forms of weak-supervision used in open-vocabulary detection (OVD) include pretrained CLIP model and image-level supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-object-and-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calibrate to Interpret</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrate-to-interpret</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we show a first link between uncertainty and explainability, by studying the relation between calibration and interpretation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrate-to-interpret</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large Scale Search Dataset for Unbiased Learning to Rank</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-search-dataset-for-unbiased</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The unbiased learning to rank (ULTR) problem has been greatly advanced by recent deep learning techniques and well-designed debias algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-search-dataset-for-unbiased</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Stein critics with staged $L^2$-regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-stein-critics-with-staged-l-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Theoretically, we relate the training dynamic with large regularization weight to the kernel regression optimization of "lazy training" regime in early training times.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-stein-critics-with-staged-l-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The DynaSig-ML Python package: automated learning of biomolecular dynamics-function relationships</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dynasig-ml-python-package-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Summary: The DynaSig-ML (Dynamical Signatures - Machine Learning) Python package allows the efficient, user-friendly exploration of 3D dynamics-function relationships in biomolecules, using datasets of experimental measures from large numbers of sequence variants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dynasig-ml-python-package-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Learning from Spatio-Temporal Mixed Skeleton Sequences for Self-Supervised Skeleton-Based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-from-spatio-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, SkeleMix utilizes the topological information of skeleton data to mix two skeleton sequences by randomly combing the cropped skeleton fragments (the trimmed view) with the remaining skeleton sequences (the truncated view).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-from-spatio-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do We Really Need Inertia?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-we-really-need-inertia</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emphasis on inertia for system stability has been a long-held tradition in conventional grids.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-we-really-need-inertia</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolution of Popularity Bias: Empirical Study and Debiasing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolution-of-popularity-bias-empirical-study</link>
      <description><![CDATA[and how to debias in this long-term dynamic process?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolution-of-popularity-bias-empirical-study</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCTS with Refinement for Proposals Selection Games in Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcts-with-refinement-for-proposals-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also introduce a novel differentiable method for rendering the polygonal shapes of these proposals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcts-with-refinement-for-proposals-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to restore images degraded by atmospheric turbulence using uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-restore-images-degraded-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Atmospheric turbulence can significantly degrade the quality of images acquired by long-range imaging systems by causing spatially and temporally random fluctuations in the index of refraction of the atmosphere.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-restore-images-degraded-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VeriDark: A Large-Scale Benchmark for Authorship Verification on the Dark Web</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/veridark-a-large-scale-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The DarkWeb represents a hotbed for illicit activity, where users communicate on different market forums in order to exchange goods and services.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/veridark-a-large-scale-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D2HNet: Joint Denoising and Deblurring with Hierarchical Network for Robust Night Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d2hnet-joint-denoising-and-deblurring-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Night imaging with modern smartphone cameras is troublesome due to low photon count and unavoidable noise in the imaging system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d2hnet-joint-denoising-and-deblurring-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A unified interpretable intelligent learning diagnosis framework for smart education</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-interpretable-intelligent-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intelligent learning diagnosis is a critical engine of smart education, which aims to estimate learners' current knowledge mastery status and predict their future learning performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-interpretable-intelligent-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TFCNs: A CNN-Transformer Hybrid Network for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tfcns-a-cnn-transformer-hybrid-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image segmentation is one of the most fundamental tasks concerning medical information analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tfcns-a-cnn-transformer-hybrid-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Stream Computer-Generated Image Detection Network Based On Channel Joint And Softpool</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-stream-computer-generated-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed network architecture includes a residual module for extracting image noise information and a joint channel information extraction module for capturing the shallow semantic information of image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-stream-computer-generated-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Log Instructions in Log-based Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-log-instructions-in-log-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence for IT Operations (AIOps) describes the process of maintaining and operating large IT systems using diverse AI-enabled methods and tools for, e. g., anomaly detection and root cause analysis, to support the remediation, optimization, and automatic initiation of self-stabilizing IT activities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-log-instructions-in-log-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deformer: Towards Displacement Field Learning for Unsupervised Medical Image Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deformer-towards-displacement-field-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a novel Deformer module along with a multi-scale framework for the deformable image registration task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deformer-towards-displacement-field-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Rotation Correction without Angle Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-rotation-correction-without-angle-prior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new and practical task, named Rotation Correction, to automatically correct the tilt with high content fidelity in the condition that the rotated angle is unknown.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-rotation-correction-without-angle-prior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust optimal well control using an adaptive multi-grid reinforcement learning framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-optimal-well-control-using-an-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RL control policies are initially learned using computationally efficient low fidelity simulations using coarse grid discretization of the underlying partial differential equations (PDEs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-optimal-well-control-using-an-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Pretraining Objectives for Tabular Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-pretraining-objectives-for-tabular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent deep learning models for tabular data currently compete with the traditional ML models based on decision trees (GBDT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-pretraining-objectives-for-tabular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic optimal well control in subsurface reservoirs using reinforcement learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-optimal-well-control-in-subsurface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this problem, the system is partially observed since the data is only available at well locations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-optimal-well-control-in-subsurface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring Structural Parameters of Low-Surface-Brightness-Galaxies with Uncertainty Quantification using Bayesian Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-structural-parameters-of-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Measuring the structural parameters (size, total brightness, light concentration, etc.)]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-structural-parameters-of-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Stream Transformer for Generic Event Boundary Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-stream-transformer-for-generic-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes our champion solution for the CVPR2022 Generic Event Boundary Captioning (GEBC) competition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-stream-transformer-for-generic-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to the Basics: Revisiting Out-of-Distribution Detection Baselines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/back-to-the-basics-revisiting-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study simple methods for out-of-distribution (OOD) image detection that are compatible with any already trained classifier, relying on only its predictions or learned representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/back-to-the-basics-revisiting-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Surfel Prediction for Self-Supervised Point Cloud Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-surfel-prediction-for-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we make the first attempt, to the best of our knowledge, to consider the local geometry information explicitly into the masked auto-encoding, and propose a novel Masked Surfel Prediction (MaskSurf) method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-surfel-prediction-for-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Additive Instance-Wise Approach to Multi-class Model Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-additive-instance-wise-approach-to-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interpretable machine learning offers insights into what factors drive a certain prediction of a black-box system and whether to trust it for high-stakes decisions or large-scale deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-additive-instance-wise-approach-to-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Modeling of Language-Evoked Event-Related Potentials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-modeling-of-language-evoked-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian hierarchical models are well-suited to analyzing the often noisy data from electroencephalography experiments in cognitive neuroscience: these models provide an intuitive framework to account for structures and correlations in the data, and they allow a straightforward handling of uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-modeling-of-language-evoked-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-training helps Bayesian optimization too</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-helps-bayesian-optimization-too</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrary to a common belief that BO is suited to optimizing black-box functions, it actually requires domain knowledge on characteristics of those functions to deploy BO successfully.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-helps-bayesian-optimization-too</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Representation Learning via Class-Pose Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-representation-learning-via-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a general method for learning representations that are equivariant to symmetries of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-representation-learning-via-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Transformers Together</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-transformers-together</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The infrastructure necessary for training state-of-the-art models is becoming overly expensive, which makes training such models affordable only to large corporations and institutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-transformers-together</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpansionNet: exploring the sequence length bottleneck in the Transformer for Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expansionnet-exploring-the-sequence-length</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most recent state of art architectures rely on combinations and variations of three approaches: convolutional, recurrent and self-attentive methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expansionnet-exploring-the-sequence-length</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the instrumental variable estimation with many weak and invalid instruments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-instrumental-variable-estimation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discuss the fundamental issue of identification in linear instrumental variable (IV) models with unknown IV validity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-instrumental-variable-estimation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SC2EGSet: StarCraft II Esport Replay and Game-state Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sc2egset-starcraft-ii-esport-replay-and-game</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on initial investigation of available StarCraft II datasets, we observed that our dataset is the largest publicly available source of StarCraft II esports data upon its publication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sc2egset-starcraft-ii-esport-replay-and-game</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving Synthetic Educational Data Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-synthetic-educational-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Institutions collect massive learning traces but they may not disclose it for privacy issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-synthetic-educational-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Weaknesses of Adversarial Camouflage in Overhead Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-weaknesses-of-adversarial-camouflage-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we explore the efficacy and drawbacks of adversarial camouflage in an overhead imagery context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-weaknesses-of-adversarial-camouflage-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network Pruning via Feature Shift Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-pruning-via-feature-shift</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel Feature Shift Minimization (FSM) method to compress CNN models, which evaluates the feature shift by converging the information of both features and filters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-pruning-via-feature-shift</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Domain Adaptation through Shape Modeling for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-through-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous methods proposed Variational Autoencoder (VAE) based models to learn the distribution of shape for a particular organ and used it to automatically evaluate the quality of a segmentation prediction by fitting it into the learned shape distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-through-shape</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is the U-Net Directional-Relationship Aware?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-the-u-net-directional-relationship-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CNNs are often assumed to be capable of using contextual information about distinct objects (such as their directional relations) inside their receptive field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-the-u-net-directional-relationship-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FewSOL: A Dataset for Few-Shot Object Learning in Robotic Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fewsol-a-dataset-for-few-shot-object-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Few-Shot Object Learning (FewSOL) dataset for object recognition with a few images per object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fewsol-a-dataset-for-few-shot-object-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Value of Gazetteer in Chinese Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-value-of-gazetteer-in-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gazetteer is widely used in Chinese named entity recognition (NER) to enhance span boundary detection and type classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-value-of-gazetteer-in-chinese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Pay Attention to the Noise: Learning Self-supervised Representations of Light Curves with a Denoising Time Series Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-pay-attention-to-the-noise-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Astrophysical light curves are particularly challenging data objects due to the intensity and variety of noise contaminating them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-pay-attention-to-the-noise-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowing Earlier what Right Means to You: A Comprehensive VQA Dataset for Grounding Relative Directions via Multi-Task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowing-earlier-what-right-means-to-you-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatial reasoning poses a particular challenge for intelligent agents and is at the same time a prerequisite for their successful interaction and communication in the physical world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowing-earlier-what-right-means-to-you-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pure Transformers are Powerful Graph Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pure-transformers-are-powerful-graph-learners</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that standard Transformers without graph-specific modifications can lead to promising results in graph learning both in theory and practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pure-transformers-are-powerful-graph-learners</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAST-VQA: Efficient End-to-end Video Quality Assessment with Fragment Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-vqa-efficient-end-to-end-video-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consisting of fragments and FANet, the proposed FrAgment Sample Transformer for VQA (FAST-VQA) enables efficient end-to-end deep VQA and learns effective video-quality-related representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-vqa-efficient-end-to-end-video-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Language Left Behind: Scaling Human-Centered Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-language-left-behind-scaling-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driven by the goal of eradicating language barriers on a global scale, machine translation has solidified itself as a key focus of artificial intelligence research today.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-language-left-behind-scaling-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Manifold Alignment with Joint Multidimensional Scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-manifold-alignment-with-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach integrates Multidimensional Scaling (MDS) and Wasserstein Procrustes analysis into a joint optimization problem to simultaneously generate isometric embeddings of data and learn correspondences between instances from two different datasets, while only requiring intra-dataset pairwise dissimilarities as input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-manifold-alignment-with-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Transparency in Dermatology Image Datasets with Skin Tone Annotations by Experts, Crowds, and an Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-transparency-in-dermatology-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a start towards increasing transparency, AI researchers have appropriated the use of the Fitzpatrick skin type (FST) from a measure of patient photosensitivity to a measure for estimating skin tone in algorithmic audits of computer vision applications including facial recognition and dermatology diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-transparency-in-dermatology-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOv7: Trainable bag-of-freebies sets new state-of-the-art for real-time object detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov7-trainable-bag-of-freebies-sets-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[YOLOv7 surpasses all known object detectors in both speed and accuracy in the range from 5 FPS to 160 FPS and has the highest accuracy 56. 8% AP among all known real-time object detectors with 30 FPS or higher on GPU V100.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov7-trainable-bag-of-freebies-sets-new</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
