<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:10:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Exp4Fuse: A Rank Fusion Framework for Enhanced Sparse Retrieval using Large Language Model-based Query Expansion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exp4fuse-a-rank-fusion-framework-for-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the efficacy of this method is highly dependent on the quality of the generated documents, which often requires complex prompt strategies and the integration of advanced dense retrieval techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exp4fuse-a-rank-fusion-framework-for-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLFer: Smaller LM-Generated Documents Hallucination Filter &amp; Combiner for Query Expansion in Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/golfer-smaller-lm-generated-documents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs)-based query expansion for information retrieval augments queries with generated hypothetical documents with LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/golfer-smaller-lm-generated-documents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time to Talk: LLM Agents for Asynchronous Group Communication in Mafia Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-to-talk-llm-agents-for-asynchronous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, in group chats, online team meetings, or social games, there is no inherent notion of turns; therefore, the decision of when to speak forms a crucial part of the participant's decision making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-to-talk-llm-agents-for-asynchronous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Tempering Sampler with Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-tempering-sampler-with-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also introduce a novel method to combine high-temperature diffusion models to generate approximate lower-temperature samples, which are minimally refined using MCMC and used to train the next diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-tempering-sampler-with-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OGGSplat: Open Gaussian Growing for Generalizable Reconstruction with Expanded Field-of-View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oggsplat-open-gaussian-growing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate our method, we establish a Gaussian Outpainting (GO) benchmark that assesses both semantic and generative quality of reconstructed open-vocabulary scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oggsplat-open-gaussian-growing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FPGA-Enabled Machine Learning Applications in Earth Observation: A Systematic Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fpga-enabled-machine-learning-applications-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[New UAV technologies and the NewSpace era are transforming Earth Observation missions and data acquisition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fpga-enabled-machine-learning-applications-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViTSGMM: A Robust Semi-Supervised Image Recognition Network Using Sparse Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitsgmm-a-robust-semi-supervised-image-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present ViTSGMM, an image recognition network that leverages semi-supervised learning in a highly efficient manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitsgmm-a-robust-semi-supervised-image-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photoreal Scene Reconstruction from an Egocentric Device</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/photoreal-scene-reconstruction-from-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the challenges associated with using egocentric devices to photorealistic reconstruct the scene in high dynamic range.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/photoreal-scene-reconstruction-from-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Domain Teacher: Diffusion Guided Domain Adaptive Object Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-domain-teacher-diffusion-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To effectively leverage the cross-domain feature representation of diffusion models, in this paper, we train a detector with frozen-weight diffusion model on the source domain, then employ it as a teacher model to generate pseudo labels on the unlabeled target domain, which are used to guide the supervised learning of the student model on the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-domain-teacher-diffusion-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pruning Everything, Everywhere, All at Once</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pruning-everything-everywhere-all-at-once</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill this gap and leverage the benefits of eliminating neurons and layers at once, we propose a new method capable of pruning different structures within a model as follows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pruning-everything-everywhere-all-at-once</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextAtari: 100K Frames Game Playing with Language Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textatari-100k-frames-game-playing-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present TextAtari, a benchmark for evaluating language agents on very long-horizon decision-making tasks spanning up to 100, 000 steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textatari-100k-frames-game-playing-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>N$^2$: A Unified Python Package and Test Bench for Nearest Neighbor-Based Matrix Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/n-2-a-unified-python-package-and-test-bench</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nearest neighbor (NN) methods have re-emerged as competitive tools for matrix completion, offering strong empirical performance and recent theoretical guarantees, including entry-wise error bounds, confidence intervals, and minimax optimality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/n-2-a-unified-python-package-and-test-bench</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survey of Active Learning Hyperparameters: Insights from a Large-Scale Experimental Grid</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survey-of-active-learning-hyperparameters</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we first compiled a large hyperparameter grid of over 4. 6 million hyperparameter combinations, second, recorded the performance of all combinations in the so-far biggest conducted AL study, and third, analyzed the impact of each hyperparameter in the experiment results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survey-of-active-learning-hyperparameters</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GARG-AML against Smurfing: A Scalable and Interpretable Graph-Based Framework for Anti-Money Laundering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/garg-aml-against-smurfing-a-scalable-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Money laundering poses a significant challenge as it is estimated to account for 2%-5% of the global GDP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/garg-aml-against-smurfing-a-scalable-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapt before Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapt-before-continual-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual Learning (CL) seeks to enable neural networks to incrementally acquire new knowledge (plasticity) while retaining existing knowledge (stability).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapt-before-continual-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLARIS: A High-contrast Polarimetric Imaging Benchmark Dataset for Exoplanetary Disk Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polaris-a-high-contrast-polarimetric-imaging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With over 1, 000, 000 images from more than 10, 000 exposures using state-of-the-art high-contrast imagers (e. g., Gemini Planet Imager, VLT/SPHERE) in the search for exoplanets, can artificial intelligence (AI) serve as a transformative tool in imaging Earth-like exoplanets in the coming decade?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polaris-a-high-contrast-polarimetric-imaging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Stability-Plasticity Trade-off in Continual Learning from an Architectural Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-stability-plasticity-trade-off</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While numerous CL methods aim to achieve this trade-off, they often overlook the impact of network architecture on stability and plasticity, restricting the trade-off to the parameter level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-stability-plasticity-trade-off</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Theory to Practice with RAVEN-UCB: Addressing Non-Stationarity in Multi-Armed Bandits through Variance Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-theory-to-practice-with-raven-ucb</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Multi-Armed Bandit (MAB) problem is challenging in non-stationary environments where reward distributions evolve dynamically.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-theory-to-practice-with-raven-ucb</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EyeNavGS: A 6-DoF Navigation Dataset and Record-n-Replay Software for Real-World 3DGS Scenes in VR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eyenavgs-a-6-dof-navigation-dataset-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The EyeNavGS dataset is available at: https://symmru. github. io/EyeNavGS/.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eyenavgs-a-6-dof-navigation-dataset-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dense Match Summarization for Faster Two-view Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-match-summarization-for-faster-two-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we speed up robust two-view relative pose from dense correspondences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-match-summarization-for-faster-two-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Occlusion-Aware Ground Target Tracking by a Dubins Vehicle Using Visibility Volumes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occlusion-aware-ground-target-tracking-by-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The time-varying VV is approximated by placing static VVs along the POI's trajectory using an adaptive metric that restricts the volume change of consecutive visibility volumes to below a specified rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occlusion-aware-ground-target-tracking-by-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeneA-SLAM2: Dynamic SLAM with AutoEncoder-Preprocessed Genetic Keypoints Resampling and Depth Variance-Guided Dynamic Region Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genea-slam2-dynamic-slam-with-autoencoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, this paper proposes a robust and efficient GeneA-SLAM2 system that leverages depth variance constraints to handle dynamic scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genea-slam2-dynamic-slam-with-autoencoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SViMo: Synchronized Diffusion for Video and Motion Generation in Hand-object Interaction Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svimo-synchronized-diffusion-for-video-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizing that visual appearance and motion patterns share fundamental physical laws in the real world, we propose a novel framework that combines visual priors and dynamic constraints within a synchronized diffusion process to generate the HOI video and motion simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svimo-synchronized-diffusion-for-video-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthesis of discrete-continuous quantum circuits with multimodal diffusion models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesis-of-discrete-continuous-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficiently compiling quantum operations remains a major bottleneck in scaling quantum computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesis-of-discrete-continuous-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHEN TO ACT, WHEN TO WAIT: Modeling Structural Trajectories for Intent Triggerability in Task-Oriented Dialogue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-act-when-to-wait-modeling-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Task-oriented dialogue systems often face difficulties when user utterances seem semantically complete but lack necessary structural information for appropriate system action.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-act-when-to-wait-modeling-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentCPM-GUI: Building Mobile-Use Agents with Reinforcement Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentcpm-gui-building-mobile-use-agents-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent progress of large language model agents has opened new possibilities for automating tasks through graphical user interfaces (GUIs), especially in mobile environments where intelligent interaction can greatly enhance usability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentcpm-gui-building-mobile-use-agents-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimeGraph: Synthetic Benchmark Datasets for Robust Time-Series Causal Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timegraph-synthetic-benchmark-datasets-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust causal discovery in time series datasets depends on reliable benchmark datasets with known ground-truth causal relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timegraph-synthetic-benchmark-datasets-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constrained Sliced Wasserstein Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-sliced-wasserstein-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a constrained learning approach to optimize the slicing directions for SW distances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-sliced-wasserstein-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Stage Lighting Control: Is it a Rule-Driven Process or Generative Task?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-stage-lighting-control-is-it-a-rule</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stage lighting plays an essential role in live music performances, influencing the engaging experience of both musicians and audiences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-stage-lighting-control-is-it-a-rule</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confidence intervals for forced alignment boundaries using model ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-intervals-for-forced-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Forced alignment is a common tool to align audio with orthographic and phonetic transcriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-intervals-for-forced-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOC-DGL: Social Interaction Behavior Inspired Dual Graph Learning Framework for Drug-Target Interaction Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soc-dgl-social-interaction-behavior-inspired</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The identification of drug-target interactions (DTI) is crucial for drug discovery and repositioning, as it reveals potential uses of existing drugs, aiding in the acceleration of the drug development process and reducing associated costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soc-dgl-social-interaction-behavior-inspired</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compiler Optimization via LLM Reasoning for Efficient Model Serving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compiler-optimization-via-llm-reasoning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To that end, we introduce a novel compilation framework (dubbed REASONING COMPILER) that formulates optimization as a sequential, context-aware decision process, guided by a large language model and structured Monte Carlo tree search (MCTS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compiler-optimization-via-llm-reasoning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter Efficient Fine Tuning Llama 3.1 for Answering Arabic Legal Questions: A Case Study on Jordanian Laws</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-llama-3-1-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study uses Jordanian law as a case study to explore the fine-tuning of the Llama-3. 1 large language model for Arabic question-answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-llama-3-1-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is PMBOK Guide the Right Fit for AI? Re-evaluating Project Management in the Face of Artificial Intelligence Projects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-pmbok-guide-the-right-fit-for-ai-re</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper critically evaluates the applicability of the Project Management Body of Knowledge (PMBOK) Guide framework to Artificial Intelligence (AI) software projects, highlighting key limitations and proposing tailored adaptations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-pmbok-guide-the-right-fit-for-ai-re</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaxaDiffusion: Progressively Trained Diffusion Model for Fine-Grained Species Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taxadiffusion-progressively-trained-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose TaxaDiffusion, a taxonomy-informed training framework for diffusion models to generate fine-grained animal images with high morphological and identity accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taxadiffusion-progressively-trained-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EfficientFER: EfficientNetv2 Based Deep Learning Approach for Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficientfer-efficientnetv2-based-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial expression recognition (FER), aiming to classify human emotions automatically, is a significant problem in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficientfer-efficientnetv2-based-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning-Table: Exploring Reinforcement Learning for Table Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-table-exploring-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The approach also achieves excellent performance on text-to-SQL tasks, reaching 68. 3% performance on the BIRD dev dataset with a 7B model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-table-exploring-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLoSS: Generative Language Models with Semantic Search for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gloss-generative-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Generative Low-rank language model with Semantic Search (GLoSS), a generative recommendation framework that combines large language models with dense retrieval for sequential recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gloss-generative-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ridgeformer: Mutli-Stage Contrastive Training For Fine-grained Cross-Domain Fingerprint Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ridgeformer-mutli-stage-contrastive-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing demand for hygienic and portable biometric systems has underscored the critical need for advancements in contactless fingerprint recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ridgeformer-mutli-stage-contrastive-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACCESS DENIED INC: The First Benchmark Environment for Sensitivity Awareness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/access-denied-inc-the-first-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose the concept of sensitivity awareness (SA), which enables LLMs to adhere to predefined access rights rules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/access-denied-inc-the-first-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mispronunciation Detection Without L2 Pronunciation Dataset in Low-Resource Setting: A Case Study in Finland Swedish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mispronunciation-detection-without-l2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mispronunciation detection (MD) models are the cornerstones of many language learning applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mispronunciation-detection-without-l2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEMONADE: A Large Multilingual Expert-Annotated Abstractive Event Dataset for the Real World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lemonade-a-large-multilingual-expert</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents LEMONADE, a large-scale conflict event dataset comprising 39, 786 events across 20 languages and 171 countries, with extensive coverage of region-specific entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lemonade-a-large-multilingual-expert</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geo-Sign: Hyperbolic Contrastive Regularisation for Geometrically Aware Sign Language Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geo-sign-hyperbolic-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work demonstrates the potential of hyperbolic geometry to improve skeletal representations for Sign Language Translation, improving on SOTA RGB methods while preserving privacy and improving computational efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geo-sign-hyperbolic-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Soundness in the Real World: On the Challenges of the Verification of Deployed Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-soundness-in-the-real-world-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mislead the verifiers, we create adversarial networks that detect and exploit features of the deployment environment, such as the order and precision of floating point operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-soundness-in-the-real-world-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedBookVQA: A Systematic and Comprehensive Medical Benchmark Derived from Open-Access Book</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medbookvqa-a-systematic-and-comprehensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings highlight critical capability gaps in current GMAI systems while establishing textbook-derived multimodal benchmarks as essential evaluation tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medbookvqa-a-systematic-and-comprehensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuro2Semantic: A Transfer Learning Framework for Semantic Reconstruction of Continuous Language from Human Intracranial EEG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro2semantic-a-transfer-learning-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decoding continuous language from neural signals remains a significant challenge in the intersection of neuroscience and artificial intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro2semantic-a-transfer-learning-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRT-Router: Effective and Interpretable Multi-LLM Routing via Item Response Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irt-router-effective-and-interpretable-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, selecting the optimal LLM to respond to a user query often necessitates a delicate balance between performance and cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irt-router-effective-and-interpretable-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIRROR: Cognitive Inner Monologue Between Conversational Turns for Persistent Reflection and Reasoning in Conversational LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mirror-cognitive-inner-monologue-between</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human intelligence relies on inner monologue to process complex information through simultaneous reflection, memory retrieval, and response formulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mirror-cognitive-inner-monologue-between</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G2S: A General-to-Specific Learning Framework for Temporal Knowledge Graph Forecasting with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g2s-a-general-to-specific-learning-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enhance the generalization ability of LLMs on this task, in this paper, we propose a General-to-Specific learning framework (G2S) that disentangles the learning processes of the above two kinds of knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g2s-a-general-to-specific-learning-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinical Annotations for Automatic Stuttering Severity Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clinical-annotations-for-automatic-stuttering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stuttering is a complex disorder that requires specialized expertise for effective assessment and treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clinical-annotations-for-automatic-stuttering</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
