<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 21:08:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmark and Evaluation for Real-World Out-of-Distribution Detection Using Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-and-evaluation-for-real-world-out</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments reveal that recent CLIP-based OOD detection methods struggle to varying degrees across the three proposed benchmarks, and none of them consistently outperforms the others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-and-evaluation-for-real-world-out</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating Multi-chirp Parameters using Curvature-guided Langevin Monte Carlo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-multi-chirp-parameters-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper considers the problem of estimating chirp parameters from a noisy mixture of chirps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-multi-chirp-parameters-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDformer: Going Beyond Subsequence Isolation for Multivariate Time Series Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gdformer-going-beyond-subsequence-isolation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised anomaly detection of multivariate time series is a challenging task, given the requirements of deriving a compact detection criterion without accessing the anomaly points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gdformer-going-beyond-subsequence-isolation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepFRC: An End-to-End Deep Learning Model for Functional Registration and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepfrc-an-end-to-end-deep-learning-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Functional data analysis (FDA) is essential for analyzing continuous, high-dimensional data, yet existing methods often decouple functional registration and classification, limiting their efficiency and performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepfrc-an-end-to-end-deep-learning-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>adabmDCA 2.0 -- a flexible but easy-to-use package for Direct Coupling Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adabmdca-2-0-a-flexible-but-easy-to-use</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this methods article, we provide a flexible but easy-to-use implementation of Direct Coupling Analysis (DCA) based on Boltzmann machine learning, together with a tutorial on how to use it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adabmdca-2-0-a-flexible-but-easy-to-use</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDE-DKL: PDE-constrained deep kernel learning in high dimensionality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pde-dkl-pde-constrained-deep-kernel-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This synergy unifies the strengths of both NNs and GPs, yielding high accuracy, robust uncertainty estimates, and computational efficiency for high-dimensional PDEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pde-dkl-pde-constrained-deep-kernel-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advances in Multimodal Adaptation and Generalization: From Traditional Approaches to Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-multimodal-adaptation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, the recent advent of large-scale pre-trained multimodal foundation models, such as CLIP, has inspired works leveraging these models to enhance adaptation and generalization performances or adapting them to downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-multimodal-adaptation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReactEmbed: A Cross-Domain Framework for Protein-Molecule Representation Learning via Biochemical Reaction Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reactembed-a-cross-domain-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The challenge in computational biology and drug discovery lies in creating comprehensive representations of proteins and molecules that capture their intrinsic properties and interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reactembed-a-cross-domain-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Random Feature Representation Boosting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-feature-representation-boosting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Random Feature Representation Boosting (RFRBoost), a novel method for constructing deep residual random feature neural networks (RFNNs) using boosting theory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-feature-representation-boosting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILDCHAT-50M: A Deep Dive Into the Role of Synthetic Data in Post-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wildchat-50m-a-deep-dive-into-the-role-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language model (LLM) post-training, from DPO to distillation, can refine behaviors and unlock new skills, but the open science supporting these post-training techniques is still in its infancy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wildchat-50m-a-deep-dive-into-the-role-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Private Steering for Large Language Model Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-steering-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also develop the first Membership Inference Attack (MIA) for evaluating and auditing the empirical privacy for the problem of LLM steering via activation editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-steering-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UDC-VIT: A Real-World Video Dataset for Under-Display Cameras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/udc-vit-a-real-world-video-dataset-for-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a real-world UDC video dataset called UDC-VIT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/udc-vit-a-real-world-video-dataset-for-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VQLTI: Long-Term Tropical Cyclone Intensity Forecasting with Physical Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vqlti-long-term-tropical-cyclone-intensity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(2) Incorporating physical knowledge and physical constraints can help mitigate the accumulation of forecasting errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vqlti-long-term-tropical-cyclone-intensity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resampling Filter Design for Multirate Neural Audio Effect Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resampling-filter-design-for-multirate-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we investigate interpolation and decimation filters for the task of integer oversampling and show that cascaded half-band IIR and FIR designs can be used in conjunction with the model adjustment method to reduce aliasing in a range of distortion effect models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resampling-filter-design-for-multirate-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSA: Reconstructing Object Shape and Appearance Textures by Adaptive Detail Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rosa-reconstructing-object-shape-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we refine the mesh and locally condition the surface smoothness based on the estimated normal texture and mesh curvature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rosa-reconstructing-object-shape-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Cartesian Encoding Graph Neural Network for Crystal Structures Property Prediction: Application to Thermal Ellipsoid Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cartesian-encoding-graph-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In diffraction-based crystal structure analysis, thermal ellipsoids, quantified via Anisotropic Displacement Parameters (ADPs), are critical yet challenging to determine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cartesian-encoding-graph-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Equations Needed: Learning System Dynamics Without Relying on Closed-Form ODEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-equations-needed-learning-system-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Discovery of closed-form ordinary differential equations (ODEs) can be employed to obtain such insights by finding a compact mathematical equation and then analyzing it (a two-step approach).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-equations-needed-learning-system-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing Aleatoric and Epistemic Uncertainty through Multi-modal Data Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-aleatoric-and-epistemic-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To generate accurate and reliable predictions, modern AI systems need to combine data from multiple modalities, such as text, images, audio, spreadsheets, and time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-aleatoric-and-epistemic-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALM: Unleashing the Cross-Lingual Self-Aligning Ability of Language Model Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calm-unleashing-the-cross-lingual-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we explore the Cross-Lingual Self-Aligning ability of Language Models (CALM) to align knowledge across languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calm-unleashing-the-cross-lingual-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behavior Modeling Space Reconstruction for E-Commerce Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behavior-modeling-space-reconstruction-for-e</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Delivering superior search services is crucial for enhancing customer experience and driving revenue growth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behavior-modeling-space-reconstruction-for-e</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Input layer regularization and automated regularization hyperparameter tuning for myelin water estimation using deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/input-layer-regularization-and-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On in vivo brain data, our architecture again outperformed other comparison methods, with GCV proving to be somewhat superior to a NN for regularization parameter selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/input-layer-regularization-and-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scattering approach to diffusion quantifies axonal damage in brain injury</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scattering-approach-to-diffusion-quantifies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Early diagnosis and noninvasive monitoring of neurological disorders require sensitivity to elusive cellular-level alterations that occur much earlier than volumetric changes observable with the millimeter-resolution of medical imaging modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scattering-approach-to-diffusion-quantifies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RbFT: Robust Fine-tuning for Retrieval-Augmented Generation against Retrieval Defects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rbft-robust-fine-tuning-for-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) enhances large language models (LLMs) by integrating external knowledge retrieved from a knowledge base.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rbft-robust-fine-tuning-for-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Minimax Group Fairness in Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-minimax-group-fairness-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our contributions include (i) a novel application of CVaR to recommenders, (ii) showing that the DRO methods improve group metrics as well as overall performance, and (iii) demonstrating CVaR's effectiveness in the practical scenario of intersecting user groups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-minimax-group-fairness-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free-T2M: Frequency Enhanced Text-to-Motion Diffusion Model With Consistency Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-t2m-frequency-enhanced-text-to-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rapid progress in text-to-motion generation has been largely driven by diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-t2m-frequency-enhanced-text-to-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illusions of Relevance: Using Content Injection Attacks to Deceive Retrievers, Rerankers, and LLM Judges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illusions-of-relevance-using-content</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study systematically examines the factors that influence an attack's success, such as the placement of injected content and the balance between relevant and non-relevant material.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illusions-of-relevance-using-content</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sebra: Debiasing Through Self-Guided Bias Ranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sebra-debiasing-through-self-guided-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ranking samples by fine-grained estimates of spuriosity (the degree to which spurious cues are present) has recently been shown to significantly benefit bias mitigation, over the traditional binary biased-\textit{vs}-unbiased partitioning of train sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sebra-debiasing-through-self-guided-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLoQ: Enhancing Fine-Tuning of Quantized LLMs via Calibrated LoRA Initialization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cloq-enhancing-fine-tuning-of-quantized-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning large language models (LLMs) using low-rank adaptation (LoRA) has become a highly efficient approach for downstream tasks, particularly in scenarios with limited computational resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cloq-enhancing-fine-tuning-of-quantized-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GBFRS: Robust Fuzzy Rough Sets via Granular-ball Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gbfrs-robust-fuzzy-rough-sets-via-granular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fuzzy rough set theory is effective for processing datasets with complex attributes, supported by a solid mathematical foundation and closely linked to kernel methods in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gbfrs-robust-fuzzy-rough-sets-via-granular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging LLM Agents for Automated Optimization Modeling for SASP Problems: A Graph-RAG based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-llm-agents-for-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated optimization modeling (AOM) has evoked considerable interest with the rapid evolution of large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-llm-agents-for-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Neural Theorem Proving via Fine-grained Proof Structure Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-neural-theorem-proving-via-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The superiority of our method is validated on the miniF2F-test benchmark using the open-source deepseek-math-7b-base model and the Isabelle proof assistant.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-neural-theorem-proving-via-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panacea: Mitigating Harmful Fine-tuning for Large Language Models via Post-fine-tuning Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panacea-mitigating-harmful-fine-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mainstream defenses aim to vaccinate the model such that the later harmful fine-tuning attack is less effective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panacea-mitigating-harmful-fine-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs can see and hear without any training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-can-see-and-hear-without-any-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present MILS: Multimodal Iterative LLM Solver, a surprisingly simple, training-free approach, to imbue multimodal capabilities into your favorite LLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-can-see-and-hear-without-any-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Transformer for High Resolution Image Motion Deblurring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-transformer-for-high-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also provide detailed ablation studies analyzing the impact of our modifications on model behavior and performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-transformer-for-high-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Optimal Stopping for Early Classification within Finite Horizons via Sequential Probability Ratio Test</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-optimal-stopping-for-early</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We thus introduce FIRMBOUND, an SPRT-based framework that efficiently estimates the solution to backward induction from training data, bridging the gap between optimal stopping theory and real-world deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-optimal-stopping-for-early</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFPE: A Diverse Fingerprint Ensemble for Enhancing LLM Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfpe-a-diverse-fingerprint-ensemble-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have shown remarkable capabilities across various natural language processing tasks but often struggle to excel uniformly in diverse or complex domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfpe-a-diverse-fingerprint-ensemble-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning With Individualized Privacy Through Client Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-with-individualized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on this idea, we propose an adapted method for enabling Individualized Differential Privacy (IDP) in Federated Learning (FL) by handling clients according to their personal privacy preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-with-individualized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Making Flowchart Images Machine Interpretable</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-making-flowchart-images-machine-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computer programming textbooks and software documentations often contain flowcharts to illustrate the flow of an algorithm or procedure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-making-flowchart-images-machine-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Quantification and Decomposition for LLM-based Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-and-decomposition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the widespread adoption of large language models (LLMs) for recommendation, we demonstrate that LLMs often exhibit uncertainty in their recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-and-decomposition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Action Recognition Using Temporal Shift Module and Ensemble Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/action-recognition-using-temporal-shift</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The competition aimed to recognize human actions using a diverse dataset of 20 action classes, collected from multi-modal sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/action-recognition-using-temporal-shift</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Conversational XAI All You Need? Human-AI Decision Making With a Conversational XAI Assistant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-conversational-xai-all-you-need-human-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In comparison to an XAI dashboard, we found that the conversational XAI interface can bring about a better understanding of the AI system among users and higher user trust.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-conversational-xai-all-you-need-human-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When less is more: evolving large neural networks from small ones</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-less-is-more-evolving-large-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to conventional artificial neural networks, which are large and structurally static, we study feed-forward neural networks that are small and dynamic, whose nodes can be added (or subtracted) during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-less-is-more-evolving-large-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransRAD: Retentive Vision Transformer for Enhanced Radar Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transrad-retentive-vision-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant advancements in environment perception capabilities for autonomous driving and intelligent robotics, cameras and LiDARs remain notoriously unreliable in low-light conditions and adverse weather, which limits their effectiveness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transrad-retentive-vision-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>acoupi: An Open-Source Python Framework for Deploying Bioacoustic AI Models on Edge Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acoupi-an-open-source-python-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By modularising key elements of the bioacoustic monitoring workflow, acoupi allows users to easily customise, extend, or select specific components to fit their unique monitoring needs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acoupi-an-open-source-python-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Beyond the Surface: How Far Can Continual Pre-Training with LoRA Enhance LLMs' Domain-Specific Insight Learning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-beyond-the-surface-how-far-can</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable performance on various tasks, yet their ability to extract and internalize deeper insights from domain-specific datasets remains underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-beyond-the-surface-how-far-can</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2SSP: A Two-Stage Framework for Structured Pruning of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2ssp-a-two-stage-framework-for-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The second stage (Depth Pruning), instead, removes entire Attention submodules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2ssp-a-two-stage-framework-for-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the Gap Between Synthetic and Ground Truth Time Series Distributions via Neural Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-gap-between-synthetic-and-ground</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Neural Mapper for Vector Quantized Time Series Generator (NM-VQTSG), a novel method aimed at addressing fidelity challenges in vector quantized (VQ) time series generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-gap-between-synthetic-and-ground</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PulmoFusion: Advancing Pulmonary Health with Efficient Multi-Modal Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pulmofusion-advancing-pulmonary-health-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel, non-invasive approach using multimodal predictive models that integrate RGB or thermal video data with patient metadata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pulmofusion-advancing-pulmonary-health-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Your Model Ranking on Chatbot Arena by Vote Rigging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-your-model-ranking-on-chatbot-arena</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first introduce a straightforward target-only rigging strategy that focuses on new battles involving $m_{t}$, identifying it via watermarking or a binary classifier, and exclusively voting for $m_{t}$ wins.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-your-model-ranking-on-chatbot-arena</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Multimodal LLM for Inspirational User Interface Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-multimodal-llm-for-inspirational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspirational search, the process of exploring designs to inform and inspire new creative work, is pivotal in mobile user interface (UI) design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-multimodal-llm-for-inspirational</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
