<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 21:08:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>GM-TCNet: Gated Multi-scale Temporal Convolutional Network using Emotion Causality for Speech Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gm-tcnet-gated-multi-scale-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Gated Multi-scale Temporal Convolutional Network (GM-TCNet) to construct a novel emotional causality representation learning component with a multi-scale receptive field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gm-tcnet-gated-multi-scale-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Few-Shot Open-Set Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-few-shot-open-set-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We seek a solution for few-shot open-set object detection (FSOSOD), which aims to quickly train a detector based on few samples while detecting all known classes and identifying unknown classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-few-shot-open-set-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Generalization through the Lens of Angular Invariance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalization-through-the-lens-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the proposed term of invariance, we propose a novel deep DG method called Angular Invariance Domain Generalization Network (AIDGN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalization-through-the-lens-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bi-Directional Iterative Prompt-Tuning for Event Argument Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-directional-iterative-prompt-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, prompt-tuning has attracted growing interests in event argument extraction (EAE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-directional-iterative-prompt-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Trustworthy Multi-Modal Motion Prediction: Evaluation and Interpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-trustworthy-multi-modal-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we comprehensively analyse the evaluation metrics, identify the main gaps of current benchmarks, and propose a new holistic evaluation framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-trustworthy-multi-modal-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Measuring Calibration When Humans Disagree</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stop-measuring-calibration-when-humans</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Calibration is a popular framework to evaluate whether a classifier knows when it does not know - i. e., its predictive probabilities are a good indication of how likely a prediction is to be correct.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stop-measuring-calibration-when-humans</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESUS: Warm-Up Cold Users via Meta-Learning Residual User Preferences in CTR Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resus-warm-up-cold-users-via-meta-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we employ a shared predictor to infer basis user preferences, which acquires global preference knowledge from the interactions of different users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resus-warm-up-cold-users-via-meta-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cRedAnno+: Annotation Exploitation in Self-Explanatory Lung Nodule Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/credanno-annotation-exploitation-in-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, attempts have been made to reduce annotation requirements in feature-based self-explanatory models for lung nodule diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/credanno-annotation-exploitation-in-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk-Aware Bid Optimization for Online Display Advertisement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-aware-bid-optimization-for-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research focuses on the bid optimization problem in the real-time bidding setting for online display advertisements, where an advertiser, or the advertiser's agent, has access to the features of the website visitor and the type of ad slots, to decide the optimal bid prices given a predetermined total advertisement budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-aware-bid-optimization-for-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Use of Modality-Specific Large-Scale Pre-Trained Encoders for Multimodal Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-of-modality-specific-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the effectiveness and implementation of modality-specific large-scale pre-trained encoders for multimodal sentiment analysis~(MSA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-of-modality-specific-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vox-Fusion: Dense Tracking and Mapping with Voxel-based Neural Implicit Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vox-fusion-dense-tracking-and-mapping-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a dense tracking and mapping system named Vox-Fusion, which seamlessly fuses neural implicit representations with traditional volumetric fusion methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vox-fusion-dense-tracking-and-mapping-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object Segmentation of Cluttered Airborne LiDAR Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-segmentation-of-cluttered-airborne</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Airborne topographic LiDAR is an active remote sensing technology that emits near-infrared light to map objects on the Earth's surface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-segmentation-of-cluttered-airborne</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DORE: Document Ordered Relation Extraction based on Generative Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dore-document-ordered-relation-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the root cause of the underwhelming performance of the existing generative DocRE models and discover that the culprit is the inadequacy of the training paradigm, instead of the capacities of the models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dore-document-ordered-relation-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Zero-Shot Multilingual Translation with Universal Representations and Cross-Mappings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-zero-shot-multilingual-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The many-to-many multilingual neural machine translation can translate between language pairs unseen during training, i. e., zero-shot translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-zero-shot-multilingual-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextual Learning in Fourier Complex Field for VHR Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-learning-in-fourier-complex-field</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By stacking various layers of CSA blocks, we propose the Fourier Complex Transformer (FCT) model to learn global contextual information from VHR aerial images following the hierarchical manners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-learning-in-fourier-complex-field</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goal Exploration Augmentation via Pre-trained Skills for Sparse-Reward Long-Horizon Goal-Conditioned Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goal-exploration-augmentation-via-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In GCRL, exploring novel sub-goals is essential for the agent to ultimately find the pathway to the desired goal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goal-exploration-augmentation-via-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking performance of object detection under image distortions in an uncontrolled environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-performance-of-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we present a performance evaluation framework for the state-of-the-art object detection methods using a dedicated dataset containing images with various distortions at different levels of severity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-performance-of-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NNSVS: A Neural Network-Based Singing Voice Synthesis Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nnsvs-a-neural-network-based-singing-voice</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes the design of NNSVS, an open-source software for neural network-based singing voice synthesis research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nnsvs-a-neural-network-based-singing-voice</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Learning with Multi-View Rendering for 3D Point Cloud Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-with-multi-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the success of deep learning in the image domain, we devise a novel pre-training technique for better model initialization by utilizing the multi-view rendering of the 3D data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-with-multi-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Space is Feature Space: Regularization Term for GANs Training on Limited Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-space-is-feature-space-regularization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, a large amount of data is required, or the model would prone to generate images with similar patterns (mode collapse) and bad quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-space-is-feature-space-regularization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Lipschitz-Constrained Neural Networks by Learning Activation Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-lipschitz-constrained-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lipschitz-constrained neural networks have several advantages compared to unconstrained ones and can be applied to various different problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-lipschitz-constrained-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-driven discovery of Green's functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-discovery-of-green-s-functions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, theoretical results on Green's functions and rational NNs are combined to design a human-understandable deep learning method for discovering Green's functions from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-discovery-of-green-s-functions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributed Optimal Control of Graph Symmetric Systems via Graph Filters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributed-optimal-control-of-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing distributed optimal controllers subject to communication constraints is a difficult problem unless structural assumptions are imposed on the underlying dynamics and information exchange structure, e. g., sparsity, delay, or spatial invariance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributed-optimal-control-of-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Neural Topic Models Broken?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-neural-topic-models-broken</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, the relationship between automated and human evaluation of topic models has been called into question.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-neural-topic-models-broken</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complex Handwriting Trajectory Recovery: Evaluation Metrics and Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-handwriting-trajectory-recovery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many important tasks such as forensic signature verification, calligraphy synthesis, etc, rely on handwriting trajectory recovery of which, however, even an appropriate evaluation metric is still missing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-handwriting-trajectory-recovery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Adverse Biological Effect Predictions Using Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-adverse-biological-effect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An effect prediction model, with and without background knowledge, was used to predict mean adverse biological effect concentration of chemicals as a prototypical type of stressors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-adverse-biological-effect</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Label Correlations in a Multi-label Setting: A Case Study in Emotion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-label-correlations-in-a-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we develop two modeling approaches to the problem in order to capture word associations of the emotion words themselves, by either including the emotions in the input, or by leveraging Masked Language Modeling (MLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-label-correlations-in-a-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Spatial-Temporal Features for Deepfake Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-spatial-temporal-features-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a Spatial-Temporal Deepfake Detection and Localization (ST-DDL) network that simultaneously explores spatial and temporal features for detecting and localizing forged regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-spatial-temporal-features-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Analog Quantum Computing for Optimization and Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-analog-quantum-computing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We formulate the first differentiable analog quantum computing framework with a specific parameterization design at the analog signal (pulse) level to better exploit near-term quantum devices via variational methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-analog-quantum-computing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoChBert: Towards Robust BERT Fine-tuning for Chinese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rochbert-towards-robust-bert-fine-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite of the superb performance on a wide range of tasks, pre-trained language models (e. g., BERT) have been proved vulnerable to adversarial texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rochbert-towards-robust-bert-fine-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLT: Vision-Language Transformer and Query Generation for Referring Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlt-vision-language-transformer-and-query</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a Vision-Language Transformer (VLT) framework for referring segmentation to facilitate deep interactions among multi-modal information and enhance the holistic understanding to vision-language features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlt-vision-language-transformer-and-query</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergence of sector and spiral patterns from a two-species mutualistic cross-feeding model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-sector-and-spiral-patterns-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Focusing on the interplay among nutrient diffusion and individual cell division, we discover three general classes of colony morphology: co-existing sectors, co-existing spirals, and engulfment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-sector-and-spiral-patterns-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectrograms Are Sequences of Patches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectrograms-are-sequences-of-patches</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised pre-training models have been used successfully in several machine learning domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectrograms-are-sequences-of-patches</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preferential Subsampling for Stochastic Gradient Langevin Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preferential-subsampling-for-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stochastic gradient MCMC (SGMCMC) offers a scalable alternative to traditional MCMC, by constructing an unbiased estimate of the gradient of the log-posterior with a small, uniformly-weighted subsample of the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preferential-subsampling-for-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight and High-Fidelity End-to-End Text-to-Speech with Multi-Band Generation and Inverse Short-Time Fourier Transform</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-and-high-fidelity-end-to-end-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a lightweight end-to-end text-to-speech model using multi-band generation and inverse short-time Fourier transform.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-and-high-fidelity-end-to-end-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERNIE-ViLG 2.0: Improving Text-to-Image Diffusion Model with Knowledge-Enhanced Mixture-of-Denoising-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ernie-vilg-2-0-improving-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in diffusion models has revolutionized the popular technology of text-to-image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ernie-vilg-2-0-improving-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Networks with Quantization Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-with-quantization-constraints</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we show that dual variables indicate the sensitivity of the objective with respect to constraint perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-with-quantization-constraints</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting the ACVI Method for Constrained Variational Inequalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-acvi-method-for-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show that the same guarantee holds when only assuming that the operator is monotone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-acvi-method-for-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Adaptive Object Detection for Autonomous Driving under Foggy Weather</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-object-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel domain adaptive object detection framework for autonomous driving under foggy weather.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-object-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermarking for Out-of-distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watermarking-for-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-distribution (OOD) detection aims to identify OOD data based on representations extracted from well-trained deep models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watermarking-for-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COST-EFF: Collaborative Optimization of Spatial and Temporal Efficiency with Slenderized Multi-exit Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-eff-collaborative-optimization-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by such considerations, we propose a collaborative optimization for PLMs that integrates static model compression and dynamic inference acceleration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-eff-collaborative-optimization-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Convolutional Neural Networks for Multi-Target Tracking: A Transfer Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-convolutional-neural-networks-for-multi-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We represent the target states and sensor measurements as images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-convolutional-neural-networks-for-multi-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Complex Backgrounds: A Unified Difference-Aware Decoder for Binary Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-complex-backgrounds-a-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Stage A, the first branch decoder of the difference-aware decoder is used to obtain a guide map.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-complex-backgrounds-a-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MorphTE: Injecting Morphology in Tensorized Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphte-injecting-morphology-in-tensorized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the era of deep learning, word embeddings are essential when dealing with text tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphte-injecting-morphology-in-tensorized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmentation of Multiple Sclerosis Lesions across Hospitals: Learn Continually or Train from Scratch?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-of-multiple-sclerosis-lesions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segmentation of Multiple Sclerosis (MS) lesions is a challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-of-multiple-sclerosis-lesions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrapping Human Optical Flow and Pose</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bootstrapping-human-optical-flow-and-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a bootstrapping framework to enhance human optical flow and pose.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bootstrapping-human-optical-flow-and-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Articulation GAN: Unsupervised modeling of articulatory learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/articulation-gan-unsupervised-modeling-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Articulatory analysis of the generated EMA representations suggests that the network learns to control articulators in a manner that closely follows human articulators during speech production.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/articulation-gan-unsupervised-modeling-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Inter-Dependence Between Time and Mark in Multivariate Temporal Point Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-inter-dependence-between-time-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we model the conditional inter-dependence of time and mark to overcome the limitations of conditionally independent models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-inter-dependence-between-time-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dictionary-Assisted Supervised Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dictionary-assisted-supervised-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text analysis in the social sciences often involves using specialized dictionaries to reason with abstract concepts, such as perceptions about the economy or abuse on social media.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dictionary-assisted-supervised-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening the Black Box of wav2vec Feature Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opening-the-black-box-of-wav2vec-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised models, namely, wav2vec and its variants, have shown promising results in various downstream tasks in the speech domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opening-the-black-box-of-wav2vec-feature</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
