<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 21:08:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Ninth NTIRE 2024 Efficient Super-Resolution Challenge Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ninth-ntire-2024-efficient-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In sub-track 1, the practical runtime performance of the submissions was evaluated, and the corresponding score was used to determine the ranking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ninth-ntire-2024-efficient-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph neural network-based surrogate modelling for real-time hydraulic prediction of urban drainage networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-network-based-surrogate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the model structure adheres to the flow routing mechanisms and hydraulic constraints in urban drainage networks, it provides an interpretable and effective solution for data-driven surrogate modelling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-network-based-surrogate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLINGER-UCB: A novel algorithm for stochastic multi-armed bandit problem and cold start problem in recommender system</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hellinger-ucb-a-novel-algorithm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the stochastic multi-armed bandit problem, where the reward is driven by an unknown random variable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hellinger-ucb-a-novel-algorithm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnable Prompt for Few-Shot Semantic Segmentation in Remote Sensing Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-prompt-for-few-shot-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few-shot segmentation is a task to segment objects or regions of novel classes within an image given only a few annotated examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-prompt-for-few-shot-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demonstration of DB-GPT: Next Generation Data Interaction System Empowered by Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demonstration-of-db-gpt-next-generation-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent breakthroughs in large language models (LLMs) are positioned to transition many areas of software.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demonstration-of-db-gpt-next-generation-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analytical Approximation of the ELBO Gradient in the Context of the Clutter Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analytical-approximation-of-the-elbo-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an analytical solution for approximating the gradient of the Evidence Lower Bound (ELBO) in variational inference problems where the statistical model is a Bayesian network consisting of observations drawn from a mixture of a Gaussian distribution embedded in unrelated clutter, known as the clutter problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analytical-approximation-of-the-elbo-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEEL: Multi-Modal Event Evolution Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meel-multi-modal-event-evolution-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we observe that models trained in this way are still struggling to fully comprehend event evolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meel-multi-modal-event-evolution-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Conditional Diffusion Model with Probability Flow Sampling for Image Super-resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-conditional-diffusion-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing diffusion-based super-resolution methods have high time consumption with the use of iterative sampling, while the quality and consistency of generated images are less than ideal due to problems like color shifting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-conditional-diffusion-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiral of Silences: How is Large Language Model Killing Information Retrieval? -- A Case Study on Open Domain Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiral-of-silences-how-is-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The practice of Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG), which integrates Large Language Models (LLMs) with retrieval systems, has become increasingly prevalent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiral-of-silences-how-is-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intriguing Properties of Positional Encoding in Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intriguing-properties-of-positional-encoding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by these findings, we introduce two new PEs: Temporal Position Encoding (T-PE) for temporal tokens and Variable Positional Encoding (V-PE) for variable tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intriguing-properties-of-positional-encoding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Autoencoders for Microscopy are Scalable Learners of Cellular Biology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-for-microscopy-are</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Featurizing microscopy images for use in biological research remains a significant challenge, especially for large-scale experiments spanning millions of images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-for-microscopy-are</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoE-TinyMed: Mixture of Experts for Tiny Medical Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moe-tinymed-mixture-of-experts-for-tiny</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mixture of Expert Tuning (MoE-Tuning) has effectively enhanced the performance of general MLLMs with fewer parameters, yet its application in resource-limited medical settings has not been fully explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moe-tinymed-mixture-of-experts-for-tiny</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plug-and-Play Acceleration of Occupancy Grid-based NeRF Rendering using VDB Grid and Hierarchical Ray Traversal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-acceleration-of-occupancy-grid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transmittance estimators such as Occupancy Grid (OG) can accelerate the training and rendering of Neural Radiance Field (NeRF) by predicting important samples that contributes much to the generated image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-acceleration-of-occupancy-grid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViTextVQA: A Large-Scale Visual Question Answering Dataset for Evaluating Vietnamese Text Comprehension in Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitextvqa-a-large-scale-visual-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Question Answering (VQA) is a complicated task that requires the capability of simultaneously processing natural language and images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitextvqa-a-large-scale-visual-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-driven subgrouping of patient trajectories with chronic diseases: Evidence from low back pain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-subgrouping-of-patient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we discuss the applicability of the model to other chronic and long-lasting diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-subgrouping-of-patient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future Language Modeling from Temporal Document History</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/future-language-modeling-from-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While there are many automated systems for predicting future numerical data, such as weather, stock prices, and demand for products, there is relatively little work in automatically predicting textual data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/future-language-modeling-from-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VDTuner: Automated Performance Tuning for Vector Data Management Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vdtuner-automated-performance-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to the inherent characteristics of VDMS, automatic performance tuning for VDMS faces several critical challenges, which cannot be well addressed by the existing auto-tuning methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vdtuner-automated-performance-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Context Merging: Better Long Context Understanding for Pre-trained LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-context-merging-better-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown remarkable performance in various natural language processing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-context-merging-better-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MobileNetV4 - Universal Models for the Mobile Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobilenetv4-universal-models-for-the-mobile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the latest generation of MobileNets, known as MobileNetV4 (MNv4), featuring universally efficient architecture designs for mobile devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobilenetv4-universal-models-for-the-mobile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-playing Adversarial Language Game Enhances LLM Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-playing-adversarial-language-game</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, we are curious about whether LLMs' reasoning ability can be further enhanced by Self-Play in this Adversarial language Game (SPAG).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-playing-adversarial-language-game</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warm-Start Variational Quantum Policy Iteration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/warm-start-variational-quantum-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This objective can be achieved using policy iteration, which requires to solve a typically large linear system of equations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/warm-start-variational-quantum-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Symbolic Task Representation from a Human-Led Demonstration: A Memory to Store, Retrieve, Consolidate, and Forget Experiences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-symbolic-task-representation-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a symbolic learning framework inspired by cognitive-like memory functionalities (i. e., storing, retrieving, consolidating and forgetting) to generate task representations to support high-level task planning and knowledge bootstrapping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-symbolic-task-representation-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LWIRPOSE: A novel LWIR Thermal Image Dataset and Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lwirpose-a-novel-lwir-thermal-image-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human pose estimation faces hurdles in real-world applications due to factors like lighting changes, occlusions, and cluttered environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lwirpose-a-novel-lwir-thermal-image-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpolation and differentiation of alchemical degrees of freedom in machine learning interatomic potentials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpolation-and-differentiation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning interatomic potentials (MLIPs) have become a workhorse of modern atomistic simulations, and recently published universal MLIPs, pre-trained on large datasets, have demonstrated remarkable accuracy and generalizability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpolation-and-differentiation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing BioTac Simulation for Realistic Tactile Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-biotac-simulation-for-realistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, our results reveal that the XGBoost regressor and transformer outperform traditional feed-forward neural networks in this task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-biotac-simulation-for-realistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiniCheck: Efficient Fact-Checking of LLMs on Grounding Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minicheck-efficient-fact-checking-of-llms-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We release LLM-AggreFact, code for data synthesis, and models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minicheck-efficient-fact-checking-of-llms-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision-and-Language Navigation via Causal Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-and-language-navigation-via-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the pursuit of robust and generalizable environment perception and language understanding, the ubiquitous challenge of dataset bias continues to plague vision-and-language navigation (VLN) agents, hindering their performance in unseen environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-and-language-navigation-via-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaDiC: Are Diffusion Models Really Inferior to Autoregressive Counterparts for Image-to-Text Generation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ladic-are-diffusion-models-really-inferior-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have exhibited remarkable capabilities in text-to-image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ladic-are-diffusion-models-really-inferior-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TorchSurv: A Lightweight Package for Deep Survival Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchsurv-a-lightweight-package-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TorchSurv is a Python package that serves as a companion tool to perform deep survival modeling within the PyTorch environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchsurv-a-lightweight-package-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CULTURE-GEN: Revealing Global Cultural Perception in Language Models through Natural Language Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/culture-gen-revealing-global-cultural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the utilization of large language models (LLMs) has proliferated worldwide, it is crucial for them to have adequate knowledge and fair representation for diverse global cultures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/culture-gen-revealing-global-cultural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Instructive Information from Ranked Multiple Candidates for Multi-Document Scientific Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-instructive-information-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our insights are twofold: Firstly, summary candidates can provide instructive information from both positive and negative perspectives, and secondly, selecting higher-quality candidates from multiple options contributes to producing better summaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-instructive-information-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Offline Reinforcement Learning via Diffusion-based Dual Generative Replay</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-offline-reinforcement-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, by interleaving pseudo samples with real ones of the new task, we continually update the state and behavior generators to model progressively diverse behaviors, and regularize the multi-head critic via behavior cloning to mitigate forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-offline-reinforcement-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cluster-based Graph Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-based-graph-collaborative-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This model performs high-order graph convolution on cluster-specific graphs, which are constructed by capturing the multiple interests of users and identifying the common interests among them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-based-graph-collaborative-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>in2IN: Leveraging individual Information to Generate Human INteractions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in2in-leveraging-individual-information-to-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this, we introduce in2IN, a novel diffusion model for human-human motion generation which is conditioned not only on the textual description of the overall interaction but also on the individual descriptions of the actions performed by each person involved in the interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in2in-leveraging-individual-information-to-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plus Strategies are Exponentially Slower for Planted Optima of Random Height</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plus-strategies-are-exponentially-slower-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the $(1,\lambda)$-EA and the $(1 + \lambda)$-EA on the recently introduced benchmark DisOM, which is the OneMax function with randomly planted local optima.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plus-strategies-are-exponentially-slower-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring Behavior-Specific Context Improves Zero-Shot Generalization in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-behavior-specific-context-improves</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address the challenge of zero-shot generalization (ZSG) in Reinforcement Learning (RL), where agents must adapt to entirely novel environments without additional training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-behavior-specific-context-improves</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMPCliff: quantitative definition and benchmarking of activity cliffs in antimicrobial peptides</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ampcliff-quantitative-definition-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our analysis reveals that these models are capable of detecting AMP AC events and the pre-trained protein language ESM2 model demonstrates superior performance across the evaluations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ampcliff-quantitative-definition-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Vision and Language Spaces with Assignment Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-vision-and-language-spaces-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces VLAP, a novel approach that bridges pretrained vision models and large language models (LLMs) to make frozen LLMs understand the visual world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-vision-and-language-spaces-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Reinforcement Learning Based on Structural Information Principles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-reinforcement-learning-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An innovative two-layer skill-based learning mechanism is introduced to compute the common path entropy of each state transition as its identified probability, thereby obviating the requirement for expert knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-reinforcement-learning-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tango 2: Aligning Diffusion-based Text-to-Audio Generations through Direct Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tango-2-aligning-diffusion-based-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These models do not explicitly focus on the presence of concepts or events and their temporal ordering in the output audio with respect to the input prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tango-2-aligning-diffusion-based-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOISe: Nuclei-Aware Osteoclast Instance Segmentation for Mouse-to-Human Domain Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-nuclei-aware-osteoclast-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the last few years, a handful of machine learning approaches for osteoclast image analysis have been developed, but none have addressed the full instance segmentation task required to produce the same output as that of the human expert led process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-nuclei-aware-osteoclast-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-KD: Towards Alignment Invariant Face Image Quality Assessment Using Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-kd-towards-alignment-invariant-face-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we present in this paper a novel knowledge distillation approach, termed AI-KD that can extend on any existing FIQA technique, improving its robustness to alignment variations and, in turn, performance with different alignment procedures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-kd-towards-alignment-invariant-face-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MyGO: Discrete Modality Information as Fine-Grained Tokens for Multi-modal Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mygo-discrete-modality-information-as-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome their inherent incompleteness, multi-modal knowledge graph completion (MMKGC) aims to discover unobserved knowledge from given MMKGs, leveraging both structural information from the triples and multi-modal information of the entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mygo-discrete-modality-information-as-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Collaborative Fine-Tuning for On-Device Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-collaborative-fine-tuning-for-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore on-device self-supervised collaborative fine-tuning of large language models with limited local data availability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-collaborative-fine-tuning-for-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Training Network Compression for 3D Medical Image Segmentation: Reducing Computational Efforts via Tucker Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-training-network-compression-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The application of Tucker decomposition to the TS model substantially reduced the model parameters and FLOPs across various compression rates, with limited loss in segmentation accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-training-network-compression-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If there's a Trigger Warning, then where's the Trigger? Investigating Trigger Warnings at the Passage Level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/if-there-s-a-trigger-warning-then-where-s-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trigger warnings are labels that preface documents with sensitive content if this content could be perceived as harmful by certain groups of readers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/if-there-s-a-trigger-warning-then-where-s-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amplitude-Phase Fusion for Enhanced Electrocardiogram Morphological Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amplitude-phase-fusion-for-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering the variability of amplitude and phase patterns in electrocardiogram (ECG) signals due to cardiac activity and individual differences, existing entropy-based studies have not fully utilized these two patterns and lack integration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amplitude-phase-fusion-for-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-objective evolutionary GAN for tabular data synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-evolutionary-gan-for-tabular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, there are unique challenges in tabular data compared to images, eg tabular data may contain both continuous and discrete variables and conditional sampling, and, critically, the data should possess high utility and low disclosure risk (the risk of re-identifying a population unit or learning something new about them), providing an opportunity for multi-objective (MO) optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-evolutionary-gan-for-tabular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PD-L1 Classification of Weakly-Labeled Whole Slide Images of Breast Cancer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pd-l1-classification-of-weakly-labeled-whole</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also tested the performance with or without human preprocessing to remove brown artefacts Colour distance based models achieve the best performances on testing configuration (1) with artefact removal, while autoencoder-based models are superior in the remaining cases, which are prone to greater data variability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pd-l1-classification-of-weakly-labeled-whole</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AesExpert: Towards Multi-modality Foundation Model for Image Aesthetics Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aesexpert-towards-multi-modality-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above challenge, we first introduce a comprehensively annotated Aesthetic Multi-Modality Instruction Tuning (AesMMIT) dataset, which serves as the footstone for building multi-modality aesthetics foundation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aesexpert-towards-multi-modality-foundation</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
