<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 09:16:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Quantification via Gaussian Latent Space Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantification-via-gaussian-latent-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantification, or prevalence estimation, is the task of predicting the prevalence of each class within an unknown bag of examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantification-via-gaussian-latent-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Transformer-based Autoregressive Decoder Architecture for Hierarchical Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transformer-based-autoregressive-decoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, unlike existing approaches for HTC, the encoder of RADAr has no explicit encoding of the label hierarchy and the decoder solely relies on the label sequences of the samples observed during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transformer-based-autoregressive-decoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Efficient Diffusion-based Non-Autoregressive Solver for Traveling Salesman Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-diffusion-based-non</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enhance the solution quality while maintaining fast inference, we propose DEITSP, a diffusion model with efficient iterations tailored for TSP that operates in a NAR manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-diffusion-based-non</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularizing cross entropy loss via minimum entropy and K-L divergence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-cross-entropy-loss-via-minimum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The two loss functions extend standard cross entropy loss by regularizing it with minimum entropy and Kullback-Leibler (K-L) divergence terms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-cross-entropy-loss-via-minimum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Vision-Language Models for Knowledge-Grounded Data Annotation of Memes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-vision-language-models-for-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Memes have emerged as a powerful form of communication, integrating visual and textual elements to convey humor, satire, and cultural messages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-vision-language-models-for-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning for Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, this survey aims to provide a comprehensive overview of PEFT techniques applied to diverse FMs and address critical gaps in understanding the techniques, trends, and applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoPixel: Pixel Grounding Large Multimodal Model in Remote Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geopixel-pixel-grounding-large-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GeoPixel supports up to 4K HD resolution in any aspect ratio, ideal for high-precision RS image analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geopixel-pixel-grounding-large-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Prompt-One-Story: Free-Lunch Consistent Text-to-Image Generation Using a Single Prompt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-prompt-one-story-free-lunch-consistent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Drawing inspiration from the inherent context consistency, we propose a novel training-free method for consistent text-to-image (T2I) generation, termed "One-Prompt-One-Story" (1Prompt1Story).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-prompt-one-story-free-lunch-consistent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Video Understanding and Multi-round Interaction with Memory-enhanced Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-video-understanding-and-multi-round</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in Large Language Models (LLMs) have enabled the development of Video-LLMs, advancing multimodal learning by bridging video data with language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-video-understanding-and-multi-round</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pix2Cap-COCO: Advancing Visual Comprehension via Pixel-Level Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pix2cap-coco-advancing-visual-comprehension</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results demonstrate that Pix2Cap-COCO is a particularly challenging dataset, as it requires models to excel in both fine-grained visual understanding and detailed language generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pix2cap-coco-advancing-visual-comprehension</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantized Spike-driven Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantized-spike-driven-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate this issue, we take inspiration from mutual information entropy and propose a bi-level optimization strategy to rectify the information distribution in Q-SDSA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantized-spike-driven-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LITE: Efficiently Estimating Gaussian Probability of Maximality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lite-efficiently-estimating-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of computing the probability of maximality (PoM) of a Gaussian random vector, i. e., the probability for each dimension to be maximal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lite-efficiently-estimating-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utilizing Evolution Strategies to Train Transformers in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilizing-evolution-strategies-to-train</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore a capability of evolution strategies to train an agent with its policy based on a transformer architecture in a reinforcement learning setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilizing-evolution-strategies-to-train</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixRec: Individual and Collective Mixing Empowers Data Augmentation for Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixrec-individual-and-collective-mixing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, data sparsity caused by difficult-to-access interaction data severely limits the effectiveness of recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixrec-individual-and-collective-mixing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable XR: Understanding User Behaviors of XR Environments using LLM-assisted Analytics Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-xr-understanding-user-behaviors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Explainable XR, an end-to-end framework for analyzing user behavior in diverse eXtended Reality (XR) environments by leveraging Large Language Models (LLMs) for data interpretation assistance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-xr-understanding-user-behaviors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAMQA: A Unified Framework for Retrieval-Augmented Multi-Modal Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ramqa-a-unified-framework-for-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal retrieval-augmented Question Answering (MRAQA), integrating text and images, has gained significant attention in information retrieval (IR) and natural language processing (NLP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ramqa-a-unified-framework-for-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do as We Do, Not as You Think: the Conformity of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-as-we-do-not-as-you-think-the-conformity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) revolutionize the field of intelligent agents, enabling collaborative multi-agent systems capable of tackling complex problems across various domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-as-we-do-not-as-you-think-the-conformity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentRec: Agent Recommendation Using Sentence Embeddings Aligned to Human Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentrec-agent-recommendation-using-sentence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel architecture for recommending which LLM agent out of many should perform a task given a natural language prompt by extending the Sentence-BERT (SBERT) encoder model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentrec-agent-recommendation-using-sentence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M3PT: A Transformer for Multimodal, Multi-Party Social Signal Prediction with Person-aware Blockwise Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3pt-a-transformer-for-multimodal-multi-party</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding social signals in multi-party conversations is important for human-robot interaction and artificial social intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3pt-a-transformer-for-multimodal-multi-party</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can We Generate Images with CoT? Let's Verify and Reinforce Image Generation Step by Step</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-generate-images-with-cot-let-s-verify</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope our study provides unique insights and paves a new path for integrating CoT reasoning with autoregressive image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-generate-images-with-cot-let-s-verify</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensuring Medical AI Safety: Explainable AI-Driven Detection and Mitigation of Spurious Model Behavior and Associated Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensuring-medical-ai-safety-explainable-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks are increasingly employed in high-stakes medical applications, despite their tendency for shortcut learning in the presence of spurious correlations, which can have potentially fatal consequences in practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensuring-medical-ai-safety-explainable-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Disentangled Training for Nonlinear Transform in Learned Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-disentangled-training-for-nonlinear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On such basis, we propose a linear auxiliary transform (AuxT) to disentangle energy compaction in training nonlinear transforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-disentangled-training-for-nonlinear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Realistic Forehead-Creases for User Verification via Conditioned Piecewise Polynomial Curves</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-realistic-forehead-creases-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a trait-specific image generation method that models forehead creases geometrically using B-spline and B\'ezier curves.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-realistic-forehead-creases-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-driven Online Action Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-driven-online-action-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting actions as they occur is essential for applications like video surveillance, autonomous driving, and human-robot interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-driven-online-action-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Multimodal Open-set Test-time Adaptation via Adaptive Entropy-aware Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-multimodal-open-set-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This task becomes more challenging when multiple modalities are involved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-multimodal-open-set-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NUDT4MSTAR: A New Dataset and Benchmark Towards SAR Target Recognition in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nudt4mstar-a-new-dataset-and-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces NUDT4MSTAR, a large-scale SAR dataset for vehicle target recognition in the wild, including 40 target types and a wide array of imaging conditions across 5 different scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nudt4mstar-a-new-dataset-and-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EgoHand: Ego-centric Hand Pose Estimation and Gesture Recognition with Head-mounted Millimeter-wave Radar and IMUs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egohand-ego-centric-hand-pose-estimation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advanced Virtual Reality (VR) headsets, such as the Apple Vision Pro, employ bottom-facing cameras to detect hand gestures and inputs, which offers users significant convenience in VR interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egohand-ego-centric-hand-pose-estimation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MambaQuant: Quantizing the Mamba Family with Variance Aligned Rotation Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambaquant-quantizing-the-mamba-family-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To these ends, we propose MambaQuant, a post-training quantization (PTQ) framework consisting of: 1) Karhunen-Loeve Transformation (KLT) enhanced rotation, rendering the rotation matrix adaptable to diverse channel distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambaquant-quantizing-the-mamba-family-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unraveling Normal Anatomy via Fluid-Driven Anomaly Randomization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-normal-anatomy-via-fluid-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[UNA is trained on a combination of synthetic and real data, and can be applied directly to real images with potential pathology without the need for fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-normal-anatomy-via-fluid-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAA: Kolmogorov-Arnold Attention for Enhancing Attentive Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kaa-kolmogorov-arnold-attention-for-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) with attention mechanisms, often referred to as attentive GNNs, have emerged as a prominent paradigm in advanced GNN models in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kaa-kolmogorov-arnold-attention-for-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Conformance Checking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-conformance-checking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We generate synthetic event logs for each organization as well as the complete process, and we apply our approach to identify and evaluate the cost of pre-injected miscommunications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-conformance-checking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating the Conformal Prediction Threshold from Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-the-conformal-prediction-threshold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conformal Prediction (CP) is a method to control prediction uncertainty by producing a small prediction set, ensuring a predetermined probability that the true class lies within this set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-the-conformal-prediction-threshold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O1-Pruner: Length-Harmonizing Fine-Tuning for O1-Like Reasoning Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/o1-pruner-length-harmonizing-fine-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on various mathematical reasoning benchmarks show that O1-Pruner not only significantly reduces inference overhead but also achieves higher accuracy, providing a novel and promising solution to this challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/o1-pruner-length-harmonizing-fine-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pairwise RM: Perform Best-of-N Sampling with Knockout Tournament</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pairwise-rm-perform-best-of-n-sampling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose a Pairwise Reward Model (Pairwise RM) combined with a knockout tournament for BoN sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pairwise-rm-perform-best-of-n-sampling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distillation Quantification for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-quantification-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model distillation is a technique for transferring knowledge from large language models (LLMs) to smaller ones, aiming to create resource-efficient yet high-performing models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-quantification-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularization, Semi-supervision, and Supervision for a Plausible Attention-Based Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularization-semi-supervision-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We thus propose 3 additional constraints to the learning objective function to improve the plausibility of the attention map: regularization to increase the attention weight sparsity, semi-supervision to supervise the map by a heuristic and supervision by human annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularization-semi-supervision-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Table Source Matter? Benchmarking and Improving Multimodal Scientific Table Understanding and Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-table-source-matter-benchmarking-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While multimodal large language models (MLLMs) enable direct visual processing, they face limitations in handling scientific tables due to fixed input image resolutions and insufficient numerical reasoning capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-table-source-matter-benchmarking-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring GPT's Ability as a Judge in Music Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-gpt-s-ability-as-a-judge-in-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We convert the music data to symbolic inputs and evaluate LLMs' ability in detecting annotation errors in three key MIR tasks: beat tracking, chord extraction, and key estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-gpt-s-ability-as-a-judge-in-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Data Augmentation for Ultrasound Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-data-augmentation-for-ultrasound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results demonstrate that many of the augmentations commonly used for tasks on natural images are also effective on ultrasound images, even more so than augmentations developed specifically for ultrasound images in some cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-data-augmentation-for-ultrasound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDFORM: A Foundation Model for Contrastive Learning of CT Imaging and Clinical Numeric Data in Multi-Cancer Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medform-a-foundation-model-for-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose MEDFORM, a multimodal pre-training strategy that guides CT image representation learning using complementary information from clinical data for medical foundation model development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medform-a-foundation-model-for-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Invariant Learning Framework for Graph Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-invariant-learning-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It provides a unified perspective on invariant graph learning, emphasizing both structural and semantic invariance principles to identify more robust stable features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-invariant-learning-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Modeling for Multi-order Human Visual Motion Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-modeling-for-multi-order</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While recent advances in computer vision (CV) have enabled DNN-based models to accurately estimate optical flow in naturalistic images, a significant disparity remains between CV models and the biological visual system in both architecture and behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-modeling-for-multi-order</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let SSMs be ConvNets: State-space Modeling with Optimal Tensor Contractions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-ssms-be-convnets-state-space-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Centaurus, a class of networks composed of generalized state-space model (SSM) blocks, where the SSM operations can be treated as tensor contractions during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-ssms-be-convnets-state-space-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlanEC: Exploring Flan-T5 for Post-ASR Error Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flanec-exploring-flan-t5-for-post-asr-error</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an encoder-decoder model leveraging Flan-T5 for post-Automatic Speech Recognition (ASR) Generative Speech Error Correction (GenSEC), and we refer to it as FlanEC.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flanec-exploring-flan-t5-for-post-asr-error</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Representation Consistency Model via Contrastive Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-representation-consistency-model-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, our method outperforms the certified accuracy of diffusion-based methods on ImageNet across all perturbation radii by 5. 3% on average, with up to 11. 6% at larger radii, while reducing inference costs by 85$\times$ on average.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-representation-consistency-model-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Losses for Hierarchical Embedding Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-losses-for-hierarchical-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In traditional supervised learning, the cross-entropy loss treats all incorrect predictions equally, ignoring the relevance or proximity of wrong labels to the correct answer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-losses-for-hierarchical-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimeFilter: Patch-Specific Spatial-Temporal Graph Filtration for Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timefilter-patch-specific-spatial-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current time series forecasting methods can be broadly classified into two categories: Channel Independent (CI) and Channel Dependent (CD) strategies, both aiming to capture the complex dependencies within time series data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timefilter-patch-specific-spatial-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PPO-Based Vehicle Control for Ramp Merging Scheme Assisted by Enhanced C-V2X</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppo-based-vehicle-control-for-ramp-merging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On-ramp merging presents a critical challenge in autonomous driving, as vehicles from merging lanes need to dynamically adjust their positions and speeds while monitoring traffic on the main road to prevent collisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppo-based-vehicle-control-for-ramp-merging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STMDNet: A Lightweight Directional Framework for Motion Pattern Recognition of Tiny Targets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stmdnet-a-lightweight-directional-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizing motions of tiny targets - only few dozen pixels - in cluttered backgrounds remains a fundamental challenge when standard feature-based or deep learning methods fail under scarce visual cues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stmdnet-a-lightweight-directional-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAMED-Snake: Gradient-aware Adaptive Momentum Evolution Deep Snake Model for Multi-organ Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gamed-snake-gradient-aware-adaptive-momentum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-organ segmentation is a critical yet challenging task due to complex anatomical backgrounds, blurred boundaries, and diverse morphologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gamed-snake-gradient-aware-adaptive-momentum</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
