<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:14:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hypothesizing Missing Causal Variables with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypothesizing-missing-causal-variables-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the scientific discovery process, in this work, we formulate a novel task where the input is a partial causal graph with missing variables, and the output is a hypothesis about the missing variables to complete the partial graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypothesizing-missing-causal-variables-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Spurious Bias in Few-Shot Image Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-spurious-bias-in-few-shot-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a systematic and rigorous benchmark framework, termed FewSTAB, to fairly demonstrate and quantify varied degrees of robustness of few-shot classifiers to spurious bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-spurious-bias-in-few-shot-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurgTrack: CAD-Free 3D Tracking of Real-world Surgical Instruments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgtrack-cad-free-3d-tracking-of-real-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared with 2D instrument tracking methods, 3D instrument tracking has broader value in clinical practice, but is also more challenging due to weak texture, occlusion, and lack of Computer-Aided Design (CAD) models for 3D registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgtrack-cad-free-3d-tracking-of-real-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pooling And Attention: What Are Effective Designs For LLm-Based Embedding Models?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pooling-and-attention-what-are-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While these models, employing different pooling and attention strategies, have achieved state-of-the-art performance on public embedding benchmarks, questions still arise about what constitutes an effective design for LLM-based embedding models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pooling-and-attention-what-are-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdvSecureNet: A Python Toolkit for Adversarial Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advsecurenet-a-python-toolkit-for-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce AdvSecureNet, a PyTorch based toolkit for adversarial machine learning that is the first to natively support multi-GPU setups for attacks, defenses, and evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advsecurenet-a-python-toolkit-for-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongLLaVA: Scaling Multi-modal LLMs to 1000 Images Efficiently via Hybrid Architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longllava-scaling-multi-modal-llms-to-1000</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Expanding the long-context capabilities of Multi-modal Large Language Models~(MLLMs) is crucial for video understanding, high-resolution image understanding, and multi-modal agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longllava-scaling-multi-modal-llms-to-1000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topological Methods in Machine Learning: A Tutorial for Practitioners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topological-methods-in-machine-learning-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topological Machine Learning (TML) is an emerging field that leverages techniques from algebraic topology to analyze complex data structures in ways that traditional machine learning methods may not capture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topological-methods-in-machine-learning-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TP-GMOT: Tracking Generic Multiple Object by Textual Prompt with Motion-Appearance Cost (MAC) SORT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tp-gmot-tracking-generic-multiple-object-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Multi-Object Tracking (MOT) has made substantial advancements, it is limited by heavy reliance on prior knowledge and limited to predefined categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tp-gmot-tracking-generic-multiple-object-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleTokenizer: Defining Image Style by a Single Instance for Controlling Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styletokenizer-defining-image-style-by-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these challenges, we introduce StyleTokenizer, a zero-shot style control image generation method that aligns style representation with text representation using a style tokenizer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styletokenizer-defining-image-style-by-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Korean Food Using Image using Hierarchical Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-korean-food-using-image-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A solution was made available for Korean Food lovers who have dietary restrictions to identify the Korean food before consuming.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-korean-food-using-image-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UC-NeRF: Uncertainty-aware Conditional Neural Radiance Fields from Endoscopic Sparse Views</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uc-nerf-uncertainty-aware-conditional-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In neural rendering, we design a base-adaptive NeRF network to exploit the uncertainty estimation for explicitly handling the photometric inconsistencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uc-nerf-uncertainty-aware-conditional-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oops, I Sampled it Again: Reinterpreting Confidence Intervals in Few-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oops-i-sampled-it-again-reinterpreting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The predominant method for computing confidence intervals (CI) in few-shot learning (FSL) is based on sampling the tasks with replacement, i. e.\ allowing the same samples to appear in multiple tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oops-i-sampled-it-again-reinterpreting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiPrompt: Tuning-free Higher-Resolution Generation with Hierarchical MLLM Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiprompt-tuning-free-higher-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The hierarchical prompts offer both global and local guidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiprompt-tuning-free-higher-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAPF-GPT: Imitation Learning for Multi-Agent Pathfinding at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapf-gpt-imitation-learning-for-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The resulting MAPF-GPT model demonstrates zero-shot learning abilities when solving the MAPF problem instances that were not present in the training dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapf-gpt-imitation-learning-for-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentRE: An Agent-Based Framework for Navigating Complex Information Landscapes in Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentre-an-agent-based-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The relation extraction (RE) in complex scenarios faces challenges such as diverse relation types and ambiguous relations between entities within a single sentence, leading to the poor performance of pure "text-in, text-out" language models (LMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentre-an-agent-based-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map-Assisted Remote-Sensing Image Compression at Extremely Low Bitrates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-assisted-remote-sensing-image-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these generative models struggle to reconstruct visually plausible images due to the highly ill-posed nature of extremely low-bitrate image compression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-assisted-remote-sensing-image-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stacked ensemble\-based mutagenicity prediction model using multiple modalities with graph attention network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stacked-ensemble-based-mutagenicity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, we achieve an area under the curve of 95. 21\% on the Hansen benchmark dataset, affirming the efficacy of our method in predicting mutagenicity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stacked-ensemble-based-mutagenicity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FC-KAN: Function Combinations in Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fc-kan-function-combinations-in-kolmogorov</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce FC-KAN, a Kolmogorov-Arnold Network (KAN) that leverages combinations of popular mathematical functions such as B-splines, wavelets, and radial basis functions on low-dimensional data through element-wise operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fc-kan-function-combinations-in-kolmogorov</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming CLIP for Fine-grained and Structured Visual Understanding of Museum Exhibits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-clip-for-fine-grained-and-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we aim to adapt CLIP for fine-grained and structured -- in the form of tabular data -- visual understanding of museum exhibits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-clip-for-fine-grained-and-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LinFusion: 1 GPU, 1 Minute, 16K Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linfusion-1-gpu-1-minute-16k-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the distilled model, termed LinFusion, achieves performance on par with or superior to the original SD after only modest training, while significantly reducing time and memory complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linfusion-1-gpu-1-minute-16k-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application of Langevin Dynamics to Advance the Quantum Natural Gradient Optimization Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-langevin-dynamics-to-advance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A Quantum Natural Gradient (QNG) algorithm for optimization of variational quantum circuits has been proposed recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-langevin-dynamics-to-advance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Advancement of Representation Learning and Clustering for Sparse and Noisy Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-advancement-of-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse and noisy images (SNIs), like those in spatial gene expression data, pose significant challenges for effective representation learning and clustering, which are essential for thorough data analysis and interpretation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-advancement-of-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Vision-Language Models for Histopathology Classification: Predict all at once</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-vision-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of vision-language models (VLMs) for histo-pathology has shown promising new usages and zero-shot performances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-vision-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling Advanced Frequency Disentanglement Paradigm for Low-Light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-advanced-frequency-disentanglement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous low-light image enhancement (LLIE) approaches, while employing frequency decomposition techniques to address the intertwined challenges of low frequency (e. g., illumination recovery) and high frequency (e. g., noise reduction), primarily focused on the development of dedicated and complex networks to achieve improved performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-advanced-frequency-disentanglement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booster: Tackling Harmful Fine-tuing for Large Language Models via Attenuating Harmful Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/booster-tackling-harmful-fine-tuing-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the first time in the literature, we in this paper show that \textit{harmful perturbation} over the model weights should be the root cause of alignment-broken of harmful fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/booster-tackling-harmful-fine-tuing-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Does Visual Prompting Outperform Linear Probing for Vision-Language Models? A Likelihood Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-does-visual-prompting-outperform-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adapting pre-trained models to new tasks can exhibit varying effectiveness across datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-does-visual-prompting-outperform-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPiKE: 3D Human Pose from Point Cloud Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spike-3d-human-pose-from-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D Human Pose Estimation (HPE) is the task of locating keypoints of the human body in 3D space from 2D or 3D representations such as RGB images, depth maps or point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spike-3d-human-pose-from-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency-Spatial Entanglement Learning for Camouflaged Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-spatial-entanglement-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Camouflaged object detection has attracted a lot of attention in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-spatial-entanglement-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LSTMSE-Net: Long Short Term Speech Enhancement Network for Audio-visual Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lstmse-net-long-short-term-speech-enhancement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The system scales and concatenates visual and audio features, then processes them through a separator network for optimized speech enhancement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lstmse-net-long-short-term-speech-enhancement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PMLBmini: A Tabular Classification Benchmark Suite for Data-Scarce Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pmlbmini-a-tabular-classification-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In practice, we are often faced with small-sized tabular data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pmlbmini-a-tabular-classification-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech Foundation Model Ensembles for the Controlled Singing Voice Deepfake Detection (CtrSVDD) Challenge 2024</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-foundation-model-ensembles-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work details our approach to achieving a leading system with a 1. 79% pooled equal error rate (EER) on the evaluation set of the Controlled Singing Voice Deepfake Detection (CtrSVDD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-foundation-model-ensembles-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Distillation for Continual Object Detection at the Edge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-distillation-for-continual-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address the memory and computation constraints of edge devices in the Continual Learning for Object Detection (CLOD) scenario.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-distillation-for-continual-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PINNIES: An Efficient Physics-Informed Neural Network Framework to Integral Operator Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pinnies-an-efficient-physics-informed-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces an efficient tensor-vector product technique for the rapid and accurate approximation of integral operators within physics-informed deep learning frameworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pinnies-an-efficient-physics-informed-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NoiseAttack: An Evasive Sample-Specific Multi-Targeted Backdoor Attack Through White Gaussian Noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noiseattack-an-evasive-sample-specific-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In these attacks, data can be manipulated to cause a trained model to behave improperly when a specific trigger pattern is applied, providing the adversary with unauthorized advantages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noiseattack-an-evasive-sample-specific-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting the Vulnerability of Large Language Models via Defense-Aware Architectural Backdoor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-the-vulnerability-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that the training-free architectural backdoor on a large language model poses a genuine threat.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-the-vulnerability-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmenting Object Affordances: Reproducibility and Sensitivity to Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmenting-object-affordances-reproducibility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual affordance segmentation identifies image regions of an object an agent can interact with.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmenting-object-affordances-reproducibility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foundations of Large Language Model Compression -- Part 1: Weight Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundations-of-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, compression of large language models (LLMs) has emerged as an important problem to allow language model deployment on resource-constrained devices, reduce computational costs, and mitigate the environmental footprint of large-scale AI infrastructure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundations-of-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling Deep Shadows: A Survey on Image and Video Shadow Detection, Removal, and Generation in the Era of Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-deep-shadows-a-survey-on-image-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Shadows are formed when light encounters obstacles, leading to areas of diminished illumination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-deep-shadows-a-survey-on-image-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buffer-based Gradient Projection for Continual Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/buffer-based-gradient-projection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, in a task-incremental learning scenario using the CIFAR-100 dataset, our method can increase the accuracy by up to 27%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/buffer-based-gradient-projection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPRecon: An Efficient Framework for Real-Time Panoptic 3D Reconstruction from Monocular Video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eprecon-an-efficient-framework-for-real-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To end this, we propose a lightweight module to directly estimate scene depth priors in a 3D volume for reconstruction quality improvement by generating occupancy probabilities of all voxels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eprecon-an-efficient-framework-for-real-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guide-and-Rescale: Self-Guidance Mechanism for Effective Tuning-Free Real Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guide-and-rescale-self-guidance-mechanism-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore the self-guidance technique to preserve the overall structure of the input image and its local regions appearance that should not be edited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guide-and-rescale-self-guidance-mechanism-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Sample Efficiency and Exploration in Reinforcement Learning through the Integration of Diffusion Models and Proximal Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-sample-efficiency-and-exploration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in reinforcement learning (RL) have been fueled by large-scale data and deep neural networks, particularly for high-dimensional and complex tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-sample-efficiency-and-exploration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KMTalk: Speech-Driven 3D Facial Animation with Key Motion Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kmtalk-speech-driven-3d-facial-animation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a progressive learning mechanism that generates 3D facial animations by introducing key motion capture to decrease cross-modal mapping uncertainty and learning complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kmtalk-speech-driven-3d-facial-animation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merging Multiple Datasets for Improved Appearance-Based Gaze Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merging-multiple-datasets-for-improved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose two innovations to improve the performance of gaze estimation by leveraging multiple datasets, a change in the estimator architecture and the intro-duction of a gaze adaptation module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merging-multiple-datasets-for-improved</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MRI-based and metabolomics-based age scores act synergetically for mortality prediction shown by multi-cohort federated learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mri-based-and-metabolomics-based-age-scores</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We trained a federated deep learning model to estimate BrainAge in three cohorts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mri-based-and-metabolomics-based-age-scores</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-Driven Data Replay: A Novel Approach to Combat Forgetting in Federated Class Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-driven-data-replay-a-novel-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Class Continual Learning (FCCL) merges the challenges of distributed client learning with the need for seamless adaptation to new classes without forgetting old ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-driven-data-replay-a-novel-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Mixers for Language Generation and Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-mixers-for-language-generation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hypothesized that the information loss exhibited by transformers would be much more detrimental to retrieval than generation, and to test this we introduce an efficient training approach for retrieval models based on existing generative model embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-mixers-for-language-generation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOOD-ImageNet: a Large-Scale Dataset for Semantic Out-Of-Distribution Image Classification and Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sood-imagenet-a-large-scale-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-Distribution (OOD) detection in computer vision is a crucial research area, with related benchmarks playing a vital role in assessing the generalizability of models and their applicability in real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sood-imagenet-a-large-scale-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EnsLoss: Stochastic Calibrated Loss Ensembles for Preventing Overfitting in Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensloss-stochastic-calibrated-loss-ensembles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, the convexity and calibration (CC) properties of a loss function ensure consistency of ERM in maximizing accuracy, thereby offering a wide range of options for surrogate losses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensloss-stochastic-calibrated-loss-ensembles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-Learning: Code Learning for Multi-Agent Reinforcement Collaborative Framework with Conversational Natural Language Interfaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-learning-code-learning-for-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online question-and-answer (Q\&A) systems based on the Large Language Model (LLM) have progressively diverged from recreational to professional use.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-learning-code-learning-for-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
