<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 09:14:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lazy Data Practices Harm Fairness Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lazy-data-practices-harm-fairness-research</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data practices shape research and practice on fairness in machine learning (fair ML).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lazy-data-practices-harm-fairness-research</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trust Dynamics and Market Behavior in Cryptocurrency: A Comparative Study of Centralized and Decentralized Exchanges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trust-dynamics-and-market-behavior-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the evolving landscape of digital finance, the transition from centralized to decentralized trust mechanisms, primarily driven by blockchain technology, plays a critical role in shaping the cryptocurrency ecosystem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trust-dynamics-and-market-behavior-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TruthSR: Trustworthy Sequential Recommender Systems via User-generated Multimodal Content</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truthsr-trustworthy-sequential-recommender</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we design a trustworthy decision mechanism that integrates subjective user perspective and objective item perspective to dynamically evaluate the uncertainty of prediction results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truthsr-trustworthy-sequential-recommender</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Process Mining Embeddings: Learning Vector Representations for Petri Nets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/process-mining-embeddings-learning-vector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Process mining offers powerful techniques for discovering, analyzing, and enhancing real-world business processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/process-mining-embeddings-learning-vector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3SHNet: Boosting Image-Sentence Retrieval via Visual Semantic-Spatial Self-Highlighting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3shnet-boosting-image-sentence-retrieval-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel visual Semantic-Spatial Self-Highlighting Network (termed 3SHNet) for high-precision, high-efficiency and high-generalization image-sentence retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3shnet-boosting-image-sentence-retrieval-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MovieChat+: Question-aware Sparse Memory for Long Video Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moviechat-question-aware-sparse-memory-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, integrating video foundation models and large language models to build a video understanding system can overcome the limitations of specific pre-defined vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moviechat-question-aware-sparse-memory-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Vulnerability Prediction in Low-Resource Languages: An Empirical Study of CodeBERT and ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/software-vulnerability-prediction-in-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aims: We conduct an empirical study to evaluate the impact of SV data scarcity in emerging languages on the state-of-the-art SV prediction model and investigate potential solutions to enhance the performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/software-vulnerability-prediction-in-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Retrieval Leveraging Fine-grained Feedback for Fact Checking News Claims with Black-Box LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-retrieval-leveraging-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-augmented language models have exhibited promising performance across various areas of natural language processing (NLP), including fact-critical tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-retrieval-leveraging-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAGHOG: Self-Supervised Autoencoder for Generating HOG Features for Writer Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saghog-self-supervised-autoencoder-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces SAGHOG, a self-supervised pretraining strategy for writer retrieval using HOG features of the binarized input image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saghog-self-supervised-autoencoder-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ObjectAdd: Adding Objects into Image via a Training-Free Diffusion Modification Fashion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/objectadd-adding-objects-into-image-via-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce ObjectAdd, a training-free diffusion modification method to add user-expected objects into user-specified area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/objectadd-adding-objects-into-image-via-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Better Use of Unlabelled Data in Bayesian Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-better-use-of-unlabelled-data-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fully supervised models are predominant in Bayesian active learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-better-use-of-unlabelled-data-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tabular Data Contrastive Learning via Class-Conditioned and Feature-Correlation Based Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabular-data-contrastive-learning-via-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive learning is a model pre-training technique by first creating similar views of the original data, and then encouraging the data and its corresponding views to be close in the embedding space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabular-data-contrastive-learning-via-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FairGT: A Fairness-aware Graph Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairgt-a-fairness-aware-graph-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The design of Graph Transformers (GTs) generally neglects considerations for fairness, resulting in biased outcomes against certain sensitive subgroups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairgt-a-fairness-aware-graph-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Training for Hologram Verification in Identity Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-training-for-hologram</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method to remotely verify the authenticity of Optically Variable Devices (OVDs), often referred to as ``holograms'', in identity documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-training-for-hologram</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binarizing Documents by Leveraging both Space and Frequency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binarizing-documents-by-leveraging-both-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Document Image Binarization is a well-known problem in Document Analysis and Computer Vision, although it is far from being solved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binarizing-documents-by-leveraging-both-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Evaluation of Additive Kernels: Feature Arrangement, Fourier Methods, and Kernel Derivatives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-evaluation-of-additive-kernels-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We here present a technique based on the non-equispaced fast Fourier transform (NFFT) with rigorous error analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-evaluation-of-additive-kernels-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuro-Symbolic Embedding for Short and Effective Feature Selection via Autoregressive Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-embedding-for-short-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within the learned embedding space, we leverage a multi-gradient search algorithm to find more robust and generalized embeddings with the objective of improving model performance and reducing feature subset redundancy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-embedding-for-short-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluations of Machine Learning Privacy Defenses are Misleading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluations-of-machine-learning-privacy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirical defenses for machine learning privacy forgo the provable guarantees of differential privacy in the hope of achieving higher utility while resisting realistic adversaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluations-of-machine-learning-privacy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptCIR: Blind Compressed Image Restoration with Prompt Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptcir-blind-compressed-image-restoration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing works on blind CIR often seek assistance from a quality factor prediction network to facilitate their network to restore compressed images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptcir-blind-compressed-image-restoration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing the Potential of Fractional Calculus in Graph Neural Networks with FROND</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-potential-of-fractional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the FRactional-Order graph Neural Dynamical network (FROND), a new continuous graph neural network (GNN) framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-potential-of-fractional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ag2Manip: Learning Novel Manipulation Skills with Agent-Agnostic Visual and Action Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ag2manip-learning-novel-manipulation-skills</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous robotic systems capable of learning novel manipulation tasks are poised to transform industries from manufacturing to service automation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ag2manip-learning-novel-manipulation-skills</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Continuous Relaxation for Discrete Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-continuous-relaxation-for-discrete-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To optimize efficiently over discrete data and with only few available target observations is a challenge in Bayesian optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-continuous-relaxation-for-discrete-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part-Guided 3D RL for Sim2Real Articulated Object Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/part-guided-3d-rl-for-sim2real-articulated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Manipulating unseen articulated objects through visual feedback is a critical but challenging task for real robots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/part-guided-3d-rl-for-sim2real-articulated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChangeBind: A Hybrid Change Encoder for Remote Sensing Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/changebind-a-hybrid-change-encoder-for-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Change detection (CD) is a fundamental task in remote sensing (RS) which aims to detect the semantic changes between the same geographical regions at different time stamps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/changebind-a-hybrid-change-encoder-for-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MV-VTON: Multi-View Virtual Try-On with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mv-vton-multi-view-virtual-try-on-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we introduce Multi-View Virtual Try-ON (MV-VTON), which aims to reconstruct the dressing results of a person from multiple views using the given clothes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mv-vton-multi-view-virtual-try-on-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-shot Calligraphy Style Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-calligraphy-style-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduced "Presidifussion," a novel approach to learning and replicating the unique style of calligraphy of President Xu, using a pretrained diffusion model adapted through a two-stage training process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-calligraphy-style-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Evaluation on Event Reasoning of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-evaluation-on-event-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on these findings, we introduce two methods to guide the LLMs to utilize the event schema knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-evaluation-on-event-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certified MaxSAT Preprocessing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certified-maxsat-preprocessing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For SAT, this is largely a solved problem thanks to the use of proof logging, meaning that solvers emit machine-verifiable proofs of (un)satisfiability to certify correctness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certified-maxsat-preprocessing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metronome: tracing variation in poetic meters via local sequence alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metronome-tracing-variation-in-poetic-meters</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces an unsupervised method for detecting structural similarities in poems using local sequence alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metronome-tracing-variation-in-poetic-meters</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MER 2024: Semi-Supervised Learning, Noise Robustness, and Open-Vocabulary Multimodal Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mer-2024-semi-supervised-learning-noise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to expanding the dataset size, we introduce a new track around open-vocabulary emotion recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mer-2024-semi-supervised-learning-noise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter Efficient Fine-tuning of Self-supervised ViTs without Catastrophic Forgetting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-of-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial neural networks often suffer from catastrophic forgetting, where learning new concepts leads to a complete loss of previously acquired knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-of-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Adaptive and Fine-grained Anomaly Detection for Single-cell Sequencing Data and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-and-fine-grained-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response, we propose ACSleuth, a novel, reconstruction deviation-guided generative framework that integrates the detection, domain adaptation, and fine-grained annotating of anomalous cells into a methodologically cohesive workflow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-and-fine-grained-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising: from classical methods to deep CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-from-classical-methods-to-deep-cnns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper aims to explore the evolution of image denoising in a pedagological way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-from-classical-methods-to-deep-cnns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAD: Patch-Agnostic Defense against Adversarial Patch Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pad-patch-agnostic-defense-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial patch attacks present a significant threat to real-world object detectors due to their practical feasibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pad-patch-agnostic-defense-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep learning-based blind image super-resolution with iterative kernel reconstruction and noise estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-blind-image-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, there is a gap in the literature to provide a well-generalized deep learning-based solution that performs well on images with unknown and highly complex degradations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-blind-image-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConsistentID: Portrait Generation with Multimodal Fine-Grained Identity Preserving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistentid-portrait-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ConsistentID comprises two key components: a multimodal facial prompt generator that combines facial features, corresponding facial descriptions and the overall facial context to enhance precision in facial details, and an ID-preservation network optimized through the facial attention localization strategy, aimed at preserving ID consistency in facial regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistentid-portrait-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVE -- A Detect-and-Verify Paradigm for Low-Shot Counting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dave-a-detect-and-verify-paradigm-for-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DAVE outperforms the top density-based counters by ~20% in the total count MAE, it outperforms the most recent detection-based counter by ~20% in detection quality and sets a new state-of-the-art in zero-shot as well as text-prompt-based counting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dave-a-detect-and-verify-paradigm-for-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-objective Optimization Benchmark Test Suite for Real-time Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-objective-optimization-benchmark-test</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge the gap, we introduce a tailored streamline to transform the task of HW-NAS for real-time semantic segmentation into standard MOPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-objective-optimization-benchmark-test</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AAPL: Adding Attributes to Prompt Learning for Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aapl-adding-attributes-to-prompt-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through our experiments, we have identified important issues in CoOp and CoCoOp: the context learned through traditional image augmentation is biased toward seen classes, negatively impacting generalization to unseen classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aapl-adding-attributes-to-prompt-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEED-Bench-2-Plus: Benchmarking Multimodal Large Language Models with Text-Rich Visual Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seed-bench-2-plus-benchmarking-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope that our work can serve as a valuable addition to existing MLLM benchmarks, providing insightful observations and inspiring further research in the area of text-rich visual comprehension with MLLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seed-bench-2-plus-benchmarking-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision-based robot manipulation of transparent liquid containers in a laboratory setting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-based-robot-manipulation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Laboratory processes involving small volumes of solutions and active ingredients are often performed manually due to challenges in automation, such as high initial costs, semi-structured environments and protocol variability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-based-robot-manipulation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>History repeats itself: A Baseline for Temporal Knowledge Graph Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/history-repeats-itself-a-baseline-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal Knowledge Graph (TKG) Forecasting aims at predicting links in Knowledge Graphs for future timesteps based on a history of Knowledge Graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/history-repeats-itself-a-baseline-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinyChart: Efficient Chart Understanding with Visual Token Merging and Program-of-Thoughts Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinychart-efficient-chart-understanding-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Charts are important for presenting and explaining complex data relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinychart-efficient-chart-understanding-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpreting Answers to Yes-No Questions in Dialogues from Multiple Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-answers-to-yes-no-questions-in-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[People often answer yes-no questions without explicitly saying yes, no, or similar polar keywords.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-answers-to-yes-no-questions-in-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning of Large Language Models: A Comprehensive Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-of-large-language-models-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this survey, we provide a comprehensive overview of the current research progress on LLMs within the context of CL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-of-large-language-models-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Modulated Function for Computational Optimal Continuous Image Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-modulated-function-for-computational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, we propose a novel Latent Modulated Function (LMF), which decouples the HR-HD decoding process into shared latent decoding in LR-HD space and independent rendering in HR Low-Dimensional (LD) space, thereby realizing the first computational optimal paradigm of continuous image representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-modulated-function-for-computational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning-Based Efficient Approximation of Data-enabled Predictive Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-efficient-approximation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the size of the optimization problem in DeePC grows linearly with respect to the data size, which prohibits its application due to high computational costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-efficient-approximation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging tropical reef, bird and unrelated sounds for superior transfer learning in marine bioacoustics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-tropical-reef-bird-and-unrelated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning has the potential to revolutionize passive acoustic monitoring (PAM) for ecological assessments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-tropical-reef-bird-and-unrelated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WheelPose: Data Synthesis Techniques to Improve Pose Estimation Performance on Wheelchair Users</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wheelpose-data-synthesis-techniques-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a data synthesis pipeline to address this disparity in data collection and subsequently improve pose estimation performance for wheelchair users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wheelpose-data-synthesis-techniques-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProbGate at EHRSQL 2024: Enhancing SQL Query Generation Accuracy through Probabilistic Threshold Filtering and Error Handling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probgate-at-ehrsql-2024-enhancing-sql-query</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, deep learning-based language models have significantly enhanced text-to-SQL tasks, with promising applications in retrieving patient records within the medical domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probgate-at-ehrsql-2024-enhancing-sql-query</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
