<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:08:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Predictive Dynamic Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictive-dynamic-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accordingly, we further propose a relative calibration strategy to calibrate the predicted Co-Belief for potential uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictive-dynamic-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaRC and SpaRP: Spatial Reasoning Characterization and Path Generation for Understanding Spatial Reasoning Capability of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparc-and-sparp-spatial-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a comprehensive study of the capability of current state-of-the-art large language models (LLMs) on spatial reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparc-and-sparp-spatial-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenHeld: Generating and Editing Handheld Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genheld-generating-and-editing-handheld</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose GenHeld to address the inverse problem of synthesizing held objects conditioned on 3D hand model or 2D image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genheld-generating-and-editing-handheld</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Russian Legislative Corpus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-russian-legislative-corpus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the comprehensive Russian primary and secondary legislation corpus covering 1991 to 2023.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-russian-legislative-corpus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERTs are Generative In-Context Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/berts-are-generative-in-context-learners</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the in-context learning capabilities of masked language models, challenging the common view that this ability does not 'emerge' in them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/berts-are-generative-in-context-learners</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLoG: Benchmarking Continual Learning of Image Generation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clog-benchmarking-continual-learning-of-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We adapt three types of existing CL methodologies, replay-based, regularization-based, and parameter-isolation-based methods to generative tasks and introduce comprehensive benchmarks for CLoG that feature great diversity and broad task coverage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clog-benchmarking-continual-learning-of-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PolyLUT-Add: FPGA-based LUT Inference with Wide Inputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polylut-add-fpga-based-lut-inference-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FPGAs have distinct advantages as a technology for deploying deep neural networks (DNNs) at the edge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polylut-add-fpga-based-lut-inference-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PQPP: A Joint Benchmark for Text-to-Image Prompt and Query Performance Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pqpp-a-joint-benchmark-for-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to determine the difficulty of the same prompts in image retrieval, we also collect manual annotations that represent retrieval performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pqpp-a-joint-benchmark-for-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEFT: Memory-Efficient Fine-Tuning through Sparse Adapter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meft-memory-efficient-fine-tuning-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We store and update the parameters of larger adapters on the CPU.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meft-memory-efficient-fine-tuning-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating and Mitigating IP Infringement in Visual Generative AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-and-mitigating-ip-infringement-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate such IP infringement problems, we also propose a defense method against it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-and-mitigating-ip-infringement-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVMR: Open-Vocabulary Recognition with Multi-Modal References</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ovmr-open-vocabulary-recognition-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing works have proposed different methods to embed category cues into the model, \eg, through few-shot fine-tuning, providing category names or textual descriptions to Vision-Language Models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ovmr-open-vocabulary-recognition-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR: Skeleton-aware Text-based 4D Avatar Generation with In-Network Motion Retargeting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/star-skeleton-aware-text-based-4d-avatar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The creation of 4D avatars (i. e., animated 3D avatars) from text description typically uses text-to-image (T2I) diffusion models to synthesize 3D avatars in the canonical space and subsequently applies animation with target motions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/star-skeleton-aware-text-based-4d-avatar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimeSieve: Extracting Temporal Dynamics through Information Bottlenecks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timesieve-extracting-temporal-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results validate the effectiveness of our approach in addressing the key challenges in time series forecasting, paving the way for more reliable and efficient predictive models in practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timesieve-extracting-temporal-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RU-AI: A Large Multimodal Dataset for Machine Generated Content Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ru-ai-a-large-multimodal-dataset-for-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to a lack of aligned multimodal datasets, effective and robust methods for detecting machine-generated content are still in the early stages of development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ru-ai-a-large-multimodal-dataset-for-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooperative Meta-Learning with Gradient Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-meta-learning-with-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In general, the injection of noise into the gradient of the model for augmenting the gradient is one of the widely used regularization methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-meta-learning-with-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLOPE: Search with Learned Optimal Pruning-based Expansion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slope-search-with-learned-optimal-pruning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the effectiveness of our approach evaluating it as a standalone search method and in conjunction with learned heuristic functions, achieving comparable-or-better node expansion metrics, while lowering the number of child nodes in the open list.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slope-search-with-learned-optimal-pruning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skill-aware Mutual Information Optimisation for Generalisation in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skill-aware-mutual-information-optimisation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve RL generalisation to different tasks, we first introduce Skill-aware Mutual Information (SaMI), an optimisation objective that aids in distinguishing context embeddings according to skills, thereby equipping RL agents with the ability to identify and execute different skills across tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skill-aware-mutual-information-optimisation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GANetic Loss for Generative Adversarial Networks with a Focus on Medical Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ganetic-loss-for-generative-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments were performed with histopathological, gastrointestinal or glaucoma images to evaluate the GANetic loss in medical image generation, resulting in improved image quality compared to the baseline models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ganetic-loss-for-generative-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Granularity Language-Guided Multi-Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-language-guided-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a new multi-object tracking framework, named LG-MOT, that explicitly leverages language information at different levels of granularity (scene-and instance-level) and combines it with standard visual features to obtain discriminative representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-language-guided-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WildBench: Benchmarking LLMs with Challenging Tasks from Real Users in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wildbench-benchmarking-llms-with-challenging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For automated evaluation with WildBench, we have developed two metrics, WB-Reward and WB-Score, which are computable using advanced LLMs such as GPT-4-turbo.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wildbench-benchmarking-llms-with-challenging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helpful or Harmful Data? Fine-tuning-free Shapley Attribution for Explaining Language Model Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helpful-or-harmful-data-fine-tuning-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing complexity of foundational models underscores the necessity for explainability, particularly for fine-tuning, the most widely used training method for adapting models to downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helpful-or-harmful-data-fine-tuning-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiNeR: a Large Realistic Dataset for Evaluating Compositional Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diner-a-large-realistic-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better investigate compositional generalization with more linguistic phenomena and compositional diversity, we propose the DIsh NamE Recognition (DiNeR) task and create a large realistic Chinese dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diner-a-large-realistic-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XctDiff: Reconstruction of CT Images with Consistent Anatomical Structures from a Single Radiographic Projection Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xctdiff-reconstruction-of-ct-images-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present XctDiff, an algorithm framework for reconstructing CT from a single radiograph, which decomposes the reconstruction process into two easily controllable tasks: feature extraction and CT reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xctdiff-reconstruction-of-ct-images-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Attention Weights as Interpretations of Message-Passing Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-attention-weights-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing studies often use naive calculations to derive attribution scores from attention, and do not take the precise and careful calculation of edge attribution into consideration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-attention-weights-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Piano Practice Policy with a Gaussian Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-piano-practice-policy-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because we each learn differently and there are many choices for possible piano practice tasks and methods, the set of practice modes should be dynamically adapted to the human learner, a process typically guided by a teacher.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-piano-practice-policy-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On PI Controllers for Updating Lagrange Multipliers in Constrained Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-pi-controllers-for-updating-lagrange</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide theoretical and empirical insights explaining the inability of momentum methods to address the shortcomings of gradient descent-ascent, and contrast this with the empirical success of our proposed $\nu$PI controller.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-pi-controllers-for-updating-lagrange</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGBD: A Global-scale Biomass Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agbd-a-global-scale-biomass-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This dataset combines AGB reference data from the GEDI mission with data from Sentinel-2 and PALSAR-2 imagery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agbd-a-global-scale-biomass-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpanGNN: Towards Memory-Efficient Graph Neural Networks via Spanning Subgraph Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spangnn-towards-memory-efficient-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this memory problem, a popular solution is mini-batch GNN training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spangnn-towards-memory-efficient-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let Go of Your Labels with Unsupervised Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-go-of-your-labels-with-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, TURTLE matches the average performance of CLIP zero-shot on 26 datasets by employing the same representation space, spanning a wide range of architectures and model sizes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-go-of-your-labels-with-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LawGPT: A Chinese Legal Knowledge-Enhanced Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lawgpt-a-chinese-legal-knowledge-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs), including both proprietary and open-source models, have showcased remarkable capabilities in addressing a wide range of downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lawgpt-a-chinese-legal-knowledge-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Head RAG: Solving Multi-Aspect Problems with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-head-rag-solving-multi-aspect-problems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) enhances the abilities of Large Language Models (LLMs) by enabling the retrieval of documents into the LLM context to provide more accurate and relevant responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-head-rag-solving-multi-aspect-problems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corpus Poisoning via Approximate Greedy Gradient Descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/corpus-poisoning-via-approximate-greedy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dense retrievers are widely used in information retrieval and have also been successfully extended to other knowledge intensive areas such as language models, e. g., Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/corpus-poisoning-via-approximate-greedy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling up Probabilistic PDE Simulators with Structured Volumetric Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-probabilistic-pde-simulators-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modeling real-world problems with partial differential equations (PDEs) is a prominent topic in scientific machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-probabilistic-pde-simulators-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Weather Forecasting with Hierarchical Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-weather-forecasting-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While most current machine learning models focus on deterministic forecasts, accurately capturing the uncertainty in the chaotic weather system calls for probabilistic modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-weather-forecasting-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massively Multiagent Minigames for Training Generalist Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/massively-multiagent-minigames-for-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore generalization across Meta MMO by learning to play several minigames with a single set of weights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/massively-multiagent-minigames-for-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHIQ: Contextual History Enhancement for Improving Query Rewriting in Conversational Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chiq-contextual-history-enhancement-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study how open-source large language models (LLMs) can be effectively deployed for improving query rewriting in conversational search, especially for ambiguous queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chiq-contextual-history-enhancement-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concept Drift Detection using Ensemble of Integrally Private Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-drift-detection-using-ensemble-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on the notion of integrally private DNNs to detect concept drifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-drift-detection-using-ensemble-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Recurrent Network Topologies for Dynamical Systems Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-recurrent-network-topologies-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, here we find this strategy does not work for DSR, where even low magnitude parameters can contribute considerably to the system dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-recurrent-network-topologies-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMC++: Masked Learning of Unsupervised Video Semantic Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smc-masked-learning-of-unsupervised-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Masked Video Modeling (MVM)-powered compression framework that particularly preserves video semantics, by jointly mining and compressing the semantics in a self-supervised manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smc-masked-learning-of-unsupervised-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeGA: Merging Multiple Independently Trained Neural Networks Based on Genetic Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mega-merging-multiple-independently-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel method for merging the weights of multiple pre-trained neural networks using a genetic algorithm called MeGA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mega-merging-multiple-independently-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Deep Jansen-Rit Parameter Inference: An in Silico Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-deep-jansen-rit-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model-driven estimation of EC is a powerful approach that requires estimating global and local parameters of a generative model of neural activity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-deep-jansen-rit-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGIMM: Multi-Granularity Instruction Multimodal Model for Attribute-Guided Remote Sensing Image Detailed Description</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgimm-multi-granularity-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, with the multimodal model aligned on region-attribute, guided by multi-grain visual features, MGIMM fully perceives both region-level and global image information, utilizing large language models for comprehensive descriptions of remote sensing images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgimm-multi-granularity-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising-Aware Contrastive Learning for Noisy Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-aware-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this pre-processing approach may not fully eliminate the effect of noise in SSL for two reasons: (i) the diverse types of noise in time series make it difficult to automatically determine suitable denoising methods; (ii) noise can be amplified after mapping raw data into latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-aware-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Divergence Fields for Shift-Robust Graph Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-divergence-fields-for-shift-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-world data generation often involves certain geometries (e. g., graphs) that induce instance-level interdependence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-divergence-fields-for-shift-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Time-Varying Linear Prediction in the Context of End-to-End Analysis-by-Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-time-varying-linear-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training the linear prediction (LP) operator end-to-end for audio synthesis in modern deep learning frameworks is slow due to its recursive formulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-time-varying-linear-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classification Metrics for Image Explanations: Towards Building Reliable XAI-Evaluations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classification-metrics-for-image-explanations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this, a slew of different proxy metrics have been defined, which are - as the explainability methods themselves - often built on intuition and thus, are possibly unreliable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classification-metrics-for-image-explanations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Size Generalization in Graph Neural Networks through Disentangled Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-size-generalization-in-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although most graph neural networks (GNNs) can operate on graphs of any size, their classification performance often declines on graphs larger than those encountered during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-size-generalization-in-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ComplexTempQA: A Large-Scale Dataset for Complex Temporal Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complextempqa-a-large-scale-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce ComplexTempQA, a large-scale dataset consisting of over 100 million question-answer pairs designed to tackle the challenges in temporal question answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complextempqa-a-large-scale-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Adaptation for Enhancing Imitation Learning Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-adaptation-for-enhancing-imitation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Imitation learning enables autonomous agents to learn from human examples, without the need for a reward signal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-adaptation-for-enhancing-imitation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characterizing Similarities and Divergences in Conversational Tones in Humans and LLMs by Sampling with People</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-similarities-and-divergences</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We run 100 iterations of this process with human participants and GPT-4, then obtain a dataset of sentences and frequent conversational tones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-similarities-and-divergences</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
