<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 21:08:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>HDC: Hierarchical Semantic Decoding with Counting Assistance for Generalized Referring Expression Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hdc-hierarchical-semantic-decoding-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The newly proposed Generalized Referring Expression Segmentation (GRES) amplifies the formulation of classic RES by involving multiple/non-target scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hdc-hierarchical-semantic-decoding-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating deep learning methods applied to Landsat time series subsequences to detect and classify boreal forest disturbances events: The challenge of partial and progressive disturbances</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-deep-learning-methods-applied-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of this paper is to explore the use of a subset of Landsat time series and deep learning models to identify both the type and the year of disturbances, including low-severity and gradual disturbances, in the boreal forest of eastern Canada at the pixel level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-deep-learning-methods-applied-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U3M: Unbiased Multiscale Modal Fusion Model for Multimodal Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u3m-unbiased-multiscale-modal-fusion-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we leverage the inherent capabilities of the model itself to discover the optimal equilibrium in multimodal fusion and introduce U3M: An Unbiased Multiscale Modal Fusion Model for Multimodal Semantic Segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u3m-unbiased-multiscale-modal-fusion-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label-efficient Semantic Scene Completion with Scribble Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-efficient-semantic-scene-completion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic scene completion aims to infer the 3D geometric structures with semantic classes from camera or LiDAR, which provide essential occupancy information in autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-efficient-semantic-scene-completion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructAvatar: Text-Guided Emotion and Motion Control for Avatar Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructavatar-text-guided-emotion-and-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent talking avatar generation models have made strides in achieving realistic and accurate lip synchronization with the audio, but often fall short in controlling and conveying detailed expressions and emotions of the avatar, making the generated video less vivid and controllable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructavatar-text-guided-emotion-and-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NMGrad: Advancing Histopathological Bladder Cancer Grading with Weakly Supervised Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nmgrad-advancing-histopathological-bladder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To distinguish different levels of malignancy within specific regions of the slide, we include the origins of the tiles in our analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nmgrad-advancing-histopathological-bladder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meteor: Mamba-based Traversal of Rationale for Large Language and Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meteor-mamba-based-traversal-of-rationale-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, open-source LLVMs have curated high-quality visual instruction tuning datasets and utilized additional vision encoders or multiple computer vision models in order to narrow the performance gap with powerful closed-source LLVMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meteor-mamba-based-traversal-of-rationale-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fieldscale: Locality-Aware Field-based Adaptive Rescaling for Thermal Infrared Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fieldscale-locality-aware-field-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thermal infrared (TIR) cameras are emerging as promising sensors in safety-related fields due to their robustness against external illumination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fieldscale-locality-aware-field-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Solution-based LLM API-using Methodology for Academic Information Seeking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-solution-based-llm-api-using-methodology</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applying large language models (LLMs) for academic API usage shows promise in reducing researchers' academic information seeking efforts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-solution-based-llm-api-using-methodology</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from True-False Labels via Multi-modal Prompt Retrieving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-true-false-labels-via-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly supervised learning has recently achieved considerable success in reducing annotation costs and label noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-true-false-labels-via-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Counterfactual Regression through the Lens of Gromov-Wasserstein Information Bottleneck</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-counterfactual-regression-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the selection bias between control and treatment groups often imbalances the two groups' latent distributions and negatively impacts this method's performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-counterfactual-regression-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking Backward: Streaming Video-to-Video Translation with Feature Banks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-backward-streaming-video-to-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces StreamV2V, a diffusion model that achieves real-time streaming video-to-video (V2V) translation with user prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-backward-streaming-video-to-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroAdam: Accurate Adaptive Optimization with Low Space Overhead and Provable Convergence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/microadam-accurate-adaptive-optimization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new variant of the Adam optimizer [Kingma and Ba, 2014] called MICROADAM that specifically minimizes memory overheads, while maintaining theoretical convergence guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/microadam-accurate-adaptive-optimization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less is More: Discovering Concise Network Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-discovering-concise-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It produces 1/30 of CRP's explanations while only resulting in a slight reduction in explanation quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-discovering-concise-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disease-informed Adaptation of Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disease-informed-adaptation-of-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In medical image analysis, the expertise scarcity and the high cost of data annotation limits the development of large artificial intelligence models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disease-informed-adaptation-of-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defensive Unlearning with Adversarial Training for Robust Concept Erasure in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defensive-unlearning-with-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The techniques of machine unlearning, also known as concept erasing, have been developed to address these risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defensive-unlearning-with-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring Adaptive Binding Prototypes to Generalized Referring Expression Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bring-adaptive-binding-prototypes-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Referring Expression Segmentation (RES) has attracted rising attention, aiming to identify and segment objects based on natural language expressions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bring-adaptive-binding-prototypes-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NuwaTS: Mending Every Incomplete Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nuwats-mending-every-incomplete-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By combining this contrastive loss with the missing data imputation task, we train PLMs to obtain a one-for-all imputation model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nuwats-mending-every-incomplete-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyCellMech: A shape-based feature extraction pipeline for use in medical and biological studies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pycellmech-a-shape-based-feature-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The significance of shape-based features has been explored extensively in research for several decades, but there is no single package available in which all shape-related features can be extracted easily by the researcher.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pycellmech-a-shape-based-feature-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Road Less Scheduled</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-road-less-scheduled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing learning rate schedules that do not require specification of the optimization stopping step T are greatly out-performed by learning rate schedules that depend on T. We propose an approach that avoids the need for this stopping time by eschewing the use of schedules entirely, while exhibiting state-of-the-art performance compared to schedules across a wide family of problems ranging from convex problems to large-scale deep learning problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-road-less-scheduled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Law for Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-law-for-time-series-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We take into account the impact of dataset size and model complexity, as well as time series data granularity, particularly focusing on the look-back horizon, an aspect that has been unexplored in previous theories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-law-for-time-series-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuously Learning, Adapting, and Improving: A Dual-Process Approach to Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuously-learning-adapting-and-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments also demonstrate that as the memory bank expands, the Heuristic Process with only 1. 8B parameters can inherit the knowledge from a GPT-4 powered Analytic Process and achieve continuous performance improvement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuously-learning-adapting-and-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Adverse Drug Event Detection with Multimodal Dataset: Corpus Creation and Model Development</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-adverse-drug-event-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we introduce a framework that leverages the capabilities of LLMs and VLMs for ADE detection by generating detailed descriptions of medical images depicting ADEs, aiding healthcare professionals in visually identifying adverse events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-adverse-drug-event-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coordinated Multi-Neighborhood Learning on a Directed Acyclic Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coordinated-multi-neighborhood-learning-on-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method facilitates causal discovery without learning the entire DAG structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coordinated-multi-neighborhood-learning-on-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEP: Self-Enhanced Prompt Tuning for Visual-Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sep-self-enhanced-prompt-tuning-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comprehensive evaluations across various benchmarks and tasks confirm SEP's efficacy in prompt tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sep-self-enhanced-prompt-tuning-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trackastra: Transformer-based cell tracking for live-cell microscopy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trackastra-transformer-based-cell-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cell tracking is an omnipresent image analysis task in live-cell microscopy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trackastra-transformer-based-cell-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoinTramba: A Hybrid Transformer-Mamba Framework for Point Cloud Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointramba-a-hybrid-transformer-mamba</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce PoinTramba, a pioneering hybrid framework that synergies the analytical power of Transformer with the remarkable computational efficiency of Mamba for enhanced point cloud analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointramba-a-hybrid-transformer-mamba</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less is more: Summarizing Patch Tokens for efficient Multi-Label Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-summarizing-patch-tokens-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since independent pathways in truly incremental scenarios will result in an explosion of computation due to the quadratically complex multi-head self-attention (MSA) operation in prompt tuning, we propose to reduce the original patch token embeddings into summarized tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-summarizing-patch-tokens-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Optimization of Functions over Node Subsets in Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-optimization-of-functions-over-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the problem of optimizing over functions defined on node subsets in a graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-optimization-of-functions-over-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Unlearning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-unlearning-in-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a dual-pronged approach to enhance the ethical and safe behavior of large language models (LLMs) by addressing the issues of harmful responses and copyrighted content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-unlearning-in-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shopping Queries Image Dataset (SQID): An Image-Enriched ESCI Dataset for Exploring Multimodal Learning in Product Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shopping-queries-image-dataset-sqid-an-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in the fields of Information Retrieval and Machine Learning have focused on improving the performance of search engines to enhance the user experience, especially in the world of online shopping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shopping-queries-image-dataset-sqid-an-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GroundGrid:LiDAR Point Cloud Ground Segmentation and Terrain Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/groundgrid-lidar-point-cloud-ground</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, we propose our system GroundGrid which relies on 2D elevation maps to solve the terrain estimation and point cloud ground segmentation problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/groundgrid-lidar-point-cloud-ground</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the differences in Foundation Models: Attention, State Space Models, and Recurrent Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-differences-in-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While connections between these approaches exist, such models are commonly developed in isolation and there is a lack of theoretical understanding of the shared principles underpinning these architectures and their subtle differences, greatly influencing performance and scalability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-differences-in-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConvLLaVA: Hierarchical Backbones as Visual Encoder for Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convllava-hierarchical-backbones-as-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enhance the capabilities of ConvLLaVA, we propose two critical optimizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convllava-hierarchical-backbones-as-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Pollinator Conservation towards Agriculture 4.0: Monitoring of Bees through Object Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-pollinator-conservation-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an era of rapid climate change and its adverse effects on food production, technological intervention to monitor pollinator conservation is of paramount importance for environmental monitoring and conservation for global food security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-pollinator-conservation-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Go-Explore: Standing on the Shoulders of Giant Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intelligent-go-explore-standing-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Go-Explore is a powerful family of algorithms designed to solve hard-exploration problems, built on the principle of archiving discovered states, and iteratively returning to and exploring from the most promising states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intelligent-go-explore-standing-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-enhanced Relation Graph and Task Sampling for Few-shot Molecular Property Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-enhanced-relation-graph-and-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The knowledge-enhanced relation graph module constructs the molecule-property multi-relation graph (MPMRG) to capture the many-to-many relationships between molecules and properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-enhanced-relation-graph-and-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast-PGM: Fast Probabilistic Graphical Model Learning and Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-pgm-fast-probabilistic-graphical-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Probabilistic graphical models (PGMs) serve as a powerful framework for modeling complex systems with uncertainty and extracting valuable insights from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-pgm-fast-probabilistic-graphical-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVS-Solver: Video Diffusion Model as Zero-Shot Novel View Synthesizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nvs-solver-video-diffusion-model-as-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By harnessing the potent generative capabilities of pre-trained large video diffusion models, we propose NVS-Solver, a new novel view synthesis (NVS) paradigm that operates \textit{without} the need for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nvs-solver-video-diffusion-model-as-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PriCE: Privacy-Preserving and Cost-Effective Scheduling for Parallelizing the Large Medical Image Processing Workflow over Hybrid Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/price-privacy-preserving-and-cost-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Running deep neural networks for large medical images is a resource-hungry and time-consuming task with centralized computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/price-privacy-preserving-and-cost-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Evolution of Hidden Activations with Live-Update Visualization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-evolution-of-hidden-activations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monitoring the training of neural networks is essential for identifying potential data anomalies, enabling timely interventions and conserving significant computational resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-evolution-of-hidden-activations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Organic Data-Driven Approach for Turkish Grammatical Error Correction and LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/organic-data-driven-approach-for-turkish</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, synthetic datasets are not organic enough in some cases and even require clean data to start with.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/organic-data-driven-approach-for-turkish</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Context Retrieval Augmented Generation Pipeline: LLM-Augmented Knowledge Graphs and Vector Database for Accreditation Reporting Assistance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-context-retrieval-augmented-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For a business school to receive and subsequently maintain accreditation, the school must undertake a rigorous, time consuming reporting and peer review process, to demonstrate alignment with the AACSB Standards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-context-retrieval-augmented-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeTikZify: Synthesizing Graphics Programs for Scientific Figures and Sketches with TikZ</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detikzify-synthesizing-graphics-programs-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Creating high-quality scientific figures can be time-consuming and challenging, even though sketching ideas on paper is relatively easy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detikzify-synthesizing-graphics-programs-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperInterval: Hypernetwork approach to training weight interval regions in continual learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperinterval-hypernetwork-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we introduce HyperInterval, a technique that employs interval arithmetic within the embedding space and utilizes a hypernetwork to map these intervals to the target network parameter space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperinterval-hypernetwork-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinking Forward: Memory-Efficient Federated Finetuning of Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thinking-forward-memory-efficient-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirically, Spry reduces the memory footprint during training by 1. 4-7. 1$\times$ in contrast to backpropagation, while reaching comparable accuracy, across a wide range of language tasks, models, and FL settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thinking-forward-memory-efficient-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M4U: Evaluating Multilingual Understanding and Reasoning for Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m4u-evaluating-multilingual-understanding-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce M4U, a novel and challenging benchmark for assessing the capability of multi-discipline multilingual multimodal understanding and reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m4u-evaluating-multilingual-understanding-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bisimulation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bisimulation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a data-driven approach to computing finite bisimulations for state transition systems with very large, possibly infinite state space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bisimulation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Domain Policy Adaptation by Capturing Representation Mismatch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-policy-adaptation-by-capturing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We perform representation learning only in the target domain and measure the representation deviations on the transitions from the source domain, which we show can be a signal of dynamics mismatch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-policy-adaptation-by-capturing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOAP: Enhancing Efficiency of Generated Code via Self-Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soap-enhancing-efficiency-of-generated-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These profiles are fed back to the LLM, which then revises the code to reduce overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soap-enhancing-efficiency-of-generated-code</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
