<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 09:13:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>RL$^3$: Boosting Meta Reinforcement Learning via RL inside RL$^2$</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-3-boosting-meta-reinforcement-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meta reinforcement learning (meta-RL) methods such as RL$^2$ have emerged as promising approaches for learning data-efficient RL algorithms tailored to a given task distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-3-boosting-meta-reinforcement-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Path-Controllable Deep Unfolding Network for Compressive Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-path-controllable-deep-unfolding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep unfolding network (DUN) that unfolds the optimization algorithm into a deep neural network has achieved great success in compressive sensing (CS) due to its good interpretability and high performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-path-controllable-deep-unfolding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reduce Computational Complexity for Convolutional Layers by Skipping Zeros</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduce-computational-complexity-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper gives C-K-S algorithm (ConvV2, KS-deconv, Sk-dilated), which skips these 0s in two ways: trim the filters to exclude padded 0s; transform sparse tensors to dense tensors, to avoid inserted 0s in deconvolution and dilated-convolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduce-computational-complexity-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiZoo &amp; MultiBench: A Standardized Toolkit for Multimodal Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multizoo-multibench-a-standardized-toolkit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning multimodal representations involves integrating information from multiple heterogeneous sources of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multizoo-multibench-a-standardized-toolkit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Land Cover Segmentation with Sparse Annotations from Sentinel-2 Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/land-cover-segmentation-with-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Land cover (LC) segmentation plays a critical role in various applications, including environmental analysis and natural disaster management.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/land-cover-segmentation-with-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model as Attributed Training Data Generator: A Tale of Diversity and Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-as-attributed-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we present a comprehensive empirical study on data generation encompassing vital aspects like bias, diversity, and efficiency, and highlight three key observations: firstly, synthetic datasets generated by simple prompts exhibit significant biases, such as regional bias; secondly, attribute diversity plays a pivotal role in enhancing model performance; lastly, attributed prompts achieve the performance of simple class-conditional prompts while utilizing only 5\% of the querying cost of ChatGPT associated with the latter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-as-attributed-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taqyim: Evaluating Arabic NLP Tasks Using ChatGPT Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taqyim-evaluating-arabic-nlp-tasks-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated impressive performance on various downstream tasks without requiring fine-tuning, including ChatGPT, a chat-based model built on top of LLMs such as GPT-3. 5 and GPT-4.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taqyim-evaluating-arabic-nlp-tasks-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Points for Energy Renovation (PointER): A LiDAR-Derived Point Cloud Dataset of One Million English Buildings Linked to Energy Characteristics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/points-for-energy-renovation-pointer-a-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building point clouds in new regions can be generated with the open-source code published alongside the paper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/points-for-energy-renovation-pointer-a-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Regularization in Optimal Time Variable Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-regularization-in-optimal-time-variable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, optimal time variable learning in deep neural networks (DNNs) was introduced in arXiv:2204. 08528.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-regularization-in-optimal-time-variable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBBQ: A Chinese Bias Benchmark Dataset Curated with Human-AI Collaboration for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbbq-a-chinese-bias-benchmark-dataset-curated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a Chinese Bias Benchmark dataset that consists of over 100K questions jointly constructed by human experts and generative language models, covering stereotypes and societal biases in 14 social dimensions related to Chinese culture and values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbbq-a-chinese-bias-benchmark-dataset-curated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Open Vocabulary Learning: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-open-vocabulary-learning-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our knowledge, this is the first comprehensive literature review of open vocabulary learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-open-vocabulary-learning-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Sampling and Aggregation Operations in GNN Frameworks with GPU Initiated Direct Storage Accesses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-sampling-and-aggregation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose the GPU Initiated Direct Storage Access (GIDS) dataloader, to enable GPU-oriented GNN training for large-scale graphs while efficiently utilizing all hardware resources, such as CPU memory, storage, and GPU memory with a hybrid data placement strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-sampling-and-aggregation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Framework for Identifying Depression on Social Media: MentalRiskES@IberLEF 2023</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-identifying-depression-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes our participation in the MentalRiskES task at IberLEF 2023.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-identifying-depression-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural directional distance field object representation for uni-directional path-traced rendering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-directional-distance-field-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Faster rendering of synthetic images is a core problem in the field of computer graphics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-directional-distance-field-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Systematic analysis of the impact of label noise correction on ML Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/systematic-analysis-of-the-impact-of-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply the methodology to analyze six label noise correction methods according to several fairness metrics on standard OpenML datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/systematic-analysis-of-the-impact-of-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributional Modeling for Location-Aware Adversarial Patches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-modeling-for-location-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the Distribution-Optimized Adversarial Patch (DOPatch), a novel method that optimizes a multimodal distribution of adversarial locations instead of individual ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-modeling-for-location-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Individual and Structural Graph Information Bottlenecks for Out-of-Distribution Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individual-and-structural-graph-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To remove class spurious feature caused by distribution shifts, we propose Individual Graph Information Bottleneck (I-GIB) which discards irrelevant information by minimizing the mutual information between the input graph and its embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individual-and-structural-graph-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Surgical Instruments Segmentation to Unseen Domains with One-to-Many Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-surgical-instruments</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we mitigate data-related issues by efficiently leveraging minimal source images to generate synthetic surgical instrument segmentation datasets and achieve outstanding generalization performance on unseen real domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-surgical-instruments</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Separable Physics-Informed Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/separable-physics-informed-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The number of training points (collocation points) required on these challenging PDEs grows substantially, but it is severely limited due to the expensive computational costs and heavy memory overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/separable-physics-informed-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curious Replay for Model-based Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curious-replay-for-model-based-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Agents must be able to adapt quickly as an environment changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curious-replay-for-model-based-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S2SNet: A Pretrained Neural Network for Superconductivity Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s2snet-a-pretrained-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, S2SNet is the first work to predict superconductivity with only information of crystal structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s2snet-a-pretrained-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Language Models can be Poets too: An AI Writing Assistant and Constrained Text Generation Studio</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/most-language-models-can-be-poets-too-an-ai-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a simple and universally applicable technique for modifying the output of a language model by compositionally applying filter functions to the language models vocabulary before a unit of text is generated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/most-language-models-can-be-poets-too-an-ai-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More efficient manual review of automatically transcribed tabular data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-efficient-manual-review-of-automatically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We allocated those 90, 000 codes to human reviewers, who used our annotation tool to review the codes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-efficient-manual-review-of-automatically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Pan-sharpening with Memories of Spatial Details</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-pan-sharpening-with-memories-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, in this paper, we observe that the spatial details from PAN images are mainly high-frequency cues, i. e., the edges reflect the contour of input PAN images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-pan-sharpening-with-memories-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MyDigitalFootprint: an extensive context dataset for pervasive computing applications at the edge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mydigitalfootprint-an-extensive-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demonstrate the dataset's effectiveness, we present three context-aware applications utilizing various machine learning tasks: (i) a social link prediction algorithm based on physical proximity data, (ii) daily-life activity recognition using smartphone-embedded sensors data, and (iii) a pervasive context-aware recommender system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mydigitalfootprint-an-extensive-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing Dataset Quality Through Decision Tree Characteristics in Autoencoder-Processed Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-dataset-quality-through-decision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we delve into the critical aspect of dataset quality assessment in machine learning classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-dataset-quality-through-decision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Annotation of Direct Speech in Written French Narratives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-annotation-of-direct-speech-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The automatic annotation of direct speech (AADS) in written text has been often used in computational narrative understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-annotation-of-direct-speech-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-parametric online market regime detection and regime clustering for multidimensional and path-dependent data structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-parametric-online-market-regime-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we present a non-parametric online market regime detection method for multidimensional data structures using a path-wise two-sample test derived from a maximum mean discrepancy-based similarity metric on path space that uses rough path signatures as a feature map.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-parametric-online-market-regime-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Truss Design with Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-truss-design-with-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Directly applying end-to-end reinforcement learning (RL) methods to truss layout design is infeasible either, since only a tiny portion of the entire layout space is valid under the physical constraints, leading to particularly sparse rewards for RL training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-truss-design-with-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Client Reactions in Online Mental Health Counseling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-client-reactions-in-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Communication success relies heavily on reading participants' reactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-client-reactions-in-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face Morphing Attack Detection with Denoising Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-morphing-attack-detection-with-denoising-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing MAD techniques predominantly rely on discriminative models that learn from examples of bona fide and morphed images and, as a result, often exhibit sub-optimal generalization performance when confronted with unknown types of morphing attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-morphing-attack-detection-with-denoising-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Pseudo Future Contexts for Emotion Recognition in Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-pseudo-future-contexts-for-emotion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, for an utterance, we generate its future context with pre-trained language models, potentially containing extra beneficial knowledge in a conversational form homogeneous with the historical ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-pseudo-future-contexts-for-emotion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constructing Multilingual Code Search Dataset Using Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-multilingual-code-search-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Code search is a task to find programming codes that semantically match the given natural language queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-multilingual-code-search-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyBADS: Fast and robust black-box optimization in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pybads-fast-and-robust-black-box-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PyBADS is a Python implementation of the Bayesian Adaptive Direct Search (BADS) algorithm for fast and robust black-box optimization (Acerbi and Ma 2017).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pybads-fast-and-robust-black-box-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShuttleSet22: Benchmarking Stroke Forecasting with Stroke-Level Badminton Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shuttleset22-benchmarking-stroke-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also hold a challenge, Track 2: Forecasting Future Turn-Based Strokes in Badminton Rallies, at CoachAI Badminton Challenge 2023 to boost researchers to tackle this problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shuttleset22-benchmarking-stroke-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube-ASL: A Large-Scale, Open-Domain American Sign Language-English Parallel Corpus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/youtube-asl-a-large-scale-open-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning for sign languages is bottlenecked by data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/youtube-asl-a-large-scale-open-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KnowPrefix-Tuning: A Two-Stage Prefix-Tuning Framework for Knowledge-Grounded Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowprefix-tuning-a-two-stage-prefix-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Knowledgeable Prefix Tuning (KnowPrefix-Tuning), a two-stage tuning framework, bypassing the retrieval process in a knowledge-grounded conversation system by injecting prior knowledge into the lightweight knowledge prefix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowprefix-tuning-a-two-stage-prefix-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulating counterfactuals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-counterfactuals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterfactual inference considers a hypothetical intervention in a parallel world that shares some evidence with the factual world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-counterfactuals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easing Color Shifts in Score-Based Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easing-color-shifts-in-score-based-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This network architecture substantially improves the resulting spatial means of the generated images, and we show that the improvement is approximately independent of the size of the generated images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easing-color-shifts-in-score-based-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine learning in solar physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-in-solar-physics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The application of machine learning in solar physics has the potential to greatly enhance our understanding of the complex processes that take place in the atmosphere of the Sun.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-in-solar-physics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Meta-analytical Comparison of Naive Bayes and Random Forest for Software Defect Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-meta-analytical-comparison-of-naive-bayes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conducted a systematic literature review by establishing criteria to search and choose papers, resulting in five studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-meta-analytical-comparison-of-naive-bayes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Makes ImageNet Look Unlike LAION</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-makes-imagenet-look-unlike-laion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ImageNet was famously created from Flickr image search results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-makes-imagenet-look-unlike-laion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly Detection in Networks via Score-Based Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomaly-detection-in-networks-via-score-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Node outlier detection in attributed graphs is a challenging problem for which there is no method that would work well across different datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomaly-detection-in-networks-via-score-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Re] Double Sampling Randomized Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-double-sampling-randomized-smoothing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper is a contribution to the reproducibility challenge in the field of machine learning, specifically addressing the issue of certifying the robustness of neural networks (NNs) against adversarial perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-double-sampling-randomized-smoothing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Inferential Structure in Neural Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-inferential-structure-in-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Processes (NPs) are appealing due to their ability to perform fast adaptation based on a context set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-inferential-structure-in-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Annealed Importance Sampling with Constant Rate Progress</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-annealed-importance-sampling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This algorithm relies on a sequence of interpolating distributions bridging the target to an initial tractable distribution such as the well-known geometric mean path of unnormalized distributions which is assumed to be suboptimal in general.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-annealed-importance-sampling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transferability Metrics for Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferability-metrics-for-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our experiments, we compare TLogME to state-of-the-art metrics in the estimation of transfer performance of the Faster-RCNN object detector.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferability-metrics-for-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CellViT: Vision Transformers for Precise Cell Segmentation and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cellvit-vision-transformers-for-precise-cell</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nuclei detection and segmentation in hematoxylin and eosin-stained (H&E) tissue images are important clinical tasks and crucial for a wide range of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cellvit-vision-transformers-for-precise-cell</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCID: Deep Canonical Information Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcid-deep-canonical-information-decomposition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Canonical Correlation Analysis (CCA)-based methods have traditionally been used to identify shared variables, however, they were designed for multivariate targets and only offer trivial solutions for univariate cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcid-deep-canonical-information-decomposition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-supervised Multimodal Representation Learning through a Global Workspace</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-multimodal-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent deep learning models can efficiently combine inputs from different modalities (e. g., images and text) and learn to align their latent representations, or to translate signals from one domain to another (as in image captioning, or text-to-image generation).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-multimodal-representation</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
