<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 21:09:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable Person Re-identification via Balancing Alignment and Uniformity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-person-re-identification-via-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel framework, Balancing Alignment and Uniformity (BAU), which effectively mitigates this effect by maintaining a balance between alignment and uniformity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-person-re-identification-via-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relational Contrastive Learning and Masked Image Modeling for Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-contrastive-learning-and-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this, we further conduct relational contrastive learning to model the intra- and inter-hierarchical relations for frames, sub-words and words. On the other hand, MIM can naturally boost the context information via masking, where we find that the block masking strategy is more effective for STR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-contrastive-learning-and-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise Filtering Benchmark for Neuromorphic Satellites Observations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-filtering-benchmark-for-neuromorphic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we introduce a new high-resolution satellite dataset with ground truth from a real-world platform under various noise conditions, which we have made publicly available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-filtering-benchmark-for-neuromorphic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuvis.Ai: An Open-Source, Low-Code Software Ecosystem for Hyperspectral Processing and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuvis-ai-an-open-source-low-code-software</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning is an important tool for analyzing high-dimension hyperspectral data; however, existing software solutions are either closed-source or inextensible research products.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuvis-ai-an-open-source-low-code-software</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Geometric-Physical-Driven Robot Manipulation Skill Transfer via Skill Library and Tactile Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-geometric-physical-driven-robot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The framework hierarchically organizes operational knowledge by constructing a "task graph" and a "scene graph" to represent task and scene semantic information, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-geometric-physical-driven-robot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Few-Step Diffusion Models with Dense Reward Difference Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-few-step-diffusion-models-with-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results demonstrate that SDPO consistently outperforms prior methods in reward-based alignment across diverse step configurations, underscoring its robust step generalization capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-few-step-diffusion-models-with-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant spatio-hemispherical networks for diffusion MRI deconvolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-spatio-hemispherical-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Each voxel in a diffusion MRI (dMRI) image contains a spherical signal corresponding to the direction and strength of water diffusion in the brain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-spatio-hemispherical-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZeFaV: Boosting Large Language Models for Zero-shot Fact Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zefav-boosting-large-language-models-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose ZeFaV - a zero-shot based fact-checking verification framework to enhance the performance on fact verification task of large language models by leveraging the in-context learning ability of large language models to extract the relations among the entities within a claim, re-organized the information from the evidence in a relationally logical form, and combine the above information with the original evidence to generate the context from which our fact-checking model provide verdicts for the input claims.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zefav-boosting-large-language-models-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Artificial Intelligence for Quantifying Compatibility Mechanisms in Traditional Chinese Medicine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-artificial-intelligence-for-quantifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional Chinese Medicine (TCM) involves complex compatibility mechanisms characterized by multi-component and multi-target interactions, which are challenging to quantify.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-artificial-intelligence-for-quantifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifted Model Construction without Normalisation: A Vectorised Approach to Exploit Symmetries in Factor Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifted-model-construction-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lifted probabilistic inference exploits symmetries in a probabilistic model to allow for tractable probabilistic inference with respect to domain sizes of logical variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifted-model-construction-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color-Oriented Redundancy Reduction in Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-oriented-redundancy-reduction-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the image level, we employ a palette network, a specialized neural network, to dynamically allocate colors from a reduced color space to each pixel.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-oriented-redundancy-reduction-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Fitness Exercise Classification and Counting from Video Frames</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-fitness-exercise-classification-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model was trained and validated on these diverse datasets, achieving an accuracy of over 99% on the test set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-fitness-exercise-classification-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCExpert: Advancing MLLM Capability in Remote Sensing Change Captioning with Difference-Aware Integration and a Foundational Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccexpert-advancing-mllm-capability-in-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel model, CCExpert, based on a new, advanced multimodal large model framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccexpert-advancing-mllm-capability-in-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ST-Tree with Interpretability for Multivariate Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/st-tree-with-interpretability-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, deep neural network models such as Transformers exhibit high accuracy in multivariate time series classification but lack interpretability and fail to provide insights into the decision-making process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/st-tree-with-interpretability-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SADDE: Semi-supervised Anomaly Detection with Dependable Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sadde-semi-supervised-anomaly-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this research paper, we introduce SADDE, a general framework designed to accomplish two primary objectives: (1) to render the anomaly detection process interpretable and enhance the credibility of interpretation outcomes, and (2) to assign high-confidence pseudo labels to unlabeled samples, thereby boosting the performance of anomaly detection systems when supervised data is scarce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sadde-semi-supervised-anomaly-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual-Semantic Graph Matching Net for Zero-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-semantic-graph-matching-net-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, methods trained under this paradigm often struggle to learn robust embedding space because they align the two modalities in an isolated manner among classes, which ignore the crucial class relationship during the alignment process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-semantic-graph-matching-net-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edge-Enhanced Dilated Residual Attention Network for Multimodal Medical Image Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge-enhanced-dilated-residual-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal medical image fusion is a crucial task that combines complementary information from different imaging modalities into a unified representation, thereby enhancing diagnostic accuracy and treatment planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge-enhanced-dilated-residual-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TS-LLaVA: Constructing Visual Tokens through Thumbnail-and-Sampling for Training-Free Video Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ts-llava-constructing-visual-tokens-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For video understanding tasks, training-based video LLMs are difficult to build due to the scarcity of high-quality, curated video-text paired data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ts-llava-constructing-visual-tokens-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dialectal Toxicity Detection: Evaluating LLM-as-a-Judge Consistency Across Language Varieties</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialectal-toxicity-detection-evaluating-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, if we have to rank the consistency, the weakest area is LLM-human agreement, followed by dialectal consistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialectal-toxicity-detection-evaluating-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VeGaS: Video Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vegas-video-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One potential solution is to use a 3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) based model, such as the Video Gaussian Representation (VGR), which is capable of encoding video as a multitude of 3D Gaussians and is applicable for numerous video processing operations, including editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vegas-video-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving User Experience in Preference-Based Optimization of Reward Functions for Assistive Robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-user-experience-in-preference-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assistive robots interact with humans and must adapt to different users' preferences to be effective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-user-experience-in-preference-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Primes to Paths: Enabling Fast Multi-Relational Graph Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-primes-to-paths-enabling-fast-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This enables a compact representation of a complete multi-relational graph using a single adjacency matrix, which, in turn, facilitates quick computation of multi-hop adjacency matrices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-primes-to-paths-enabling-fast-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BianCang: A Traditional Chinese Medicine Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biancang-a-traditional-chinese-medicine-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise of large language models (LLMs) has driven significant progress in medical applications, including traditional Chinese medicine (TCM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biancang-a-traditional-chinese-medicine-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Multimodal LLMs: the Mechanistic Interpretability of Llava in Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-multimodal-llms-the-mechanistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the mechanisms behind Large Language Models (LLMs) is crucial for designing improved models and strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-multimodal-llms-the-mechanistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Neural Joint Activity in Spiking Neural Networks for Fraud Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-neural-joint-activity-in-spiking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed SNN approach with neural joint activity enables the classification of fraudulent opening of bank accounts more accurately and fairly than standard SNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-neural-joint-activity-in-spiking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Bayesian Bow tie Neural Networks with Shrinkage</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-bayesian-bow-tie-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the dominant role of deep models in machine learning, limitations persist, including overconfident predictions, susceptibility to adversarial attacks, and underestimation of variability in predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-bayesian-bow-tie-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SageAttention2 Technical Report: Accurate 4 Bit Attention for Plug-and-play Inference Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sageattention2-technical-report-accurate-4</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we propose a method to smooth $Q$ and $V$, enhancing the accuracy of attention with INT4 $QK$ and FP8 $PV$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sageattention2-technical-report-accurate-4</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StableV2V: Stablizing Shape Consistency in Video-to-Video Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stablev2v-stablizing-shape-consistency-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements of generative AI have significantly promoted content creation and editing, where prevailing studies further extend this exciting progress to video editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stablev2v-stablizing-shape-consistency-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformation Generation using Transformer Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformation-generation-using-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fast generation of valid conformations is thus central to molecular modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformation-generation-using-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going Beyond Conventional OOD Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/going-beyond-conventional-ood-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a unified Approach to Spurious, fine-grained, and Conventional OOD Detection (ASCOOD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/going-beyond-conventional-ood-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-based Layer-wise Semantic Reconstruction for Unsupervised Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-layer-wise-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The innovation of our approach is that we leverage the diffusion model's intrinsic data reconstruction ability to distinguish ID samples from OOD samples in the latent feature space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-layer-wise-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeomCLIP: Contrastive Geometry-Text Pre-training for Molecules</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geomclip-contrastive-geometry-text-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this dataset, we propose the GeomCLIP framework to enhance for multi-modal representation learning from molecular structures and biomedical text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geomclip-contrastive-geometry-text-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM Decoding: Speculative Decoding via Suffix Automaton</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-decoding-speculative-decoding-via-suffix</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SAM-Decoding constructs static and dynamic suffix automatons for the text corpus and input prompts, respectively, enabling fast and precise draft generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-decoding-speculative-decoding-via-suffix</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underwater Image Enhancement with Cascaded Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/underwater-image-enhancement-with-cascaded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to address this issue by designing a two-stage deep learning framework and taking advantage of cascaded contrastive learning to guide the network training of each stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/underwater-image-enhancement-with-cascaded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChannelDropBack: Forward-Consistent Stochastic Regularization for Deep Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/channeldropback-forward-consistent-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a consequence, it allows for seamless integration into the training process of any model and layers without the need to change its architecture, making it applicable to various network topologies, and the exact same network is deployed during training and inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/channeldropback-forward-consistent-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awaker2.5-VL: Stably Scaling MLLMs with Parameter-Efficient Mixture of Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/awaker2-5-vl-stably-scaling-mllms-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the research of Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) becomes popular, an advancing MLLM model is typically required to handle various textual and visual tasks (e. g., VQA, Detection, OCR, and ChartQA) simultaneously for real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/awaker2-5-vl-stably-scaling-mllms-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improvement in Facial Emotion Recognition using Synthetic Data Generated by Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improvement-in-facial-emotion-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we tackle the issue of data imbalance by incorporating synthetic data augmentation and leveraging the ResEmoteNet model to enhance the overall performance on facial emotion recognition task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improvement-in-facial-emotion-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Fraud Detection with 1D-Convolutional Spiking Neural Networks Through Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-fraud-detection-with-1d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach consists of applying 1D-Convolutional Spiking Neural Networks to improve fraud detection on the Bank Account Fraud dataset with the Bayesian optimization of hyperparameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-fraud-detection-with-1d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing the Evolution of Order in Materials Microstructures Using Multi-Modal Computer Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-the-evolution-of-order-in-materials</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of high-performance materials for microelectronics, energy storage, and extreme environments depends on our ability to describe and direct property-defining microstructural order.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-the-evolution-of-order-in-materials</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modification Takes Courage: Seamless Image Stitching via Reference-Driven Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modification-takes-courage-seamless-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current image stitching methods often produce noticeable seams in challenging scenarios such as uneven hue and large parallax.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modification-takes-courage-seamless-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USP-Gaussian: Unifying Spike-based Image Reconstruction, Pose Correction and Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/usp-gaussian-unifying-spike-based-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging the multi-view consistency afforded by 3DGS and the motion capture capability of the spike camera, our framework enables a joint iterative optimization that seamlessly integrates information between the spike-to-image network and 3DGS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/usp-gaussian-unifying-spike-based-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Domain Generalization via Prompt Learning and Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-domain-generalization-via-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a novel FedDG framework through Prompt Learning and AggregatioN (PLAN), which comprises two training stages to collaboratively generate local prompts and global prompts at each federated round.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-domain-generalization-via-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEAGULL: No-reference Image Quality Assessment for Regions of Interest via Vision-Language Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seagull-no-reference-image-quality-assessment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The quality analysis of ROIs can provide fine-grained guidance for image quality improvement and is crucial for scenarios focusing on region-level quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seagull-no-reference-image-quality-assessment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Sycophancy in Decoder-Only Transformer Architectures: Synthetic Data Intervention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-sycophancy-in-decoder-only</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the sycophancy problem caused by reinforcement learning from human feedback in large language models, this research applies synthetic data intervention technology to the decoder-only transformer architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-sycophancy-in-decoder-only</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-shot Voice Conversion with Diffusion Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-voice-conversion-with-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zero-shot voice conversion aims to transform a source speech utterance to match the timbre of a reference speech from an unseen speaker.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-voice-conversion-with-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embedding Byzantine Fault Tolerance into Federated Learning via Virtual Data-Driven Consistency Scoring Plugin</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embedding-byzantine-fault-tolerance-into</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By utilizing this scoring mechanism before the aggregation phase, the proposed plugin enables existing FL techniques to become robust against Byzantine attacks while maintaining their original benefits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embedding-byzantine-fault-tolerance-into</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScribbleVS: Scribble-Supervised Medical Image Segmentation via Dynamic Competitive Pseudo Label Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scribblevs-scribble-supervised-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In clinical medicine, precise image segmentation can provide substantial support to clinicians.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scribblevs-scribble-supervised-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dawn of GUI Agent: A Preliminary Case Study with Claude 3.5 Computer Use</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dawn-of-gui-agent-a-preliminary-case</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recently released model, Claude 3. 5 Computer Use, stands out as the first frontier AI model to offer computer use in public beta as a graphical user interface (GUI) agent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dawn-of-gui-agent-a-preliminary-case</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Creativity and Deception in Large Language Models: A Simulation Framework for Multi-Agent Balderdash</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-creativity-and-deception-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a simulation framework utilizing the game Balderdash to evaluate both the creativity and logical reasoning of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-creativity-and-deception-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Inversion Attacks: A Survey of Approaches and Countermeasures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-inversion-attacks-a-survey-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These attacks highlight the vulnerability of neural networks and raise awareness about the risk of privacy leakage within the research community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-inversion-attacks-a-survey-of</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
