<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 21:09:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>LR0.FM: Low-Resolution Zero-shot Classification Benchmark For Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lr0-fm-low-resolution-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce LR0. FM, a comprehensive benchmark evaluating the impact of low resolution on the zero-shot classification performance of 10 FM(s) across 66 backbones and 15 datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lr0-fm-low-resolution-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great Models Think Alike and this Undermines AI Oversight</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/great-models-think-alike-and-this-undermines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study how model similarity affects both aspects of AI oversight by proposing a probabilistic metric for LM similarity based on overlap in model mistakes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/great-models-think-alike-and-this-undermines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STURM-Flood: a curated dataset for deep learning-based flood extent mapping leveraging Sentinel-1 and Sentinel-2 imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sturm-flood-a-curated-dataset-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Flooding is a major global natural disaster exacerbated by climate change and urbanization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sturm-flood-a-curated-dataset-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Meta Coordination Graphs for Multi-agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-meta-coordination-graphs-for-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents deep meta coordination graphs (DMCG) for learning cooperative policies in multi-agent reinforcement learning (MARL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-meta-coordination-graphs-for-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Randomized Experiments Using Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-randomized-experiments-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirical results across several randomized experiments show that our estimator offers substantial precision gains, equivalent to a reduction of up to 20% in the sample size needed to match the same precision as the standard estimator based on experimental data alone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-randomized-experiments-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Uniformly Rotated Mondrian Kernel</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-uniformly-rotated-mondrian-kernel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First proposed by Rahimi and Recht, random features are used to decrease the computational cost of kernel machines in large-scale problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-uniformly-rotated-mondrian-kernel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Circuit Design using a Progressive Widening Monte Carlo Tree Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-circuit-design-using-a-progressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of Variational Quantum Algorithms (VQAs) strongly depends on the choice of the parameterized quantum circuit to optimize.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-circuit-design-using-a-progressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Retrospective Systematic Study on Hierarchical Sparse Query Transformer-assisted Ultrasound Screening for Early Hepatocellular Carcinoma</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-retrospective-systematic-study-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) ranks as the third leading cause of cancer-related mortality worldwide, with early detection being crucial for improving patient survival rates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-retrospective-systematic-study-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinically-Inspired Hierarchical Multi-Label Classification of Chest X-rays with a Penalty-Based Loss Function</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clinically-inspired-hierarchical-multi-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a novel approach to multi-label chest X-ray (CXR) image classification that enhances clinical interpretability while maintaining a streamlined, single-model, single-run training pipeline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clinically-inspired-hierarchical-multi-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZISVFM: Zero-Shot Object Instance Segmentation in Indoor Robotic Environments with Vision Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zisvfm-zero-shot-object-instance-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Service robots operating in unstructured environments must effectively recognize and segment unknown objects to enhance their functionality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zisvfm-zero-shot-object-instance-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rule-based Evolving Fuzzy System for Time Series Forecasting: New Perspectives Based on Type-2 Fuzzy Sets Measures Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rule-based-evolving-fuzzy-system-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the existing methods to deal with this type of data is the use of the evolving Fuzzy Systems (eFSs), which have been proven to be a powerful class of models for time series forecasting, due to their autonomy to handle the data and highly complex problems in real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rule-based-evolving-fuzzy-system-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Subspace Inference for the Laplace Approximation of Bayesian Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-subspace-inference-for-the-laplace</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subspace inference for neural networks assumes that a subspace of their parameter space suffices to produce a reliable uncertainty quantification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-subspace-inference-for-the-laplace</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Fast Graph Generation via Autoregressive Noisy Filtration Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-fast-graph-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Autoregressive Noisy Filtration Modeling (ANFM), a novel approach that addresses both challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-fast-graph-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coreset-Based Task Selection for Sample-Efficient Meta-Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coreset-based-task-selection-for-sample</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose a coreset-based task selection approach that selects a weighted subset of tasks based on how diverse they are in gradient space, prioritizing the most informative and diverse tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coreset-based-task-selection-for-sample</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Ensemble Learning for Cross-View Isolated Sign Language Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-ensemble-learning-for-cross-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present our solution to the Cross-View Isolated Sign Language Recognition (CV-ISLR) challenge held at WWW 2025.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-ensemble-learning-for-cross-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combinatorial Optimization Perspective based Framework for Multi-behavior Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combinatorial-optimization-perspective-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these problems, we propose a novel multi-behavior recommendation framework based on the combinatorial optimization perspective, named COPF.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combinatorial-optimization-perspective-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VerteNet -- A Multi-Context Hybrid CNN Transformer for Accurate Vertebral Landmark Localization in Lateral Spine DXA Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vertenet-a-multi-context-hybrid-cnn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lateral Spine Image (LSI) analysis is important for medical diagnosis, treatment planning, and detailed spinal health assessments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vertenet-a-multi-context-hybrid-cnn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNIP: Rethinking Pre-trained Attention Patterns for Infrared Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unip-rethinking-pre-trained-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-training techniques significantly enhance the performance of semantic segmentation tasks with limited training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unip-rethinking-pre-trained-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UD-Mamba: A pixel-level uncertainty-driven Mamba model for medical image segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ud-mamba-a-pixel-level-uncertainty-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements have highlighted the Mamba framework, a state-space model known for its efficiency in capturing long-range dependencies with linear computational complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ud-mamba-a-pixel-level-uncertainty-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepForest: Sensing Into Self-Occluding Volumes of Vegetation With Aerial Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepforest-sensing-into-self-occluding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Access to below-canopy volumetric vegetation data is crucial for understanding ecosystem dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepforest-sensing-into-self-occluding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAIR: Improving Safety Alignment with Introspective Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stair-improving-safety-alignment-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ensuring the safety and harmlessness of Large Language Models (LLMs) has become equally critical as their performance in applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stair-improving-safety-alignment-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FewTopNER: Integrating Few-Shot Learning with Topic Modeling and Named Entity Recognition in a Multilingual Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fewtopner-integrating-few-shot-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce FewTopNER, a novel framework that integrates few-shot named entity recognition (NER) with topic-aware contextual modeling to address the challenges of cross-lingual and low-resource scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fewtopner-integrating-few-shot-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Self-improvement LLM Agentic System for ML Library Development</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-self-improvement-llm-agentic-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to evaluate the effectiveness of our system, we construct a benchmark of a typical ML library and generate ASPL code with both open and closed-source LLMs on this benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-self-improvement-llm-agentic-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QLASS: Boosting Language Agent Inference via Q-Guided Stepwise Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qlass-boosting-language-agent-inference-via-q</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the stepwise guidance, we propose a Q-guided generation strategy to enable language agents to better adapt to long-term value, resulting in significant performance improvement during model inference on complex interactive agent tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qlass-boosting-language-agent-inference-via-q</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>deCIFer: Crystal Structure Prediction from Powder Diffraction Data using Autoregressive Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decifer-crystal-structure-prediction-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce an autoregressive language model that performs crystal structure prediction (CSP) from powder diffraction data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decifer-crystal-structure-prediction-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-SCEND: Test-time Scalable MCTS-enhanced Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-scend-test-time-scalable-mcts-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Test-time Scalable MCTS-enhanced Diffusion Model (T-SCEND), a novel framework that significantly improves diffusion model's reasoning capabilities with better energy-based training and scaling up test-time computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-scend-test-time-scalable-mcts-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Ensembled Multiagent Q-Learning with Hypernet Regularizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-ensembled-multiagent-q-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we propose a novel hypernet regularizer on hypernetwork weights and biases to constrain the optimization of online global Q-network to prevent overestimation accumulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-ensembled-multiagent-q-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaptBot: Combining LLM with Knowledge Graphs and Human Input for Generic-to-Specific Task Decomposition and Knowledge Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptbot-combining-llm-with-knowledge-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Embodied agents assisting humans are often asked to complete a new task in a new scenario.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptbot-combining-llm-with-knowledge-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurvHive: a package to consistently access multiple survival-analysis packages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survhive-a-package-to-consistently-access</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Survival analysis, a foundational tool for modeling time-to-event data, has seen growing integration with machine learning (ML) approaches to handle the complexities of censored data and time-varying risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survhive-a-package-to-consistently-access</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Guidance of Flow Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-guidance-of-flow-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From this framework, we derive a family of guidance techniques that can be applied to general flow matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-guidance-of-flow-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIDLE: Generalized Self-supervised Learning with Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridle-generalized-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these limitations, we introduce BRIDLE (Bidirectional Residual Quantization Interleaved Discrete Learning Encoder), a self-supervised encoder pretraining framework that incorporates residual quantization (RQ) into the bidirectional training process, and is generalized for pretraining with audio, image, and video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridle-generalized-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Generalization Ability for 3D Object Detection by Learning Sparsity-invariant Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-generalization-ability-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a method to improve the generalization ability for 3D object detection on a single domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-generalization-ability-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A comparison of translation performance between DeepL and Supertext</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-of-translation-performance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As strong machine translation (MT) systems are increasingly based on large language models (LLMs), reliable quality benchmarking requires methods that capture their ability to leverage extended context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-of-translation-performance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk-Aware Driving Scenario Analysis with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-aware-driving-scenario-analysis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) can capture nuanced contextual relationships, reasoning, and complex problem-solving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-aware-driving-scenario-analysis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness through Difference Awareness: Measuring Desired Group Discrimination in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-through-difference-awareness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Algorithmic fairness has conventionally adopted a perspective of racial color-blindness (i. e., difference unaware treatment).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-through-difference-awareness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diff9D: Diffusion-Based Domain-Generalized Category-Level 9-DoF Object Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diff9d-diffusion-based-domain-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our motivation is to leverage the latent generalization ability of the diffusion model to address the domain generalization challenge in object pose estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diff9d-diffusion-based-domain-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMER: Crafting Interactive Extended Reality Worlds with JSON Data Generated by Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmer-crafting-interactive-extended-reality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike prior approaches focusing on coding script generation, LLMER translates natural language inputs into JSON data, significantly reducing the likelihood of application crashes and processing latency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmer-crafting-interactive-extended-reality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Power Plant CO2 Emission Estimation with Deep Learning and Satellite/Simulated Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-power-plant-co2-emission-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CO2 emissions from power plants, as significant super emitters, contribute substantially to global warming.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-power-plant-co2-emission-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Attacks on Image AutoRegressive Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-attacks-on-image-autoregressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using this MIA, we perform dataset inference (DI) and find that IARs require as few as six samples to detect dataset membership, compared to 200 for DMs, indicating higher information leakage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-attacks-on-image-autoregressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Spatial-Temporal Edge-Enhanced Graph Networks for Pedestrian Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-spatial-temporal-edge-enhanced-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the Edge-to-Edge-Node-to-Node Graph Convolution (E2E-N2N-GCN), a novel dual-graph network that jointly models explicit N2N social interactions among pedestrians and implicit E2E influence propagation across these interaction patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-spatial-temporal-edge-enhanced-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimBEV: A Synthetic Multi-Task Multi-Sensor Driving Data Generation Tool and Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simbev-a-synthetic-multi-task-multi-sensor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bird's-eye view (BEV) perception for autonomous driving has garnered significant attention in recent years, in part because BEV representation facilitates the fusion of multi-sensor data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simbev-a-synthetic-multi-task-multi-sensor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OverThink: Slowdown Attacks on Reasoning LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overthinking-slowdown-attacks-on-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluated our attack across closed-(OpenAI o1, o1-mini, o3-mini) and open-(DeepSeek R1) weights reasoning models on the FreshQA and SQuAD datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overthinking-slowdown-attacks-on-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinRLlama: A Solution to LLM-Engineered Signals Challenge at FinRL Contest 2024</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finrllama-a-solution-to-llm-engineered</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response to Task II of the FinRL Challenge at ACM ICAIF 2024, this study proposes a novel prompt framework for fine-tuning large language models (LLM) with Reinforcement Learning from Market Feedback (RLMF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finrllama-a-solution-to-llm-engineered</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass-Editing Memory with Attention in Transformers: A cross-lingual exploration of knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mass-editing-memory-with-attention-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research has explored methods for updating and modifying factual knowledge in large language models, often focusing on specific multi-layer perceptron blocks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mass-editing-memory-with-attention-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activation-Informed Merging of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activation-informed-merging-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model merging, a method that combines the parameters and embeddings of multiple fine-tuned large language models (LLMs), offers a promising approach to enhance model performance across various tasks while maintaining computational efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activation-informed-merging-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust and Conjugate Spatio-Temporal Gaussian Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-and-conjugate-spatio-temporal-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-space formulations allow for Gaussian process (GP) regression with linear-in-time computational cost in spatio-temporal settings, but performance typically suffers in the presence of outliers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-and-conjugate-spatio-temporal-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards graph neural networks for provably solving convex optimization problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-graph-neural-networks-for-provably</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, message-passing graph neural networks (MPNNs) have shown potential for solving combinatorial and continuous optimization problems due to their ability to capture variable-constraint interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-graph-neural-networks-for-provably</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Dimensionality Hurts: The Role of LLM Embedding Compression for Noisy Regression Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-dimensionality-hurts-the-role-of-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown remarkable success in language modelling due to scaling laws found in model size and the hidden dimension of the model's text representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-dimensionality-hurts-the-role-of-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Skin Game: Revolutionizing Standards for AI Dermatology Model Comparison</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-skin-game-revolutionizing-standards-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a dual contribution: first, a systematic analysis of current methodological practices in skin disease classification research, revealing substantial inconsistencies in data preparation, augmentation strategies, and performance reporting; second, a comprehensive training and evaluation framework demonstrated through experiments with the DINOv2-Large vision transformer across three benchmark datasets (HAM10000, DermNet, ISIC Atlas).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-skin-game-revolutionizing-standards-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event-aided Semantic Scene Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-aided-semantic-scene-completion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in Semantic Scene Completion (SSC) for autonomous driving underscore the limitations of RGB-based approaches, which struggle under motion blur, poor lighting, and adverse weather.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-aided-semantic-scene-completion</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
