<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 21:08:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>TransDeepLab: Convolution-Free Transformer-based DeepLab v3+ for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transdeeplab-convolution-free-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Especially, deep neural networks based on seminal architectures such as U-shaped models with skip-connections or atrous convolution with pyramid pooling have been tailored to a wide range of medical image analysis tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transdeeplab-convolution-free-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weighted Scaling Approach for Metabolomics Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-scaling-approach-for-metabolomics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluated the performance of the proposed method in comparison to the other existing conventional scaling techniques using metabolomics data analysis in both the absence and presence of different percentages of outliers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-scaling-approach-for-metabolomics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Package for Automated Analysis of Lung Ultrasound Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/software-package-for-automated-analysis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the recent past with the rapid surge of COVID-19 infections, lung ultrasound has emerged as a fast and powerful diagnostic tool particularly for continuous and periodic monitoring of the lung.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/software-package-for-automated-analysis-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Polygonal Mapping of Buildings in Satellite Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-polygonal-mapping-of-buildings-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We addressed such an issue by exploiting the hierarchical supervision (of bottom-level vertices, mid-level line segments and the high-level regional masks) and proposed a novel interaction mechanism of feature embedding sourced from different levels of supervision signals to obtain reversible building masks for polygonal mapping of buildings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-polygonal-mapping-of-buildings-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSLA: Dynamic smooth label assignment for efficient anchor-free object detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsla-dynamic-smooth-label-assignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dynamic smooth label is assigned to supervise the classification branch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsla-dynamic-smooth-label-assignment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Collection and Analysis of French Dialects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-collection-and-analysis-of-french</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper discusses creating and analysing a new dataset for data mining and text analytics research, contributing to a joint Leeds University research project for the Corpus of National Dialects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-collection-and-analysis-of-french</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off-Policy Correction for Actor-Critic Algorithms in Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/off-policy-correction-for-actor-critic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the well-studied importance sampling and off-policy policy gradient techniques were proposed to compensate for this discrepancy, they usually require a collection of long trajectories that increases the computational complexity and induce additional problems such as vanishing or exploding gradients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/off-policy-correction-for-actor-critic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What do Deep Neural Networks Learn in Medical Images?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-deep-neural-networks-learn-in-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning is increasingly gaining rapid adoption in healthcare to help improve patient outcomes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-deep-neural-networks-learn-in-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Grasp on the Moon from 3D Octree Observations with Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-grasp-on-the-moon-from-3d-octree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain randomization improves the generalization of learned policies to novel scenes with previously unseen objects and different illumination conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-grasp-on-the-moon-from-3d-octree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoF-NeRF: Depth-of-Field Meets Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dof-nerf-depth-of-field-meets-neural-radiance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate this issue, we introduce DoF-NeRF, a novel neural rendering approach that can deal with shallow DoF inputs and can simulate DoF effect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dof-nerf-depth-of-field-meets-neural-radiance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Perception-Aware Transformer for Aerial Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-perception-aware-transformer-for-aerial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, with local-modeling to global-search mechanism, the proposed tracker replaces the global encoder by a novel local-recognition encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-perception-aware-transformer-for-aerial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Computing an Optimal Abstraction for Structural Causal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-computing-an-optimal-abstraction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Working with causal models at different levels of abstraction is an important feature of science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-computing-an-optimal-abstraction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacking Adversarial Defences by Smoothing the Loss Landscape</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attacking-adversarial-defences-by-smoothing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates a family of methods for defending against adversarial attacks that owe part of their success to creating a noisy, discontinuous, or otherwise rugged loss landscape that adversaries find difficult to navigate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attacking-adversarial-defences-by-smoothing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Fine-Grained Visual Recognition in Low Data Regimes via Self-Boosting Attention Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-fine-grained-visual-recognition-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In low data regimes, a network often struggles to choose the correct regions for recognition and tends to overfit spurious correlated patterns from the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-fine-grained-visual-recognition-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FrOoDo: Framework for Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/froodo-framework-for-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FrOoDo is an easy-to-use and flexible framework for Out-of-Distribution detection tasks in digital pathology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/froodo-framework-for-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-shot Adaptation Works with UnpredicTable Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-adaptation-works-with-unpredictable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finetuning on the resulting dataset leads to improved FSL performance on Natural Language Processing (NLP) tasks, but not proportionally to dataset scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-adaptation-works-with-unpredictable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Document Summarization with Centroid-Based Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-document-summarization-with-centroid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In multi-document summarization (MDS), the input is a cluster of documents, and the output is the cluster summary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-document-summarization-with-centroid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBAG: An Efficient Genetic Algorithm for the Graph Burning Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbag-an-efficient-genetic-algorithm-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph burning is a simplified deterministic model for how information spreads within networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbag-an-efficient-genetic-algorithm-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIFF: Carrying Location Information in Full Frames into Human Pose and Shape Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cliff-carrying-location-information-in-full</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Top-down methods dominate the field of 3D human pose and shape estimation, because they are decoupled from human detection and allow researchers to focus on the core problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cliff-carrying-location-information-in-full</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross Attention Based Style Distribution for Controllable Person Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-attention-based-style-distribution-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a cross attention based style distribution module that computes between the source semantic styles and target pose for pose transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-attention-based-style-distribution-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Adversarial Robustness of Vision Transformers via Cauchy Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-adversarial-robustness-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research on the robustness of deep learning has shown that Vision Transformers (ViTs) surpass the Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) under some perturbations, e. g., natural corruption, adversarial attacks, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-adversarial-robustness-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance Comparison of Deep RL Algorithms for Energy Systems Optimal Scheduling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-comparison-of-deep-rl-algorithms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This trade-off introduces extra hyperparameters that impact the DRL algorithms' performance and capability of providing feasible solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-comparison-of-deep-rl-algorithms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XOOD: Extreme Value Based Out-Of-Distribution Detection For Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xood-extreme-value-based-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting out-of-distribution (OOD) data at inference time is crucial for many applications of machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xood-extreme-value-based-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic failure of cell infection post viral entry: Implications for infection outcomes and antiviral therapy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-failure-of-cell-infection-post</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that infections wherein virus is release by an infected cell as a single burst, rather than at a constant rate over the cell's infectious lifespan, has the same probability of infection extinction, despite previous claims to this effect [Pearson 2011, doi:10. 1371/journal. pcbi. 1001058].]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-failure-of-cell-infection-post</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically Discovering Novel Visual Categories with Self-supervised Prototype Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatically-discovering-novel-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first stage, we obtain a robust feature extractor, which could serve for all images with base and novel categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatically-discovering-novel-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint covariate-alignment and concept-alignment: a framework for domain generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-covariate-alignment-and-concept</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, our framework proposes to jointly minimize both the covariate-shift as well as the concept-shift between the seen domains for a better performance on the unseen domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-covariate-alignment-and-concept</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-Scale Product Retrieval with Weakly Supervised Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-product-retrieval-with-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale weakly supervised product retrieval is a practically useful yet computationally challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-product-retrieval-with-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotic Dough Shaping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robotic-dough-shaping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the problem of shaping a piece of dough-like deformable material into a 2D target shape presented upfront.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robotic-dough-shaping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-Distribution Detection with Semantic Mismatch under Masking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel out-of-distribution (OOD) detection framework named MoodCat for image classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Semi-Supervised Methods for Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-semi-supervised-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reduce the reliance of deep neural solutions on labeled data, state-of-the-art semi-supervised methods have been proposed in the literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-semi-supervised-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COCOA: Cross Modality Contrastive Learning for Sensor Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cocoa-cross-modality-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive Learning (CL) is one of the most well-known approaches in SSL that attempts to learn general, informative representations of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cocoa-cross-modality-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Real-World Image Super-Resolution against Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-real-world-image-super-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the frequency masking may not only destroys the adversarial perturbations but also affects the sharp details in a clean image, we further develop an adversarial sample classifier based on the frequency domain of images to determine if applying the proposed mask module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-real-world-image-super-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Understanding WordArt: Corner-Guided Transformer for Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-understanding-wordart-corner-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thirdly, we utilize Transformer to learn the global feature on image-level and model the global relationship of the corner points, with the assistance of a corner-query cross-attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-understanding-wordart-corner-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSightR-Net: Interpretable Neural Network for Regression using Similarity-based Comparisons to Prototypical Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insightr-net-interpretable-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convolutional neural networks (CNNs) have shown exceptional performance for a range of medical imaging tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insightr-net-interpretable-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skeleton-Parted Graph Scattering Networks for 3D Human Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-parted-graph-scattering-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the first issue, we propose adaptive graph scattering, which leverages multiple trainable band-pass graph filters to decompose pose features into richer graph spectrum bands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-parted-graph-scattering-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speckle2Speckle: Unsupervised Learning of Ultrasound Speckle Filtering Without Clean Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speckle2speckle-unsupervised-learning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enable this, we make use of realistic ultrasound simulation techniques that allow for instantiation of several independent speckle realizations that represent the exact same tissue, thus allowing for the application of image reconstruction techniques that work with pairs of differently corrupted data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speckle2speckle-unsupervised-learning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eco2AI: carbon emissions tracking of machine learning models as the first step towards sustainable AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eco2ai-carbon-emissions-tracking-of-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The size and complexity of deep neural networks continue to grow exponentially, significantly increasing energy consumption for training and inference by these models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eco2ai-carbon-emissions-tracking-of-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Edge Offloading for Image Classification Under Rate Limit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-edge-offloading-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because of limited computing capacity, embedded devices rely on a parsimonious classification model with uneven accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-edge-offloading-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggretriever: A Simple Approach to Aggregate Textual Representation for Robust Dense Passage Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aggretriever-a-simple-approach-to-aggregate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work demonstrates that MLM pre-trained transformers can be used to effectively encode text information into a single-vector for dense retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aggretriever-a-simple-approach-to-aggregate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting the Critical Factors of Augmentation-Invariant Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-critical-factors-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We focus on better understanding the critical factors of augmentation-invariant representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-critical-factors-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Automatic Control of Vehicular Systems with Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-automatic-control-of-vehicular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is a key challenge to efficient analysis of diverse vehicular and mobility systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-automatic-control-of-vehicular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Algorithms for Diversity Maximization with Fairness Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-algorithms-for-diversity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a set $X$ of $n$ elements, it asks to select a subset $S$ of $k \ll n$ elements with maximum \emph{diversity}, as quantified by the dissimilarities among the elements in $S$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-algorithms-for-diversity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Practice for Improving the Search Results of E-commerce</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/some-practice-for-improving-the-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the Amazon KDD Cup 2022, we aim to apply natural language processing methods to improve the quality of search results that can significantly enhance user experience and engagement with search engines for e-commerce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/some-practice-for-improving-the-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resolution enhancement of placenta histological images using deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resolution-enhancement-of-placenta</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this purpose, a paired series of high- and low-resolution images have been collected to train a deep neural network model that can predict image residuals required to improve the resolution of the input images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resolution-enhancement-of-placenta</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAS: Densely-Anchored Sampling for Deep Metric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/das-densely-anchored-sampling-for-deep-metric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a Densely-Anchored Sampling (DAS) scheme that considers the embedding with corresponding data point as "anchor" and exploits the anchor's nearby embedding space to densely produce embeddings without data points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/das-densely-anchored-sampling-for-deep-metric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Fine-tuning of Self-supervised Models with Contrastive Initialization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-fine-tuning-of-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning (SSL) has achieved remarkable performance in pretraining the models that can be further used in downstream tasks via fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-fine-tuning-of-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBP-Pose: Residual Bounding Box Projection for Category-Level Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rbp-pose-residual-bounding-box-projection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Category-level object pose estimation aims to predict the 6D pose as well as the 3D metric size of arbitrary objects from a known set of categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rbp-pose-residual-bounding-box-projection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HPO X ELA: Investigating Hyperparameter Optimization Landscapes by Means of Exploratory Landscape Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hpo-x-ela-investigating-hyperparameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We identify a subset of BBOB problems that are close to the HPO problems in ELA feature space and show that optimizer performance is comparably similar on these two sets of benchmark problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hpo-x-ela-investigating-hyperparameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal extrapolation of heart wall segmentation in cardiac magnetic resonance images via pixel tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-extrapolation-of-heart-wall</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pixel tracking process starts from the end-diastolic frame of the heart cycle using the available manually segmented images to predict the end-systolic segmentation mask.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-extrapolation-of-heart-wall</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Pseudo Front Depth for 2D Forward-Looking Sonar-based Multi-view Stereo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-pseudo-front-depth-for-2d-forward</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, owing to the unique image formulation principle, estimating 3D information from a single image faces severe ambiguity problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-pseudo-front-depth-for-2d-forward</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
