<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 21:06:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>TSegFormer: 3D Tooth Segmentation in Intraoral Scans with Geometry Guided Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsegformer-3d-tooth-segmentation-in-intraoral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optical Intraoral Scanners (IOS) are widely used in digital dentistry to provide detailed 3D information of dental crowns and the gingiva.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsegformer-3d-tooth-segmentation-in-intraoral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRIFu: Differentiable Rendering and Implicit Function-based Single-View 3D Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drifu-differentiable-rendering-and-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our innovative alignment tools play a pivotal role in mapping these diverse synthetic animal models onto a unified template, facilitating precise predictions of animal shape and texture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drifu-differentiable-rendering-and-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naturalness of Attention: Revisiting Attention in Code Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naturalness-of-attention-revisiting-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models for code such as CodeBERT offer the capability to learn advanced source code representation, but their opacity poses barriers to understanding of captured properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naturalness-of-attention-revisiting-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A projected nonlinear state-space model for forecasting time series signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-projected-nonlinear-state-space-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning and forecasting stochastic time series is essential in various scientific fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-projected-nonlinear-state-space-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ComPEFT: Compression for Communicating Parameter Efficient Updates via Sparsification and Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compeft-compression-for-communicating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the efficiency of PEFT methods, the size of expert models can make it onerous to retrieve expert models per query over high-latency networks like the Internet or serve multiple experts on a single GPU.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compeft-compression-for-communicating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DA-STC: Domain Adaptive Video Semantic Segmentation via Spatio-Temporal Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/da-stc-domain-adaptive-video-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve the challenge, we propose a novel DA-STC method for domain adaptive video semantic segmentation, which incorporates a bidirectional multi-level spatio-temporal fusion module and a category-aware spatio-temporal feature alignment module to facilitate consistent learning for domain-invariant features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/da-stc-domain-adaptive-video-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight High-Speed Photography Built on Coded Exposure and Implicit Neural Representation of Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-high-speed-photography-built-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, by leveraging classical coded exposure imaging technique and emerging implicit neural representation for videos, we tactfully embed the motion direction cues into the blurry image during the imaging process and develop a novel self-recursive neural network to sequentially retrieve the latent video sequence from the blurry image utilizing the embedded motion direction cues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-high-speed-photography-built-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applications of Spiking Neural Networks in Visual Place Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applications-of-spiking-neural-networks-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lastly, we investigate the role of sequence matching in SNN-based VPR, a technique where consecutive images are used to refine place recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applications-of-spiking-neural-networks-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion360: Seamless 360 Degree Panoramic Image Generation based on Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion360-seamless-360-degree-panoramic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is a technical report on the 360-degree panoramic image generation task based on diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion360-seamless-360-degree-panoramic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applying Dimensionality Reduction as Precursor to LSTM-CNN Models for Classifying Imagery and Motor Signals in ECoG-Based BCIs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applying-dimensionality-reduction-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motor impairments, frequently caused by neurological incidents like strokes or traumatic brain injuries, present substantial obstacles in rehabilitation therapy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applying-dimensionality-reduction-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SegVol: Universal and Interactive Volumetric Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segvol-universal-and-interactive-volumetric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the remarkable progress achieved in medical image segmentation, there is still an absence of foundation segmentation model that can segment a wide range of anatomical categories with easy user interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segvol-universal-and-interactive-volumetric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PG-Video-LLaVA: Pixel Grounding Large Video-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pg-video-llava-pixel-grounding-large-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extending image-based Large Multimodal Models (LMM) to videos is challenging due to the inherent complexity of video data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pg-video-llava-pixel-grounding-large-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Numerical Integration in Reproducing Kernel Hilbert Spaces via Leverage Scores Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-numerical-integration-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we consider the problem of numerical integration, i. e., approximating integrals with respect to a target probability measure using only pointwise evaluations of the integrand.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-numerical-integration-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAE-Net: Deforming Auto-Encoder for fine-grained shape co-segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dae-net-deforming-auto-encoder-for-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an unsupervised 3D shape co-segmentation method which learns a set of deformable part templates from a shape collection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dae-net-deforming-auto-encoder-for-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Inference in Molecular Diffusion Models with Latent Representations of Protein Structure</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-inference-in-molecular-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion generative models have emerged as a powerful framework for addressing problems in structural biology and structure-based drug design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-inference-in-molecular-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immunohistochemistry guided segmentation of benign epithelial cells, in situ lesions, and invasive epithelial cells in breast cancer slides</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/immunohistochemistry-guided-segmentation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we aimed to develop an AI model for segmentation of epithelial cells in sections from breast cancer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/immunohistochemistry-guided-segmentation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Robust Imperceptible Perturbation against Unauthorized Text-to-image Diffusion-based Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-robust-imperceptible-perturbation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve these challenges, we propose MetaCloak, which solves the bi-level poisoning problem with a meta-learning framework with an additional transformation sampling process to craft transferable and robust perturbation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-robust-imperceptible-perturbation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Images to Connections: Can DQN with GNNs learn the Strategic Game of Hex?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-images-to-connections-can-dqn-with-gnns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The gameplay of strategic board games such as chess, Go and Hex is often characterized by combinatorial, relational structures -- capturing distinct interactions and non-local patterns -- and not just images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-images-to-connections-can-dqn-with-gnns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SkeletonGait: Gait Recognition Using Skeleton Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeletongait-gait-recognition-using-skeleton</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel skeletal gait representation named Skeleton Map, together with SkeletonGait, a skeleton-based method to exploit structural information from human skeleton maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeletongait-gait-recognition-using-skeleton</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot at the Mirror: Learning to Imitate via Associating Self-supervised Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robot-at-the-mirror-learning-to-imitate-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an approach to building a custom model from ready-made self-supervised models via their associating instead of training and fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robot-at-the-mirror-learning-to-imitate-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soulstyler: Using Large Language Model to Guide Image Style Transfer for Target Object</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soulstyler-using-large-language-model-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a large language model to parse the text and identify stylization goals and specific styles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soulstyler-using-large-language-model-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViStruct: Visual Structural Knowledge Extraction via Curriculum Guided Code-Vision Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vistruct-visual-structural-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We adopt a weakly-supervised approach to directly generate visual event structures from captions for ViStruct training, capitalizing on abundant image-caption pairs from the web.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vistruct-visual-structural-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard Label Black Box Node Injection Attack on Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-label-black-box-node-injection-attack-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we will propose a non-targeted Hard Label Black Box Node Injection Attack on Graph Neural Networks, which to the best of our knowledge, is the first of its kind.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-label-black-box-node-injection-attack-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volumetric Reconstruction Resolves Off-Resonance Artifacts in Static and Dynamic PROPELLER MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volumetric-reconstruction-resolves-off</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Off-resonance artifacts in magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) are visual distortions that occur when the actual resonant frequencies of spins within the imaging volume differ from the expected frequencies used to encode spatial information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volumetric-reconstruction-resolves-off</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FusionFrames: Efficient Architectural Aspects for Text-to-Video Generation Pipeline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusionframes-efficient-architectural-aspects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first stage concerns keyframes synthesis to figure the storyline of a video, while the second one is devoted to interpolation frames generation to make movements of the scene and objects smooth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusionframes-efficient-architectural-aspects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Uncertainty-Based Hallucination Detection with Stronger Focus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-uncertainty-based-hallucination</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have gained significant popularity for their impressive performance across diverse fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-uncertainty-based-hallucination</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animatable 3D Gaussians for High-fidelity Synthesis of Human Motions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animatable-3d-gaussians-for-high-fidelity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The learnable code serves as a pose-dependent appearance embedding for refining the erroneous appearance caused by geometric transformation of Gaussians, based on which an appearance refinement model is learned to produce residual Gaussian properties to match the appearance in target pose.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animatable-3d-gaussians-for-high-fidelity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDS: Resource-Efficient Deep Subnetworks for Dynamic Resource Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reds-resource-efficient-deep-subnetworks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[REDS support conventional deep networks frequently deployed on the edge and provide computational benefits even for small and simple networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reds-resource-efficient-deep-subnetworks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Fly in Seconds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-fly-in-seconds</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our framework enables Simulation-to-Reality (Sim2Real) transfer for direct RPM control after only 18 seconds of training on a consumer-grade laptop as well as its deployment on microcontrollers to control a multirotor under real-time guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-fly-in-seconds</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FuseNet: Self-Supervised Dual-Path Network for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusenet-self-supervised-dual-path-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation, a crucial task in computer vision, often relies on labor-intensive and costly annotated datasets for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusenet-self-supervised-dual-path-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Unlearnable Example: Enhancing the Robustness of Unlearnable Examples via Stable Error-Minimizing Noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-unlearnable-example-enhancing-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Observing that simply removing the adversarial noise on the training process of the defensive noise can improve the performance of robust unlearnable examples, we identify that solely the surrogate model's robustness contributes to the performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-unlearnable-example-enhancing-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physical Reasoning and Object Planning for Household Embodied Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physical-reasoning-and-object-planning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we explore the sophisticated domain of task planning for robust household embodied agents, with a particular emphasis on the intricate task of selecting substitute objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physical-reasoning-and-object-planning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LM-Cocktail: Resilient Tuning of Language Models via Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lm-cocktail-resilient-tuning-of-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite simplicity, LM-Cocktail is surprisingly effective: the resulted model is able to achieve a strong empirical performance in the whole scope of general tasks while preserving a superior capacity in its targeted domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lm-cocktail-resilient-tuning-of-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual In-Context Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-in-context-prompting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In-context prompting in large language models (LLMs) has become a prevalent approach to improve zero-shot capabilities, but this idea is less explored in the vision domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-in-context-prompting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting out-of-distribution text using topological features of transformer-based language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-out-of-distribution-text-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We attempt to detect out-of-distribution (OOD) text samples though applying Topological Data Analysis (TDA) to attention maps in transformer-based language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-out-of-distribution-text-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep-learning-based acceleration of MRI for radiotherapy planning of pediatric patients with brain tumors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-acceleration-of-mri-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI) is a non-invasive diagnostic and radiotherapy (RT) planning tool, offering detailed insights into the anatomy of the human body.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-acceleration-of-mri-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Instruction Optimization for Open-source LLM Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-instruction-optimization-for-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the manual creation of high-quality instruction datasets is costly, leading to the adoption of automatic generation of instruction pairs by LLMs as a popular alternative in the training of open-source LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-instruction-optimization-for-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEND: Benchmarking DNA Language Models on biologically meaningful tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bend-benchmarking-dna-language-models-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The genome sequence contains the blueprint for governing cellular processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bend-benchmarking-dna-language-models-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camera-Independent Single Image Depth Estimation from Defocus Blur</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camera-independent-single-image-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We created a synthetic dataset which can be used to test the camera independent performance of depth from defocus blur models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camera-independent-single-image-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Deconfounding Against Spatio-Temporal Shifts: Theory and Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-deconfounding-against-spatio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It first encodes traffic data into two disentangled representations for associating invariant and variant ST contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-deconfounding-against-spatio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orthogonally weighted $\ell_{2,1}$ regularization for rank-aware joint sparse recovery: algorithm and analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orthogonally-weighted-ell-21-regularization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose and analyze an efficient algorithm for solving the joint sparse recovery problem using a new regularization-based method, named orthogonally weighted $\ell_{2, 1}$ ($\mathit{ow}\ell_{2, 1}$), which is specifically designed to take into account the rank of the solution matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orthogonally-weighted-ell-21-regularization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Board-to-Board: Evaluating Moonboard Grade Prediction Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/board-to-board-evaluating-moonboard-grade</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we apply classical and deep-learning modelling techniques to the 2016, 2017 and 2019 Moonboard datasets, achieving state of the art grade prediction performance with 0. 87 MAE and 1. 12 RMSE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/board-to-board-evaluating-moonboard-grade</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLAD: Global-Local View Alignment and Background Debiasing for Unsupervised Video Domain Adaptation with Large Domain Gap</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glad-global-local-view-alignment-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We specifically focus on scenarios with a substantial domain gap, in contrast to existing works primarily deal with small domain gaps between labeled source domains and unlabeled target domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glad-global-local-view-alignment-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intrinsic Image Decomposition via Ordinal Shading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsic-image-decomposition-via-ordinal-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We encourage the model to learn an accurate decomposition by computing losses on the estimated shading as well as the albedo implied by the intrinsic model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsic-image-decomposition-via-ordinal-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LowResource at BLP-2023 Task 2: Leveraging BanglaBert for Low Resource Sentiment Analysis of Bangla Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lowresource-at-blp-2023-task-2-leveraging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes the system of the LowResource Team for Task 2 of BLP-2023, which involves conducting sentiment analysis on a dataset composed of public posts and comments from diverse social media platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lowresource-at-blp-2023-task-2-leveraging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine-Guided Discovery of a Real-World Rogue Wave Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-guided-discovery-of-a-real-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, it is still not clear how we can use the superior pattern matching abilities of machine learning models for scientific discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-guided-discovery-of-a-real-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Challenges in Video-Based Infant Action Recognition: A Critical Examination of the State of the Art</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenges-in-video-based-infant-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated human action recognition, a burgeoning field within computer vision, boasts diverse applications spanning surveillance, security, human-computer interaction, tele-health, and sports analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenges-in-video-based-infant-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Graph Meets Large Language Model: Progress and Future Directions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-graph-meets-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First of all, we propose a new taxonomy, which organizes existing methods into three categories based on the role (i. e., enhancer, predictor, and alignment component) played by LLMs in graph-related tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-graph-meets-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a more inductive world for drug repurposing approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-more-inductive-world-for-drug</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we first perform an in-depth evaluation of current DTI datasets and prediction models through a robust benchmarking process, and show that DTI prediction methods based on transductive models lack generalization and lead to inflated performance when evaluated as previously done in the literature, hence not being suited for drug repurposing approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-more-inductive-world-for-drug</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>minimax: Efficient Baselines for Autocurricula in JAX</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimax-efficient-baselines-for-autocurricula</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This compute requirement is a major obstacle to rapid innovation for the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimax-efficient-baselines-for-autocurricula</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
