<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 21:07:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Task-Driven Multi-UAV Coalition Formation Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-task-driven-multi-uav-coalition-formation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid advancement of UAV technology, the problem of UAV coalition formation has become a hotspot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-task-driven-multi-uav-coalition-formation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Backward and Galerkin Methods for the Finite State Master Equation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-backward-and-galerkin-methods-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes and analyzes two neural network methods to solve the master equation for finite-state mean field games (MFGs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-backward-and-galerkin-methods-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Multigraph Convolution Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-multigraph-convolution-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing multigraph convolution methods either ignore the cross-view interaction among multiple graphs, or induce extremely high computational cost due to standard cross-view polynomial operators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-multigraph-convolution-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debiasing Large Visual Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-large-visual-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realms of computer vision and natural language processing, Large Vision-Language Models (LVLMs) have become indispensable tools, proficient in generating textual descriptions based on visual inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-large-visual-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFORecon: Generalizable Sparse-View Surface Reconstruction from Arbitrary and UnFavOrable Data Sets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uforecon-generalizable-sparse-view-surface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalizable neural implicit surface reconstruction aims to obtain an accurate underlying geometry given a limited number of multi-view images from unseen scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uforecon-generalizable-sparse-view-surface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agile Multi-Source-Free Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agile-multi-source-free-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficiently utilizing rich knowledge in pretrained models has become a critical topic in the era of large models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agile-multi-source-free-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFWave: Multi-band Rectified Flow for Audio Waveform Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rfwave-multi-band-rectified-flow-for-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in generative modeling have led to significant progress in audio waveform reconstruction from diverse representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rfwave-multi-band-rectified-flow-for-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PrimeComposer: Faster Progressively Combined Diffusion for Image Composition with Attention Steering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/primecomposer-faster-progressively-combined</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This prior information is encoded into the attention weights, which are then integrated into the self-attention layers of the generator to guide the synthesis process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/primecomposer-faster-progressively-combined</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoElevator: Elevating Video Generation Quality with Versatile Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videoelevator-elevating-video-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from conventional T2V sampling (i. e., temporal and spatial modeling), VideoElevator explicitly decomposes each sampling step into temporal motion refining and spatial quality elevating.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videoelevator-elevating-video-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face2Diffusion for Fast and Editable Face Personalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face2diffusion-for-fast-and-editable-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, it is still challenging for previous methods to preserve both the identity similarity and editability due to overfitting to training samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face2diffusion-for-fast-and-editable-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEAR: An Efficient KV Cache Compression Recipefor Near-Lossless Generative Inference of LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gear-an-efficient-kv-cache-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Key-value (KV) caching has become the de-facto to accelerate generation speed for large language models (LLMs) inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gear-an-efficient-kv-cache-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal and Uni-Modal Soft-Label Alignment for Image-Text Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-and-uni-modal-soft-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, our method can also boost the uni-modal retrieval performance of image-text retrieval models, enabling it to achieve universal retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-and-uni-modal-soft-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LightM-UNet: Mamba Assists in Lightweight UNet for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightm-unet-mamba-assists-in-lightweight-unet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This highlights the potential of Mamba in facilitating model lightweighting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightm-unet-mamba-assists-in-lightweight-unet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACLSum: A New Dataset for Aspect-based Summarization of Scientific Publications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aclsum-a-new-dataset-for-aspect-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive efforts in the past have been directed toward the development of summarization datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aclsum-a-new-dataset-for-aspect-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic data generation for system identification: leveraging knowledge transfer from similar systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-data-generation-for-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the challenge of overfitting in the learning of dynamical systems by introducing a novel approach for the generation of synthetic data, aimed at enhancing model generalization and robustness in scenarios characterized by data scarcity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-data-generation-for-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending Against Unforeseen Failure Modes with Latent Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defending-against-unforeseen-failure-modes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This suggests that LAT can be a promising tool for defending against failure modes that are not explicitly identified by developers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defending-against-unforeseen-failure-modes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unity by Diversity: Improved Representation Learning in Multimodal VAEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unity-by-diversity-improved-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such architectures impose hard constraints on the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unity-by-diversity-improved-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Transformers Pre-training for Multi-Spectral Satellite Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-transformers-pre-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in unsupervised learning have demonstrated the ability of large vision models to achieve promising results on downstream tasks by pre-training on large amount of unlabelled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-transformers-pre-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIRST-5K: Exploring Massive Negatives Synthesis with Self-supervised Learning for Robust Infrared Small Target Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sirst-5k-exploring-massive-negatives</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The quality, quantity, and diversity of the infrared dataset are critical to the detection of small targets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sirst-5k-exploring-massive-negatives</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can't Remember Details in Long Documents? You Need Some R&amp;R</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-t-remember-details-in-long-documents-you</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long-context large language models (LLMs) hold promise for tasks such as question-answering (QA) over long documents, but they tend to miss important information in the middle of context documents (arXiv:2307. 03172v3).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-t-remember-details-in-long-documents-you</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedFMS: Exploring Federated Foundation Models for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedfms-exploring-federated-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Segmentation Anything Model (SAM) serves as a powerful foundation model for visual segmentation and can be adapted for medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedfms-exploring-federated-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CommitBench: A Benchmark for Commit Message Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/commitbench-a-benchmark-for-commit-message</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Writing commit messages is a tedious daily task for many software developers, and often remains neglected.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/commitbench-a-benchmark-for-commit-message</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SplattingAvatar: Realistic Real-Time Human Avatars with Mesh-Embedded Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/splattingavatar-realistic-real-time-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SplattingAvatar, a hybrid 3D representation of photorealistic human avatars with Gaussian Splatting embedded on a triangle mesh, which renders over 300 FPS on a modern GPU and 30 FPS on a mobile device.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/splattingavatar-realistic-real-time-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectrogram-Based Detection of Auto-Tuned Vocals in Music Recordings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectrogram-based-detection-of-auto-tuned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the domain of music production and audio processing, the implementation of automatic pitch correction of the singing voice, also known as Auto-Tune, has significantly transformed the landscape of vocal performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectrogram-based-detection-of-auto-tuned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPS: Reconstruction-based Point Cloud Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reps-reconstruction-based-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method outperforms previous approaches in preserving the structural features of the sampled point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reps-reconstruction-based-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERBench: An Entity-Relationship based Automatically Verifiable Hallucination Benchmark for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/erbench-an-entity-relationship-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our key idea is to construct questions using the database schema, records, and functional dependencies such that they can be automatically verified.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/erbench-an-entity-relationship-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeek-VL: Towards Real-World Vision-Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseek-vl-towards-real-world-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The DeepSeek-VL family (both 1. 3B and 7B models) showcases superior user experiences as a vision-language chatbot in real-world applications, achieving state-of-the-art or competitive performance across a wide range of visual-language benchmarks at the same model size while maintaining robust performance on language-centric benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseek-vl-towards-real-world-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention-guided Feature Distillation for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-guided-feature-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to existing complex methodologies commonly employed for distilling knowledge from a teacher to a student, the pro-posed method showcases the efficacy of a simple yet powerful method for utilizing refined feature maps to transfer attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-guided-feature-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Potential of Multimodal Unified Discrete Representation through Training-Free Codebook Optimization and Hierarchical Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-potential-of-multimodal-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Dual Cross-modal Information Disentanglement (DCID) model, utilizing a unified codebook, shows promising results in achieving fine-grained representation and cross-modal generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-potential-of-multimodal-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Micro-action Recognition: Dataset, Methods, and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-micro-action-recognition-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It offers insights into the feelings and intentions of individuals and is important for human-oriented applications such as emotion recognition and psychological assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-micro-action-recognition-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arbitrary-Scale Point Cloud Upsampling by Voxel-Based Network with Latent Geometric-Consistent Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbitrary-scale-point-cloud-upsampling-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, arbitrary-scale point cloud upsampling mechanism became increasingly popular due to its efficiency and convenience for practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbitrary-scale-point-cloud-upsampling-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stealing Stable Diffusion Prior for Robust Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stealing-stable-diffusion-prior-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel approach named Stealing Stable Diffusion (SSD) prior for robust monocular depth estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stealing-stable-diffusion-prior-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bias-Augmented Consistency Training Reduces Biased Reasoning in Chain-of-Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bias-augmented-consistency-training-reduces</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, this model generalizes to other forms of bias, reducing biased reasoning on held-out biases by an average of 37%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bias-augmented-consistency-training-reduces</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECToNAS: Evolutionary Cross-Topology Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ectonas-evolutionary-cross-topology-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present ECToNAS, a cost-efficient evolutionary cross-topology neural architecture search algorithm that does not require any pre-trained meta controllers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ectonas-evolutionary-cross-topology-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM4Decompile: Decompiling Binary Code with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm4decompile-decompiling-binary-code-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we release the first open-access decompilation LLMs ranging from 1B to 33B pre-trained on 4 billion tokens of C source code and the corresponding assembly code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm4decompile-decompiling-binary-code-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HistGen: Histopathology Report Generation via Local-Global Feature Encoding and Cross-modal Context Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histgen-histopathology-report-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Histopathology serves as the gold standard in cancer diagnosis, with clinical reports being vital in interpreting and understanding this process, guiding cancer treatment and patient care.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histgen-histopathology-report-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BjTT: A Large-scale Multimodal Dataset for Traffic Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bjtt-a-large-scale-multimodal-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key challenge of the TTG task is how to associate text with the spatial structure of the road network and traffic data for generating traffic situations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bjtt-a-large-scale-multimodal-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency-Adaptive Dilated Convolution for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-adaptive-dilated-convolution-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dilated convolution, which expands the receptive field by inserting gaps between its consecutive elements, is widely employed in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-adaptive-dilated-convolution-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Learning of Harmonic Analysis Based on Neural HSMM with Code Quality Templates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-of-harmonic-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a method of unsupervised learning of harmonic analysis based on a hidden semi-Markov model (HSMM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-of-harmonic-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Influence of Dimensionality Reduction on Anomaly Detection Performance in Multivariate Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-influence-of-dimensionality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an extensive empirical study on the integration of dimensionality reduction techniques with advanced unsupervised time series anomaly detection models, focusing on the MUTANT and Anomaly-Transformer models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-influence-of-dimensionality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphInstruct: Empowering Large Language Models with Graph Understanding and Reasoning Capability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphinstruct-empowering-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate and enhance the graph understanding abilities of LLMs, in this paper, we propose a benchmark named GraphInstruct, which comprehensively includes 21 classical graph reasoning tasks, providing diverse graph generation pipelines and detailed reasoning steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphinstruct-empowering-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster Neighborhood Attention: Reducing the O(n^2) Cost of Self Attention at the Threadblock Level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-neighborhood-attention-reducing-the-o</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that our fused kernels successfully circumvent some of the unavoidable inefficiencies in unfused implementations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-neighborhood-attention-reducing-the-o</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervision in Time for Satellite Images(S3-TSS): A novel method of SSL technique in Satellite images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervision-in-time-for-satellite-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the limited availability of labeled data with various atmospheric conditions in remote sensing images, it seems useful to work with self-supervised algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervision-in-time-for-satellite-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Recommendation via Hybrid Retrieval Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-recommendation-via-hybrid-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose GPT-FedRec, a federated recommendation framework leveraging ChatGPT and a novel hybrid Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-recommendation-via-hybrid-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Court View Generation with Knowledge Injection and Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-court-view-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Court View Generation (CVG) is a challenging task in the field of Legal Artificial Intelligence (LegalAI), which aims to generate court views based on the plaintiff claims and the fact descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-court-view-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech Emotion Recognition Via CNN-Transforemr and Multidimensional Attention Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-emotion-recognition-via-cnn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, to model local and global information at different levels of granularity in speech and capture temporal, spatial and channel dependencies in speech signals, we propose a Speech Emotion Recognition network based on CNN-Transformer and multi-dimensional attention mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-emotion-recognition-via-cnn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KnowledgeVIS: Interpreting Language Models by Comparing Fill-in-the-Blank Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledgevis-interpreting-language-models-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent growth in the popularity of large language models has led to their increased usage for summarizing, predicting, and generating text, making it vital to help researchers and engineers understand how and why they work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledgevis-interpreting-language-models-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAGS: Blur Agnostic Gaussian Splatting through Multi-Scale Kernel Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bags-blur-agnostic-gaussian-splatting-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent efforts in using 3D Gaussians for scene reconstruction and novel view synthesis can achieve impressive results on curated benchmarks; however, images captured in real life are often blurry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bags-blur-agnostic-gaussian-splatting-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Can't Believe It's Not Scene Flow!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-can-t-believe-it-s-not-scene-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current scene flow methods broadly fail to describe motion on small objects, and current scene flow evaluation protocols hide this failure by averaging over many points, with most drawn larger objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-can-t-believe-it-s-not-scene-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iScore: Visual Analytics for Interpreting How Language Models Automatically Score Summaries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iscore-visual-analytics-for-interpreting-how</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent explosion in popularity of large language models (LLMs) has inspired learning engineers to incorporate them into adaptive educational tools that automatically score summary writing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iscore-visual-analytics-for-interpreting-how</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
