<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 09:15:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the positive role of cluster structure in complex networks for link prediction tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-positive-role-of-cluster</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose that it is easier to establish links between nodes with similar representation vectors and cluster tendencies in undirected graphs, while nodes in a directed graphs can more easily point to nodes similar to their representation vectors and have greater influence in their own cluster.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-positive-role-of-cluster</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Materials Property Prediction with Uncertainty Quantification: A Benchmark Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/materials-property-prediction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Uncertainty quantification (UQ) has increasing importance in building robust high-performance and generalizable materials property prediction models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/materials-property-prediction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rickrolling the Artist: Injecting Invisible Backdoors into Text-Guided Image Generation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rickrolling-the-artist-injecting-invisible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce backdoor attacks against text-guided generative models and demonstrate that their text encoders pose a major tampering risk.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rickrolling-the-artist-injecting-invisible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial-Temporal Convolutional Attention for Mapping Functional Brain Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-temporal-convolutional-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To validate the performance of the proposed method, we evaluate the approach on HCP-rest dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-temporal-convolutional-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Theoretical Study on Solving Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-theoretical-study-on-solving-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual learning (CL) learns a sequence of tasks incrementally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-theoretical-study-on-solving-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dealing with Abbreviations in the Slovenian Biographical Lexicon</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dealing-with-abbreviations-in-the-slovenian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose and present the results of a method for expanding the identified abbreviations in context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dealing-with-abbreviations-in-the-slovenian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Logits are predictive of network type</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logits-are-predictive-of-network-type</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A classifier is then trained on the logit vectors of the trained set of this dataset to map the logit vector to the network index that has generated it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logits-are-predictive-of-network-type</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PP-YOLOE-R: An Efficient Anchor-Free Rotated Object Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pp-yoloe-r-an-efficient-anchor-free-rotated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With multi-scale training and testing, PP-YOLOE-R-l and PP-YOLOE-R-x further improve the detection precision to 80. 02 and 80. 73 mAP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pp-yoloe-r-an-efficient-anchor-free-rotated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensor Robust PCA with Nonconvex and Nonlocal Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensor-robust-pca-with-nonconvex-and-nonlocal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we integrate nonlocal self-similarity into N-TRPCA, and further develop a nonconvex and nonlocal TRPCA (NN-TRPCA) model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensor-robust-pca-with-nonconvex-and-nonlocal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Path to Autonomous Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-path-to-autonomous-learners</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new theoretical approach for enabling domain knowledge acquisition by intelligent systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-path-to-autonomous-learners</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating and Improving Factuality in Multimodal Abstractive Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-and-improving-factuality-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current metrics for evaluating factuality for abstractive document summarization have achieved high correlations with human judgment, but they do not account for the vision modality and thus are not adequate for vision-and-language summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-and-improving-factuality-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSDA-YOLO: Semi-supervised Domain Adaptive YOLO for Cross-Domain Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssda-yolo-semi-supervised-domain-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain adaptive object detection (DAOD) aims to alleviate transfer performance degradation caused by the cross-domain discrepancy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssda-yolo-semi-supervised-domain-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Quality-Diversity Algorithms on Neuroevolution for Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-quality-diversity-algorithms-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a Quality-Diversity benchmark suite for Deep Neuroevolution in Reinforcement Learning domains for robot control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-quality-diversity-algorithms-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Target Sound Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-target-sound-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the first neural network model to achieve real-time and streaming target sound extraction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-target-sound-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soft Masking for Cost-Constrained Channel Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soft-masking-for-cost-constrained-channel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Structured channel pruning has been shown to significantly accelerate inference time for convolution neural networks (CNNs) on modern hardware, with a relatively minor loss of network accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soft-masking-for-cost-constrained-channel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Models for Dataset Drift Controls in Machine Learning With Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-models-for-dataset-drift-controls-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This can lead to speed up and stabilization of classifier training at a margin of up to 20% in validation accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-models-for-dataset-drift-controls-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music Mixing Style Transfer: A Contrastive Learning Approach to Disentangle Audio Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/music-mixing-style-transfer-a-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an end-to-end music mixing style transfer system that converts the mixing style of an input multitrack to that of a reference song.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/music-mixing-style-transfer-a-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPEAKER VGG CCT: Cross-corpus Speech Emotion Recognition with Speaker Embedding and Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speaker-vgg-cct-cross-corpus-speech-emotion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we start from the general idea above and develop a new learning solution for SER, which is based on Compact Convolutional Transformers (CCTs) combined with a speaker embedding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speaker-vgg-cct-cross-corpus-speech-emotion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the transfer learning for FCN based polyp segmentation in colonoscopy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-transfer-learning-for-fcn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides the complex nature of colonoscopy frames with intrinsic frame formation artefacts such as light reflections and the diversity of polyp types/shapes, the publicly available polyp segmentation training datasets are limited, small and imbalanced.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-transfer-learning-for-fcn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-free Defense of Black Box Models Against Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-free-defense-of-black-box-models-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At test time, WNR combined with trained regenerator network is prepended to the black box network, resulting in a high boost in adversarial accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-free-defense-of-black-box-models-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convex Clustering through MM: An Efficient Algorithm to Perform Hierarchical Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convex-clustering-through-mm-an-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convex clustering is a modern method with both hierarchical and $k$-means clustering characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convex-clustering-through-mm-an-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models Are Human-Level Prompt Engineers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-human-level-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By conditioning on natural language instructions, large language models (LLMs) have displayed impressive capabilities as general-purpose computers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-human-level-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Translated Skip Connections -- Expanding the Receptive Fields of Fully Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/translated-skip-connections-expanding-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The effective receptive field of a fully convolutional neural network is an important consideration when designing an architecture, as it defines the portion of the input visible to each convolutional kernel.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/translated-skip-connections-expanding-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single SMPC Invocation DPHelmet: Differentially Private Distributed Learning on a Large Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-smpc-invocation-dphelmet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that locally training support vector machines (SVMs) and computing their averages leads to a learning technique that is scalable to a large number of users, satisfies differential privacy, and is applicable to non-trivial tasks, such as CIFAR-10.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-smpc-invocation-dphelmet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating the Carbon Footprint of BLOOM, a 176B Parameter Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-the-carbon-footprint-of-bloom-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Progress in machine learning (ML) comes with a cost to the environment, given that training ML models requires significant computational resources, energy and materials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-the-carbon-footprint-of-bloom-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning safety in model-based Reinforcement Learning using MPC and Gaussian Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-safety-in-model-based-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a method to encourage safety in a Model Predictive Control (MPC)-based Reinforcement Learning (RL) agent via Gaussian Process (GP) regression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-safety-in-model-based-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computed tomography coronary angiogram images, annotations and associated data of normal and diseased arteries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computed-tomography-coronary-angiogram-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cases were classified as normal (zero calcium score with no signs of stenosis) or diseased (confirmed coronary artery disease).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computed-tomography-coronary-angiogram-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and robust Bayesian Inference using Gaussian Processes with GPry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-robust-bayesian-inference-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GPry does not need any pre-training, special hardware such as GPUs, and is intended as a drop-in replacement for traditional Monte Carlo methods for Bayesian inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-robust-bayesian-inference-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Spatially Sparse Inference for Conditional GANs and Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-spatially-sparse-inference-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With 1. 2%-area edited regions, our method reduces the computation of DDIM by 7. 5$\times$ and GauGAN by 18$\times$ while preserving the visual fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-spatially-sparse-inference-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INGREX: An Interactive Explanation Framework for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ingrex-an-interactive-explanation-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) are widely used in many modern applications, necessitating explanations for their decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ingrex-an-interactive-explanation-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair and Optimal Classification via Transports to Wasserstein-Barycenter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-and-optimal-classification-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our insight comes from the key observation that finding the optimal fair classifier is equivalent to solving a Wasserstein-barycenter problem under $\ell_1$-norm restricted to the vertices of the probability simplex.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-and-optimal-classification-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empirical Analysis of Model Selection for Heterogenous Causal Effect Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-analysis-of-model-selection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike model selection in machine learning, we cannot use the technique of cross-validation here as we do not observe the counterfactual potential outcome for any data point.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-analysis-of-model-selection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Tuning Language Models via Epistemic Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-language-models-via-epistemic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These models learn a wide range of capabilities from training on large unsupervised text corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-language-models-via-epistemic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crosslingual Generalization through Multitask Finetuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crosslingual-generalization-through-multitask</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find finetuning large multilingual language models on English tasks with English prompts allows for task generalization to non-English languages that appear only in the pretraining corpus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crosslingual-generalization-through-multitask</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedTP: Federated Learning by Transformer Personalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedtp-federated-learning-by-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of using a vanilla personalization mechanism that maintains personalized self-attention layers of each client locally, we develop a learn-to-personalize mechanism to further encourage the cooperation among clients and to increase the scablability and generalization of FedTP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedtp-federated-learning-by-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Log-density gradient covariance and automatic metric tensors for Riemann manifold Monte Carlo methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/log-density-gradient-covariance-and-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When implemented in conjunction with a Riemann manifold variant of the recently proposed numerical generalized randomized Hamiltonian Monte Carlo processes, the proposed methodology is highly competitive, in particular for the more challenging target distributions associated with Bayesian hierarchical models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/log-density-gradient-covariance-and-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolution channel separation and frequency sub-bands aggregation for music genre classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolution-channel-separation-and-frequency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In music, short-term features such as pitch and tempo constitute long-term semantic features such as melody and narrative.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolution-channel-separation-and-frequency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming Barriers to Skill Injection in Language Modeling: Case Study in Arithmetic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-barriers-to-skill-injection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through their transfer learning abilities, highly-parameterized large pre-trained language models have dominated the NLP landscape for a multitude of downstream language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-barriers-to-skill-injection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Few-shot Learning Without Using any Adversarial Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-few-shot-learning-without-using-any</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These methods rely on the generation of adversarial samples in every episode of training, which further adds a computational burden.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-few-shot-learning-without-using-any</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Vocabulary Argument Role Prediction for Event Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-argument-role-prediction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we formulate the role prediction problem as an in-filling task and construct prompts for a pre-trained language model to generate candidate roles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-argument-role-prediction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MALUNet: A Multi-Attention and Light-weight UNet for Skin Lesion Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/malunet-a-multi-attention-and-light-weight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose a light-weight model to achieve competitive performances for skin lesion segmentation at the lowest cost of parameters and computational complexity so far.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/malunet-a-multi-attention-and-light-weight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning of Neural Machine Translation within Low Forgetting Risk Regions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-of-neural-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose two methods to search the low forgetting risk regions, which are based on the curvature of loss and the impacts of the parameters on the model output, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-of-neural-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the State-of-the-Art Language Modeling Methods and Data Augmentation Techniques for Multilingual Clause-Level Morphology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-state-of-the-art-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Transformer architectures with data augmentation and pipeline architectures achieved the best results for inflection and reinflection tasks, pipelines and prefix-tuning on mGPT received the highest results for the analysis task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-state-of-the-art-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Image Deconvolution for Weak Gravitational Lensing with Physics-informed Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galaxy-image-deconvolution-for-weak</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Removing optical and atmospheric blur from galaxy images significantly improves galaxy shape measurements for weak gravitational lensing and galaxy evolution studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galaxy-image-deconvolution-for-weak</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Unsupervised Outlier Model Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-unsupervised-outlier-model-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At its core, ELECT is based on meta-learning; transferring prior knowledge (e. g. model performance) on historical datasets that are similar to the new one to facilitate UOMS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-unsupervised-outlier-model-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embed and Emulate: Learning to estimate parameters of dynamical systems with uncertainty quantification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embed-and-emulate-learning-to-estimate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores learning emulators for parameter estimation with uncertainty estimation of high-dimensional dynamical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embed-and-emulate-learning-to-estimate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Discovering Neural Architectures from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-discovering-neural-architectures-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The discovery of neural architectures from scratch is the long-standing goal of Neural Architecture Search (NAS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-discovering-neural-architectures-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A $k$-additive Choquet integral-based approach to approximate the SHAP values for local interpretability in machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-k-additive-choquet-integral-based-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides accuracy, recent studies on machine learning models have been addressing the question on how the obtained results can be interpreted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-k-additive-choquet-integral-based-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verifying And Interpreting Neural Networks using Finite Automata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifying-and-interpreting-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Verifying properties and interpreting the behaviour of deep neural networks (DNN) is an important task given their ubiquitous use in applications, including safety-critical ones, and their blackbox nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifying-and-interpreting-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPM-Solver++: Fast Solver for Guided Sampling of Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpm-solver-fast-solver-for-guided-sampling-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The commonly-used fast sampler for guided sampling is DDIM, a first-order diffusion ODE solver that generally needs 100 to 250 steps for high-quality samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpm-solver-fast-solver-for-guided-sampling-of</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
