<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 21:09:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Structure from Motion to Localize Inaccessible Bus Stops</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-structure-from-motion-to-localize</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our method learns the locations of sidewalks in a given scene by applying a segmentation model and SfM to images from bus cameras during clear weather.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-structure-from-motion-to-localize</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAD: A realistic Continual Learning benchmark for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clad-a-realistic-continual-learning-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we describe the design and the ideas motivating a new Continual Learning benchmark for Autonomous Driving (CLAD), that focuses on the problems of object classification and object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clad-a-realistic-continual-learning-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PS-ARM: An End-to-End Attention-aware Relation Mixer Network for Person Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ps-arm-an-end-to-end-attention-aware-relation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our PS-ARM achieves state-of-the-art performance on both datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ps-arm-an-end-to-end-attention-aware-relation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preprocessors Matter! Realistic Decision-Based Attacks on Machine Learning Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preprocessors-matter-realistic-decision-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By adding just a single preprocessor in front of a classifier, we find that state-of-the-art query-based attacks are as much as seven times less effective at attacking a prediction pipeline than attacking the machine learning model alone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preprocessors-matter-realistic-decision-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Object Tracking from appearance by hierarchically clustering tracklets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-object-tracking-from-appearance-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current approaches in Multiple Object Tracking (MOT) rely on the spatio-temporal coherence between detections combined with object appearance to match objects from consecutive frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-object-tracking-from-appearance-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpeechUT: Bridging Speech and Text with Hidden-Unit for Encoder-Decoder Based Speech-Text Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechut-bridging-speech-and-text-with-hidden</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of single-modal pre-training has prompted researchers to pay more attention to cross-modal pre-training methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechut-bridging-speech-and-text-with-hidden</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longtonotes: OntoNotes with Longer Coreference Chains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longtonotes-ontonotes-with-longer-coreference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ontonotes has served as the most important benchmark for coreference resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longtonotes-ontonotes-with-longer-coreference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring Smooth Control: Monte Carlo Posterior Policy Iteration with Gaussian Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-smooth-control-monte-carlo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monte Carlo methods have become increasingly relevant for control of non-differentiable systems, approximate dynamics models and learning from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-smooth-control-monte-carlo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring and Narrowing the Compositionality Gap in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-and-narrowing-the-compositionality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then demonstrate how elicitive prompting (such as chain of thought) narrows the compositionality gap by reasoning explicitly instead of implicitly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-and-narrowing-the-compositionality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PCAE: A Framework of Plug-in Conditional Auto-Encoder for Controllable Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcae-a-framework-of-plug-in-conditional-auto</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visualization of the local latent prior well confirms the primary devotion in hidden space of the proposed model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcae-a-framework-of-plug-in-conditional-auto</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Forward Gradient With Local Losses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-forward-gradient-with-local-losses</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Forward gradient learning computes a noisy directional gradient and is a biologically plausible alternative to backprop for learning deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-forward-gradient-with-local-losses</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calibrating Factual Knowledge in Pretrained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrating-factual-knowledge-in-pretrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we find that facts stored in the PLMs are not always correct.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrating-factual-knowledge-in-pretrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Multi-Modal Sarcasm Detection via Hierarchical Congruity Modeling with Knowledge Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-multi-modal-sarcasm-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel hierarchical framework for sarcasm detection by exploring both the atomic-level congruity based on multi-head cross attention mechanism and the composition-level congruity based on graph neural networks, where a post with low congruity can be identified as sarcasm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-multi-modal-sarcasm-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying Map Space Exploration for NPUs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-map-space-exploration-for-npus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Map Space Exploration is the problem of finding optimized mappings of a Deep Neural Network (DNN) model on an accelerator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-map-space-exploration-for-npus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class-wise and reduced calibration methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-wise-and-reduced-calibration-methods</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove for several notions of calibration that solving the reduced problem minimizes the corresponding notion of miscalibration in the full problem, allowing the use of non-parametric recalibration methods that fail in higher dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-wise-and-reduced-calibration-methods</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Transformer Memorization Recall Through Idioms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-transformer-memorization-recall</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we offer the first methodological framework for probing and characterizing recall of memorized sequences in transformer LMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-transformer-memorization-recall</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look at Hardware-Friendly Weight Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-hardware-friendly-weight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the two methods on MobileNetV1 and MobileNetV2 using multiple empirical metrics to identify the sources of performance differences between the two classes, namely, sensitivity to outliers and convergence instability of the quantizer scaling factor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-hardware-friendly-weight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Large Language Models are Transforming Machine-Paraphrased Plagiarism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-large-language-models-are-transforming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent success of large language models for text generation poses a severe threat to academic integrity, as plagiarists can generate realistic paraphrases indistinguishable from original work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-large-language-models-are-transforming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Chain of Thought Prompting in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-chain-of-thought-prompting-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Providing these steps for prompting demonstrations is called chain-of-thought (CoT) prompting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-chain-of-thought-prompting-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set2Box: Similarity Preserving Representation Learning of Sets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/set2box-similarity-preserving-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through extensive experiments on 8 real-world datasets, we show that, compared to baseline approaches, Set2Box+ is (a) Accurate: achieving up to 40. 8X smaller estimation error while requiring 60% fewer bits to encode sets, (b) Concise: yielding up to 96. 8X more concise representations with similar estimation error, and (c) Versatile: enabling the estimation of four set-similarity measures from a single representation of each set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/set2box-similarity-preserving-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Neural ODEs with Sparse Bayesian Multiple Shooting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-neural-odes-with-sparse-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training dynamic models, such as neural ODEs, on long trajectories is a hard problem that requires using various tricks, such as trajectory splitting, to make model training work in practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-neural-odes-with-sparse-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarially Robust Prototypical Few-shot Segmentation with Neural-ODEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarially-robust-prototypical-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that our framework is more robust compared to traditional adversarial defense mechanisms such as adversarial training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarially-robust-prototypical-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceQA: Answering Questions about the Design of Space Missions and Space Craft Concepts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spaceqa-answering-questions-about-the-design</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SpaceQA, to the best of our knowledge the first open-domain QA system in Space mission design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spaceqa-answering-questions-about-the-design</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDa-Det: An Information Discrepancy-aware Distillation for 1-bit Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ida-det-an-information-discrepancy-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This explains why existing KD methods are less effective for 1-bit detectors, caused by a significant information discrepancy between the real-valued teacher and the 1-bit student.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ida-det-an-information-discrepancy-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GMA3D: Local-Global Attention Learning to Estimate Occluded Motions of Scene Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gma3d-local-global-attention-learning-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scene flow is the collection of each point motion information in the 3D point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gma3d-local-global-attention-learning-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bi-directional Weakly Supervised Knowledge Distillation for Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-directional-weakly-supervised-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, an attention-based bag classifier is used as the teacher network, which is trained with weak bag labels, and an instance classifier is used as the student network, which is trained using the normalized attention scores obtained from the teacher network as soft pseudo labels for the instances in positive bags.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-directional-weakly-supervised-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoML for Climate Change: A Call to Action</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automl-for-climate-change-a-call-to-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The challenge that climate change poses to humanity has spurred a rapidly developing field of artificial intelligence research focused on climate change applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automl-for-climate-change-a-call-to-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Investigation into Whitening Loss for Self-supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-investigation-into-whitening-loss-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A desirable objective in self-supervised learning (SSL) is to avoid feature collapse.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-investigation-into-whitening-loss-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Feature Alignment in Contrastive Self-Supervised Learning for Human Activity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-feature-alignment-in-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated Human Activity Recognition has long been a problem of great interest in human-centered and ubiquitous computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-feature-alignment-in-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UU-Tax at SemEval-2022 Task 3: Improving the generalizability of language models for taxonomy classification through data augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uu-tax-at-semeval-2022-task-3-improving-the-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of the task is to identify if a sentence is deemed acceptable or not, depending on the taxonomic relationship that holds between a noun pair contained in the sentence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uu-tax-at-semeval-2022-task-3-improving-the-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flexible Alignment Super-Resolution Network for Multi-Contrast MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-alignment-super-resolution-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, the Flexible Alignment module is proposed to endow receptive fields with flexibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-alignment-super-resolution-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance Segmentation of Dense and Overlapping Objects via Layering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-segmentation-of-dense-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instance segmentation aims to delineate each individual object of interest in an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-segmentation-of-dense-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans need not label more humans: Occlusion Copy &amp; Paste for Occluded Human Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humans-need-not-label-more-humans-occlusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our work, we propose a simple yet effective data-centric approach, Occlusion Copy & Paste, to introduce occluded examples to models during training - we tailor the general copy & paste augmentation approach to tackle the difficult problem of same-class occlusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humans-need-not-label-more-humans-occlusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRF: Keypoint Refinement with Fusion Network for 6D Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/krf-keypoint-refinement-with-fusion-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The CIKP method introduces color information into registration and registers point cloud around each keypoint to increase stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/krf-keypoint-refinement-with-fusion-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARAGEN : A Parallel Generation Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paragen-a-parallel-generation-toolkit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PARAGEN is a PyTorch-based NLP toolkit for further development on parallel generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paragen-a-parallel-generation-toolkit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-trained Adversarial Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-trained-adversarial-perturbations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised pre-training has drawn increasing attention in recent years due to its superior performance on numerous downstream tasks after fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-trained-adversarial-perturbations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IronDepth: Iterative Refinement of Single-View Depth using Surface Normal and its Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irondepth-iterative-refinement-of-single-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The depth of each pixel can be propagated to a query pixel, using the predicted surface normal as guidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irondepth-iterative-refinement-of-single-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mars Rover Localization Based on A2G Obstacle Distribution Pattern Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mars-rover-localization-based-on-a2g-obstacle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rover localization is one of the perquisites for large scale rover exploration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mars-rover-localization-based-on-a2g-obstacle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans2k: Unlocking the Power of Deep Models for Transparent Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trans2k-unlocking-the-power-of-deep-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual object tracking has focused predominantly on opaque objects, while transparent object tracking received very little attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trans2k-unlocking-the-power-of-deep-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Ranking-based Sample Selection for Weakly Supervised Class-imbalanced Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ars2-adaptive-ranking-based-sample-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To obtain a large amount of training labels inexpensively, researchers have recently adopted the weak supervision (WS) paradigm, which leverages labeling rules to synthesize training labels rather than using individual annotations to achieve competitive results for natural language processing (NLP) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ars2-adaptive-ranking-based-sample-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melody Infilling with User-Provided Structural Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melody-infilling-with-user-provided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel Transformer-based model for music score infilling, to generate a music passage that fills in the gap between given past and future contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melody-infilling-with-user-provided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sound of Silence: Efficiency of First Digit Features in Synthetic Audio Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-sound-of-silence-efficiency-of-first</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent integration of generative neural strategies and audio processing techniques have fostered the widespread of synthetic speech synthesis or transformation algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-sound-of-silence-efficiency-of-first</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Boosted Decision Trees with Differential Privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-boosted-decision-trees-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is great demand for scalable, secure, and efficient privacy-preserving machine learning models that can be trained over distributed data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-boosted-decision-trees-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Shot Calibration of Set Predictors via Meta-Learned Cross-Validation-Based Conformal Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-calibration-of-set-predictors-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional frequentist learning is known to yield poorly calibrated models that fail to reliably quantify the uncertainty of their decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-calibration-of-set-predictors-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IR2Net: Information Restriction and Information Recovery for Accurate Binary Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ir2net-information-restriction-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, considering the limited learning ability and information loss caused by the limited representational capability of BNNs, we propose IR$^2$Net to stimulate the potential of BNNs and improve the network accuracy by restricting the input information and recovering the feature information, including: 1) information restriction: for a BNN, by evaluating the learning ability on the input information, discarding some of the information it cannot focus on, and limiting the amount of input information to match its learning ability; 2) information recovery: due to the information loss in forward propagation, the output feature information of the network is not enough to support accurate classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ir2net-information-restriction-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>hyperbox-brain: A Toolbox for Hyperbox-based Machine Learning Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbox-brain-a-toolbox-for-hyperbox-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[hyperbox-brain is an open-source Python library implementing the leading hyperbox-based machine learning algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbox-brain-a-toolbox-for-hyperbox-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guess the Instruction! Making Language Models Stronger Zero-Shot Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guess-the-instruction-making-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meta-training, which fine-tunes the language model (LM) on various downstream tasks by maximizing the likelihood of the target label given the task instruction and input instance, has improved the zero-shot task generalization performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guess-the-instruction-making-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmentor or Filter? Reconsider the Role of Pre-trained Language Model in Text Classification Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmentor-or-filter-reconsider-the-role-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study shows that even employing pre-trained language models, existing text augmentation methods generate numerous low-quality instances and lead to the feature space shift problem in augmentation instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmentor-or-filter-reconsider-the-role-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orthogonal Non-negative Matrix Factorization: a Maximum-Entropy-Principle Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orthogonal-non-negative-matrix-factorization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a new methodology to solve the orthogonal non-negative matrix factorization (ONMF) problem, where the objective is to approximate an input data matrix by the product of two non-negative matrices, the features matrix and the mixing matrix, while one of them is orthogonal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orthogonal-non-negative-matrix-factorization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSVRF: Learning to restore Pitch-Shifted Voice without reference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psvrf-learning-to-restore-pitch-shifted-voice</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pitch scaling algorithms have a significant impact on the security of Automatic Speaker Verification (ASV) systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psvrf-learning-to-restore-pitch-shifted-voice</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
