<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 09:13:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>BPJDet: Extended Object Representation for Generic Body-Part Joint Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bpjdet-extended-object-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on the joint detection of human body and its corresponding parts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bpjdet-extended-object-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Individual Fairness in Bayesian Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individual-fairness-in-bayesian-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study Individual Fairness (IF) for Bayesian neural networks (BNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individual-fairness-in-bayesian-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Common Misassumption in Online Experiments with Machine Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-common-misassumption-in-online-experiments</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online experiments such as Randomised Controlled Trials (RCTs) or A/B-tests are the bread and butter of modern platforms on the web.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-common-misassumption-in-online-experiments</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GCNH: A Simple Method For Representation Learning On Heterophilous Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gcnh-a-simple-method-for-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, achievement of consistent GNN performance on heterophilous graphs remains an open research problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gcnh-a-simple-method-for-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Multiview Clustering by Contrasting Cluster Assignments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-multiview-clustering-by-contrasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, a cluster-level CVCL strategy is presented to explore consistent semantic label information among the multiple views in the fine-tuning stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-multiview-clustering-by-contrasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoLayoutLM: Geometric Pre-training for Visual Information Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geolayoutlm-geometric-pre-training-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, novel relation heads, which are pre-trained by the geometric pre-training tasks and fine-tuned for RE, are elaborately designed to enrich and enhance the feature representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geolayoutlm-geometric-pre-training-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China and the U.S. produce more impactful AI research when collaborating together</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/china-and-the-u-s-produce-more-impactful-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given AI's massive potential, as well as the fierce geopolitical tensions between the two nations, a number of policies have been put in place that discourage AI scientists from migrating to, or collaborating with, the other country.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/china-and-the-u-s-produce-more-impactful-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Adversarial Imitation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-adversarial-imitation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address this limitation by incorporating a discriminator into the original framework, offering two key advantages and directly solving a learning problem previous work had.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-adversarial-imitation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HabitatDyn Dataset: Dynamic Object Detection to Kinematics Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/habitatdyn-dataset-dynamic-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[HabitatDyn was created from the perspective of a mobile robot with a moving camera, and contains 30 scenes featuring six different types of moving objects with varying velocities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/habitatdyn-dataset-dynamic-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EulerNet: Adaptive Feature Interaction Learning via Euler's Formula for CTR Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eulernet-adaptive-feature-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[EulerNet converts the exponential powers of feature interactions into simple linear combinations of the modulus and phase of the complex features, making it possible to adaptively learn the high-order feature interactions in an efficient way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eulernet-adaptive-feature-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Well Does the Metropolis Algorithm Cope With Local Optima?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-well-does-the-metropolis-algorithm-cope</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even with the optimal temperature (the only parameter of the MA), the MA optimizes most cliff functions less efficiently than simple elitist evolutionary algorithms (EAs), which can only leave the local optimum by generating a superior solution possibly far away.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-well-does-the-metropolis-algorithm-cope</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can SAM Count Anything? An Empirical Study on SAM Counting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-sam-count-anything-an-empirical-study-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meta AI recently released the Segment Anything model (SAM), which has garnered attention due to its impressive performance in class-agnostic segmenting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-sam-count-anything-an-empirical-study-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Sign Language Translation with Monolingual Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-sign-language-translation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sign language translation (SLT) systems, which are often decomposed into video-to-gloss (V2G) recognition and gloss-to-text (G2T) translation through the pivot gloss, heavily relies on the availability of large-scale parallel G2T pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-sign-language-translation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReCEval: Evaluating Reasoning Chains via Correctness and Informativeness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/receval-evaluating-reasoning-chains-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-step reasoning ability is fundamental to many natural language tasks, yet it is unclear what constitutes a good reasoning chain and how to evaluate them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/receval-evaluating-reasoning-chains-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Benchmarks for Cross-modal Image-text Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-benchmarks-for-cross-modal-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The reason is that a large amount of images and texts in the benchmarks are coarse-grained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-benchmarks-for-cross-modal-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIN-SQL: Decomposed In-Context Learning of Text-to-SQL with Self-Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/din-sql-decomposed-in-context-learning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of decomposing a complex text-to-sql task into smaller sub-tasks and how such a decomposition can significantly improve the performance of Large Language Models (LLMs) in the reasoning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/din-sql-decomposed-in-context-learning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FindVehicle and VehicleFinder: A NER dataset for natural language-based vehicle retrieval and a keyword-based cross-modal vehicle retrieval system</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/findvehicle-and-vehiclefinder-a-ner-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Natural language (NL) based vehicle retrieval is a task aiming to retrieve a vehicle that is most consistent with a given NL query from among all candidate vehicles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/findvehicle-and-vehiclefinder-a-ner-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tree-structured Parzen estimator: Understanding its algorithm components and their roles for better empirical performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-structured-parzen-estimator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in many domains require more and more complicated experiment design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-structured-parzen-estimator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Importance of Exploration for Real Life Learned Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-importance-of-exploration-for-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The quality of data driven learning algorithms scales significantly with the quality of data available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-importance-of-exploration-for-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balancing Simulation-based Inference for Conservative Posteriors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-simulation-based-inference-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show empirically that the balanced versions tend to produce conservative posterior approximations on a wide variety of benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-simulation-based-inference-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing Modality Robustness in Semi-Supervised Multi-Modal Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/missing-modality-robustness-in-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We create the first benchmark for semi-supervised multi-modal semantic segmentation and also report the robustness to missing modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/missing-modality-robustness-in-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate your neural signals from mine: individual-to-individual EEG converters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generate-your-neural-signals-from-mine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An ideal individual-to-individual neural converter is expected to generate real neural signals of one subject from those of another one, which can overcome the problem of individual differences for cognitive and computational models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generate-your-neural-signals-from-mine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisFusion: Visibility-aware Online 3D Scene Reconstruction from Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visfusion-visibility-aware-online-3d-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from their works which sparsify voxels globally with a fixed occupancy threshold, we perform the sparsification on a local feature volume along each visual ray to preserve at least one voxel per ray for more fine details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visfusion-visibility-aware-online-3d-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picking Up Quantization Steps for Compressed Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/picking-up-quantization-steps-for-compressed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The sensitivity of deep neural networks to compressed images hinders their usage in many real applications, which means classification networks may fail just after taking a screenshot and saving it as a compressed file.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/picking-up-quantization-steps-for-compressed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persistently Trained, Diffusion-assisted Energy-based Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persistently-trained-diffusion-assisted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Maximum likelihood (ML) learning for energy-based models (EBMs) is challenging, partly due to non-convergence of Markov chain Monte Carlo. Several variations of ML learning have been proposed, but existing methods all fail to achieve both post-training image generation and proper density estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persistently-trained-diffusion-assisted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Token Pruning and Squeezing Towards More Aggressive Compression of Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-token-pruning-and-squeezing-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on various transformers demonstrate the effectiveness of our method, while analysis experiments prove our higher robustness to the errors of the token pruning policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-token-pruning-and-squeezing-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Attention in Colors: Another Take on Encoding Graph Structure in Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-attention-in-colors-another-take-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel self-attention mechanism, which we call CSA (Chromatic Self-Attention), which extends the notion of attention scores to attention _filters_, independently modulating the feature channels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-attention-in-colors-another-take-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can GPT-4 Perform Neural Architecture Search?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-gpt-4-perform-neural-architecture-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the potential of GPT-4~\cite{gpt4} to perform Neural Architecture Search (NAS) -- the task of designing effective neural architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-gpt-4-perform-neural-architecture-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Medical Coding on MIMIC-III and MIMIC-IV: A Critical Review and Replicability Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-medical-coding-on-mimic-iii-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical coding is the task of assigning medical codes to clinical free-text documentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-medical-coding-on-mimic-iii-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SequeL: A Continual Learning Library in PyTorch and JAX</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequel-a-continual-learning-library-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual Learning is an important and challenging problem in machine learning, where models must adapt to a continuous stream of new data without forgetting previously acquired knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequel-a-continual-learning-library-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noisy Universal Domain Adaptation via Divergence Optimization for Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisy-universal-domain-adaptation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To transfer the knowledge learned from a labeled source domain to an unlabeled target domain, many studies have worked on universal domain adaptation (UniDA), where there is no constraint on the label sets of the source domain and target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisy-universal-domain-adaptation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PED-ANOVA: Efficiently Quantifying Hyperparameter Importance in Arbitrary Subspaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ped-anova-efficiently-quantifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent rise in popularity of Hyperparameter Optimization (HPO) for deep learning has highlighted the role that good hyperparameter (HP) space design can play in training strong models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ped-anova-efficiently-quantifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiniGPT-4: Enhancing Vision-Language Understanding with Advanced Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minigpt-4-enhancing-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To examine this phenomenon, we present MiniGPT-4, which aligns a frozen visual encoder with a frozen LLM, Vicuna, using just one projection layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minigpt-4-enhancing-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-supervised Single-cell Segmentation via Collaborative Knowledge Sharing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-supervised-single-cell-segmentation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This strategy achieves self-learning by sharing knowledge between a principal model and a very light-weight collaborator model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-supervised-single-cell-segmentation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CKBP v2: An Expert-Annotated Evaluation Set for Commonsense Knowledge Base Population</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ckbp-v2-an-expert-annotated-evaluation-set</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Populating Commonsense Knowledge Bases (CSKB) is an important yet hard task in NLP, as it tackles knowledge from external sources with unseen events and entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ckbp-v2-an-expert-annotated-evaluation-set</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Analysis of Customer Churn Using Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-analysis-of-customer-churn-using-deep-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal analysis of the churn model can predict whether a customer will churn in the foreseeable future and assist enterprises to identify effects and possible causes for churn and subsequently use that knowledge to apply tailored incentives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-analysis-of-customer-churn-using-deep-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Manipulating Tokenization Aid Cross-Lingual Transfer? A Study on POS Tagging for Non-Standardized Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-manipulating-tokenization-aid-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This can for instance be observed when finetuning PLMs on one language and evaluating them on data in a closely related language variety with no standardized orthography.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-manipulating-tokenization-aid-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ellipsoid fitting with the Cayley transform</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ellipsoid-fitting-with-the-cayley-transform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an algorithm, Cayley transform ellipsoid fitting (CTEF), that uses the Cayley transform to fit ellipsoids to noisy data in any dimension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ellipsoid-fitting-with-the-cayley-transform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards replacing precipitation ensemble predictions systems using machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-replacing-precipitation-ensemble</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the feasibility of generating realistic precipitation ensemble members on unseen higher resolutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-replacing-precipitation-ensemble</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Program with Natural Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-program-with-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we further propose the Learning to Program (LP) method to ask LLMs themselves to learn natural language programs from the training dataset of complex tasks and then use the learned program to guide inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-program-with-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Cellular Coverage from Real Network Configurations using GNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-cellular-coverage-from-real-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cellular coverage quality estimation has been a critical task for self-organized networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-cellular-coverage-from-real-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety Assessment of Chinese Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-assessment-of-chinese-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further promote the safe deployment of LLMs, we develop a Chinese LLM safety assessment benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-assessment-of-chinese-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image-text Retrieval via preserving main Semantics of Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-text-retrieval-via-preserving-main</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, this paper presents a semantic optimization approach, implemented as a Visual Semantic Loss (VSL), to assist the model in focusing on an image's main content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-text-retrieval-via-preserving-main</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Implicit Neural Representations in Low-Level Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-implicit-neural-representations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implicit Neural Representation (INR) has been emerging in computer vision in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-implicit-neural-representations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt-Learning for Cross-Lingual Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-learning-for-cross-lingual-relation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on WMT17-EnZh XRE also show the effectiveness of our Prompt-XRE against other competitive baselines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-learning-for-cross-lingual-relation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omni Aggregation Networks for Lightweight Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omni-aggregation-networks-for-lightweight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While lightweight ViT framework has made tremendous progress in image super-resolution, its uni-dimensional self-attention modeling, as well as homogeneous aggregation scheme, limit its effective receptive field (ERF) to include more comprehensive interactions from both spatial and channel dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omni-aggregation-networks-for-lightweight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature-compatible Progressive Learning for Video Copy Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-compatible-progressive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video Copy Detection (VCD) has been developed to identify instances of unauthorized or duplicated video content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-compatible-progressive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Censoring chemical data to mitigate dual use risk</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/censoring-chemical-data-to-mitigate-dual-use</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dual use of machine learning applications, where models can be used for both beneficial and malicious purposes, presents a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/censoring-chemical-data-to-mitigate-dual-use</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Open Intent Classification with K-center Contrastive Learning and Adjustable Decision Boundary</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-open-intent-classification-with-k</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce novel K-center contrastive learning and adjustable decision boundary learning (CLAB) to improve the effectiveness of open intent classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-open-intent-classification-with-k</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A geometry-aware deep network for depth estimation in monocular endoscopy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-geometry-aware-deep-network-for-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we introduce a gradient loss to penalize edge fluctuations ambiguous around stepped edge structures and a normal loss to explicitly express the sensitivity to frequently small structures, and propose a geometric consistency loss to spreads the spatial information across the sample grids to constrain the global geometric anatomy structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-geometry-aware-deep-network-for-depth</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
