<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 21:08:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Effect of Prolonged Smartphone Use on Trapezius and Neck Extensor Muscle Activity, Using sEMG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-prolonged-smartphone-use-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intensive use of touchscreen mobile devices has increased musculoskeletal problems, particularly in the neck and shoulders, known as "text-neck."]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-prolonged-smartphone-use-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaCQR: Enhancing Query Reformulation for Conversational Search via Sparse and Dense Retrieval Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adacqr-enhancing-query-reformulation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational Query Reformulation (CQR) has significantly advanced in addressing the challenges of conversational search, particularly those stemming from the latent user intent and the need for historical context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adacqr-enhancing-query-reformulation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Holistic Framework for Multimodal Large Language Models in Three-dimensional Brain CT Report Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-holistic-framework-for-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal large language models (MLLMs) have been given free rein to explore exciting medical applications with a primary focus on radiology report generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-holistic-framework-for-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeMemo: On-device Retrieval Augmentation for Private and Personalized Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mememo-on-device-retrieval-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the pressing need for client-side dense retrieval, we introduce MeMemo, the first open-source JavaScript toolkit that adapts the state-of-the-art approximate nearest neighbor search technique HNSW to browser environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mememo-on-device-retrieval-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CountFormer: Multi-View Crowd Counting Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/countformer-multi-view-crowd-counting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-view counting (MVC) methods have shown their superiority over single-view counterparts, particularly in situations characterized by heavy occlusion and severe perspective distortions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/countformer-multi-view-crowd-counting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ValueScope: Unveiling Implicit Norms and Values via Return Potential Model of Social Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valuescope-unveiling-implicit-norms-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The framework thus highlights the pivotal role of social norms in shaping online interactions, presenting a substantial advance in both the theory and application of social norm studies in digital spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valuescope-unveiling-implicit-norms-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neurocache: Efficient Vector Retrieval for Long-range Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurocache-efficient-vector-retrieval-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces Neurocache, an approach to extend the effective context size of large language models (LLMs) using an external vector cache to store its past states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurocache-efficient-vector-retrieval-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real HSI-MSI-PAN image dataset for the hyperspectral/multi-spectral/panchromatic image fusion and super-resolution fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-hsi-msi-pan-image-dataset-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This reduces the credibility of the fusion algorithm, causing unfairness in the comparison between different algorithms and hindering the development of the field of hyperspectral image fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-hsi-msi-pan-image-dataset-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety-Driven Deep Reinforcement Learning Framework for Cobots: A Sim2Real Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-driven-deep-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The study then evaluated the efficiency of these safety constraints by subjecting the DRL model to various scenarios, including grasping tasks with and without obstacle avoidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-driven-deep-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Temporal Context Learning for Camera-based Semantic Scene Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-temporal-context-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we present HTCL, a novel Hierarchical Temporal Context Learning paradigm for improving camera-based semantic scene completion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-temporal-context-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparison of Means of Electrocardiographic Parameters in Peruvian University Students Based on Their Body Mass Index</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-of-means-of-electrocardiographic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several studies indicate that the body mass index is a measure correlated with the incidence of cardiovascular diseases, making it an important factor that doctors and nutritionists consider when analyzing a person’s physical condition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-of-means-of-electrocardiographic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VSP: Assessing the dual challenges of perception and reasoning in spatial planning tasks for VLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vsp-assessing-the-dual-challenges-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One understudied capability in VLMs is visual spatial planning -- the ability to comprehend the spatial arrangements of objects and devise action plans to achieve desired outcomes in visual scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vsp-assessing-the-dual-challenges-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HC-GLAD: Dual Hyperbolic Contrastive Learning for Unsupervised Graph-Level Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hc-glad-dual-hyperbolic-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, to preserve the hierarchy of real-world graphs, we introduce hyperbolic geometry into this field and conduct both graph and hypergraph embedding learning in hyperbolic space with hyperboloid model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hc-glad-dual-hyperbolic-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable the Right to be Forgotten with Federated Client Unlearning in Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enable-the-right-to-be-forgotten-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we delve into the paradigm of Federated Client Unlearning (FCU) to guarantee a client the right to erase the contribution or the influence, introducing the first FU framework in medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enable-the-right-to-be-forgotten-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Grained Contrast for Data-Efficient Unsupervised Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-grained-contrast-for-data-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The existing contrastive learning methods mainly focus on single-grained representation learning, e. g., part-level, object-level or scene-level ones, thus inevitably neglecting the transferability of representations on other granularity levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-grained-contrast-for-data-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Forget or Not? Towards Practical Knowledge Unlearning for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-forget-or-not-towards-practical-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) trained on extensive corpora inevitably retain sensitive data, such as personal privacy information and copyrighted material.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-forget-or-not-towards-practical-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Refreshed Similarity-based Upsampler for Direct High-Ratio Feature Upsampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-refreshed-similarity-based-upsampler-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These shortcomings make the existing methods along this pipeline primarily applicable to hierarchical network architectures with iterative features as guidance and they are not readily extended to a broader range of structures, especially for a direct high-ratio upsampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-refreshed-similarity-based-upsampler-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Refine with Fine-Grained Natural Language Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-refine-with-fine-grained-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work has explored the capability of large language models (LLMs) to identify and correct errors in LLM-generated responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-refine-with-fine-grained-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTMamba: Enhancing Multi-Task Dense Scene Understanding by Mamba-Based Decoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtmamba-enhancing-multi-task-dense-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-task dense scene understanding, which learns a model for multiple dense prediction tasks, has a wide range of application scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtmamba-enhancing-multi-task-dense-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Modality Balanced Online Knowledge Distillation for Brain-Eye-Computer based Dim Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-modality-balanced-online-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enhance the performance and robust capability of the fusion modality, simultaneous training and mutual learning between modalities are enabled by end-to-end online knowledge distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-modality-balanced-online-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BeNeRF: Neural Radiance Fields from a Single Blurry Image and Event Stream</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benerf-neural-radiance-fields-from-a-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method can jointly learn both the implicit neural scene representation and recover the camera motion by minimizing the differences between the synthesized data and the real measurements without pre-computed camera poses from COLMAP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benerf-neural-radiance-fields-from-a-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoP: Unlock the Power of Social Facilitation for Automatic Jailbreak Attack</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sop-unlock-the-power-of-social-facilitation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The widespread applications of large language models (LLMs) have brought about concerns regarding their potential misuse.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sop-unlock-the-power-of-social-facilitation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Similarity Distance-Based Label Assignment for Tiny Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/similarity-distance-based-label-assignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although there are some effective label assignment strategies for tiny objects, most of them focus on reducing the sensitivity to the bounding boxes to increase the number of positive samples and have some fixed hyperparameters need to set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/similarity-distance-based-label-assignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WildAvatar: Web-scale In-the-wild Video Dataset for 3D Avatar Creation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wildavatar-web-scale-in-the-wild-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, their annotating requirements are impractical for real-world images or videos, posing challenges toward real-world applications on current avatar creation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wildavatar-web-scale-in-the-wild-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScaleDreamer: Scalable Text-to-3D Synthesis with Asynchronous Score Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaledreamer-scalable-text-to-3d-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current state-of-the-arts such as Variational Score Distillation finetune the pretrained diffusion model to minimize the noise prediction error so as to align the distributions, which are however unstable to train and will impair the model's comprehension capability to numerous text prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaledreamer-scalable-text-to-3d-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributional Regression U-Nets for the Postprocessing of Precipitation Ensemble Forecasts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-regression-u-nets-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate precipitation forecasts have a high socio-economic value due to their role in decision-making in various fields such as transport networks and farming.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-regression-u-nets-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SiamTST: A Novel Representation Learning Framework for Enhanced Multivariate Time Series Forecasting applied to Telco Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siamtst-a-novel-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce SiamTST, a novel representation learning framework for multivariate time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siamtst-a-novel-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Occlusion-Aware Seamless Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occlusion-aware-seamless-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Panoramic images can broaden the Field of View (FoV), occlusion-aware prediction can deepen the understanding of the scene, and domain adaptation can transfer across viewing domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occlusion-aware-seamless-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiasDora: Exploring Hidden Biased Associations in Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biasdora-exploring-hidden-biased-associations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing works examining Vision Language Models (VLMs) for social biases predominantly focus on a limited set of documented bias associations, such as gender:profession or race:crime.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biasdora-exploring-hidden-biased-associations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking Bias, Building Bridges: Evaluation and Mitigation of Social Biases in LLMs via Contact Hypothesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-bias-building-bridges-evaluation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a unique debiasing technique, Social Contact Debiasing (SCD), that instruction-tunes these models with unbiased responses to prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-bias-building-bridges-evaluation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instruct-IPT: All-in-One Image Processing Transformer via Weight Modulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruct-ipt-all-in-one-image-processing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We have conducted experiments on Instruct-IPT to demonstrate the effectiveness of our method on manifold tasks, and we have effectively extended our method to diffusion denoisers as well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruct-ipt-all-in-one-image-processing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrate the Essence and Eliminate the Dross: Fine-Grained Self-Consistency for Free-Form Language Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrate-the-essence-and-eliminate-the-dross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These methods, however, face limitations due to their inability to fully utilize the nuanced consensus knowledge present within multiple candidate samples, often resulting in suboptimal outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrate-the-essence-and-eliminate-the-dross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Ergonomic Risk in University Study Environments During Class Days</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-ergonomic-risk-in-university</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the ergonomic impact of university seating on students’ musculoskeletal health, focusing on lumbar muscle fatigue during prolonged study sessions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-ergonomic-risk-in-university</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GlyphDraw2: Automatic Generation of Complex Glyph Posters with Diffusion Models and Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glyphdraw2-automatic-generation-of-complex</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments validate the ability of our method to generate poster images featuring intricate and contextually rich backgrounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glyphdraw2-automatic-generation-of-complex</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Referring Atomic Video Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/referring-atomic-video-action-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since these existing methods underperform on RAVAR, we introduce RefAtomNet -- a novel cross-stream attention-driven method specialized for the unique challenges of RAVAR: the need to interpret a textual referring expression for the targeted individual, utilize this reference to guide the spatial localization and harvest the prediction of the atomic actions for the referring person.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/referring-atomic-video-action-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossroads of Continents: Automated Artifact Extraction for Cultural Adaptation with Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crossroads-of-continents-automated-artifact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a comprehensive three-phase study to examine (1) the effectiveness of large multimodal models (LMMs) in recognizing cultural contexts; (2) the accuracy of their representations of diverse cultures; and (3) their ability to adapt content across cultural boundaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crossroads-of-continents-automated-artifact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attack-Aware Noise Calibration for Differential Privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attack-aware-noise-calibration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We empirically demonstrate that calibrating noise to attack sensitivity/specificity, rather than $\epsilon$, when training privacy-preserving ML models substantially improves model accuracy for the same risk level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attack-aware-noise-calibration-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classification of Phobia Levels in Patients with Arachnophobia Using BPM Analysis of ECG Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classification-of-phobia-levels-in-patients</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study proposes a method to accurately classify phobia levels in patients with arachnophobia using electrocardiogram (ECG) signal analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classification-of-phobia-levels-in-patients</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MInference 1.0: Accelerating Pre-filling for Long-Context LLMs via Dynamic Sparse Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minference-1-0-accelerating-pre-filling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the pattern and sparse indices, we perform efficient sparse attention calculations via our optimized GPU kernels to significantly reduce the latency in the pre-filling stage of long-context LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minference-1-0-accelerating-pre-filling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIAL: Attention-based eXplainability for Interpretable Alzheimer's Localized Diagnosis using 2D CNNs on 3D MRI brain scans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/axial-attention-based-explainability-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To test our method and ensure the reproducibility of our results, we chose a standardized collection of MRI data from the Alzheimer's Disease Neuroimaging Initiative (ADNI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/axial-attention-based-explainability-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TokenPacker: Efficient Visual Projector for Multimodal LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenpacker-efficient-visual-projector-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the visual tokens are redundant and can be considerably increased when dealing with high-resolution images, impairing the efficiency of MLLMs significantly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenpacker-efficient-visual-projector-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedIA: Federated Medical Image Segmentation with Heterogeneous Annotation Completeness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedia-federated-medical-image-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We begin by evaluating the completeness of annotations at the client level using a designed indicator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedia-federated-medical-image-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effect of caffeine and energy drinks on sleep quality and brain activity in college students</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-caffeine-and-energy-drinks-on-sleep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the impact of caffeine and energy drink consumption on sleep quality and brain activity among college students.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-caffeine-and-energy-drinks-on-sleep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistency Flow Matching: Defining Straight Flows with Velocity Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-flow-matching-defining-straight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we propose a multi-segment training approach for Consistency-FM to enhance expressiveness, achieving a better trade-off between sampling quality and speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-flow-matching-defining-straight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Study Environments: Assessment of Posture and Muscle Fatigue Using Superficial Electromyography in the Context of Virtual Education After the Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/home-study-environments-assessment-of-posture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The COVID-19 pandemic led to a rapid shift to virtual education, raising concerns about the ergonomics and posture of college students at home.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/home-study-environments-assessment-of-posture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swish-T : Enhancing Swish Activation with Tanh Bias for Improved Neural Network Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swish-t-enhancing-swish-activation-with-tanh</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We ultimately propose the Swish-T$_{\textbf{C}}$ function, while Swish-T and Swish-T$_{\textbf{B}}$, byproducts of Swish-T$_{\textbf{C}}$, also demonstrate satisfactory performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swish-t-enhancing-swish-activation-with-tanh</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empathic Grounding: Explorations using Multimodal Interaction and Large Language Models with Conversational Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empathic-grounding-explorations-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the concept of "empathic grounding" in conversational agents as an extension of Clark's conceptualization of grounding in conversation in which the grounding criterion includes listener empathy for the speaker's affective state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empathic-grounding-explorations-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiscoveryBench: Towards Data-Driven Discovery with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discoverybench-towards-data-driven-discovery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Can the rapid advances in code generation, function calling, and data analysis using large language models (LLMs) help automate the search and verification of hypotheses purely from a set of provided datasets?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discoverybench-towards-data-driven-discovery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RegMix: Data Mixture as Regression for Language Model Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regmix-data-mixture-as-regression-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the fitted regression model, we simulate the top-ranked mixture and use it to train a large-scale model with orders of magnitude more compute.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regmix-data-mixture-as-regression-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MathCAMPS: Fine-grained Synthesis of Mathematical Problems From Human Curricula</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathcamps-fine-grained-synthesis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mathematical problem solving is an important skill for Large Language Models (LLMs), both as an important capability and a proxy for a range of reasoning abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathcamps-fine-grained-synthesis-of</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
