<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:17:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Variational Framework for Improving Naturalness in Generative Spoken Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-variational-framework-for-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of large language models in text processing has inspired their adaptation to speech modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-variational-framework-for-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expressive Score-Based Priors for Distribution Matching with Geometry-Preserving Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressive-score-based-priors-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach eliminates biases from fixed priors (e. g., in VAEs), enabling more effective use of geometry-preserving regularization, while avoiding the challenge of learning an explicit prior density model (e. g., a flow-based prior).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressive-score-based-priors-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RMIT-ADM+S at the SIGIR 2025 LiveRAG Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmit-adm-s-at-the-sigir-2025-liverag</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the RMIT--ADM+S participation in the SIGIR 2025 LiveRAG Challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmit-adm-s-at-the-sigir-2025-liverag</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refining music sample identification with a self-supervised graph neural network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refining-music-sample-identification-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic sample identification (ASID), the detection and identification of portions of audio recordings that have been reused in new musical works, is an essential but challenging task in the field of audio query-based retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refining-music-sample-identification-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Learning to Optimize with Theoretical Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-learning-to-optimize-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our proposed methodology of aligning OOD problems to InD problems, we also demonstrate that the L2O model's convergence rate in OOD scenarios will deteriorate by an equation of the L2O model's input features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-learning-to-optimize-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TriGuard: Testing Model Safety with Attribution Entropy, Verification, and Drift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triguard-testing-model-safety-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks often achieve high accuracy, but ensuring their reliability under adversarial and distributional shifts remains a pressing challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triguard-testing-model-safety-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KDMOS:Knowledge Distillation for Motion Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kdmos-knowledge-distillation-for-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To handle the severe imbalance between moving and non-moving classes, we decouple them and apply tailored distillation strategies, allowing the teacher model to better learn key motion-related features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kdmos-knowledge-distillation-for-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Predictive Equivalence in Decision Trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-predictive-equivalence-in-decision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a boolean logical representation of decision trees that does not exhibit predictive equivalence and is faithful to the underlying decision boundary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-predictive-equivalence-in-decision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common Benchmarks Undervalue the Generalization Power of Programmatic Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/common-benchmarks-undervalue-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Algorithms for learning programmatic representations for sequential decision-making problems are often evaluated on out-of-distribution (OOD) problems, with the common conclusion that programmatic policies generalize better than neural policies on OOD problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/common-benchmarks-undervalue-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the growing field of research on AI for software testing -- the taxonomy for AI-augmented software testing and an ontology-driven literature survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-the-growing-field-of-research-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper reviews recent research on AI augmentation in software test automation, from no automation to full automation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-the-growing-field-of-research-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Busting the Paper Ballot: Voting Meets Adversarial Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/busting-the-paper-ballot-voting-meets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show the security risk associated with using machine learning classifiers in United States election tabulators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/busting-the-paper-ballot-voting-meets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Déjà Vu: Efficient Video-Language Query Engine with Learning-based Inter-Frame Computation Reuse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deja-vu-efficient-video-language-query-engine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces D\'ej\`a Vu, a video-language query engine that accelerates ViT-based VideoLMs by reusing computations across consecutive frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deja-vu-efficient-video-language-query-engine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RL-Obfuscation: Can Language Models Learn to Evade Latent-Space Monitors?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-obfuscation-can-language-models-learn-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Latent-space monitors aim to detect undesirable behaviours in large language models by leveraging internal model representations rather than relying solely on black-box outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-obfuscation-can-language-models-learn-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Verilog Design Problems: A Next-Generation Benchmark Dataset for Evaluating Large Language Models and Agents on RTL Design and Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-verilog-design-problems-a-next</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Comprehensive Verilog Design Problems (CVDP) benchmark, a new dataset and infrastructure to advance LLM and agent research in hardware design and verification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-verilog-design-problems-a-next</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Aggregation and Targeted Embedding Optimization for Collective Moral Reasoning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-aggregation-and-targeted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have shown impressive moral reasoning abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-aggregation-and-targeted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataset distillation for memorized data: Soft labels can leak held-out teacher knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-distillation-for-memorized-data-soft</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show that students trained on soft labels from teachers can achieve non-trivial accuracy on held-out memorized data they never directly observed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-distillation-for-memorized-data-soft</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCISSOR: Mitigating Semantic Bias through Cluster-Aware Siamese Networks for Robust Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scissor-mitigating-semantic-bias-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study redefines the landscape of model generalization by addressing overlooked semantic biases, establishing SCISSOR as a foundational framework for mitigating shortcut learning and fostering more robust, bias-resistant AI systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scissor-mitigating-semantic-bias-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming Overfitting in Reinforcement Learning via Gaussian Process Diffusion Policy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-overfitting-in-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the key challenges that Reinforcement Learning (RL) faces is its limited capability to adapt to a change of data distribution caused by uncertainties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-overfitting-in-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Membership Inference Attacks as Privacy Tools: Reliability, Disparity and Ensemble</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membership-inference-attacks-as-privacy-tools</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Membership inference attacks (MIAs) pose a significant threat to the privacy of machine learning models and are widely used as tools for privacy assessment, auditing, and machine unlearning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membership-inference-attacks-as-privacy-tools</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeakWeather: MeteoSwiss Weather Station Measurements for Spatiotemporal Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peakweather-meteoswiss-weather-station</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate weather forecasts are essential for supporting a wide range of activities and decision-making processes, as well as mitigating the impacts of adverse weather events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peakweather-meteoswiss-weather-station</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vector Ontologies as an LLM world view extraction method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vector-ontologies-as-an-llm-world-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) possess intricate internal representations of the world, yet these latent structures are notoriously difficult to interpret or repurpose beyond the original prediction task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vector-ontologies-as-an-llm-world-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EAQuant: Enhancing Post-Training Quantization for MoE Models via Expert-Aware Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eaquant-enhancing-post-training-quantization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing post-training quantization (PTQ) methods struggle to address activation outliers, router consistency and sparse expert calibration, leading to significant performance degradation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eaquant-enhancing-post-training-quantization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vine Copulas as Differentiable Computational Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vine-copulas-as-differentiable-computational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vine copulas are sophisticated models for multivariate distributions and are increasingly used in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vine-copulas-as-differentiable-computational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Convergence of Adjoint-Optimized Neural PDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-convergence-of-adjoint-optimized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The resulting neural-network PDE model, being a function of the neural network parameters, can be calibrated to available data by optimizing over the PDE using gradient descent, where the gradient is evaluated in a computationally efficient manner by solving an adjoint PDE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-convergence-of-adjoint-optimized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELENA: High-Efficiency Learning-based channel Estimation using dual Neural Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helena-high-efficiency-learning-based-channel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate channel estimation is critical for high-performance Orthogonal Frequency-Division Multiplexing systems such as 5G New Radio, particularly under low signal-to-noise ratio and stringent latency constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helena-high-efficiency-learning-based-channel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Approximate Temporal Triangle Counting in Streaming with Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-approximate-temporal-triangle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Streaming processing and resource efficiency are crucial requirements for counting triangles in modern massive temporal graphs, with millions of nodes and up to billions of temporal edges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-approximate-temporal-triangle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlearning Isn't Invisible: Detecting Unlearning Traces in LLMs from Model Outputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlearning-isn-t-invisible-detecting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These traces can be identified from output responses, even when prompted with forget-irrelevant inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlearning-isn-t-invisible-detecting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sketched Sum-Product Networks for Joins</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sketched-sum-product-networks-for-joins</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By representing these univariate distributions as sketches, Sum-Product Networks can combine them element-wise to efficiently approximate the sketch of any query selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sketched-sum-product-networks-for-joins</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Density-aware Walks for Coordinated Campaign Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/density-aware-walks-for-coordinated-campaign</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings demonstrate that incorporating density-aware structural encoding with MPNNs provides a robust framework for identifying coordinated inauthentic behavior on social media networks such as Twitter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/density-aware-walks-for-coordinated-campaign</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rectifying Privacy and Efficacy Measurements in Machine Unlearning: A New Inference Attack Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rectifying-privacy-and-efficacy-measurements</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we first identify several key pitfalls of the existing unlearning evaluation frameworks, e. g., focusing on average-case evaluation or targeting random samples for evaluation, incomplete comparisons with the retraining baseline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rectifying-privacy-and-efficacy-measurements</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperPoint-SLAM3: Augmenting ORB-SLAM3 with Deep Features, Adaptive NMS, and Learning-Based Loop Closure</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superpoint-slam3-augmenting-orb-slam3-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual simultaneous localization and mapping (SLAM) must remain accurate under extreme viewpoint, scale and illumination variations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superpoint-slam3-augmenting-orb-slam3-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lecture Video Visual Objects (LVVO) Dataset: A Benchmark for Visual Object Detection in Educational Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lecture-video-visual-objects-lvvo-dataset-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Lecture Video Visual Objects (LVVO) dataset, a new benchmark for visual object detection in educational video content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lecture-video-visual-objects-lvvo-dataset-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stream-Omni: Simultaneous Multimodal Interactions with Large Language-Vision-Speech Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stream-omni-simultaneous-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emergence of GPT-4o-like large multimodal models (LMMs) has raised the exploration of integrating text, vision, and speech modalities to support more flexible multimodal interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stream-omni-simultaneous-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoVLA: A Vision-Language-Action Model for End-to-End Autonomous Driving with Adaptive Reasoning and Reinforcement Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autovla-a-vision-language-action-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in Vision-Language-Action (VLA) models have shown promise for end-to-end autonomous driving by leveraging world knowledge and reasoning capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autovla-a-vision-language-action-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on World Models Grounded in Acoustic Physical Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-world-models-grounded-in-acoustic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This survey provides a comprehensive overview of the emerging field of world models grounded in the foundation of acoustic physical information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-world-models-grounded-in-acoustic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DETRPose: Real-time end-to-end transformer model for multi-person pose estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detrpose-real-time-end-to-end-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper presents a family of transformer-based models capable of performing multi-person 2D pose estimation in real-time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detrpose-real-time-end-to-end-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SatHealth: A Multimodal Public Health Dataset with Satellite-based Environmental Factors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sathealth-a-multimodal-public-health-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Living environments play a vital role in the prevalence and progression of diseases, and understanding their impact on patient's health status becomes increasingly crucial for developing AI models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sathealth-a-multimodal-public-health-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arctic Long Sequence Training: Scalable And Efficient Training For Multi-Million Token Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arctic-long-sequence-training-scalable-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ALST supports training Meta's Llama 8B model with 500K sequence length on a single H100 GPU, 3. 7M on a single 8xH100 GPU node, and over 15M on a 4 node cluster, an increase of over 400x compared to the 32K baseline for the latter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arctic-long-sequence-training-scalable-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAGDA: Open-Source Synthetic Agriculture Data for Africa</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sagda-open-source-synthetic-agriculture-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data scarcity in African agriculture hampers machine learning (ML) model performance, limiting innovations in precision agriculture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sagda-open-source-synthetic-agriculture-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalizable Long-Context Symbolic Music Infilling with MIDI-RWKV</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalizable-long-context-symbolic-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing work in automatic music generation has primarily focused on end-to-end systems that produce complete compositions or continuations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalizable-long-context-symbolic-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIS-Shepherd: Constructing Critic for LLM-based Data Visualization Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vis-shepherd-constructing-critic-for-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data visualization generation using Large Language Models (LLMs) has shown promising results but often produces suboptimal visualizations that require human intervention for improvement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vis-shepherd-constructing-critic-for-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verifying the Verifiers: Unveiling Pitfalls and Potentials in Fact Verifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifying-the-verifiers-unveiling-pitfalls</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we evaluate 12 pre-trained LLMs and one specialized fact-verifier, including frontier LLMs and open-weight reasoning LLMs, using a collection of examples from 14 fact-checking benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifying-the-verifiers-unveiling-pitfalls</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextureSplat: Per-Primitive Texture Mapping for Reflective Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texturesplat-per-primitive-texture-mapping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gaussian Splatting have demonstrated remarkable novel view synthesis performance at high rendering frame rates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texturesplat-per-primitive-texture-mapping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tady: A Neural Disassembler without Structural Constraint Violations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tady-a-neural-disassembler-without-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Disassembly is a crucial yet challenging step in binary analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tady-a-neural-disassembler-without-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CertDW: Towards Certified Dataset Ownership Verification via Conformal Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certdw-towards-certified-dataset-ownership</link>
      <description><![CDATA[If the number of PP values smaller than WR exceeds a threshold, the suspicious model is regarded as having been trained on the protected dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certdw-towards-certified-dataset-ownership</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent Capability Negotiation and Binding Protocol (ACNBP)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-capability-negotiation-and-binding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As multi-agent systems evolve to encompass increasingly diverse and specialized agents, the challenge of enabling effective collaboration between heterogeneous agents has become paramount, with traditional agent communication protocols often assuming homogeneous environments or predefined interaction patterns that limit their applicability in dynamic, open-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-capability-negotiation-and-binding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoIFNet: A Unified Framework for Multivariate Time Series Forecasting with Missing Values</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coifnet-a-unified-framework-for-multivariate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multivariate time series forecasting (MTSF) is a critical task with broad applications in domains such as meteorology, transportation, and economics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coifnet-a-unified-framework-for-multivariate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BeyondRPC: A Contrastive and Augmentation-Driven Framework for Robust Point Cloud Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyondrpc-a-contrastive-and-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust perception of 3D point clouds remains a significant challenge in real-world environments where sensor data is often corrupted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyondrpc-a-contrastive-and-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoundMind: RL-Incentivized Logic Reasoning for Audio-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soundmind-rl-incentivized-logic-reasoning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While large language models have shown reasoning capabilities, their application to the audio modality, particularly in large audio-language models (ALMs), remains significantly underdeveloped.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soundmind-rl-incentivized-logic-reasoning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Review of the Long Horizon Forecasting Problem in Time Series Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-the-long-horizon-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The long horizon forecasting (LHF) problem has come up in the time series literature for over the last 35 years or so.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-the-long-horizon-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
