<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 09:11:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Learning a Practical SDR-to-HDRTV Up-conversion using New Dataset and Degradation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-practical-sdr-to-hdrtv-up</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In media industry, the demand of SDR-to-HDRTV up-conversion arises when users possess HDR-WCG (high dynamic range-wide color gamut) TVs while most off-the-shelf footage is still in SDR (standard dynamic range).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-practical-sdr-to-hdrtv-up</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Generalization against Photon-Limited Corruptions via Worst-Case Sharpness Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-generalization-against-photon-limited</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimentally, we simulate photon-limited corruptions using CIFAR10/100 and ImageNet30 datasets and show that SharpDRO exhibits a strong generalization ability against severe corruptions and exceeds well-known baseline methods with large performance gains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-generalization-against-photon-limited</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Image Training for Generalizable Deep Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-image-training-for-generalizable-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we present a novel approach to enhance the generalization performance of denoising networks, known as masked training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-image-training-for-generalizable-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-Augmented Classification with Decoupled Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-classification-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct extensive experiments on various Chinese NLP tasks to evaluate existing PLMs as well as the proposed MigBERT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-classification-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human Guided Ground-truth Generation for Realistic Image Super-resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-guided-ground-truth-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A human guided GT image dataset with both positive and negative samples is then constructed, and a loss function is proposed to train the Real-ISR models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-guided-ground-truth-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MELTR: Meta Loss Transformer for Learning to Fine-tune Video Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meltr-meta-loss-transformer-for-learning-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose MEta Loss TRansformer (MELTR), a plug-in module that automatically and non-linearly combines various loss functions to aid learning the target task via auxiliary learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meltr-meta-loss-transformer-for-learning-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calibrated Out-of-Distribution Detection with a Generic Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrated-out-of-distribution-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we take a different approach and propose to leverage generic pre-trained representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrated-out-of-distribution-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complementary Pseudo Multimodal Feature for Point Cloud Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complementary-pseudo-multimodal-feature-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The 3D and 2D modality features are aggregated to obtain the CPMF for PCD anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complementary-pseudo-multimodal-feature-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D-POP - An automated annotation approach to facilitate markerless 2D-3D tracking of freely moving birds with marker-based motion capture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-pop-an-automated-annotation-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in machine learning and computer vision are revolutionizing the field of animal behavior by enabling researchers to track the poses and locations of freely moving animals without any marker attachment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-pop-an-automated-annotation-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAPS3D: Text-Guided 3D Textured Shape Generation from Pseudo Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taps3d-text-guided-3d-textured-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct extensive experiments to analyze each of our proposed components and show the efficacy of our framework in generating high-fidelity 3D textured and text-relevant shapes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taps3d-text-guided-3d-textured-shape</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrOC: Cross-View Online Clustering for Dense Visual Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/croc-cross-view-online-clustering-for-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More importantly, the clustering algorithm conjointly operates on the features of both views, thereby elegantly bypassing the issue of content not represented in both views and the ambiguous matching of objects from one crop to the other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/croc-cross-view-online-clustering-for-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plug-and-Play Regulators for Image-Text Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-regulators-for-image-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Exploiting fine-grained correspondence and visual-semantic alignments has shown great potential in image-text matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-regulators-for-image-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RLOR: A Flexible Framework of Deep Reinforcement Learning for Operation Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlor-a-flexible-framework-of-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we analyze the end-to-end autoregressive models for vehicle routing problems and show that these models can benefit from the recent advances in reinforcement learning with a careful re-implementation of the model architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlor-a-flexible-framework-of-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalization with quantum geometry for learning unitaries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalization-with-quantum-geometry-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalization is the ability of quantum machine learning models to make accurate predictions on new data by learning from training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalization-with-quantum-geometry-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinically Relevant Latent Space Embedding of Cancer Histopathology Slides through Variational Autoencoder Based Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clinically-relevant-latent-space-embedding-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We generate and visualize embeddings from the compressed latent space and demonstrate how they are useful for clinical interpretation of data, and how in the future such latent embeddings can be used to accelerate search of clinical imaging data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clinically-relevant-latent-space-embedding-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual-Language Prompt Tuning with Knowledge-guided Context Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-language-prompt-tuning-with-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representative CoOp-based work combines the learnable textual tokens with the class tokens to obtain specific textual knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-language-prompt-tuning-with-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backdoor Defense via Adaptively Splitting Poisoned Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backdoor-defense-via-adaptively-splitting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the split clean data pool and polluted data pool, ASD successfully defends against backdoor attacks during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backdoor-defense-via-adaptively-splitting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frame-Level Multi-Label Playing Technique Detection Using Multi-Scale Network and Self-Attention Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frame-level-multi-label-playing-technique</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instrument playing technique (IPT) is a key element of musical presentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frame-level-multi-label-playing-technique</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimization Dynamics of Equivariant and Augmented Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-dynamics-of-equivariant-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the optimization of multilayer perceptrons on symmetric data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-dynamics-of-equivariant-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter-Efficient Sparse Retrievers and Rerankers using Adapters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-sparse-retrievers-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While previous studies have only experimented with dense retriever or in a cross lingual retrieval scenario, in this paper we aim to complete the picture on the use of adapters in IR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-sparse-retrievers-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Knowledge Distillation to Self-Knowledge Distillation: A Unified Approach with Normalized Loss and Customized Soft Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-knowledge-distillation-to-self-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We decompose the KD loss and find the non-target loss from it forces the student's non-target logits to match the teacher's, but the sum of the two non-target logits is different, preventing them from being identical.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-knowledge-distillation-to-self-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScanERU: Interactive 3D Visual Grounding based on Embodied Reference Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaneru-interactive-3d-visual-grounding-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their effectiveness, existing methods suffer from the difficulty of low recognition accuracy in cases of multiple adjacent objects with similar appearances. To address this issue, this work intuitively introduces the human-robot interaction as a cue to facilitate the development of 3D visual grounding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaneru-interactive-3d-visual-grounding-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIEDOB: Semantic Image Editing by Disentangling Object and Background</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siedob-semantic-image-editing-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, to produce high-quality edited images, we propose some innovative designs, including Semantic-Aware Self-Propagation Module, Boundary-Anchored Patch Discriminator, and Style-Diversity Object Generator, and integrate them into SIEDOB.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siedob-semantic-image-editing-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orthogonal Annotation Benefits Barely-supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orthogonal-annotation-benefits-barely</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, by introducing unlabeled volumes, we propose a dual-network paradigm named Dense-Sparse Co-training (DeSCO) that exploits dense pseudo labels in early stage and sparse labels in later stage and meanwhile forces consistent output of two networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orthogonal-annotation-benefits-barely</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keypoint-Guided Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/keypoint-guided-optimal-transport</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel KeyPoint-Guided model by ReLation preservation (KPG-RL) that searches for the optimal matching (i. e., transport plan) guided by the keypoints in OT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/keypoint-guided-optimal-transport</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENVIDR: Implicit Differentiable Renderer with Neural Environment Lighting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/envidr-implicit-differentiable-renderer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce ENVIDR, a rendering and modeling framework for high-quality rendering and reconstruction of surfaces with challenging specular reflections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/envidr-implicit-differentiable-renderer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is ChatGPT A Good Keyphrase Generator? A Preliminary Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-chatgpt-a-good-keyphrase-generator-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our findings, we conclude that ChatGPT has great potential for keyphrase generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-chatgpt-a-good-keyphrase-generator-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Preset for Color Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-preset-for-color-style-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a Neural Preset technique to address the limitations of existing color style transfer methods, including visual artifacts, vast memory requirement, and slow style switching speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-preset-for-color-style-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SwissBERT: The Multilingual Language Model for Switzerland</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swissbert-the-multilingual-language-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SwissBERT, a masked language model created specifically for processing Switzerland-related text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swissbert-the-multilingual-language-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Framework for Learned Sparse Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-framework-for-learned-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then reproduce all prominent methods using a common codebase and re-train them in the same environment, which allows us to quantify how components of the framework affect effectiveness and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-framework-for-learned-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paraphrasing evades detectors of AI-generated text, but retrieval is an effective defense</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paraphrasing-evades-detectors-of-ai-generated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To increase the robustness of AI-generated text detection to paraphrase attacks, we introduce a simple defense that relies on retrieving semantically-similar generations and must be maintained by a language model API provider.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paraphrasing-evades-detectors-of-ai-generated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DARE-GRAM : Unsupervised Domain Adaptation Regression by Aligning Inverse Gram Matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dare-gram-unsupervised-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised Domain Adaptation Regression (DAR) aims to bridge the domain gap between a labeled source dataset and an unlabelled target dataset for regression problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dare-gram-unsupervised-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Deep Probabilistic Approach for Partial Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-deep-probabilistic-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep point cloud registration methods face challenges to partial overlaps and rely on labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-deep-probabilistic-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Historical Learning: Learning Models with Learning History</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-historical-learning-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The various types of elements, deposited in the training history, are a large amount of wealth for improving learning deep models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-historical-learning-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Better Dynamic Graph Learning: New Architecture and Unified Library</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-dynamic-graph-learning-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose DyGFormer, a new Transformer-based architecture for dynamic graph learning that solely learns from the sequences of nodes' historical first-hop interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-dynamic-graph-learning-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Position-Guided Point Cloud Panoptic Segmentation Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-guided-point-cloud-panoptic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DEtection TRansformer (DETR) started a trend that uses a group of learnable queries for unified visual perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-guided-point-cloud-panoptic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness-guided Few-shot Prompting for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-guided-few-shot-prompting-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models have demonstrated surprising ability to perform in-context learning, i. e., these models can be directly applied to solve numerous downstream tasks by conditioning on a prompt constructed by a few input-output examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-guided-few-shot-prompting-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Indeterminate Probability Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-indeterminate-probability-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Third, we propose a new method to visualize the latent random variables, we use one of N dimensional latent variables as a decoder to reconstruct the input image, which can work even for classification tasks, in this way, we can see what each latent variable has learned.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-indeterminate-probability-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReVersion: Diffusion-Based Relation Inversion from Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reversion-diffusion-based-relation-inversion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a novel relation-steering contrastive learning scheme to impose two critical properties of the relation prompt: 1) The relation prompt should capture the interaction between objects, enforced by the preposition prior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reversion-diffusion-based-relation-inversion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MV-JAR: Masked Voxel Jigsaw and Reconstruction for LiDAR-Based Self-Supervised Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mv-jar-masked-voxel-jigsaw-and-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the Masked Voxel Jigsaw and Reconstruction (MV-JAR) method for LiDAR-based self-supervised pre-training and a carefully designed data-efficient 3D object detection benchmark on the Waymo dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mv-jar-masked-voxel-jigsaw-and-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning Goals for Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planning-goals-for-exploration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address this question within the goal-conditioned reinforcement learning paradigm, by identifying how the agent should set its goals at training time to maximize exploration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planning-goals-for-exploration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egocentric Audio-Visual Object Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egocentric-audio-visual-object-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore the challenging egocentric audio-visual object localization task and observe that 1) egomotion commonly exists in first-person recordings, even within a short duration; 2) The out-of-view sound components can be created while wearers shift their attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egocentric-audio-visual-object-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text2Video-Zero: Text-to-Image Diffusion Models are Zero-Shot Video Generators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2video-zero-text-to-image-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent text-to-video generation approaches rely on computationally heavy training and require large-scale video datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2video-zero-text-to-image-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ablating Concepts in Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ablating-concepts-in-text-to-image-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this goal, we propose an efficient method of ablating concepts in the pretrained model, i. e., preventing the generation of a target concept.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ablating-concepts-in-text-to-image-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large-scale Study of Spatiotemporal Representation Learning with a New Benchmark on Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-study-of-spatiotemporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of building a benchmark (suite of datasets) is to provide a unified protocol for fair evaluation and thus facilitate the evolution of a specific area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-study-of-spatiotemporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LSTM-based Video Quality Prediction Accounting for Temporal Distortions in Videoconferencing Calls</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lstm-based-video-quality-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using these features together with VMAF core features, our proposed model achieves a PCC of 0. 99 on the validation set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lstm-based-video-quality-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Oblivious Chase Termination for Linear Existential Rules: An Experimental Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-oblivious-chase-termination-for-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we focus on the semi-oblivious version of the chase, which is well-suited for practical implementations, and linear existential rules, a central class of constraints with several applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-oblivious-chase-termination-for-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Reasoning in the Presence of Latent Confounders via Neural ADMG Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-reasoning-in-the-presence-of-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we further extend the existing body of work and develop a novel gradient-based approach to learning an ADMG with non-linear functional relations from observational data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-reasoning-in-the-presence-of-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XWikiGen: Cross-lingual Summarization for Encyclopedic Text Generation in Low Resource Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xwikigen-cross-lingual-summarization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[But, for low-resource languages, the scarcity of reference articles makes monolingual summarization ineffective in solving this problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xwikigen-cross-lingual-summarization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Video Representation Learning with Unaligned Text for Sequential Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-video-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sequential video understanding, as an emerging video understanding task, has driven lots of researchers' attention because of its goal-oriented nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-video-representation</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
