<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:08:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Segment Anything Model for Source-Free Domain Adaptation via Dual Feature Guided Auto-Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-segment-anything-model-for-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Source-free domain adaptation (SFDA) for segmentation aims at adapting a model trained in the source domain to perform well in the target domain with only the source model and unlabeled target data. Inspired by the recent success of Segment Anything Model (SAM) which exhibits the generality of segmenting images of various modalities and in different domains given human-annotated prompts like bounding boxes or points, we for the first time explore the potentials of Segment Anything Model for SFDA via automatedly finding an accurate bounding box prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-segment-anything-model-for-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judging the Judges: Can Large Vision-Language Models Fairly Evaluate Chart Comprehension and Reasoning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/judging-the-judges-can-large-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While using LVLMs as judges to assess the chart comprehension capabilities of other LVLMs could streamline evaluation processes, challenges like proprietary datasets, restricted access to powerful models, and evaluation costs hinder their adoption in industrial settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/judging-the-judges-can-large-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IrrMap: A Large-Scale Comprehensive Dataset for Irrigation Method Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irrmap-a-large-scale-comprehensive-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce IrrMap, the first large-scale dataset (1. 1 million patches) for irrigation method mapping across regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irrmap-a-large-scale-comprehensive-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepMath-Creative: A Benchmark for Evaluating Mathematical Creativity of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepmath-creative-a-benchmark-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we propose an evaluation criteria for mathematical creativity and introduce DeepMath-Creative, a novel, high-quality benchmark comprising constructive problems across algebra, geometry, analysis, and other domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepmath-creative-a-benchmark-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large-Scale Empirical Analysis of Custom GPTs' Vulnerabilities in the OpenAI Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-empirical-analysis-of-custom</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we analyze 14, 904 custom GPTs to assess their susceptibility to seven exploitable threats, such as roleplay-based attacks, system prompt leakage, phishing content generation, and malicious code synthesis, across various categories and popularity tiers within the OpenAI marketplace.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-empirical-analysis-of-custom</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skeleton-Guided Diffusion Model for Accurate Foot X-ray Synthesis in Hallux Valgus Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-guided-diffusion-model-for-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image synthesis plays a crucial role in providing anatomically accurate images for diagnosis and treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-guided-diffusion-model-for-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Removing Watermarks with Partial Regeneration using Semantic Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/removing-watermarks-with-partial-regeneration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As AI-generated imagery becomes ubiquitous, invisible watermarks have emerged as a primary line of defense for copyright and provenance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/removing-watermarks-with-partial-regeneration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TiMo: Spatiotemporal Foundation Model for Satellite Image Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timo-spatiotemporal-foundation-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Satellite image time series (SITS) provide continuous observations of the Earth's surface, making them essential for applications such as environmental management and disaster assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timo-spatiotemporal-foundation-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Out-of-Distribution Detection in Medical Imaging Using Multi-Exit Class Activation Maps and Feature Masking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-out-of-distribution-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings emphasize the potential of multi-exit networks and feature masking for advancing unsupervised OOD detection in medical imaging, paving the way for more reliable and interpretable models in clinical practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-out-of-distribution-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Fitted Online Conformal Prediction for Deep Time Series Forecasting Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-fitted-online-conformal-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series forecasting is critical for many applications, where deep learning-based point prediction models have demonstrated strong performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-fitted-online-conformal-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foundation Models Knowledge Distillation For Battery Capacity Degradation Forecast</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-models-knowledge-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate estimation of lithium-ion battery capacity degradation is critical for enhancing the reliability and safety of battery operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-models-knowledge-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rejoining fragmented ancient bamboo slips with physics-driven deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rejoining-fragmented-ancient-bamboo-slips</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach enables the training of a matching network without requiring manually paired samples, providing ranked suggestions to facilitate the rejoining process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rejoining-fragmented-ancient-bamboo-slips</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSurgSAM2: Referring Segment Anything in Surgical Video via Credible Long-term Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resurgsam2-referring-segment-anything-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce ReSurgSAM2, a two-stage surgical referring segmentation framework that leverages Segment Anything Model 2 to perform text-referred target detection, followed by tracking with reliable initial frame identification and diversity-driven long-term memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resurgsam2-referring-segment-anything-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thermal Detection of People with Mobility Restrictions for Barrier Reduction at Traffic Lights Controlled Intersections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermal-detection-of-people-with-mobility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we build the thermal dataset for people with mobility restrictions (TD4PWMR), designed to capture diverse pedestrian scenarios, particularly focusing on individuals with mobility aids or mobility burden under varying environmental conditions, such as different lighting, weather, and crowded urban settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermal-detection-of-people-with-mobility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking AI scientists in omics data-driven biological research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-ai-scientists-in-omics-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise of large language models and multi-agent systems has sparked growing interest in AI scientists capable of autonomous biological research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-ai-scientists-in-omics-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAT: Benchmark for Auto-bidding Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bat-benchmark-for-auto-bidding-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The optimization of bidding strategies for online advertising slot auctions presents a critical challenge across numerous digital marketplaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bat-benchmark-for-auto-bidding-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HealthBench: Evaluating Large Language Models Towards Improved Human Health</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/healthbench-evaluating-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present HealthBench, an open-source benchmark measuring the performance and safety of large language models in healthcare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/healthbench-evaluating-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model Psychometrics: A Systematic Review of Evaluation, Validation, and Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-psychometrics-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of large language models (LLMs) has outpaced traditional evaluation methodologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-psychometrics-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TT-DF: A Large-Scale Diffusion-Based Dataset and Benchmark for Human Body Forgery Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tt-df-a-large-scale-diffusion-based-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, when it comes to human body forgery, there has been a persistent lack of datasets and detection methods, due to the later inception and complexity of human body generation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tt-df-a-large-scale-diffusion-based-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Foundation Models for Experimental Readout Systems Combining Discrete and Continuous Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-foundation-models-for-experimental</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a (proto) Foundation Model for Nuclear Physics, capable of operating on low-level detector inputs from Imaging Cherenkov Detectors at the future Electron Ion Collider.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-foundation-models-for-experimental</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VCRBench: Exploring Long-form Causal Reasoning Capabilities of Large Video Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vcrbench-exploring-long-form-causal-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advances in video understanding, the capabilities of Large Video Language Models (LVLMs) to perform video-based causal reasoning remains underexplored, largely due to the absence of relevant and dedicated benchmarks for evaluating causal reasoning in visually grounded and goal-driven settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vcrbench-exploring-long-form-causal-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Unsupervised Task-driven Models of Ventral Visual Stream via Relative Position Predictivity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-unsupervised-task-driven-models-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the concept that ventral visual stream (VVS) mainly functions for object recognition, current unsupervised task-driven methods model VVS by contrastive learning, and have achieved good brain similarity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-unsupervised-task-driven-models-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implet: A Post-hoc Subsequence Explainer for Time Series Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implet-a-post-hoc-subsequence-explainer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Explainability in time series models is crucial for fostering trust, facilitating debugging, and ensuring interpretability in real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implet-a-post-hoc-subsequence-explainer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensitivity-Constrained Fourier Neural Operators for Forward and Inverse Problems in Parametric Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensitivity-constrained-fourier-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These gains are achieved with a modest increase in training time (30% to 130% per epoch) and generalize across various types of differential equations and neural operators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensitivity-constrained-fourier-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADC-GS: Anchor-Driven Deformable and Compressed Gaussian Splatting for Dynamic Scene Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adc-gs-anchor-driven-deformable-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing 4D Gaussian Splatting methods rely on per-Gaussian deformation from a canonical space to target frames, which overlooks redundancy among adjacent Gaussian primitives and results in suboptimal performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adc-gs-anchor-driven-deformable-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models for Computer-Aided Design: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-computer-aided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have seen rapid advancements in recent years, with models like ChatGPT and DeepSeek, showcasing their remarkable capabilities across diverse domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-computer-aided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HMPNet: A Feature Aggregation Architecture for Maritime Object Detection from a Shipborne Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hmpnet-a-feature-aggregation-architecture-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based upon this dataset, we propose HMPNet, a lightweight architecture tailored for shipborne object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hmpnet-a-feature-aggregation-architecture-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALPCAH: Subspace Learning for Sample-wise Heteroscedastic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpcah-subspace-learning-for-sample-wise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper develops a subspace learning method, named ALPCAH, that can estimate the sample-wise noise variances and use this information to improve the estimate of the subspace basis associated with the low-rank structure of the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpcah-subspace-learning-for-sample-wise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Kernel Configurations at Scale: A Dataset for Performance and Evolution Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linux-kernel-configurations-at-scale-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Configuring the Linux kernel to meet specific requirements, such as binary size, is highly challenging due to its immense complexity-with over 15, 000 interdependent options evolving rapidly across different versions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linux-kernel-configurations-at-scale-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-training vs. Fine-tuning: A Reproducibility Study on Dense Retrieval Knowledge Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-vs-fine-tuning-a-reproducibility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research has questioned the role of fine-tuning vs. that of pre-training within dense retrievers, specifically arguing that retrieval knowledge is primarily gained during pre-training, meaning knowledge not acquired during pre-training cannot be sub-sequentially acquired via fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-vs-fine-tuning-a-reproducibility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cache-Efficient Posterior Sampling for Reinforcement Learning with LLM-Derived Priors Across Discrete and Continuous Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cache-efficient-posterior-sampling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Integrating large language models (LLMs) as priors in reinforcement learning (RL) offers significant advantages but comes with substantial computational costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cache-efficient-posterior-sampling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Actionable Pedagogical Feedback: A Multi-Perspective Analysis of Mathematics Teaching and Tutoring Dialogue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-actionable-pedagogical-feedback-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Effective feedback is essential for refining instructional practices in mathematics education, and researchers often turn to advanced natural language processing (NLP) models to analyze classroom dialogues from multiple perspectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-actionable-pedagogical-feedback-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web-Bench: A LLM Code Benchmark Based on Web Standards and Frameworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/web-bench-a-llm-code-benchmark-based-on-web</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Among various attempts to address benchmark saturation, approaches based on software engineering have stood out, but the saturation of existing software engineering benchmarks is rapidly increasing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/web-bench-a-llm-code-benchmark-based-on-web</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Codifying Character Logic in Role-Playing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codifying-character-logic-in-role-playing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces Codified Profiles for role-playing, a novel approach that represents character logic as structured, executable functions for behavioral decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codifying-character-logic-in-role-playing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topology-Guided Knowledge Distillation for Efficient Point Cloud Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-guided-knowledge-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results in the Nuscenes, SemanticKITTI, and Waymo datasets demonstrate that the proposed method achieves competitive performance, with an approximately 16x reduction in model size and a nearly 1. 9x decrease in inference time compared to its teacher model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-guided-knowledge-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From raw affiliations to organization identifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-raw-affiliations-to-organization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate affiliation matching, which links affiliation strings to standardized organization identifiers, is critical for improving research metadata quality, facilitating comprehensive bibliometric analyses, and supporting data interoperability across scholarly knowledge bases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-raw-affiliations-to-organization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metrics that matter: Evaluating image quality metrics for medical image generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metrics-that-matter-evaluating-image-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating generative models for synthetic medical imaging is crucial yet challenging, especially given the high standards of fidelity, anatomical accuracy, and safety required for clinical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metrics-that-matter-evaluating-image-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-Driven Dual Style Mixing for Single-Domain Generalized Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-driven-dual-style-mixing-for-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we propose image-level style mixing between the diversified images and source domain images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-driven-dual-style-mixing-for-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Global-Local Feature Matching via Anomaly Synthesis for Multi-Class Point Cloud Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-global-local-feature-matching-via-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, GLFM is structured into three stages: Stage-I proposes an anomaly synthesis pipeline that stretches point clouds to create abundant anomaly data that are utilized to adapt the point cloud feature extractor for better feature representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-global-local-feature-matching-via-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Only Look One Step: Accelerating Backpropagation in Diffusion Sampling with Gradient Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-look-one-step-accelerating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, many downstream tasks require guiding the generated content based on specific differentiable metrics, typically necessitating backpropagation during the generation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-look-one-step-accelerating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-Based Floor Separation Using Node Embeddings and Clustering of WiFi Trajectories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-floor-separation-using-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Indoor positioning systems (IPSs) are increasingly vital for location-based services in complex multi-storey environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-floor-separation-using-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are LLMs complicated ethical dilemma analyzers?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-llms-complicated-ethical-dilemma</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also collect non-expert human responses for comparison, limited to the Key Factors section due to their brevity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-llms-complicated-ethical-dilemma</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Visual Autoregressive Generation via Score Maximization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-visual-autoregressive-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When applied to continuous modalities such as visual data, Visual AutoRegressive modeling (VAR) typically resorts to quantization-based approaches to cast the data into a discrete space, which can introduce significant information loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-visual-autoregressive-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anatomical Attention Alignment representation for Radiology Report Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomical-attention-alignment-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated Radiology report generation (RRG) aims at producing detailed descriptions of medical images, reducing radiologists' workload and improving access to high-quality diagnostic services.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomical-attention-alignment-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair Play for Individuals, Foul Play for Groups? Auditing Anonymization's Impact on ML Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-play-for-individuals-foul-play-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning (ML) algorithms are heavily based on the availability of training data, which, depending on the domain, often includes sensitive information about data providers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-play-for-individuals-foul-play-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skull stripping with purely synthetic data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skull-stripping-with-purely-synthetic-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While many skull stripping algorithms have been developed for multi-modal and multi-species cases, there is still a lack of a fundamentally generalizable approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skull-stripping-with-purely-synthetic-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABS-Mamba: SAM2-Driven Bidirectional Spiral Mamba Network for Medical Image Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abs-mamba-sam2-driven-bidirectional-spiral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate multi-modal medical image translation requires ha-rmonizing global anatomical semantics and local structural fidelity, a challenge complicated by intermodality information loss and structural distortion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abs-mamba-sam2-driven-bidirectional-spiral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ophora: A Large-Scale Data-Driven Text-Guided Ophthalmic Surgical Video Generation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ophora-a-large-scale-data-driven-text-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In ophthalmic surgery, developing an AI system capable of interpreting surgical videos and predicting subsequent operations requires numerous ophthalmic surgical videos with high-quality annotations, which are difficult to collect due to privacy concerns and labor consumption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ophora-a-large-scale-data-driven-text-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCPCA: Fuzzy clustering of high-dimensional time series based on common principal component analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fcpca-fuzzy-clustering-of-high-dimensional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clustering multivariate time series data is a crucial task in many domains, as it enables the identification of meaningful patterns and groups in time-evolving data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fcpca-fuzzy-clustering-of-high-dimensional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLUXSynID: A Framework for Identity-Controlled Synthetic Face Generation with Document and Live Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fluxsynid-a-framework-for-identity-controlled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce FLUXSynID, a framework for generating high-resolution synthetic face datasets with user-defined identity attribute distributions and paired document-style and trusted live capture images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fluxsynid-a-framework-for-identity-controlled</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
