<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:09:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Contextualization with SPLADE for High Recall Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextualization-with-splade-for-high-recall</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High Recall Retrieval (HRR), such as eDiscovery and medical systematic review, is a search problem that optimizes the cost of retrieving most relevant documents in a given collection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextualization-with-splade-for-high-recall</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CleanGraph: Human-in-the-loop Knowledge Graph Refinement and Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cleangraph-human-in-the-loop-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CleanGraph allows users to perform Create, Read, Update, and Delete (CRUD) operations on their graphs, as well as apply models in the form of plugins for graph refinement and completion tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cleangraph-human-in-the-loop-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Exact Retrieval for Nearest-neighbor Lookup (FERN)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-exact-retrieval-for-nearest-neighbor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately the algorithm deteriorates rapidly to a $O(dN)$ solution at high dimensions (e. g. $k=128$), in practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-exact-retrieval-for-nearest-neighbor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Chemical Space with Latent Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-chemical-space-with-latent-flows</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new framework, ChemFlow, to traverse chemical space through navigating the latent space learned by molecule generative models through flows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-chemical-space-with-latent-flows</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidirectional Adversarial Autoencoders for the design of Plasmonic Metasurfaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-adversarial-autoencoders-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An example of this is the design of photonic metasurfaces by using their photoluminescent spectrum as the input data to predict their topology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-adversarial-autoencoders-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LTLDoG: Satisfying Temporally-Extended Symbolic Constraints for Safe Diffusion-based Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ltldog-satisfying-temporally-extended</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Operating effectively in complex environments while complying with specified constraints is crucial for the safe and successful deployment of robots that interact with and operate around people.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ltldog-satisfying-temporally-extended</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Linear Block Error Correction Codes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-linear-block-error-correction-codes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose for the first time a unified encoder-decoder training of binary linear block codes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-linear-block-error-correction-codes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Sharpness-aware Minimization for Molecular Graph Transformer Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-sharpness-aware-minimization-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sharpness-aware minimization (SAM) has received increasing attention in computer vision since it can effectively eliminate the sharp local minima from the training trajectory and mitigate generalization degradation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-sharpness-aware-minimization-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeek-V2: A Strong, Economical, and Efficient Mixture-of-Experts Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseek-v2-a-strong-economical-and-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MLA guarantees efficient inference through significantly compressing the Key-Value (KV) cache into a latent vector, while DeepSeekMoE enables training strong models at an economical cost through sparse computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseek-v2-a-strong-economical-and-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Representation Learning of Daily Movement Data Using Text Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-learning-of-daily-movement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time-series representation learning is a key area of research for remote healthcare monitoring applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-learning-of-daily-movement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning To See But Forgetting To Follow: Visual Instruction Tuning Makes LLMs More Prone To Jailbreak Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-see-but-forgetting-to-follow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Augmenting Large Language Models (LLMs) with image-understanding capabilities has resulted in a boom of high-performing Vision-Language models (VLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-see-but-forgetting-to-follow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inf-DiT: Upsampling Any-Resolution Image with Memory-Efficient Diffusion Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inf-dit-upsampling-any-resolution-image-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to a quadratic increase in memory during generating ultra-high-resolution images (e. g. 4096*4096), the resolution of generated images is often limited to 1024*1024.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inf-dit-upsampling-any-resolution-image-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataset and Models for Item Recommendation Using Multi-Modal User Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-and-models-for-item-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While recommender systems with multi-modal item representations (image, audio, and text), have been widely explored, learning recommendations from multi-modal user interactions (e. g., clicks and speech) remains an open problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-and-models-for-item-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Transformer with Stack Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transformer-with-stack-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Natural languages are believed to be (mildly) context-sensitive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transformer-with-stack-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBK: a simpler, faster algorithm for enumerating maximal bicliques in large sparse bipartite graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bbk-a-simpler-faster-algorithm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also provide an open-access implementation of BBK in C++, which we use to experiment and validate its efficiency on massive real-world datasets and show that its execution time is shorter in practice than state-of-the art algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bbk-a-simpler-faster-algorithm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SwiftRL: Towards Efficient Reinforcement Learning on Real Processing-In-Memory Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swiftrl-towards-efficient-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning (RL) trains agents to learn optimal behavior by maximizing reward signals from experience datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swiftrl-towards-efficient-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy Learning with a Language Bottleneck</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-learning-with-a-language-bottleneck</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern AI systems such as self-driving cars and game-playing agents achieve superhuman performance, but often lack human-like features such as generalization, interpretability and human inter-operability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-learning-with-a-language-bottleneck</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-grained Speech Sentiment Analysis in Chinese Psychological Support Hotlines Based on Large-scale Pre-trained Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-speech-sentiment-analysis-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the high demand for psychological interventions often results in a shortage of professional operators, highlighting the need for an effective speech emotion recognition model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-speech-sentiment-analysis-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Group Fair Classifiers from Linear Post-Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-group-fair-classifiers-from-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a post-processing algorithm for fair classification that mitigates model bias under a unified family of group fairness criteria covering statistical parity, equal opportunity, and equalized odds, applicable to multi-class problems and both attribute-aware and attribute-blind settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-group-fair-classifiers-from-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DocRes: A Generalist Model Toward Unifying Document Image Restoration Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docres-a-generalist-model-toward-unifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This underscores the potential of DocRes across a broader spectrum of document image restoration tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docres-a-generalist-model-toward-unifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Curse of Diversity in Ensemble-Based Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-curse-of-diversity-in-ensemble-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We uncover a surprising phenomenon in deep reinforcement learning: training a diverse ensemble of data-sharing agents -- a well-established exploration strategy -- can significantly impair the performance of the individual ensemble members when compared to standard single-agent training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-curse-of-diversity-in-ensemble-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Feature Vectors from Phonetic Transcriptions in Cross-Linguistic Data Formats</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-feature-vectors-from-phonetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When comparing speech sounds across languages, scholars often make use of feature representations of individual sounds in order to determine fine-grained sound similarities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-feature-vectors-from-phonetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structured Click Control in Transformer-based Interactive Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-click-control-in-transformer-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then the graph nodes will be aggregated to obtain structured interaction features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-click-control-in-transformer-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Mamba: A Comprehensive Survey and Taxonomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-mamba-a-comprehensive-survey-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of deep learning, state space models are used to process sequence data, such as time series analysis, natural language processing (NLP) and video understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-mamba-a-comprehensive-survey-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting character-level adversarial attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-character-level-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial attacks in Natural Language Processing apply perturbations in the character or token levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-character-level-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Private Post-Processing for Fair Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-post-processing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes a differentially private post-processing algorithm for learning fair regressors satisfying statistical parity, addressing privacy concerns of machine learning models trained on sensitive data, as well as fairness concerns of their potential to propagate historical biases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-post-processing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Continual Knowledge Graph Embedding via Incremental Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-continual-knowledge-graph-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the one hand, existing methods usually learn new triples in a random order, destroying the inner structure of new KGs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-continual-knowledge-graph-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDVOC: Vocabulary Adaptation for Fine-tuning Pre-trained Language Models on Medical Text Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medvoc-vocabulary-adaptation-for-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to existing domain adaptation approaches in summarization, MEDVOC treats vocabulary as an optimizable parameter and optimizes the PLM vocabulary based on fragment score conditioned only on the downstream task's reference summaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medvoc-vocabulary-adaptation-for-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predictive Modeling with Temporal Graphical Representation on Electronic Health Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictive-modeling-with-temporal-graphical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An effective representation of a patient's EHR should hierarchically encompass both the temporal relationships between historical visits and medical events, and the inherent structural information within these elements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictive-modeling-with-temporal-graphical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QServe: W4A8KV4 Quantization and System Co-design for Efficient LLM Serving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qserve-w4a8kv4-quantization-and-system-co</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key insight driving QServe is that the efficiency of LLM serving on GPUs is critically influenced by operations on low-throughput CUDA cores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qserve-w4a8kv4-quantization-and-system-co</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acceleration Algorithms in GNNs: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acceleration-algorithms-in-gnns-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the critical challenges, a range of algorithms have been proposed to accelerate training and inference of GNNs, attracting increasing attention from the research community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acceleration-algorithms-in-gnns-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing the Efficiency and Accuracy of Underlying Asset Reviews in Structured Finance: The Application of Multi-agent Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-the-efficiency-and-accuracy-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Structured finance, which involves restructuring diverse assets into securities like MBS, ABS, and CDOs, enhances capital market efficiency but presents significant due diligence challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-the-efficiency-and-accuracy-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How does GPT-2 Predict Acronyms? Extracting and Understanding a Circuit via Mechanistic Interpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-does-gpt-2-predict-acronyms-extracting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discover that the prediction is performed by a circuit composed of 8 attention heads (~5% of the total heads) which we classified in three groups according to their role.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-does-gpt-2-predict-acronyms-extracting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMU-Aided Event-based Stereo Visual Odometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imu-aided-event-based-stereo-visual-odometry</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we improve our previous direct pipeline \textit{Event-based Stereo Visual Odometry} in terms of accuracy and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imu-aided-event-based-stereo-visual-odometry</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granite Code Models: A Family of Open Foundation Models for Code Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/granite-code-models-a-family-of-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Increasingly, code LLMs are being integrated into software development environments to improve the productivity of human programmers, and LLM-based agents are beginning to show promise for handling complex tasks autonomously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/granite-code-models-a-family-of-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Braced Fourier Continuation and Regression for Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/braced-fourier-continuation-and-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Braced Fourier Continuation (BFC) and BFCR algorithms are first outlined, followed by a discussion of the properties of BFCR as well as demonstrations of how BFCR trend lines may be used effectively for anomaly detection both within and at the edges of arbitrary one-dimensional data sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/braced-fourier-continuation-and-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RepVGG-GELAN: Enhanced GELAN with VGG-STYLE ConvNets for Brain Tumour Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repvgg-gelan-enhanced-gelan-with-vgg-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study proposes RepVGG-GELAN, a novel YOLO architecture enhanced with RepVGG, a reparameterized convolutional approach for object detection tasks particularly focusing on brain tumour detection within medical images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repvgg-gelan-enhanced-gelan-with-vgg-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CityLLaVA: Efficient Fine-Tuning for VLMs in City Scenario</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cityllava-efficient-fine-tuning-for-vlms-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the vast and dynamic landscape of urban settings, Traffic Safety Description and Analysis plays a pivotal role in applications ranging from insurance inspection to accident prevention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cityllava-efficient-fine-tuning-for-vlms-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vector Quantization for Recommender Systems: A Review and Outlook</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vector-quantization-for-recommender-systems-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, the survey analyzes the remaining challenges and anticipates future trends in VQ4Rec, including the challenges associated with the training of vector quantization, the opportunities presented by large language models, and emerging trends in multimodal recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vector-quantization-for-recommender-systems-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReCycle: Fast and Efficient Long Time Series Forecasting with Residual Cyclic Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recycle-fast-and-efficient-long-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ReCycle utilizes primary cycle compression to address the computational complexity of the attention mechanism in long time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recycle-fast-and-efficient-long-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGTM: Local-to-Global Text-Driven Human Motion Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgtm-local-to-global-text-driven-human-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce LGTM, a novel Local-to-Global pipeline for Text-to-Motion generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgtm-local-to-global-text-driven-human-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Direct Training High-Performance Deep Spiking Neural Networks: A Review of Theories and Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/direct-training-high-performance-deep-spiking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide a new perspective to summarize the theories and methods for training deep SNNs with high performance in a systematic and comprehensive way, including theory fundamentals, spiking neuron models, advanced SNN models and residual architectures, software frameworks and neuromorphic hardware, applications, and future trends.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/direct-training-high-performance-deep-spiking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PTQ4SAM: Post-Training Quantization for Segment Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptq4sam-post-training-quantization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze its characteristics from both per-tensor and per-channel perspectives, and propose a Bimodal Integration strategy, which utilizes a mathematically equivalent sign operation to transform the bimodal distribution into a relatively easy-quantized normal distribution offline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptq4sam-post-training-quantization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TF4CTR: Twin Focus Framework for CTR Prediction via Adaptive Sample Differentiation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tf4ctr-twin-focus-framework-for-ctr</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the framework employs the SSEM at the bottom of the model to differentiate between samples, thereby assigning a more suitable encoder for each sample.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tf4ctr-twin-focus-framework-for-ctr</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AniTalker: Animate Vivid and Diverse Talking Faces through Identity-Decoupled Facial Motion Encoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anitalker-animate-vivid-and-diverse-talking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper introduces AniTalker, an innovative framework designed to generate lifelike talking faces from a single portrait.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anitalker-animate-vivid-and-diverse-talking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Sora a World Simulator? A Comprehensive Survey on General World Models and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-sora-a-world-simulator-a-comprehensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[General world models represent a crucial pathway toward achieving Artificial General Intelligence (AGI), serving as the cornerstone for various applications ranging from virtual environments to decision-making systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-sora-a-world-simulator-a-comprehensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchored Answers: Unravelling Positional Bias in GPT-2's Multiple-Choice Questions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anchored-answers-unravelling-positional-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By updating these vectors within MLP and recalibrating attention patterns to neutralise the preference for the first choice 'A', we effectively mitigate the anchored bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anchored-answers-unravelling-positional-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D LiDAR Mapping in Dynamic Environments Using a 4D Implicit Neural Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-lidar-mapping-in-dynamic-environments</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel approach for building accurate maps of dynamic environments utilizing a sequence of LiDAR scans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-lidar-mapping-in-dynamic-environments</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Locational Differential Privacy Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-locational-differential-privacy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aggregating statistics over geographical regions is important for many applications, such as analyzing income, election results, and disease spread.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-locational-differential-privacy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequence Compression Speeds Up Credit Assignment in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequence-compression-speeds-up-credit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal credit assignment in reinforcement learning is challenging due to delayed and stochastic outcomes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequence-compression-speeds-up-credit</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
