<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:07:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Collaborative Self-Supervised Learning Method for Radiomic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-collaborative-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compared our proposed method with other state-of-the-art self-supervised learning methods on a simulation study and two independent datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-collaborative-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iQPP: A Benchmark for Image Query Performance Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iqpp-a-benchmark-for-image-query-performance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To date, query performance prediction (QPP) in the context of content-based image retrieval remains a largely unexplored task, especially in the query-by-example scenario, where the query is an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iqpp-a-benchmark-for-image-query-performance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Composer: Creative and Controllable Image Synthesis with Composable Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composer-creative-and-controllable-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent large-scale generative models learned on big data are capable of synthesizing incredible images yet suffer from limited controllability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composer-creative-and-controllable-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing the Posterior Collapse in Hierarchical Variational Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-posterior-collapse-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hierarchical Variational Autoencoders (VAEs) are among the most popular likelihood-based generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-posterior-collapse-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incremental Few-Shot Object Detection via Simple Fine-Tuning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incremental-few-shot-object-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore incremental few-shot object detection (iFSD), which incrementally learns novel classes using only a few examples without revisiting base classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incremental-few-shot-object-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTNet: Human Topology Aware Network for 3D Human Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/htnet-human-topology-aware-network-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D human pose estimation errors would propagate along the human body topology and accumulate at the end joints of limbs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/htnet-human-topology-aware-network-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friend Recall in Online Games via Pre-training Edge Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/friend-recall-in-online-games-via-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Friend recall is an important way to improve Daily Active Users (DAU) in Tencent games.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/friend-recall-in-online-games-via-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query Performance Prediction for Neural IR: Are We There Yet?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-performance-prediction-for-neural-ir</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On top of that, in lexical-oriented scenarios, QPPs fail to predict performance for neural IR systems on those queries where they differ from traditional approaches the most.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-performance-prediction-for-neural-ir</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Semi-Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-semi-supervised-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation is one of the most challenging tasks in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-semi-supervised-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demonstration-Guided Reinforcement Learning with Efficient Exploration for Task Automation of Surgical Robot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demonstration-guided-reinforcement-learning-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Task automation of surgical robot has the potentials to improve surgical efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demonstration-guided-reinforcement-learning-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hashtag-Guided Low-Resource Tweet Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hashtag-guided-low-resource-tweet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Social media classification tasks (e. g., tweet sentiment analysis, tweet stance detection) are challenging because social media posts are typically short, informal, and ambiguous.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hashtag-guided-low-resource-tweet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-domain Compositing with Pretrained Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-compositing-with-pretrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have enabled high-quality, conditional image editing capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-compositing-with-pretrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-scale Multi-Modal Pre-trained Models: A Comprehensive Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-modal-pre-trained-models-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the urgent demand for generalized deep models, many pre-trained big models are proposed, such as BERT, ViT, GPT, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-modal-pre-trained-models-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Because Every Sensor Is Unique, so Is Every Pair: Handling Dynamicity in Traffic Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/because-every-sensor-is-unique-so-is-every</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further analysis also shows that each pair of sensors also has a unique dynamic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/because-every-sensor-is-unique-so-is-every</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metropolis Theorem and Its Applications in Single Image Detail Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metropolis-theorem-and-its-applications-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional image detail enhancement is local filter-based or global filter-based.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metropolis-theorem-and-its-applications-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RecFNO: a resolution-invariant flow and heat field reconstruction method from sparse observations via Fourier neural operator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recfno-a-resolution-invariant-flow-and-heat</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The MLP embedding is propitious to more sparse input, while the others benefit from spatial information preservation and perform better with the increase of observation data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recfno-a-resolution-invariant-flow-and-heat</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can discrete information extraction prompts generalize across language models?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-discrete-information-extraction-prompts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study whether automatically-induced prompts that effectively extract information from a language model can also be used, out-of-the-box, to probe other language models for the same information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-discrete-information-extraction-prompts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMVAE: Causal Meta VAE for Unsupervised Meta-Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmvae-causal-meta-vae-for-unsupervised-meta</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised meta-learning aims to learn the meta knowledge from unlabeled data and rapidly adapt to novel tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmvae-causal-meta-vae-for-unsupervised-meta</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PriSTI: A Conditional Diffusion Framework for Spatiotemporal Imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pristi-a-conditional-diffusion-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed framework provides a conditional feature extraction module first to extract the coarse yet effective spatiotemporal dependencies from conditional information as the global context prior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pristi-a-conditional-diffusion-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nystrom Method for Accurate and Scalable Implicit Differentiation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nystrom-method-for-accurate-and-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The essential difficulty of gradient-based bilevel optimization using implicit differentiation is to estimate the inverse Hessian vector product with respect to neural network parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nystrom-method-for-accurate-and-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Face Video Coding: A Generative Compression Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-face-video-coding-a-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel framework for Interactive Face Video Coding (IFVC), which allows humans to interact with the intrinsic visual representations instead of the signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-face-video-coding-a-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happens before and after: Multi-Event Commonsense in Event Coreference Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-happens-before-and-after-multi-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event coreference models cluster event mentions pertaining to the same real-world event.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-happens-before-and-after-multi-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving User Controlled Table-To-Text Generation Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-user-controlled-table-to-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we study user controlled table-to-text generation where users explore the content in a table by selecting cells and reading a natural language description thereof automatically produce by a natural language generator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-user-controlled-table-to-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escaping limit cycles: Global convergence for constrained nonconvex-nonconcave minimax problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/escaping-limit-cycles-global-convergence-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a new extragradient-type algorithm for a class of nonconvex-nonconcave minimax problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/escaping-limit-cycles-global-convergence-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Asymptotic Optimality: Sequential Unsupervised Regression of Density Ratio for Early Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-asymptotic-optimality-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Theoretically-inspired sequential density ratio estimation (SDRE) algorithms are proposed for the early classification of time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-asymptotic-optimality-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A DNN based Normalized Time-frequency Weighted Criterion for Robust Wideband DoA Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dnn-based-normalized-time-frequency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the best-performing design of T-F weights is criterion-dependent in general.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dnn-based-normalized-time-frequency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Unbounded Machine Unlearning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-unbounded-machine-unlearning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep machine unlearning is the problem of removing the influence of a cohort of data from the weights of a trained deep model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-unbounded-machine-unlearning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerated Video Annotation driven by Deep Detector and Tracker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerated-video-annotation-driven-by-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new annotation method which leverages a combination of a learning-based detector (SSD) and a learning-based tracker (RE$^3$).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerated-video-annotation-driven-by-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Data-Free Quantization as a Zero-Sum Game</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-data-free-quantization-as-a-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[how to generate the samples with desirable adaptability to benefit the quantized network?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-data-free-quantization-as-a-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed Hierarchy Network for Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-hierarchy-network-for-image-restoration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our main proposal is a mixed hierarchy architecture, that progressively recovers contextual information and spatial details from degraded images while we design intra-blocks to reduce system complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-hierarchy-network-for-image-restoration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Deep Kernel Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guided-deep-kernel-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combining Gaussian processes with the expressive power of deep neural networks is commonly done nowadays through deep kernel learning (DKL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guided-deep-kernel-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributional Offline Policy Evaluation with Predictive Error Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-offline-policy-evaluation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our theoretical results, we show that for both finite and infinite horizon discounted settings, FLE can learn distributions that are close to the ground truth under total variation distance and Wasserstein distance, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-offline-policy-evaluation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text Classification in the Wild: a Large-scale Long-tailed Name Normalization Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-classification-in-the-wild-a-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we first collect a large-scale institution name normalization dataset LoT-insts1, which contains over 25k classes that exhibit a naturally long-tailed distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-classification-in-the-wild-a-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Label Learning Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-label-learning-flows-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we develop label learning flows (LLF), a general framework for weakly supervised learning problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-label-learning-flows-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Depth Map Super-resolution: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guided-depth-map-super-resolution-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Guided depth map super-resolution (GDSR), which aims to reconstruct a high-resolution (HR) depth map from a low-resolution (LR) observation with the help of a paired HR color image, is a longstanding and fundamental problem, it has attracted considerable attention from computer vision and image processing communities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guided-depth-map-super-resolution-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SanskritShala: A Neural Sanskrit NLP Toolkit with Web-Based Interface for Pedagogical and Annotation Purposes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sanskritshala-a-neural-sanskrit-nlp-toolkit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a neural Sanskrit Natural Language Processing (NLP) toolkit named SanskritShala (a school of Sanskrit) to facilitate computational linguistic analyses for several tasks such as word segmentation, morphological tagging, dependency parsing, and compound type identification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sanskritshala-a-neural-sanskrit-nlp-toolkit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intent Identification and Entity Extraction for Healthcare Queries in Indic Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intent-identification-and-entity-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scarcity of data and technological limitations for resource-poor languages in developing countries like India poses a threat to the development of sophisticated NLU systems for healthcare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intent-identification-and-entity-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topological Feature Selection: A Graph-Based Filter Feature Selection Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topological-feature-selection-a-graph-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel unsupervised, graph-based filter feature selection technique which exploits the power of topologically constrained network representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topological-feature-selection-a-graph-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Potential of Machine Translation for Generating Named Entity Datasets: A Case Study between Persian and English</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-potential-of-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study focuses on the generation of Persian named entity datasets through the application of machine translation on English datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-potential-of-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Class-Conditional Noise Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-class-conditional-noise-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We solve this problem by introducing a Latent Class-Conditional Noise model (LCCN) to parameterize the noise transition under a Bayesian framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-class-conditional-noise-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human Emotion Knowledge Representation Emerges in Large Language Models and Supports Discrete Emotion Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-emotion-knowledge-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the large language models (LLMs) have been shown to support effective representations of various human conceptual knowledge, the present study further employed artificial neurons in LLMs to investigate the mechanism of human emotion inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-emotion-knowledge-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual Content Moderation: A Case Study on Reddit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-content-moderation-a-case-study</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Content moderation is the process of flagging content based on pre-defined platform rules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-content-moderation-a-case-study</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled Representation for Causal Mediation Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-representation-for-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal mediation analysis is a method that is often used to reveal direct and indirect effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-representation-for-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERT is not The Count: Learning to Match Mathematical Statements with Proofs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bert-is-not-the-count-learning-to-match</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the first decoding method matches a proof to a statement without being aware of other statements or proofs, the second method treats the task as a global matching problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bert-is-not-the-count-learning-to-match</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calibrating the Rigged Lottery: Making All Tickets Reliable</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrating-the-rigged-lottery-making-all</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous research has shown that deep neural networks tend to be over-confident, and we find that sparse training exacerbates this problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrating-the-rigged-lottery-making-all</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eco-evolutionary Dynamics of Non-episodic Neuroevolution in Large Multi-agent Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eco-evolutionary-dynamics-of-non-episodic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neuroevolution (NE) has recently proven a competitive alternative to learning by gradient descent in reinforcement learning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eco-evolutionary-dynamics-of-non-episodic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Graph Completion based on Tensor Decomposition for Disease Gene Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graph-completion-based-on-tensor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we construct a biological knowledge graph centered on diseases and genes, and develop an end-to-end Knowledge graph completion model for Disease Gene Prediction using interactional tensor decomposition (called KDGene).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graph-completion-based-on-tensor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer-Based Neural Marked Spatio Temporal Point Process Model for Football Match Events Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-neural-marked-spatio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most sports sequential events modeling methods and performance metrics approaches could be incomprehensive in dealing with such large-scale spatiotemporal data (in particular, temporal process), thereby necessitating a more comprehensive spatiotemporal model and a holistic performance metric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-neural-marked-spatio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Federated Approach for Hate Speech Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-federated-approach-for-hate-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hate speech detection has been the subject of high research attention, due to the scale of content created on social media.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-federated-approach-for-hate-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Good Are GPT Models at Machine Translation? A Comprehensive Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-good-are-gpt-models-at-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a comprehensive evaluation of GPT models for machine translation, covering various aspects such as quality of different GPT models in comparison with state-of-the-art research and commercial systems, effect of prompting strategies, robustness towards domain shifts and document-level translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-good-are-gpt-models-at-machine</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
