<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 09:10:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Mixture of Experts: Learning on Large-Scale Graphs with Explicit Diversity Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-mixture-of-experts-learning-on-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, GMoE includes information aggregation experts with varying aggregation hop sizes, where the experts with larger hop sizes are specialized in capturing information over longer ranges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-mixture-of-experts-learning-on-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLPD: Context-Aware Pedestrian Detection via Vision-Language Semantic Self-Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlpd-context-aware-pedestrian-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we propose a self-supervised Vision-Language Semantic (VLS) segmentation method, which learns both fully-supervised pedestrian detection and contextual segmentation via self-generated explicit labels of semantic classes by vision-language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlpd-context-aware-pedestrian-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETPNav: Evolving Topological Planning for Vision-Language Navigation in Continuous Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/etpnav-evolving-topological-planning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To develop a robust VLN-CE agent, we propose a new navigation framework, ETPNav, which focuses on two critical skills: 1) the capability to abstract environments and generate long-range navigation plans, and 2) the ability of obstacle-avoiding control in continuous environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/etpnav-evolving-topological-planning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoUnseen: Zero-Shot Object Detection for Robotic Grasping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dounseen-zero-shot-object-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we are interested in open sets where the number of classes is unknown, varying, and without pre-knowledge about the objects' types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dounseen-zero-shot-object-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Dependency Transformers: Dependency Tree Emerges from Reversed Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-dependency-transformers-dependency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When looking at an image, we can decompose the scene into entities and their parts as well as obtain the dependencies between them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-dependency-transformers-dependency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cerebras-GPT: Open Compute-Optimal Language Models Trained on the Cerebras Wafer-Scale Cluster</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cerebras-gpt-open-compute-optimal-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study recent research advances that improve large language models through efficient pre-training and scaling, and open datasets and tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cerebras-gpt-open-compute-optimal-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SegGPT: Segmenting Everything In Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seggpt-segmenting-everything-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We unify various segmentation tasks into a generalist in-context learning framework that accommodates different kinds of segmentation data by transforming them into the same format of images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seggpt-segmenting-everything-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFAConv: Innovating Spatital Attention and Standard Convolutional Operation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rfaconv-innovating-spatital-attention-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explain the effectiveness of spatial attention from a new perspective, it is that the spatial attention mechanism essentially solves the problem of convolutional kernel parameter sharing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rfaconv-innovating-spatital-attention-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micron-BERT: BERT-based Facial Micro-Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/micron-bert-bert-based-facial-micro</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating these components into an end-to-end deep network, the proposed $\mu$-BERT significantly outperforms all previous work in various micro-expression tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/micron-bert-bert-based-facial-micro</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-task learning for tissue segmentation and tumor detection in colorectal cancer histology slides</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-tissue-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automating tissue segmentation and tumor detection in histopathology images of colorectal cancer (CRC) is an enabler for faster diagnostic pathology workflows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-tissue-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geometric-aware Pretraining for Vision-centric 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-aware-pretraining-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also conduct experiments on various image backbones and view transformations to validate the efficacy of our approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-aware-pretraining-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting the Complementarity of 2D and 3D Networks to Address Domain-Shift in 3D Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-the-complementarity-of-2d-and-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D semantic segmentation is a critical task in many real-world applications, such as autonomous driving, robotics, and mixed reality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-the-complementarity-of-2d-and-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointCAT: Cross-Attention Transformer for point cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointcat-cross-attention-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based models have significantly advanced natural language processing and computer vision in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointcat-cross-attention-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PopulAtion Parameter Averaging (PAPA)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/population-parameter-averaging-papa</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ensemble methods combine the predictions of multiple models to improve performance, but they require significantly higher computation costs at inference time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/population-parameter-averaging-papa</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthesizing Anyone, Anywhere, in Any Pose</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesizing-anyone-anywhere-in-any-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our main contribution is TriA-GAN, a keypoint-guided GAN that can synthesize Anyone, Anywhere, in Any given pose.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesizing-anyone-anywhere-in-any-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face Animation with an Attribute-Guided Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-animation-with-an-attribute-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Face animation has achieved much progress in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-animation-with-an-attribute-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALUDA: Surface-based Automotive Lidar Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saluda-surface-based-automotive-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning models on one labeled dataset that generalize well on another domain is a difficult task, as several shifts might happen between the data domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saluda-surface-based-automotive-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTK-SAP: Improving neural network pruning by aligning training dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntk-sap-improving-neural-network-pruning-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in neural tangent kernel (NTK) theory suggest that the training dynamics of large enough neural networks is closely related to the spectrum of the NTK.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntk-sap-improving-neural-network-pruning-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe MDP Planning by Learning Temporal Patterns of Undesirable Trajectories and Averting Negative Side Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-mdp-planning-by-learning-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In safe MDP planning, a cost function based on the current state and action is often used to specify safety aspects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-mdp-planning-by-learning-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffMimic: Efficient Motion Mimicking with Differentiable Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffmimic-efficient-motion-mimicking-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motion mimicking is a foundational task in physics-based character animation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffmimic-efficient-motion-mimicking-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A review of ensemble learning and data augmentation models for class imbalanced problems: combination, implementation and evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-ensemble-learning-and-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a computational review to evaluate data augmentation and ensemble learning methods used to address prominent benchmark CI problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-ensemble-learning-and-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-shot Generative Model Adaptation via Image-specific Prompt Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-generative-model-adaptation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, CLIP-guided image synthesis has shown appealing performance on adapting a pre-trained source-domain generator to an unseen target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-generative-model-adaptation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViralVectors: Compact and Scalable Alignment-free Virome Feature Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/viralvectors-compact-and-scalable-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose \emph{ViralVectors}, a compact feature vector generation from virome sequencing data that allows effective downstream analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/viralvectors-compact-and-scalable-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making AI Less "Thirsty": Uncovering and Addressing the Secret Water Footprint of AI Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-ai-less-thirsty-uncovering-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The growing carbon footprint of artificial intelligence (AI) models, especially large ones such as GPT-3 and GPT-4, has been undergoing public scrutiny.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-ai-less-thirsty-uncovering-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inductive Graph Unlearning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inductive-graph-unlearning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To extend machine unlearning to graph data, \textit{GraphEraser} has been proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inductive-graph-unlearning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Fast and Lightweight Network for Low-Light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fast-and-lightweight-network-for-low-light</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve efficient low-light image enhancement, we recognize the challenges of the lack of an absolute reference and the need for a large receptive field to obtain global contrast.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fast-and-lightweight-network-for-low-light</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unconstrained Parametrization of Dissipative and Contracting Neural Ordinary Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unconstrained-parametrization-of-dissipative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We validate the properties of NodeRENs, including the possibility of handling irregularly sampled data, in a case study in nonlinear system identification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unconstrained-parametrization-of-dissipative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Adversarial Discriminator: Mine the Non-causal Factors for Object Detection in Unseen Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-adversarial-discriminator-mine-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present an idea to remove non-causal factors from common features by multi-view adversarial training on source domains, because we observe that such insignificant non-causal factors may still be significant in other latent spaces (views) due to the multi-mode structure of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-adversarial-discriminator-mine-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Pareto Front of Multilingual Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-pareto-front-of-multilingual-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our observations, we propose the Double Power Law to predict the unique performance trade-off front in MNMT, which is robust across various languages, data adequacy and number of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-pareto-front-of-multilingual-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Concept of Forward-Forward Learning Applied to a Multi Output Perceptron</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-concept-of-forward-forward-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The concept of a recently proposed Forward-Forward learning algorithm for fully connected artificial neural networks is applied to a single multi output perceptron for classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-concept-of-forward-forward-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Content-Based Neural News Recommendation: On User Modeling and Training Objectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-content-based-neural-news</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most neural news recommenders rely on user click behavior and typically introduce dedicated user encoders that aggregate the content of clicked news into user embeddings (early fusion).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-content-based-neural-news</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TagGPT: Large Language Models are Zero-shot Multimodal Taggers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taggpt-large-language-models-are-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a new entity that needs tagging for distribution, TagGPT introduces two alternative options for zero-shot tagging, i. e., a generative method with late semantic matching with the tag set, and another selective method with early matching in prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taggpt-large-language-models-are-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient SAGE Estimation via Causal Structure Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-sage-estimation-via-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose $d$-SAGE, a method that accelerates SAGE approximation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-sage-estimation-via-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIF: A General Graph Unlearning Strategy via Influence Function</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gif-a-general-graph-unlearning-strategy-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we recognize the crux to the inability of traditional influence function for graph unlearning, and devise Graph Influence Function (GIF), a model-agnostic unlearning method that can efficiently and accurately estimate parameter changes in response to a $\epsilon$-mass perturbation in deleted data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gif-a-general-graph-unlearning-strategy-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-Resolving Face Image by Facial Parsing Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolving-face-image-by-facial-parsing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we build a novel parsing map guided face super-resolution network which extracts the face prior (i. e., parsing map) directly from low-resolution face image for the following utilization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolving-face-image-by-facial-parsing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards an Effective and Efficient Transformer for Rain-by-snow Weather Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-effective-and-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rain-by-snow weather removal is a specialized task in weather-degraded image restoration aiming to eliminate coexisting rain streaks and snow particles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-effective-and-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InterFormer: Real-time Interactive Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interformer-real-time-interactive-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, the model has to repeatedly process the image, the annotator's current click, and the model's feedback of the annotator's former clicks at each step of interaction, resulting in redundant computations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interformer-real-time-interactive-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training a Two Layer ReLU Network Analytically</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-a-two-layer-relu-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks are usually trained with different variants of gradient descent based optimization algorithms such as stochastic gradient descent or the Adam optimizer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-a-two-layer-relu-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask Detection and Classification in Thermal Face Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-detection-and-classification-in-thermal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Face masks are recommended to reduce the transmission of many viruses, especially SARS-CoV-2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-detection-and-classification-in-thermal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncurated Image-Text Datasets: Shedding Light on Demographic Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncurated-image-text-datasets-shedding-light</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing tendency to collect large and uncurated datasets to train vision-and-language models has raised concerns about fair representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncurated-image-text-datasets-shedding-light</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MemeFier: Dual-stage Modality Fusion for Image Meme Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memefier-dual-stage-modality-fusion-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hate speech is a societal problem that has significantly grown through the Internet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memefier-dual-stage-modality-fusion-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of ChatGPT Family of Models for Biomedical Reasoning and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-chatgpt-family-of-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first task is classifying whether statements of clinical and policy recommendations in scientific literature constitute health advice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-chatgpt-family-of-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segment Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Segment Anything (SA) project: a new task, model, and dataset for image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Quantigraphic Image Enhancement via Comparametric Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-quantigraphic-image-enhancement-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most recent methods of deep image enhancement can be generally classified into two types: decompose-and-enhance and illumination estimation-centric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-quantigraphic-image-enhancement-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoocRadar: A Fine-grained and Multi-aspect Knowledge Repository for Improving Cognitive Student Modeling in MOOCs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moocradar-a-fine-grained-and-multi-aspect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Student modeling, the task of inferring a student's learning characteristics through their interactions with coursework, is a fundamental issue in intelligent education.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moocradar-a-fine-grained-and-multi-aspect</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Certified Radius-Guided Attack Framework to Image Segmentation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-certified-radius-guided-attack-framework-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We are the first, from the attacker perspective, to leverage the properties of certified radius and propose a certified radius guided attack framework against image segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-certified-radius-guided-attack-framework-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Dense 3D Mapping of Underwater Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-dense-3d-mapping-of-underwater</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we propose to use SVIn2, a robust VIO method, together with a real-time 3D reconstruction pipeline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-dense-3d-mapping-of-underwater</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MethaneMapper: Spectral Absorption aware Hyperspectral Transformer for Methane Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/methanemapper-spectral-absorption-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MethaneMapper introduces two novel modules that help to locate the most relevant methane plume regions in the spectral domain and uses them to localize these accurately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/methanemapper-spectral-absorption-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Stage-wise GANs for Whistle Extraction in Time-Frequency Spectrograms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-stage-wise-gans-for-whistle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this limitation, we present a framework of stage-wise generative adversarial networks (GANs), which compile new whistle data suitable for deep model training via three stages: generation of background noise in the spectrogram, generation of whistle contours, and generation of whistle signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-stage-wise-gans-for-whistle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergent Coordination through Game-Induced Nonlinear Opinion Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergent-coordination-through-game-induced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a multi-agent decision-making framework for the emergent coordination of autonomous agents whose intents are initially undecided.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergent-coordination-through-game-induced</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
