<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 21:08:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Black-box Adversarial Attacks via Bayesian Optimization Guided by a Function Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-black-box-adversarial-attacks-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Prior-guided Bayesian Optimization (P-BO) algorithm that leverages the surrogate model as a global function prior in black-box adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-black-box-adversarial-attacks-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resurrecting Old Classes with New Data for Exemplar-Free Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resurrecting-old-classes-with-new-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then estimate the drift in the embedding space from the old to the new model using the perturbed images and compensate the prototypes accordingly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resurrecting-old-classes-with-new-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChartFormer: A Large Vision Language Model for Converting Chart Images into Tactile Accessible SVGs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chartformer-a-large-vision-language-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visualizations, such as charts, are crucial for interpreting complex data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chartformer-a-large-vision-language-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Brain Model for Learning Generic Representations with Tremendous EEG Data in BCI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-brain-model-for-learning-generic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then the models can be fine-tuned for different downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-brain-model-for-learning-generic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going beyond compositional generalization, DDPMs can produce zero-shot interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/going-beyond-compositional-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that such a model can effectively generate images in the unexplored, intermediate regions of the distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/going-beyond-compositional-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConceptPrune: Concept Editing in Diffusion Models via Skilled Neuron Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conceptprune-concept-editing-in-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While large-scale text-to-image diffusion models have demonstrated impressive image-generation capabilities, there are significant concerns about their potential misuse for generating unsafe content, violating copyright, and perpetuating societal biases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conceptprune-concept-editing-in-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Generation with Strictly Proper Scoring Rules</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-generation-with-strictly-proper</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging this strategy, we train language generation models using two classic strictly proper scoring rules, the Brier score and the Spherical score, as alternatives to the logarithmic score.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-generation-with-strictly-proper</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDQN: A Flexible Deep Q-Network Framework for Game Automation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fdqn-a-flexible-deep-q-network-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In reinforcement learning, it is often difficult to automate high-dimensional, rapid decision-making in dynamic environments, especially when domains require real-time online interaction and adaptive strategies such as web-based games.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fdqn-a-flexible-deep-q-network-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Multi-scale Contextualized Information for Byte-based Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-multi-scale-contextualized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, a vocabulary cannot be modified once it is learned, making it hard to adapt to new words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-multi-scale-contextualized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cephalo: Multi-Modal Vision-Language Models for Bio-Inspired Materials Analysis and Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cephalo-multi-modal-vision-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Cephalo, a series of multimodal vision large language models (V-LLMs) designed for materials science applications, integrating visual and linguistic data for enhanced understanding and interaction within human-AI and multi-agent AI frameworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cephalo-multi-modal-vision-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMPO: A Unified Framework for RL under Policy and Dynamics Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ompo-a-unified-framework-for-rl-under-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training reinforcement learning policies using environment interaction data collected from varying policies or dynamics presents a fundamental challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ompo-a-unified-framework-for-rl-under-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Vision-Language Model with Unmasked Token Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-vision-language-model-with-unmasked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive pre-training on image-text pairs, exemplified by CLIP, becomes a standard technique for learning multi-modal visual-language representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-vision-language-model-with-unmasked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Positive-Unlabeled Anomaly Detection for Contaminated Unlabeled Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-positive-unlabeled-anomaly-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With our approach, we can approximate the anomaly scores for normal data using the unlabeled and anomaly data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-positive-unlabeled-anomaly-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs Meet Multimodal Generation and Editing: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-meet-multimodal-generation-and-editing-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the recent advancement in large language models (LLMs), there is a growing interest in combining LLMs with multimodal learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-meet-multimodal-generation-and-editing-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Causal Framework for Evaluating Deferring Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-causal-framework-for-evaluating-deferring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This allows us to identify the causal impact of the deferring strategy on predictive accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-causal-framework-for-evaluating-deferring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Good Foundation is Worth Many Labels: Label-Efficient Panoptic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-good-foundation-is-worth-many-labels-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key challenge for the widespread application of learning-based models for robotic perception is to significantly reduce the required amount of annotated training data while achieving accurate predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-good-foundation-is-worth-many-labels-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convex neural network synthesis for robustness in the 1-norm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convex-neural-network-synthesis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With neural networks being used to control safety-critical systems, they increasingly have to be both accurate (in the sense of matching inputs to outputs) and robust.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convex-neural-network-synthesis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIG: Efficient Self-Interpretable Graph Neural Network for Continuous-time Dynamic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sig-efficient-self-interpretable-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim to predict future links within the dynamic graph while simultaneously providing causal explanations for these predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sig-efficient-self-interpretable-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOKD: Cross-domain Finetuning for Few-shot Classification via Maximizing Optimized Kernel Dependence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mokd-cross-domain-finetuning-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In cross-domain few-shot classification, \emph{nearest centroid classifier} (NCC) aims to learn representations to construct a metric space where few-shot classification can be performed by measuring the similarities between samples and the prototype of each class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mokd-cross-domain-finetuning-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Neural Image Field for Biological Microscopy Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-neural-image-field-for-biological</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid pace of innovation in biological microscopy imaging has led to large images, putting pressure on data storage and impeding efficient sharing, management, and visualization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-neural-image-field-for-biological</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Zero-Shot Facial Expression Recognition by LLM Knowledge Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-zero-shot-facial-expression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current facial expression recognition (FER) models are often designed in a supervised learning manner thus are constrained by the lack of large-scale facial expression images with high-quality annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-zero-shot-facial-expression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting Differential Molecular Representation with Hierarchical Prompts for Multi-label Property Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-differential-molecular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, our research introduces a Hierarchical Prompted Molecular Representation Learning Framework (HiPM), which enhances the differential expression of tasks in molecular representations through task-aware prompts, and utilizes shared information among labels to mitigate negative transfer between different tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-differential-molecular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniPTS: A Unified Framework for Proficient Post-Training Sparsity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unipts-a-unified-framework-for-proficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Post-training Sparsity (PTS) is a recently emerged avenue that chases efficient network sparsity with limited data in need.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unipts-a-unified-framework-for-proficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A random-key GRASP for combinatorial optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-random-key-grasp-for-combinatorial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A random-key optimizer (RKO) uses a vector of random keys to encode a solution to a combinatorial optimization problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-random-key-grasp-for-combinatorial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musical Phrase Segmentation via Grammatical Induction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musical-phrase-segmentation-via-grammatical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We outline a solution to the challenge of musical phrase segmentation that uses grammatical induction algorithms, a class of algorithms which infer a context-free grammar from an input sequence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musical-phrase-segmentation-via-grammatical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning under Partially Class-Disjoint Data via Manifold Reshaping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-under-partially-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Statistical heterogeneity severely limits the performance of federated learning (FL), motivating several explorations e. g., FedProx, MOON and FedDyn, to alleviate this problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-under-partially-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Classification Auxiliary Network for Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-classification-auxiliary-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a novel approach by tokenizing time series values to train forecasting models via cross-entropy loss, while considering the continuous nature of time series data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-classification-auxiliary-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EasyAnimate: A High-Performance Long Video Generation Method based on Transformer Architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyanimate-a-high-performance-long-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The motion module can be adapted to various DiT baseline methods to generate video with different styles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyanimate-a-high-performance-long-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Inspired Sharpness-Aware Minimization Under Domain Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-inspired-sharpness-aware-minimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a Domain-Inspired Sharpness-Aware Minimization (DISAM) algorithm for optimization under domain shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-inspired-sharpness-aware-minimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matryoshka Query Transformer for Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matryoshka-query-transformer-for-large-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This raises the question: can we achieve flexibility in the number of visual tokens to suit different tasks and computational resources?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matryoshka-query-transformer-for-large-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does learning the right latent variables necessarily improve in-context learning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-learning-the-right-latent-variables</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study highlights the intrinsic limitations of Transformers in achieving structured ICL solutions that generalize, and shows that while inferring the right latents aids interpretability, it is not sufficient to alleviate this problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-learning-the-right-latent-variables</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Exploring Language Models: Active Preference Elicitation for Online Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-exploring-language-models-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Preference optimization, particularly through Reinforcement Learning from Human Feedback (RLHF), has achieved significant success in aligning Large Language Models (LLMs) to adhere to human intentions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-exploring-language-models-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlchemistCoder: Harmonizing and Eliciting Code Capability by Hindsight Tuning on Multi-source Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alchemistcoder-harmonizing-and-eliciting-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-source Large Language Models (LLMs) and their specialized variants, particularly Code LLMs, have recently delivered impressive performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alchemistcoder-harmonizing-and-eliciting-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning with Bilateral Curation for Partially Class-Disjoint Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-with-bilateral-curation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Partially class-disjoint data (PCDD), a common yet under-explored data formation where each client contributes a part of classes (instead of all classes) of samples, severely challenges the performance of federated algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-with-bilateral-curation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poseidon: Efficient Foundation Models for PDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poseidon-efficient-foundation-models-for-pdes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, Poseidon scales with respect to model and data size, both for pretraining and for downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poseidon-efficient-foundation-models-for-pdes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single image super-resolution based on trainable feature matching attention network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-image-super-resolution-based-on-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we integrate non-local and channel attention into our proposed Trainable Feature Matching Attention Network (TFMAN) to further enhance SR performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-image-super-resolution-based-on-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CtrlA: Adaptive Retrieval-Augmented Generation via Probe-Guided Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ctrla-adaptive-retrieval-augmented-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, CtrlA employs an honesty probe to regulate the LLM's behavior by manipulating its representations for increased honesty, and a confidence probe to monitor the internal states of LLM and assess confidence levels, determining the retrieval necessity during generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ctrla-adaptive-retrieval-augmented-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vim-F: Visual State Space Model Benefiting from Learning in the Frequency Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vim-f-visual-state-space-model-benefiting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, State Space Models (SSMs) with efficient hardware-aware designs, known as the Mamba deep learning models, have made significant progress in modeling long sequences such as language understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vim-f-visual-state-space-model-benefiting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correctable Landmark Discovery via Large Models for Vision-Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correctable-landmark-discovery-via-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the noise in the priors due to the lack of visual constraints, we introduce a learnable cooccurrence scoring module, which corrects the importance of each cooccurrence according to actual observations for accurate landmark discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correctable-landmark-discovery-via-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBAR‑UNet: A novel methodology for segmentation  of cardiac magnetic resonance images using block  attention‑based deep residual neural network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbar-unet-a-novel-methodology-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to facilitate accurate segmentation, a Block Attention Based Deep Residual Neural Network, i. e., CBAR-UNet model, is proposed to perform cardiac image segmentation on short axis Magnetic Resonance Images (MRI) stacks from top to bottom slice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbar-unet-a-novel-methodology-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kernel Metric Learning for In-Sample Off-Policy Evaluation of Deterministic RL Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernel-metric-learning-for-in-sample-off</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose to relax the deterministic target policy using a kernel and learn the kernel metrics that minimize the overall mean squared error of the estimated temporal difference update vector of an action value function, where the action value function is used for policy evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernel-metric-learning-for-in-sample-off</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Learning in Chinese Checkers: Comparing Parameter Sharing in Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-learning-in-chinese-checkers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To run our experiments, we develop a new MARL environment: variable-size, six-player Chinese Checkers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-learning-in-chinese-checkers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Continually Learn with the Bayesian Principle</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-continually-learn-with-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, in the more classical literature of statistical machine learning, many models have sequential Bayesian update rules that yield the same learning outcome as the batch training, i. e., they are completely immune to catastrophic forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-continually-learn-with-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DecomCAM: Advancing Beyond Saliency Maps through Decomposition and Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decomcam-advancing-beyond-saliency-maps</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interpreting complex deep networks, notably pre-trained vision-language models (VLMs), is a formidable challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decomcam-advancing-beyond-saliency-maps</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LSPI: Heterogeneous Graph Neural Network Classification Aggregation Algorithm Based on Size Neighbor Path Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lspi-heterogeneous-graph-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, this paper proposes a Heterogeneous Graph Neural Network Classification and Aggregation Algorithm Based on Large and Small Neighbor Path Iden tification(LSPI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lspi-heterogeneous-graph-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion-Unaware Blind Image Quality Assessment using Multi-Scale Deep Feature Statistics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opinion-unaware-blind-image-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge these gaps, we propose integrating deep features from pre-trained visual models with a statistical analysis model into a Multi-scale Deep Feature Statistics (MDFS) model for achieving opinion-unaware BIQA (OU-BIQA), thereby eliminating the reliance on human rating data and significantly improving training efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opinion-unaware-blind-image-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoTree: Adaptive Tree-based Video Representation for LLM Reasoning on Long Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videotree-adaptive-tree-based-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, many long video-language understanding approaches have leveraged the reasoning capabilities of Large Language Models (LLMs) to perform long video QA, transforming videos into densely sampled frame captions, and asking LLMs to respond to text queries over captions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videotree-adaptive-tree-based-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instruction Tuning with Retrieval-based Examples Ranking for Aspect-based Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-tuning-with-retrieval-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aspect-based sentiment analysis (ABSA) identifies sentiment information related to specific aspects and provides deeper market insights to businesses and organizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-tuning-with-retrieval-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Rejection Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-rejection-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in powerful pre-trained diffusion models encourage the development of methods to improve the sampling performance under well-trained diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-rejection-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReChorus2.0: A Modular and Task-Flexible Recommendation Library</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rechorus2-0-a-modular-and-task-flexible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these libraries often impose certain restrictions on data and seldom support the same model to perform different tasks and input formats, limiting users from customized explorations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rechorus2-0-a-modular-and-task-flexible</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
