<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 21:06:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>GNNFlow: A Distributed Framework for Continuous Temporal GNN Learning on Dynamic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnnflow-a-distributed-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce GNNFlow, a distributed framework that enables efficient continuous temporal graph representation learning on dynamic graphs on multi-GPU machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnnflow-a-distributed-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-conditioned Detection Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-conditioned-detection-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use this detector to pseudo-label images with image-level labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-conditioned-detection-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eMotions: A Large-Scale Dataset for Emotion Recognition in Short Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotions-a-large-scale-dataset-for-emotion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prevailing use of SVs to spread emotions leads to the necessity of emotion recognition in SVs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotions-a-large-scale-dataset-for-emotion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When StyleGAN Meets Stable Diffusion: a $\mathscr{W}_+$ Adapter for Personalized Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-stylegan-meets-stable-diffusion-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image diffusion models have remarkably excelled in producing diverse, high-quality, and photo-realistic images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-stylegan-meets-stable-diffusion-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Scope Spatial-Spectral Information Aggregation for Hyperspectral Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-scope-spatial-spectral-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prevailing transformer-based methods have not adequately captured the long-range dependencies in both spectral and spatial dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-scope-spatial-spectral-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan LLM: Bridging the Linguistic Divide with a Culturally Aligned Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taiwan-llm-bridging-the-linguistic-divide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging a comprehensive pretraining corpus and instruction-finetuning datasets, we have developed a model that not only understands the complexities of Traditional Chinese but also embodies the cultural context of Taiwan.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taiwan-llm-bridging-the-linguistic-divide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Real-World Focus Stacking with Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-focus-stacking-with-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Focus stacking is widely used in micro, macro, and landscape photography to reconstruct all-in-focus images from multiple frames obtained with focus bracketing, that is, with shallow depth of field and different focus planes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-focus-stacking-with-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U-Net v2: Rethinking the Skip Connections of U-Net for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-net-v2-rethinking-the-skip-connections-of-u</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our method on several public medical image segmentation datasets for skin lesion segmentation and polyp segmentation, and the experimental results demonstrate the segmentation accuracy of our new method over state-of-the-art methods, while preserving memory and computational efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-net-v2-rethinking-the-skip-connections-of-u</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SigFormer: Sparse Signal-Guided Transformer for Multi-Modal Human Action Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sigformer-sparse-signal-guided-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nowadays, the majority of approaches concentrate on the fusion of dense signals (i. e., RGB, optical flow, and depth maps).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sigformer-sparse-signal-guided-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SyncTalk: The Devil is in the Synchronization for Talking Head Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synctalk-the-devil-is-in-the-synchronization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A lifelike talking head requires synchronized coordination of subject identity, lip movements, facial expressions, and head poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synctalk-the-devil-is-in-the-synchronization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group-wise Sparse and Explainable Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/group-wise-sparse-and-explainable-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, crafting such attacks poses an optimization challenge, as it involves computing norms for groups of pixels within a non-convex objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/group-wise-sparse-and-explainable-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimeBench: A Comprehensive Evaluation of Temporal Reasoning Abilities in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timebench-a-comprehensive-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding time is a pivotal aspect of human cognition, crucial in the broader framework of grasping the intricacies of the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timebench-a-comprehensive-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNNFlow: A Distributed Framework for Continuous Temporal GNN Learning on Dynamic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnnflow-a-distributed-framework-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce GNNFlow, a distributed framework that enables efficient continuous temporal graph representation learning on dynamic graphs on multi-GPU machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnnflow-a-distributed-framework-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biomedical knowledge graph-enhanced prompt generation for large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomedical-knowledge-graph-enhanced-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[KG-RAG consistently enhanced the performance of LLMs across various prompt types, including one-hop and two-hop prompts, drug repurposing queries, biomedical true/false questions, and multiple-choice questions (MCQ).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomedical-knowledge-graph-enhanced-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPERA: Alleviating Hallucination in Multi-Modal Large Language Models via Over-Trust Penalty and Retrospection-Allocation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opera-alleviating-hallucination-in-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the observation, OPERA introduces a penalty term on the model logits during the beam-search decoding to mitigate the over-trust issue, along with a rollback strategy that retrospects the presence of summary tokens in the previously generated tokens, and re-allocate the token selection if necessary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opera-alleviating-hallucination-in-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focus on Query: Adversarial Mining Transformer for Few-Shot Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focus-on-query-adversarial-mining-transformer-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we rethink the importance of support information and propose a new query-centric FSS model Adversarial Mining Transformer (AMFormer), which achieves accurate query image segmentation with only rough support guidance or even weak support labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focus-on-query-adversarial-mining-transformer-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Devil is in the Data: Learning Fair Graph Neural Networks via Partial Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-is-in-the-data-learning-fair-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on several benchmark datasets demonstrate that FairGKD, which does not require access to demographic information, significantly improves the fairness of GNNs by a large margin while maintaining their utility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-is-in-the-data-learning-fair-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing Membership Inference Attack in Federated Learning with Model Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-membership-inference-attack-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show that the effectiveness of these attacks on the clients negatively correlates with the size of the client datasets and model complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-membership-inference-attack-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pose Anything: A Graph-Based Approach for Category-Agnostic Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-anything-a-graph-based-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach not only enables object pose generation based on arbitrary keypoint definitions but also significantly reduces the associated costs, paving the way for versatile and adaptable pose estimation applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-anything-a-graph-based-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Higher Ranks via Adversarial Weight Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-higher-ranks-via-adversarial-weight-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a Rank-based PruninG (RPG) method to maintain the ranks of sparse weights in an adversarial manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-higher-ranks-via-adversarial-weight-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VITATECS: A Diagnostic Dataset for Temporal Concept Understanding of Video-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitatecs-a-diagnostic-dataset-for-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to perceive how objects change over time is a crucial ingredient in human intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitatecs-a-diagnostic-dataset-for-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Implicit Toxicity in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-implicit-toxicity-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While recent studies primarily focus on probing toxic outputs that can be easily detected with existing toxicity classifiers, we show that LLMs can generate diverse implicit toxic outputs that are exceptionally difficult to detect via simply zero-shot prompting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-implicit-toxicity-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The devil is in the fine-grained details: Evaluating open-vocabulary object detectors for fine-grained understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-is-in-the-fine-grained-details</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large vision-language models enabled visual object detection in open-vocabulary scenarios, where object classes are defined in free-text formats during inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-is-in-the-fine-grained-details</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning for Image Segmentation with Dynamic Query</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-for-image-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image segmentation based on continual learning exhibits a critical drop of performance, mainly due to catastrophic forgetting and background shift, as they are required to incorporate new classes continually.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-for-image-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Computation of Sparse and Robust Maximum Association Estimators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-computation-of-sparse-and-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates how such procedures can be used for robust sparse association estimators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-computation-of-sparse-and-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smooth Video Synthesis with Noise Constraints on Diffusion Models for One-shot Video Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smooth-video-synthesis-with-noise-constraints</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By applying the loss to existing one-shot video tuning methods, we significantly improve the overall consistency and smoothness of the generated videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smooth-video-synthesis-with-noise-constraints</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cam4DOcc: Benchmark for Camera-Only 4D Occupancy Forecasting in Autonomous Driving Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cam4docc-benchmark-for-camera-only-4d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the standardized evaluation protocol for preset multiple tasks is also provided to compare the performance of all the proposed baselines on present and future occupancy estimation with respect to objects of interest in autonomous driving scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cam4docc-benchmark-for-camera-only-4d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Self-supervised Molecular Representation Learning using Persistent Homology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-self-supervised-molecular-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning (SSL) has great potential for molecular representation learning given the complexity of molecular graphs, the large amounts of unlabelled data available, the considerable cost of obtaining labels experimentally, and the hence often only small training datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-self-supervised-molecular-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Toddler Tracking in Indoor Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-toddler-tracking-in-indoor-videos</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiple toddler tracking (MTT) involves identifying and differentiating toddlers in video footage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-toddler-tracking-in-indoor-videos</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving into the Future: Multiview Visual Forecasting and Planning with World Model for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/driving-into-the-future-multiview-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In autonomous driving, predicting future events in advance and evaluating the foreseeable risks empowers autonomous vehicles to better plan their actions, enhancing safety and efficiency on the road.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/driving-into-the-future-multiview-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Optimal Reference Translations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-optimal-reference-translations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The overall translation quality reached by current machine translation (MT) systems for high-resourced language pairs is remarkably good.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-optimal-reference-translations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Robustness of Decision-Focused Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-robustness-of-decision-focused</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decision-Focused Learning (DFL) is an emerging learning paradigm that tackles the task of training a machine learning (ML) model to predict missing parameters of an incomplete optimization problem, where the missing parameters are predicted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-robustness-of-decision-focused</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedGen: A Python Natural Language Processing Toolkit for Medical Text Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medgen-a-python-natural-language-processing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study introduces MedGen, a comprehensive natural language processing (NLP) toolkit designed for medical text processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medgen-a-python-natural-language-processing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panoptic Video Scene Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panoptic-video-scene-graph-generation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PVSG relates to the existing video scene graph generation (VidSGG) problem, which focuses on temporal interactions between humans and objects grounded with bounding boxes in videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panoptic-video-scene-graph-generation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sluggish and Chemically-Biased Interstitial Diffusion in Concentrated Solid Solution Alloys: Mechanisms and Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sluggish-and-chemically-biased-interstitial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interstitial diffusion is a pivotal process that governs the phase stability and irradiation response of materials in non-equilibrium conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sluggish-and-chemically-biased-interstitial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debiasing Multimodal Models via Causal Information Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-multimodal-models-via-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study bias arising from confounders in a causal graph for multimodal data and examine a novel approach that leverages causally-motivated information minimization to learn the confounder representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-multimodal-models-via-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sky's the Limit: Re-lightable Outdoor Scenes via a Sky-pixel Constrained Illumination Prior and Outside-In Visibility</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-sky-s-the-limit-re-lightable-outdoor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also introduce a novel `outside-in' method for computing differentiable sky visibility based on a neural directional distance function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-sky-s-the-limit-re-lightable-outdoor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text2Tree: Aligning Text Representation to the Label Tree Hierarchy for Imbalanced Medical Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2tree-aligning-text-representation-to-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning approaches exhibit promising performances on various text tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2tree-aligning-text-representation-to-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centre Stage: Centricity-based Audio-Visual Temporal Action Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centre-stage-centricity-based-audio-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous one-stage action detection approaches have modelled temporal dependencies using only the visual modality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centre-stage-centricity-based-audio-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Label Distribution Learning for Multi-Label Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-label-distribution-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing MLC methods are based on the assumption that the correlation of two labels in each label pair is symmetric, which is violated in many real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-label-distribution-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain-ID: Learning Robust Feature Representations for Brain Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-id-learning-robust-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent learning-based approaches have made astonishing advances in calibrated medical imaging like computerized tomography, yet they struggle to generalize in uncalibrated modalities -- notoriously magnetic resonance imaging (MRI), where performance is highly sensitive to the differences in MR contrast, resolution, and orientation between the training and testing data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-id-learning-robust-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaussian Processes for Monitoring Air-Quality in Kampala</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-processes-for-monitoring-air-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monitoring air pollution is of vital importance to the overall health of the population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-processes-for-monitoring-air-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Item-level Bundle Representation for Bundle Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-item-level-bundle-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach EBRec, short of Enhanced Bundle Recommendation, which incorporates two enhanced modules to explore inherent item-level bundle representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-item-level-bundle-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Prompt Learning: A Comprehensive Survey and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-prompt-learning-a-comprehensive-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a pioneering survey on the emerging domain of graph prompts in AGI, addressing key challenges and opportunities in harnessing graph data for AGI applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-prompt-learning-a-comprehensive-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVBench: A Comprehensive Multi-modal Video Understanding Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvbench-a-comprehensive-multi-modal-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid development of Multi-modal Large Language Models (MLLMs), a number of diagnostic benchmarks have recently emerged to evaluate the comprehension capabilities of these models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvbench-a-comprehensive-multi-modal-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filter-Pruning of Lightweight Face Detectors Using a Geometric Median Criterion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filter-pruning-of-lightweight-face-detectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Face detectors are becoming a crucial component of many applications, including surveillance, that often have to run on edge devices with limited processing power and memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filter-pruning-of-lightweight-face-detectors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DreamPropeller: Supercharge Text-to-3D Generation with Parallel Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreampropeller-supercharge-text-to-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent methods such as Score Distillation Sampling (SDS) and Variational Score Distillation (VSD) using 2D diffusion models for text-to-3D generation have demonstrated impressive generation quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreampropeller-supercharge-text-to-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typhoon Intensity Prediction with Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/typhoon-intensity-prediction-with-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting typhoon intensity accurately across space and time is crucial for issuing timely disaster warnings and facilitating emergency response.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/typhoon-intensity-prediction-with-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDEval: A Benchmark for Measuring the Cultural Dimensions of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdeval-a-benchmark-for-measuring-the-cultural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This benchmark serves as a valuable resource for cultural studies in LLMs, paving the way for more culturally aware and sensitive models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdeval-a-benchmark-for-measuring-the-cultural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening the Black Box: Towards inherently interpretable energy data imputation models using building physics insight</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opening-the-black-box-towards-inherently</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While no significant improvement is observed in terms of reconstruction error with the proposed PI-DAE, its enhanced robustness to varying rates of missing data and the valuable insights derived from the physics-based coefficients create opportunities for wider applications within building systems and the built environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opening-the-black-box-towards-inherently</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
