<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 09:13:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>PosterLayout: A New Benchmark and Approach for Content-aware Visual-Textual Presentation Layout</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posterlayout-a-new-benchmark-and-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Content-aware visual-textual presentation layout aims at arranging spatial space on the given canvas for pre-defined elements, including text, logo, and underlay, which is a key to automatic template-free creative graphic design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posterlayout-a-new-benchmark-and-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projected Latent Distillation for Data-Agnostic Consolidation in Distributed Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/projected-latent-distillation-for-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We formalize this problem as a Distributed Continual Learning scenario, where SCD adapt to local tasks and a CL model consolidates the knowledge from the resulting stream of models without looking at the SCD's private data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/projected-latent-distillation-for-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable, Detailed and Mask-Free Universal Photometric Stereo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-detailed-and-mask-free-universal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce SDM-UniPS, a groundbreaking Scalable, Detailed, Mask-free, and Universal Photometric Stereo network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-detailed-and-mask-free-universal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperbolic Geometry in Computer Vision: A Novel Framework for Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbolic-geometry-in-computer-vision-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we present HCNN, the first fully hyperbolic convolutional neural network (CNN) designed for computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbolic-geometry-in-computer-vision-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicit Planning Helps Language Models in Logical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-planning-helps-language-models-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models have been shown to perform remarkably well on a wide range of natural language processing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-planning-helps-language-models-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparison of HDR quality metrics in Per-Clip Lagrangian multiplier optimisation with AV1</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-of-hdr-quality-metrics-in-per-clip</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The complexity of modern codecs along with the increased need of delivering high-quality videos at low bitrates has reinforced the idea of a per-clip tailoring of parameters for optimised rate-distortion performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-of-hdr-quality-metrics-in-per-clip</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HS-Pose: Hybrid Scope Feature Extraction for Category-level Object Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hs-pose-hybrid-scope-feature-extraction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on the problem of category-level object pose estimation, which is challenging due to the large intra-category shape variation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hs-pose-hybrid-scope-feature-extraction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Behavior Recommendation with Cascading Graph Convolution Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-behavior-recommendation-with-cascading</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing multi-behavior models fail to capture such dependencies in a behavior chain for embedding learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-behavior-recommendation-with-cascading</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering the Missing Pattern: Unified Framework Towards Trajectory Imputation and Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-the-missing-pattern-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As far as we know, this is the first work to address the lack of benchmarks and techniques for trajectory imputation and prediction in a unified manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-the-missing-pattern-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KERM: Knowledge Enhanced Reasoning for Vision-and-Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kerm-knowledge-enhanced-reasoning-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed KERM can automatically select and gather crucial and relevant cues, obtaining more accurate action prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kerm-knowledge-enhanced-reasoning-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Shot 3D Point Cloud Semantic Segmentation via Stratified Class-Specific Attention Based Transformer Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-3d-point-cloud-semantic-segmentation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While a few-shot learning method was proposed recently to address these two problems, it suffers from high computational complexity caused by graph construction and inability to learn fine-grained relationships among points due to the use of pooling operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-3d-point-cloud-semantic-segmentation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>qEUBO: A Decision-Theoretic Acquisition Function for Preferential Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qeubo-a-decision-theoretic-acquisition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Preferential Bayesian optimization (PBO) is a framework for optimizing a decision maker's latent utility function using preference feedback.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qeubo-a-decision-theoretic-acquisition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CREATED: Generating Viable Counterfactual Sequences for Predictive Process Analytics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/created-generating-viable-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current methods to generate counterfactual sequences either do not take the process behavior into account, leading to generating invalid or infeasible counterfactual process instances, or heavily rely on domain knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/created-generating-viable-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaMA-Adapter: Efficient Fine-tuning of Language Models with Zero-init Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-adapter-efficient-fine-tuning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present LLaMA-Adapter, a lightweight adaption method to efficiently fine-tune LLaMA into an instruction-following model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-adapter-efficient-fine-tuning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TraffNet: Learning Causality of Traffic Generation for Road Network Digital Twins</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffnet-learning-causality-of-traffic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, their performance is unreliable for JIT decision making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffnet-learning-causality-of-traffic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask-Free Video Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-free-video-instance-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A consistency loss is then enforced on the found matches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-free-video-instance-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Adapter for All Programming Languages? Adapter Tuning for Code Search and Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-adapter-for-all-programming-languages</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate the potentially catastrophic forgetting issue in multilingual models, we fix all pre-trained model parameters, insert the parameter-efficient structure adapter, and fine-tune it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-adapter-for-all-programming-languages</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Feature Scaling of Recursive Feature Machines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-feature-scaling-of-recursive-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this technical report, we explore the behavior of Recursive Feature Machines (RFMs), a type of novel kernel machine that recursively learns features via the average gradient outer product, through a series of experiments on regression datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-feature-scaling-of-recursive-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting localized weather impacts on vegetation as seen from space with meteo-guided video prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-localized-weather-impacts-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel approach for modeling vegetation response to weather in Europe as measured by the Sentinel 2 satellite.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-localized-weather-impacts-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Diffusion Model is Secretly a Zero-Shot Classifier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/your-diffusion-model-is-secretly-a-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our generative approach to classification attains strong results on a variety of benchmarks and outperforms alternative methods of extracting knowledge from diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/your-diffusion-model-is-secretly-a-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVD-DIP: Overcoming the Overfitting Problem in DIP-based CT Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svd-dip-overcoming-the-overfitting-problem-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The deep image prior (DIP) is a well-established unsupervised deep learning method for image reconstruction; yet it is far from being flawless.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svd-dip-overcoming-the-overfitting-problem-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offline RL with No OOD Actions: In-Sample Learning via Implicit Value Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-rl-with-no-ood-actions-in-sample</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This gives a deeper understanding of why the in-sample learning paradigm works, i. e., it applies implicit value regularization to the policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-rl-with-no-ood-actions-in-sample</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Searching for long faint astronomical high energy transients: a data driven approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/searching-for-long-faint-astronomical-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main objective of HERMES Pathfinder is to prove that accurate position of high-energy cosmic transients can be obtained using miniaturized hardware.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/searching-for-long-faint-astronomical-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thread Counting in Plain Weave for Old Paintings Using Semi-Supervised Regression Deep Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thread-counting-in-plain-weave-for-old</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work the authors develop regression approaches based on deep learning to perform thread density estimation for plain weave canvas analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thread-counting-in-plain-weave-for-old</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Neural Topic Models Really Need Dropout? Analysis of the Effect of Dropout in Topic Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-neural-topic-models-really-need-dropout</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dropout is a widely used regularization trick to resolve the overfitting issue in large feedforward neural networks trained on a small dataset, which performs poorly on the held-out test subset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-neural-topic-models-really-need-dropout</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Pre-Training For Data-Efficient Text-to-Speech On Low Resource Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-pre-training-for-data-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We empirically demonstrate the effectiveness of our proposed method in low-resource language scenarios, achieving outstanding performance compared to competing methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-pre-training-for-data-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novel View Synthesis of Humans using Differentiable Rendering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-view-synthesis-of-humans-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show how our approach can be used for motion transfer between individuals; novel view synthesis of individuals captured from just a single camera; to synthesize individuals from any virtual viewpoint; and to re-render people in novel poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-view-synthesis-of-humans-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metrics for Dataset Demographic Bias: A Case Study on Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metrics-for-dataset-demographic-bias-a-case</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the most prominent types of demographic bias are statistical imbalances in the representation of demographic groups in the datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metrics-for-dataset-demographic-bias-a-case</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-scale Pre-trained Models are Surprisingly Strong in Incremental Novel Class Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-pre-trained-models-are</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Discovering novel concepts from unlabelled data and in a continuous manner is an important desideratum of lifelong learners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-pre-trained-models-are</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SFHarmony: Source Free Domain Adaptation for Distributed Neuroimaging Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfharmony-source-free-domain-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method outperforms existing SFDA approaches across a range of realistic data scenarios, demonstrating the potential utility of our approach for MRI harmonisation and general SFDA problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfharmony-source-free-domain-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unmasked Teacher: Towards Training-Efficient Video Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unmasked-teacher-towards-training-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous VFMs rely on Image Foundation Models (IFMs), which face challenges in transferring to the video domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unmasked-teacher-towards-training-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hallucinations in Large Multilingual Translation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallucinations-in-large-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale multilingual machine translation systems have demonstrated remarkable ability to translate directly between numerous languages, making them increasingly appealing for real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallucinations-in-large-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributed Graph Embedding with Information-Oriented Random Walks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributed-graph-embedding-with-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph embedding maps graph nodes to low-dimensional vectors, and is widely adopted in machine learning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributed-graph-embedding-with-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TFS-ViT: Token-Level Feature Stylization for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tfs-vit-token-level-feature-stylization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a first Token-level Feature Stylization (TFS-ViT) approach for domain generalization, which improves the performance of ViTs to unseen data by synthesizing new domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tfs-vit-token-level-feature-stylization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Multi-Objective Security Games Provably via Space Discretization Based Evolutionary Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-multi-objective-security-games</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, a many-objective EA is used for optimization in the low-dimensional discrete solution space to obtain a well-spaced Pareto front.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-multi-objective-security-games</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A source separation approach to temporal graph modelling for computer networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-source-separation-approach-to-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting malicious activity within an enterprise computer network can be framed as a temporal link prediction task: given a sequence of graphs representing communications between hosts over time, the goal is to predict which edges should--or should not--occur in the future.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-source-separation-approach-to-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuralMind-UNICAMP at 2022 TREC NeuCLIR: Large Boring Rerankers for Cross-lingual Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralmind-unicamp-at-2022-trec-neuclir-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper reports on a study of cross-lingual information retrieval (CLIR) using the mT5-XXL reranker on the NeuCLIR track of TREC 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralmind-unicamp-at-2022-trec-neuclir-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicit Attention-Enhanced Fusion for RGB-Thermal Perception Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-attention-enhanced-fusion-for-rgb</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we consider the following cases: i) both RGB data and thermal data, ii) only one of the types of data, and iii) none of them generate discriminative features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-attention-enhanced-fusion-for-rgb</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoKary2022: A Large-Scale Densely Annotated Dateset for Chromosome Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autokary2022-a-large-scale-densely-annotated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated chromosome instance segmentation from metaphase cell microscopic images is critical for the diagnosis of chromosomal disorders (i. e., karyotype analysis).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autokary2022-a-large-scale-densely-annotated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning a Deep Color Difference Metric for Photographic Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-deep-color-difference-metric-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most well-established and widely used color difference (CD) metrics are handcrafted and subject-calibrated against uniformly colored patches, which do not generalize well to photographic images characterized by natural scene complexities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-deep-color-difference-metric-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Composed Image Retrieval with Textual Inversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-composed-image-retrieval-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Composed Image Retrieval (CIR) aims to retrieve a target image based on a query composed of a reference image and a relative caption that describes the difference between the two images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-composed-image-retrieval-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>unarXive 2022: All arXiv Publications Pre-Processed for NLP, Including Structured Full-Text and Citation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unarxive-2022-all-arxiv-publications-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale data sets on scholarly publications are the basis for a variety of bibliometric analyses and natural language processing (NLP) applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unarxive-2022-all-arxiv-publications-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label-Free Liver Tumor Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-free-liver-tumor-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that AI models can accurately segment liver tumors without the need for manual annotation by using synthetic tumors in CT scans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-free-liver-tumor-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Granularity Archaeological Dating of Chinese Bronze Dings Based on a Knowledge-Guided Relation Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-archaeological-dating-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The archaeological dating of bronze dings has played a critical role in the study of ancient Chinese history.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-archaeological-dating-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A large-scale dataset for end-to-end table recognition in the wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-dataset-for-end-to-end-table</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a new large-scale dataset named Table Recognition Set (TabRecSet) with diverse table forms sourcing from multiple scenarios in the wild, providing complete annotation dedicated to end-to-end TR research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-dataset-for-end-to-end-table</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recovering 3D Hand Mesh Sequence from a Single Blurry Image: A New Dataset and Temporal Unfolding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recovering-3d-hand-mesh-sequence-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to the new dataset, we propose BlurHandNet, a baseline network for accurate 3D hand mesh recovery from a blurry hand image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recovering-3d-hand-mesh-sequence-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blind Image Quality Assessment via Vision-Language Correspondence: A Multitask Learning Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-image-quality-assessment-via-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim at advancing blind image quality assessment (BIQA), which predicts the human perception of image quality without any reference information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-image-quality-assessment-via-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dimensionality Collapse: Optimal Measurement Selection for Low-Error Infinite-Horizon Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dimensionality-collapse-optimal-measurement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implementations of both an approximate dynamic programming formulation and the proposed alternative are illustrated using an extended Kalman filter for state estimation, with results on simulated systems with limit cycles and chaotic behavior demonstrating a linear improvement in the CRLB as a function of the number of collapsing dimensions of the system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dimensionality-collapse-optimal-measurement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handwritten Text Generation from Visual Archetypes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handwritten-text-generation-from-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating synthetic images of handwritten text in a writer-specific style is a challenging task, especially in the case of unseen styles and new words, and even more when these latter contain characters that are rarely encountered during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handwritten-text-generation-from-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Video Multi-Frame Interpolation and Deblurring under Unknown Exposure Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-video-multi-frame-interpolation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, on the seemingly implausible x16 interpolation task, our method outperforms existing methods by more than 1. 5 dB in terms of PSNR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-video-multi-frame-interpolation-and</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
