<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 21:08:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>PhysVLM: Enabling Visual Language Models to Understand Robotic Physical Reachability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physvlm-enabling-visual-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the S-P Map abstracts a robot's physical reachability into a generalized spatial representation, independent of specific robot configurations, allowing the model to focus on reachability features rather than robot-specific parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physvlm-enabling-visual-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaSCALE: Adaptive Scaling for OOD Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adascale-adaptive-scaling-for-ood-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability of the deep learning model to recognize when a sample falls outside its learned distribution is critical for safe and reliable deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adascale-adaptive-scaling-for-ood-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integration of nested cross-validation, automated hyperparameter optimization, high-performance computing to reduce and quantify the variance of test performance estimation of deep learning models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integration-of-nested-cross-validation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study introduces NACHOS (Nested and Automated Cross-validation and Hyperparameter Optimization using Supercomputing) to reduce and quantify the variance of test performance metrics of deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integration-of-nested-cross-validation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMRL: Multi-Modal Representation Learning for Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmrl-multi-modal-representation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For inference, a decoupling strategy is employed, wherein both representation and class features are utilized for base classes, while only the class features, which retain more generalized knowledge, are used for new tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmrl-multi-modal-representation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate 3D Object Detection Models via Zero-Shot Attention Key Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerate-3d-object-detection-models-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a zero-shot runtime pruning method for transformer decoders in 3D object detection models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerate-3d-object-detection-models-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnyMoLe: Any Character Motion In-betweening Leveraging Video Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anymole-any-character-motion-in-betweening</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advancements in learning-based motion in-betweening, a key limitation has been overlooked: the requirement for character-specific datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anymole-any-character-motion-in-betweening</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective and Efficient Masked Image Generation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-and-efficient-masked-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, on ImageNet 512x512, with only about 60% of the NFE, eMIGM outperforms the state-of-the-art continuous diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-and-efficient-masked-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Reusing to Forecasting: Accelerating Diffusion Models with TaylorSeers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-reusing-to-forecasting-accelerating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve this problem, feature caching has been proposed to accelerate diffusion models by caching the features in the previous timesteps and then reusing them in the following timesteps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-reusing-to-forecasting-accelerating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemEval-2025 Task 11: Bridging the Gap in Text-Based Emotion Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semeval-2025-task-11-bridging-the-gap-in-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The data instances are multi-labeled into six emotional classes, with additional datasets in 11 languages annotated for emotion intensity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semeval-2025-task-11-bridging-the-gap-in-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multimodal Benchmark Dataset and Model for Crop Disease Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multimodal-benchmark-dataset-and-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the utility of the dataset by finetuning state-of-the-art multimodal models, showcasing significant improvements in crop disease diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multimodal-benchmark-dataset-and-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Availability-aware Sensor Fusion via Unified Canonical Space for 4D Radar, LiDAR, and Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/availability-aware-sensor-fusion-via-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sensor fusion of camera, LiDAR, and 4-dimensional (4D) Radar has brought a significant performance improvement in autonomous driving (AD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/availability-aware-sensor-fusion-via-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pure Exploration with Feedback Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pure-exploration-with-feedback-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the sample complexity of pure exploration in an online learning problem with a feedback graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pure-exploration-with-feedback-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REF-VLM: Triplet-Based Referring Paradigm for Unified Visual Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ref-vlm-triplet-based-referring-paradigm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address complex visual decoding scenarios, we introduce the Triplet-Based Referring Paradigm (TRP), which explicitly decouples three critical dimensions in visual decoding tasks through a triplet structure: concepts, decoding types, and targets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ref-vlm-triplet-based-referring-paradigm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CATANet: Efficient Content-Aware Token Aggregation for Lightweight Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/catanet-efficient-content-aware-token</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SR typically leverages the redundancy of images for reconstruction, and this redundancy appears not only in local regions but also in long-range regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/catanet-efficient-content-aware-token</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty quantification and posterior sampling for network reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-and-posterior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Network reconstruction is the task of inferring the unseen interactions between elements of a system, based only on their behavior or dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-and-posterior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AR-Diffusion: Asynchronous Video Generation with Auto-Regressive Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ar-diffusion-asynchronous-video-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we introduce Auto-Regressive Diffusion (AR-Diffusion), a novel model that combines the strengths of auto-regressive and diffusion models for flexible, asynchronous video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ar-diffusion-asynchronous-video-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOE: Real-Time Seeing Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yoloe-real-time-seeing-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object detection and segmentation are widely employed in computer vision applications, yet conventional models like YOLO series, while efficient and accurate, are limited by predefined categories, hindering adaptability in open scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yoloe-real-time-seeing-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Reasoning in Transformers is Reasoning through Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-reasoning-in-transformers-is</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Test-time compute is emerging as a new paradigm for enhancing language models' complex multi-step reasoning capabilities, as demonstrated by the success of OpenAI's o1 and o3, as well as DeepSeek's R1.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-reasoning-in-transformers-is</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion Anything: Any to Motion Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-anything-any-to-motion-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conditional motion generation has been extensively studied in computer vision, yet two critical challenges remain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-anything-any-to-motion-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Decision Trees as Amortized Structure Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-decision-trees-as-amortized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building predictive models for tabular data presents fundamental challenges, notably in scaling consistently, i. e., more resources translating to better performance, and generalizing systematically beyond the training data distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-decision-trees-as-amortized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMODO: Cross-Modal Video-to-IMU Distillation for Efficient Egocentric Human Activity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comodo-cross-modal-video-to-imu-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By distilling knowledge from video representations, our approach enables the IMU encoder to inherit rich semantic information from video while preserving its efficiency for real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comodo-cross-modal-video-to-imu-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRCE: Towards Reliable Malicious Concept Erasure in Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trce-towards-reliable-malicious-concept</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, TRCE starts by erasing the malicious semantics implicitly embedded in textual prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trce-towards-reliable-malicious-concept</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepNuParc: A Novel Deep Clustering Framework for Fine-scale Parcellation of Brain Nuclei Using Diffusion MRI Tractography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepnuparc-a-novel-deep-clustering-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion MRI tractography is an advanced imaging technique that can estimate the brain's white matter structural connectivity to potentially reveal the topography of the nuclei of interest for studying its subdivisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepnuparc-a-novel-deep-clustering-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Approach to Constraint-Aware Imitation Learning with Application to Autonomous Racing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-approach-to-constraint-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Guaranteeing constraint satisfaction is challenging in imitation learning (IL), particularly in tasks that require operating near a system's handling limits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-approach-to-constraint-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seg-Zero: Reasoning-Chain Guided Segmentation via Cognitive Reinforcement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seg-zero-reasoning-chain-guided-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional methods for reasoning segmentation rely on supervised fine-tuning with categorical labels and simple descriptions, limiting its out-of-domain generalization and lacking explicit reasoning processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seg-zero-reasoning-chain-guided-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WildIFEval: Instruction Following in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wildifeval-instruction-following-in-the-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce WildIFEval - a large-scale dataset of 12K real user instructions with diverse, multi-constraint conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wildifeval-instruction-following-in-the-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgiBot World Colosseo: A Large-scale Manipulation Platform for Scalable and Intelligent Embodied Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agibot-world-colosseo-a-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Introducing AgiBot World, a large-scale platform comprising over 1 million trajectories across 217 tasks in five deployment scenarios, we achieve an order-of-magnitude increase in data scale compared to existing datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agibot-world-colosseo-a-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emulating Self-attention with Convolution for Efficient Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emulating-self-attention-with-convolution-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By utilizing the ConvAttn module, we significantly reduce the reliance on self-attention and its involved memory-bound operations while maintaining the representational capability of transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emulating-self-attention-with-convolution-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SGA-INTERACT: A 3D Skeleton-based Benchmark for Group Activity Understanding in Modern Basketball Tactic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sga-interact-a-3d-skeleton-based-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This framework aligns with the feature extraction paradigm in RGB-based methods, enabling direct evaluation of RGB-based models on skeleton-based benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sga-interact-a-3d-skeleton-based-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HuixiangDou2: A Robustly Optimized GraphRAG Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/huixiangdou2-a-robustly-optimized-graphrag</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) perform well on familiar queries but struggle with specialized or emerging topics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/huixiangdou2-a-robustly-optimized-graphrag</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnywhereDoor: Multi-Target Backdoor Attacks on Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anywheredoor-multi-target-backdoor-attacks-on-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As object detection becomes integral to many safety-critical applications, understanding its vulnerabilities is essential.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anywheredoor-multi-target-backdoor-attacks-on-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Axes that matter: PCA with a difference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/axes-that-matter-pca-with-a-difference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extend the scope of differential machine learning and introduce a new breed of supervised principal component analysis to reduce dimensionality of Derivatives problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/axes-that-matter-pca-with-a-difference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HealthiVert-GAN: A Novel Framework of Pseudo-Healthy Vertebral Image Synthesis for Interpretable Compression Fracture Grading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/healthivert-gan-a-novel-framework-of-pseudo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Osteoporotic vertebral compression fractures (VCFs) are prevalent in the elderly population, typically assessed on computed tomography (CT) scans by evaluating vertebral height loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/healthivert-gan-a-novel-framework-of-pseudo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-AVSR: Zero-Shot Audio-Visual Speech Recognition with LLMs by Learning Language-Agnostic Speech Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-avsr-zero-shot-audio-visual-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To capture the wide spectrum of phonetic and linguistic diversity, we also introduce a Multilingual Audio-Visual Romanized Corpus (MARC) consisting of 2, 916 hours of audio-visual speech data across 82 languages, along with transcriptions in both language-specific graphemes and Roman text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-avsr-zero-shot-audio-visual-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rank-R1: Enhancing Reasoning in LLM-based Document Rerankers via Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rank-r1-enhancing-reasoning-in-llm-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we find that Rank-R1 achieves effectiveness on in-domain datasets at par with that of supervised fine-tuning methods, but utilizing only 18\% of the training data used by the fine-tuning methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rank-r1-enhancing-reasoning-in-llm-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathology-Guided AI System for Accurate Segmentation and Diagnosis of Cervical Spondylosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathology-guided-ai-system-for-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The segmentation is followed by an expert-based diagnostic framework that automates the calculation of critical clinical indicators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathology-guided-ai-system-for-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid CNN-Dilated Self-attention Model Using Inertial and Body-Area Electrostatic Sensing for Gym Workout Recognition, Counting, and User Authentification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-cnn-dilated-self-attention-model-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While human body capacitance ($HBC$) has been explored as a novel wearable motion sensing modality, its competence has never been quantitatively demonstrated compared to that of the dominant inertial measurement unit ($IMU$) in practical scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-cnn-dilated-self-attention-model-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AF-KAN: Activation Function-Based Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks for Efficient Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/af-kan-activation-function-based-kolmogorov</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While many KANs are designed using basis and polynomial functions, such as B-splines, ReLU-KAN utilizes a combination of ReLU functions to mimic the structure of B-splines and take advantage of ReLU's speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/af-kan-activation-function-based-kolmogorov</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Atomic Step Decomposition Enhance the Self-structured Reasoning of Multimodal Large Models?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-atomic-step-decomposition-enhance-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from existing methods that rely on structured templates or free-form paradigms, our method can not only generate cognitive CoT structures for various complex tasks but also mitigates the phenomenon of overthinking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-atomic-step-decomposition-enhance-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoPainter: Any-length Video Inpainting and Editing with Plug-and-Play Context Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videopainter-any-length-video-inpainting-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video inpainting, which aims to restore corrupted video content, has experienced substantial progress.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videopainter-any-length-video-inpainting-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy Coopetition Explains the Emergence and Transience of In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strategy-coopetition-explains-the-emergence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we find that, after the disappearance of ICL, the asymptotic strategy is a remarkable hybrid between in-weights and in-context learning, which we term "context-constrained in-weights learning" (CIWL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strategy-coopetition-explains-the-emergence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Near-Polynomially Competitive Active Logistic Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-polynomially-competitive-active-logistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the problem of active logistic regression in the realizable setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-polynomially-competitive-active-logistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear-MoE: Linear Sequence Modeling Meets Mixture-of-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-moe-linear-sequence-modeling-meets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Linear-MoE leverages the advantages of both LSM modules for linear-complexity sequence modeling and MoE layers for sparsely activation, aiming to offer high performance with efficient training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-moe-linear-sequence-modeling-meets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhiloBERTA: A Transformer-Based Cross-Lingual Analysis of Greek and Latin Lexicons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/philoberta-a-transformer-based-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present PhiloBERTA, a cross-lingual transformer model that measures semantic relationships between ancient Greek and Latin lexicons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/philoberta-a-transformer-based-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ColFigPhotoAttnNet: Reliable Finger Photo Presentation Attack Detection Leveraging Window-Attention on Color Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colfigphotoattnnet-reliable-finger-photo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finger photo Presentation Attack Detection (PAD) can significantly strengthen smartphone device security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colfigphotoattnnet-reliable-finger-photo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slim attention: cut your context memory in half without loss of accuracy -- K-cache is all you need for MHA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slim-attention-cut-your-context-memory-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For encoder-decoder transformers, the context memory size can be reduced even further: For the Whisper models for example, slim attention reduces the context memory by 8x, which can speed up token generation by 5x for batch size 64 for example.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slim-attention-cut-your-context-memory-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encrypted Vector Similarity Computations Using Partially Homomorphic Encryption: Applications and Performance Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/encrypted-vector-similarity-computations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the use of partially homomorphic encryption (PHE) for encrypted vector similarity search, with a focus on facial recognition and broader applications like reverse image search, recommendation engines, and large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/encrypted-vector-similarity-computations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptPex: Automatic Test Generation for Language Model Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptpex-automatic-test-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These tests are instrumental in identifying regressions when a prompt is changed and also serve as a tool to understand how prompts are interpreted by different models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptpex-automatic-test-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Routing for Large ML Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/routing-for-large-ml-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training large language models (LLMs), and other large machine learning models, involves repeated communication of large volumes of data across a data center network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/routing-for-large-ml-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balcony: A Lightweight Approach to Dynamic Inference of Generative Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balcony-a-lightweight-approach-to-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By freezing the pretrained LLM and inserting additional transformer layers at selected exit points, Balcony maintains the full model's performance while enabling real-time adaptation to different computational budgets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balcony-a-lightweight-approach-to-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
