<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 09:16:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing the Feature Extractor Networks for Face Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-feature-extractor-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim to give valuable insights into the behavior of feature extractors for evaluating face image synthesis methodologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-feature-extractor-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast networked data selection via distributed smoothed quantile estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-networked-data-selection-via-distributed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging the piecewise linearity of the local objective functions in quantile estimation, we characterize the iteration complexity required to achieve top-$k$ selection, a challenging task due to the lack of strong convexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-networked-data-selection-via-distributed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Adversarial Diffusion Convolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-adversarial-diffusion-convolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a min-max optimization formulation for the Graph Signal Denoising (GSD) problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-adversarial-diffusion-convolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synergetic Event Understanding: A Collaborative Approach to Cross-Document Event Coreference Resolution with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synergetic-event-understanding-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results demonstrate that our approach surpasses the performance of both the large and small language models individually, forming a complementary advantage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synergetic-event-understanding-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Conditional Distributions by Neural (Entropic) Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-conditional-distributions-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning conditional distributions is challenging because the desired outcome is not a single distribution but multiple distributions that correspond to multiple instances of the covariates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-conditional-distributions-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Generalized Transfer Attack with Initialization Derived Bilevel Optimization and Dynamic Sequence Truncation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-generalized-transfer-attack-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transfer attacks generate significant interest for real-world black-box applications by crafting transferable adversarial examples through surrogate models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-generalized-transfer-attack-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProGEO: Generating Prompts through Image-Text Contrastive Learning for Visual Geo-localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progeo-generating-prompts-through-image-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first leverage the multi-modal description capability of CLIP (Contrastive Language-Image Pretraining) to create a set of learnable text prompts for each geographic image feature to form vague descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progeo-generating-prompts-through-image-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Bayesian Approach to Online Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bayesian-approach-to-online-planning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition we propose a variant of the Bayes-UCB method applied to trees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bayesian-approach-to-online-planning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Only Text: Empowering Vision-and-Language Navigation with Multi-modal Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-only-text-empowering-vision-and-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current Vision-and-Language Navigation (VLN) tasks mainly employ textual instructions to guide agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-only-text-empowering-vision-and-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Process-Driven Autoformalization in Lean 4</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/process-driven-autoformalization-in-lean-4</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoformalization, the conversion of natural language mathematics into formal languages, offers significant potential for advancing mathematical reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/process-driven-autoformalization-in-lean-4</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-Encoding or Auto-Regression? A Reality Check on Causality of Self-Attention-Based Sequential Recommenders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-encoding-or-auto-regression-a-reality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We start by tracing the AE/AR debate back to its origin through a systematic re-evaluation of SASRec and BERT4Rec, discovering that AR models generally surpass AE models in sequential recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-encoding-or-auto-regression-a-reality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XRec: Large Language Models for Explainable Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xrec-large-language-models-for-explainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a model-agnostic framework called XRec, which enables LLMs to provide comprehensive explanations for user behaviors in recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xrec-large-language-models-for-explainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReLU-KAN: New Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks that Only Need Matrix Addition, Dot Multiplication, and ReLU</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relu-kan-new-kolmogorov-arnold-networks-that</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Limited by the complexity of basis function (B-spline) calculations, Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks (KAN) suffer from restricted parallel computing capability on GPUs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relu-kan-new-kolmogorov-arnold-networks-that</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable MatMul-free Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-matmul-free-language-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments show that our proposed MatMul-free models achieve performance on-par with state-of-the-art Transformers that require far more memory during inference at a scale up to at least 2. 7B parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-matmul-free-language-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaMixer Is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metamixer-is-all-you-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our FFNet achieves remarkable performance improvements over previous state-of-the-art methods across a wide range of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metamixer-is-all-you-need</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARS: Benchmarking the Metaphysical Reasoning Abilities of Language Models with a Multi-task Evaluation Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mars-benchmarking-the-metaphysical-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enable Large Language Models (LLMs) to function as conscious agents with generalizable reasoning capabilities, it is crucial that they possess the reasoning ability to comprehend situational changes (transitions) in distribution triggered by environmental factors or actions from other agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mars-benchmarking-the-metaphysical-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TruthEval: A Dataset to Evaluate LLM Truthfulness and Reliability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trutheval-a-dataset-to-evaluate-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Model (LLM) evaluation is currently one of the most important areas of research, with existing benchmarks proving to be insufficient and not completely representative of LLMs' various capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trutheval-a-dataset-to-evaluate-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Deep Learning Analysis for Raga Identification in Indian Art Music</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-deep-learning-analysis-for-raga</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce "Prasarbharti Indian Music" version-1 (PIM-v1), a novel dataset comprising of 191 hours of meticulously labeled Hindustani Classical Music (HCM) recordings, which is the largest labeled dataset for HCM recordings to the best of our knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-deep-learning-analysis-for-raga</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Mode-Seeking Properties of Langevin Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-mode-seeking-properties-of-langevin</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Langevin Dynamics framework, which aims to generate samples from the score function of a probability distribution, is widely used for analyzing and interpreting score-based generative modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-mode-seeking-properties-of-langevin</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistle: Data-Efficient Multilingual and Crosslingual Speech Recognition via Weakly Phonetic Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whistle-data-efficient-multilingual-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We construct a common experimental setup based on the CommonVoice dataset, called CV-Lang10, with 10 seen languages and 2 unseen languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whistle-data-efficient-multilingual-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CADE: Cosine Annealing Differential Evolution for Spiking Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cade-cosine-annealing-differential-evolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper attempts to tackle the challenges by introducing Cosine Annealing Differential Evolution (CADE), designed to modulate the mutation factor (F) and crossover rate (CR) of differential evolution (DE) for the SNN model, i. e., Spiking Element Wise (SEW) ResNet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cade-cosine-annealing-differential-evolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaceCom: Towards High-fidelity 3D Facial Shape Completion via Optimization and Inpainting Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facecom-towards-high-fidelity-3d-facial-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method can be used in medical prosthetic fabrication and the registration of deficient scanning data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facecom-towards-high-fidelity-3d-facial-shape</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Embodiment Robot Manipulation Skill Transfer using Latent Space Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-embodiment-robot-manipulation-skill</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first introduce encoders and decoders to associate the states and actions of the source robot with a latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-embodiment-robot-manipulation-skill</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Predicate and Triplet Learning for Scene Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-predicate-and-triplet-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that visual variations within the identical triplet are relatively small and certain relation cues are shared in the same type of triplet, which can potentially facilitate the relation learning in SGG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-predicate-and-triplet-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alice in Wonderland: Simple Tasks Showing Complete Reasoning Breakdown in State-Of-the-Art Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alice-in-wonderland-simple-tasks-showing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are often described as being instances of foundation models - that is, models that transfer strongly across various tasks and conditions in few-show or zero-shot manner, while exhibiting scaling laws that predict function improvement when increasing the pre-training scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alice-in-wonderland-simple-tasks-showing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing the Effect of Combined Degradations on Face Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-effect-of-combined-degradations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work emphasizes the importance of accounting for real-world complexity to assess the robustness of face recognition models in real-world settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-effect-of-combined-degradations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness-Optimized Synthetic EHR Generation for Arbitrary Downstream Predictive Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-optimized-synthetic-ehr-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed pipeline can add a widely applicable and complementary tool to the existing toolbox of methods to address fairness in health AI applications such as those modifying the design of a downstream model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-optimized-synthetic-ehr-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenS: Generalizable Neural Surface Reconstruction from Multi-View Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gens-generalizable-neural-surface-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, we introduce a multi-scale feature-metric consistency to impose the multi-view consistency in a more discriminative multi-scale feature space, which is robust to the failures of the photometric consistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gens-generalizable-neural-surface-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Scandinavian Embedding Benchmarks: Comprehensive Assessment of Multilingual and Monolingual Text Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-scandinavian-embedding-benchmarks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The evaluation of English text embeddings has transitioned from evaluating a handful of datasets to broad coverage across many tasks through benchmarks such as MTEB.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-scandinavian-embedding-benchmarks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LlamaCare: A Large Medical Language Model for Enhancing Healthcare Knowledge Sharing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llamacare-a-large-medical-language-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our contributions are : (i) We fine-tuned a large language model of medical knowledge with very low carbon emissions and achieved similar performance with ChatGPT by a 24G GPU.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llamacare-a-large-medical-language-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiding Text in Large Language Models: Introducing Unconditional Token Forcing Confusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiding-text-in-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work demonstrates that embedding hidden text in the LLM via fine-tuning, though seemingly secure due to the vast number of potential triggers (any sequence of characters or tokens could serve as a trigger), is susceptible to extraction through analysis of the LLM's output decoding process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiding-text-in-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preference Optimization for Molecule Synthesis with Conditional Residual Energy-based Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preference-optimization-for-molecule</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Molecule synthesis through machine learning is one of the fundamental problems in drug discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preference-optimization-for-molecule</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReLUs Are Sufficient for Learning Implicit Neural Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relus-are-sufficient-for-learning-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the growing theoretical understanding of neural networks that employ the Rectified Linear Unit (ReLU) as their activation function, we revisit the use of ReLU activation functions for learning implicit neural representations (INRs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relus-are-sufficient-for-learning-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study into Clustering of Unseen Datasets with Self-Supervised Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-into-clustering-of-unseen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our suite of benchmarking experiments use encoders pretrained solely on ImageNet-1k with either supervised or self-supervised training techniques, deployed on image datasets that were not seen during training, and clustered with conventional clustering algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-into-clustering-of-unseen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GrootVL: Tree Topology is All You Need in State Space Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grootvl-tree-topology-is-all-you-need-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The state space models, employing recursively propagated features, demonstrate strong representation capabilities comparable to Transformer models and superior efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grootvl-tree-topology-is-all-you-need-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Graph Rewiring with Expander Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-graph-rewiring-with-expander-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose Temporal Graph Rewiring (TGR), the first approach for graph rewiring on temporal graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-graph-rewiring-with-expander-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Learners for Partially-Identified Treatment Effects Across Multiple Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learners-for-partially-identified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we show that current assumptions from the literature on multiple environments allow us to interpret the environment as an instrumental variable (IV).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learners-for-partially-identified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-YOLO 3D: Towards Fast and Accurate Open-Vocabulary 3D Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-yolo-3d-towards-fast-and-accurate-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a fast yet accurate open-vocabulary 3D instance segmentation approach, named Open-YOLO 3D, that effectively leverages only 2D object detection from multi-view RGB images for open-vocabulary 3D instance segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-yolo-3d-towards-fast-and-accurate-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding NeMo: Localizing Neurons Responsible For Memorization in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-nemo-localizing-neurons-responsible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, this practice raises privacy and intellectual property concerns, as DMs can memorize and later reproduce their potentially sensitive or copyrighted training images at inference time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-nemo-localizing-neurons-responsible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Shot Classification of Interactive Activities of Daily Living (InteractADL)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-classification-of-interactive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding Activities of Daily Living (ADLs) is a crucial step for different applications including assistive robots, smart homes, and healthcare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-classification-of-interactive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating Canopy Height at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-canopy-height-at-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a framework for global-scale canopy height estimation based on satellite data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-canopy-height-at-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparser, Better, Deeper, Stronger: Improving Sparse Training with Exact Orthogonal Initialization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparser-better-deeper-stronger-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods mainly select such mask based on a predefined dense initialization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparser-better-deeper-stronger-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying Platform Requirements for Diverse LLM Inference Use Cases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-platform-requirements-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ultimately, this work sheds light on the platform design considerations for unlocking the full potential of large language models across a spectrum of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-platform-requirements-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Adaptive Fusion Bank for Multi-modal Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-adaptive-fusion-bank-for-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To adaptively select the appropriate fusion scheme for multi-modal input, we introduce an adaptive ensemble module that forms the adaptive fusion bank, which is embedded into hierarchical layers for sufficient fusion of different source data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-adaptive-fusion-bank-for-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Calibrating 4D Novel View Synthesis from Monocular Videos Using Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-calibrating-4d-novel-view-synthesis-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gaussian Splatting (GS) has significantly elevated scene reconstruction efficiency and novel view synthesis (NVS) accuracy compared to Neural Radiance Fields (NeRF), particularly for dynamic scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-calibrating-4d-novel-view-synthesis-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Are Large Language Models Mapping to in the Brain? A Case Against Over-Reliance on Brain Scores</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-are-large-language-models-mapping-to-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we explain the surprisingly high brain scores of untrained LLMs by showing they do not account for additional neural variance beyond two simple features: sentence length and sentence position.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-are-large-language-models-mapping-to-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Fused Multimodal Deep Learning for Plant Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-fused-multimodal-deep-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a pioneering multimodal DL-based approach for plant classification with automatic modality fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-fused-multimodal-deep-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>animal2vec and MeerKAT: A self-supervised transformer for rare-event raw audio input and a large-scale reference dataset for bioacoustics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animal2vec-and-meerkat-a-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bioacoustic research provides invaluable insights into the behavior, ecology, and conservation of animals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animal2vec-and-meerkat-a-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Task Graph Learning: Procedural Activity Representation and Online Mistake Detection from Egocentric Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-task-graph-learning-procedural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Task graphs learned with our approach are also shown to significantly enhance online mistake detection in procedural egocentric videos, achieving notable gains of +19. 8% and +7. 5% on the Assembly101 and EPIC-Tent datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-task-graph-learning-procedural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Data Generation for 3D Myocardium Deformation Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-data-generation-for-3d-myocardium</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work contributes to overcoming the limitations imposed by the scarcity of high-resolution CT datasets with precise annotations, thereby facilitating the development of accurate and reliable myocardium deformation analysis algorithms for clinical applications and diagnostics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-data-generation-for-3d-myocardium</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
