<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 09:18:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Matching Fields: Implicit Representation of Matching Fields for Visual Correspondence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-matching-fields-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing pipelines of semantic correspondence commonly include extracting high-level semantic features for the invariance against intra-class variations and background clutters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-matching-fields-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MechRetro is a chemical-mechanism-driven graph learning framework for interpretable retrosynthesis prediction and pathway planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mechretro-is-a-chemical-mechanism-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging artificial intelligence for automatic retrosynthesis speeds up organic pathway planning in digital laboratories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mechretro-is-a-chemical-mechanism-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional Feature Importance for Mixed Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-feature-importance-for-mixed-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The CPI enables CFI measurement that controls for any feature dependencies by sampling valid knockoffs - hence, generating synthetic data with similar statistical properties - for the data to be analyzed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-feature-importance-for-mixed-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Narrative Elements in Informational Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-narrative-elements-in-informational-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this purpose, we designed a new multi-label narrative annotation scheme, better suited for informational text (e. g. news media), by adapting elements from the narrative theory of Labov and Waletzky (Complication and Resolution) and adding a new narrative element of our own (Success).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-narrative-elements-in-informational-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARS2: Adaptive Ranking-based Sample Selection for Weakly supervised Class-imbalanced Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ars2-adaptive-ranking-based-sample-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To obtain a large amount of training labels inexpensively, researchers have recently adopted the weak supervision (WS) paradigm, which leverages labeling rules to synthesize training labels rather than using individual annotations to achieve competitive results for natural language processing (NLP) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ars2-adaptive-ranking-based-sample-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IR-MCL: Implicit Representation-Based Online Global Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ir-mcl-implicit-representation-based-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experiments suggest that the presented implicit representation is able to predict more accurate 2D LiDAR scans leading to an improved observation model for our particle filter-based localization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ir-mcl-implicit-representation-based-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-World Robot Learning with Masked Visual Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-world-robot-learning-with-masked-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we train a 307M parameter vision transformer on a massive collection of 4. 5M images from the Internet and egocentric videos, and demonstrate clearly the benefits of scaling visual pre-training for robot learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-world-robot-learning-with-masked-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melody Infilling with User-Provided Structural Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melody-infilling-with-user-provided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel Transformer-based model for music score infilling, to generate a music passage that fills in the gap between given past and future contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melody-infilling-with-user-provided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sound of Silence: Efficiency of First Digit Features in Synthetic Audio Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-sound-of-silence-efficiency-of-first</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent integration of generative neural strategies and audio processing techniques have fostered the widespread of synthetic speech synthesis or transformation algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-sound-of-silence-efficiency-of-first</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Boosted Decision Trees with Differential Privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-boosted-decision-trees-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is great demand for scalable, secure, and efficient privacy-preserving machine learning models that can be trained over distributed data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-boosted-decision-trees-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Shot Calibration of Set Predictors via Meta-Learned Cross-Validation-Based Conformal Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-calibration-of-set-predictors-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional frequentist learning is known to yield poorly calibrated models that fail to reliably quantify the uncertainty of their decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-calibration-of-set-predictors-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IR2Net: Information Restriction and Information Recovery for Accurate Binary Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ir2net-information-restriction-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, considering the limited learning ability and information loss caused by the limited representational capability of BNNs, we propose IR$^2$Net to stimulate the potential of BNNs and improve the network accuracy by restricting the input information and recovering the feature information, including: 1) information restriction: for a BNN, by evaluating the learning ability on the input information, discarding some of the information it cannot focus on, and limiting the amount of input information to match its learning ability; 2) information recovery: due to the information loss in forward propagation, the output feature information of the network is not enough to support accurate classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ir2net-information-restriction-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>hyperbox-brain: A Toolbox for Hyperbox-based Machine Learning Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbox-brain-a-toolbox-for-hyperbox-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[hyperbox-brain is an open-source Python library implementing the leading hyperbox-based machine learning algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbox-brain-a-toolbox-for-hyperbox-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guess the Instruction! Making Language Models Stronger Zero-Shot Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guess-the-instruction-making-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meta-training, which fine-tunes the language model (LM) on various downstream tasks by maximizing the likelihood of the target label given the task instruction and input instance, has improved the zero-shot task generalization performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guess-the-instruction-making-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmentor or Filter? Reconsider the Role of Pre-trained Language Model in Text Classification Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmentor-or-filter-reconsider-the-role-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study shows that even employing pre-trained language models, existing text augmentation methods generate numerous low-quality instances and lead to the feature space shift problem in augmentation instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmentor-or-filter-reconsider-the-role-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orthogonal Non-negative Matrix Factorization: a Maximum-Entropy-Principle Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orthogonal-non-negative-matrix-factorization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a new methodology to solve the orthogonal non-negative matrix factorization (ONMF) problem, where the objective is to approximate an input data matrix by the product of two non-negative matrices, the features matrix and the mixing matrix, while one of them is orthogonal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orthogonal-non-negative-matrix-factorization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANIFE: Crafting Canaries for Empirical Privacy Measurement in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/canife-crafting-canaries-for-empirical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel method, CANIFE, that uses canaries - carefully crafted samples by a strong adversary to evaluate the empirical privacy of a training round.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/canife-crafting-canaries-for-empirical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSVRF: Learning to restore Pitch-Shifted Voice without reference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psvrf-learning-to-restore-pitch-shifted-voice</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pitch scaling algorithms have a significant impact on the security of Automatic Speaker Verification (ASV) systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psvrf-learning-to-restore-pitch-shifted-voice</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Diagnosis and Prognosis by Controlling the Update Process of Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-diagnosis-and-prognosis-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continuous diagnosis and prognosis are essential for intensive care patients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-diagnosis-and-prognosis-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InferES : A Natural Language Inference Corpus for Spanish Featuring Negation-Based Contrastive and Adversarial Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferes-a-natural-language-inference-corpus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we focus on measuring and improving the performance of machine learning systems on negation-based adversarial examples and their ability to generalize across out-of-distribution topics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferes-a-natural-language-inference-corpus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Double-Encoder Network for RGB-D Panoptic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-double-encoder-network-for-rgb-d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel encoder-decoder neural network that processes RGB and depth separately through two encoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-double-encoder-network-for-rgb-d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Entropy Search for Multi-objective Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-entropy-search-for-multi-objective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many real-world problems can be phrased as a multi-objective optimization problem, where the goal is to identify the best set of compromises between the competing objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-entropy-search-for-multi-objective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial-Temporal Graph Convolutional Gated Recurrent Network for Traffic Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-temporal-graph-convolutional-gated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We design an attention module to capture long-term dependency by mining periodic information in traffic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-temporal-graph-convolutional-gated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Instance Features for Label Aggregation in Programmatic Weak Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-instance-features-for-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, it is built on a mixture of Bayesian label models, each corresponding to a global pattern of correlation, and the coefficients of the mixture components are predicted by a Gaussian Process classifier based on instance features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-instance-features-for-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Should I Choose You? AutoXAI: A Framework for Selecting and Tuning eXplainable AI Solutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-should-i-choose-you-autoxai-a-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose AutoXAI, a framework that recommends the best XAI solution and its hyperparameters according to specific XAI evaluation metrics while considering the user's context (dataset, ML model, XAI needs and constraints).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-should-i-choose-you-autoxai-a-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-shot Generation of Personalized Neural Surrogates for Cardiac Simulation via Bayesian Meta-Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-generation-of-personalized-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As test time, metaPNS delivers a personalized neural surrogate by fast feed-forward embedding of a small and flexible number of data available from an individual, achieving -- for the first time -- personalization and surrogate construction for expensive simulations in one end-to-end learning framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-generation-of-personalized-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiview Contextual Commonsense Inference: A New Dataset and Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiview-contextual-commonsense-inference-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that the proposed pre-training objectives are effective at adapting the pre-trained T5-Large model for the contextual commonsense inference task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiview-contextual-commonsense-inference-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 Detection Using Segmentation, Region Extraction and Classification Pipeline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covid-19-detection-using-segmentation-region</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods The methodology used in the segmentation part is traditional segmentation methods as well as UNet based segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covid-19-detection-using-segmentation-region</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLSNR:Vision-Linguistics Coordination Time Sequence-aware News Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlsnr-vision-linguistics-coordination-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our work, we propose a vision-linguistics coordinate time sequence news recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlsnr-vision-linguistics-coordination-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing the Number of Components in Finite Mixture Normal Regression Model with Panel Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testing-the-number-of-components-in-finite</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply our EM test to estimate the number of production technology types for the finite mixture Cobb-Douglas production function model studied by Kasahara et al. (2022) used the panel data of the Japanese and Chilean manufacturing firms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testing-the-number-of-components-in-finite</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Abuse Detection as Intent Classification and Slot Filling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-abuse-detection-as-intent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To proactively offer social media users a safe online experience, there is a need for systems that can detect harmful posts and promptly alert platform moderators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-abuse-detection-as-intent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binding Language Models in Symbolic Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binding-language-models-in-symbolic-languages</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Binder, a training-free neural-symbolic framework that maps the task input to a program, which (1) allows binding a unified API of language model (LM) functionalities to a programming language (e. g., SQL, Python) to extend its grammar coverage and thus tackle more diverse questions, (2) adopts an LM as both the program parser and the underlying model called by the API during execution, and (3) requires only a few in-context exemplar annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binding-language-models-in-symbolic-languages</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Distributional Lens for Multi-Aspect Controllable Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-distributional-lens-for-multi-aspect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-aspect controllable text generation is a more challenging and practical task than single-aspect control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-distributional-lens-for-multi-aspect</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised confidence for LiDAR depth maps and applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-confidence-for-lidar-depth-maps</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Depth perception is pivotal in many fields, such as robotics and autonomous driving, to name a few.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-confidence-for-lidar-depth-maps</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rolling Shutter Inversion: Bring Rolling Shutter Images to High Framerate Global Shutter Video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rolling-shutter-inversion-bring-rolling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The RSSR is a very challenging task, and to our knowledge, no practical solution exists to date.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rolling-shutter-inversion-bring-rolling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Domain Adaptation of Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) Models for Open Domain Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-domain-adaptation-of-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose \textit{RAG-end2end}, an extension to RAG, that can adapt to a domain-specific knowledge base by updating all components of the external knowledge base during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-domain-adaptation-of-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning functional sections in medical conversations: iterative pseudo-labeling and human-in-the-loop approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-functional-sections-in-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an approach that tackles the problem of learning to classify medical dialogue into functional sections without requiring a large number of annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-functional-sections-in-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Softmax, or not to Softmax: that is the question when applying Active Learning for Transformer Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-softmax-or-not-to-softmax-that-is-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite achieving state-of-the-art results in nearly all Natural Language Processing applications, fine-tuning Transformer-based language models still requires a significant amount of labeled data to work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-softmax-or-not-to-softmax-that-is-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modelling Commonsense Properties using Pre-Trained Bi-Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelling-commonsense-properties-using-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Grasping the commonsense properties of everyday concepts is an important prerequisite to language understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelling-commonsense-properties-using-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Review of Uncertainty Calibration in Pretrained Object Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-uncertainty-calibration-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of deep learning based computer vision, the development of deep object detection has led to unique paradigms (e. g., two-stage or set-based) and architectures (e. g., Faster-RCNN or DETR) which enable outstanding performance on challenging benchmark datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-uncertainty-calibration-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask3D for 3D Semantic Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask3d-for-3d-semantic-instance-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern 3D semantic instance segmentation approaches predominantly rely on specialized voting mechanisms followed by carefully designed geometric clustering techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask3d-for-3d-semantic-instance-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grape: Knowledge Graph Enhanced Passage Reader for Open-domain Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grape-knowledge-graph-enhanced-passage-reader</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In light of this, we propose a novel knowledge Graph enhanced passage reader, namely Grape, to improve the reader performance for open-domain QA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grape-knowledge-graph-enhanced-passage-reader</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Entity Typing with Curriculum Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-entity-typing-with-curriculum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these drawbacks, we propose a novel generative entity typing (GET) paradigm: given a text with an entity mention, the multiple types for the role that the entity plays in the text are generated with a pre-trained language model (PLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-entity-typing-with-curriculum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lie Derivative for Measuring Learned Equivariance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-lie-derivative-for-measuring-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to better understand the role of equivariance in recent vision models, we introduce the Lie derivative, a method for measuring equivariance with strong mathematical foundations and minimal hyperparameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-lie-derivative-for-measuring-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models are Multilingual Chain-of-Thought Reasoners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-are-multilingual-chain-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we show that the multilingual reasoning abilities of language models extend to other tasks such as commonsense reasoning and word-in-context semantic judgment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-are-multilingual-chain-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Referring Expression Comprehension via Transformer with Content-aware Query</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-referring-expression-comprehension-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce two new datasets (i. e., VID-Entity and VidSTG-Entity) by augmenting the VIDSentence and VidSTG datasets with the explicitly referred words in the whole sentence, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-referring-expression-comprehension-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaPLe: Multi-modal Prompt Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maple-multi-modal-prompt-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained vision-language (V-L) models such as CLIP have shown excellent generalization ability to downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maple-multi-modal-prompt-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Augmentation-free Unsupervised Learning for 3D Point Cloud Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-free-unsupervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised learning on 3D point clouds has undergone a rapid evolution, especially thanks to data augmentation-based contrastive methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-free-unsupervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure Representation Network and Uncertainty Feedback Learning for Dense Non-Uniform Fog Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-representation-network-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few existing image defogging or dehazing methods consider dense and non-uniform particle distributions, which usually happen in smoke, dust and fog.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-representation-network-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content-Based Search for Deep Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/content-based-search-for-deep-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The growing proliferation of pretrained generative models has made it infeasible for a user to be fully cognizant of every model in existence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/content-based-search-for-deep-generative</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
