<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 21:06:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Guiding the generation of counterfactual explanations through temporal background knowledge for Predictive Process Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-the-generation-of-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we adapt state-of-the-art techniques for counterfactual generation in the domain of XAI that are based on genetic algorithms to consider a series of temporal constraints at runtime.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-the-generation-of-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Generalizing to Unseen Domains with Few Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-generalizing-to-unseen-domains-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing domain generalization (DG) methods which are unable to exploit unlabeled data perform poorly compared to semi-supervised learning (SSL) methods under SSDG setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-generalizing-to-unseen-domains-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking the Robustness of UAV Tracking Against Common Corruptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-the-robustness-of-uav-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing this, we propose UAV-C, a large-scale benchmark for assessing robustness of UAV trackers under common corruptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-the-robustness-of-uav-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Spatial Proximity Reasoning for Vision-and-Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-spatial-proximity-reasoning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most Vision-and-Language Navigation (VLN) algorithms tend to make decision errors, primarily due to a lack of visual common sense and insufficient reasoning capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-spatial-proximity-reasoning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed3DGS: Scalable 3D Gaussian Splatting with Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fed3dgs-scalable-3d-gaussian-splatting-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In pursuit of a more scalable 3D reconstruction, we propose a federated learning framework with 3DGS, which is a decentralized framework and can potentially use distributed computational resources across millions of clients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fed3dgs-scalable-3d-gaussian-splatting-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Align and Distill: Unifying and Improving Domain Adaptive Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/align-and-distill-unifying-and-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address these problems by introducing: (1) A unified benchmarking and implementation framework, Align and Distill (ALDI), enabling comparison of DAOD methods and supporting future development, (2) A fair and modern training and evaluation protocol for DAOD that addresses benchmarking pitfalls, (3) A new DAOD benchmark dataset, CFC-DAOD, enabling evaluation on diverse real-world data, and (4) A new method, ALDI++, that achieves state-of-the-art results by a large margin.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/align-and-distill-unifying-and-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-World Semi-Supervised Learning for Node Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-world-semi-supervised-learning-for-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-world semi-supervised learning (Open-world SSL) for node classification, that classifies unlabeled nodes into seen classes or multiple novel classes, is a practical but under-explored problem in the graph community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-world-semi-supervised-learning-for-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Continual Learning of Vision-Language Models via Mixture-of-Experts Adapters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-continual-learning-of-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual learning can empower vision-language models to continuously acquire new knowledge, without the need for access to the entire historical dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-continual-learning-of-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MineDreamer: Learning to Follow Instructions via Chain-of-Imagination for Simulated-World Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minedreamer-learning-to-follow-instructions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is a long-lasting goal to design a generalist-embodied agent that can follow diverse instructions in human-like ways.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minedreamer-learning-to-follow-instructions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EchoReel: Enhancing Action Generation of Existing Video Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/echoreel-enhancing-action-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent large-scale video datasets have facilitated the generation of diverse open-domain videos of Video Diffusion Models (VDMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/echoreel-enhancing-action-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State-Separated SARSA: A Practical Sequential Decision-Making Algorithm with Recovering Rewards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/state-separated-sarsa-a-practical-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While many multi-armed bandit algorithms assume that rewards for all arms are constant across rounds, this assumption does not hold in many real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/state-separated-sarsa-a-practical-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VmambaIR: Visual State Space Model for Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vmambair-visual-state-space-model-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose VmambaIR, which introduces State Space Models (SSMs) with linear complexity into comprehensive image restoration tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vmambair-visual-state-space-model-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle Representation for Medical Instance Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circle-representation-for-medical-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, circle representation has been introduced for medical imaging, designed specifically to enhance the detection of instance objects that are spherically shaped (e. g., cells, glomeruli, and nuclei).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circle-representation-for-medical-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Calibration by Design for Neural Network Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-calibration-by-design-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the miscalibration issue of neural networks, various methods have been proposed to improve calibration, including post-hoc methods that adjust predictions after training and regularization methods that act during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-calibration-by-design-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling Datasets Into Less Than One Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-datasets-into-less-than-one-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current methods frame this as maximizing the distilled classification accuracy for a budget of K distilled images-per-class, where K is a positive integer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-datasets-into-less-than-one-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiKER-SGG: Hierarchical Knowledge Enhanced Robust Scene Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiker-sgg-hierarchical-knowledge-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Being able to understand visual scenes is a precursor for many downstream tasks, including autonomous driving, robotics, and other vision-based approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiker-sgg-hierarchical-knowledge-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Order-Preserving and Transferability for Neural Architecture Search: a Joint Architecture Refined Search and Fine-tuning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-order-preserving-and-transferability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we analyze the order-preserving ability on the whole search space (global) and a sub-space of top architectures (local), and empirically show that the local order-preserving for current two-stage NAS methods still need to be improved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-order-preserving-and-transferability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoRA-Composer: Leveraging Low-Rank Adaptation for Multi-Concept Customization in Training-Free Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lora-composer-leveraging-low-rank-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Customization generation techniques have significantly advanced the synthesis of specific concepts across varied contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lora-composer-leveraging-low-rank-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HateCOT: An Explanation-Enhanced Dataset for Generalizable Offensive Speech Detection via Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hatecot-an-explanation-enhanced-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that pre-training models for the detection of offensive content on HateCOT significantly boots open-sourced Language Models on three benchmark datasets in both zero and few-shot settings, despite differences in domain and task.}]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hatecot-an-explanation-enhanced-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Forgetting for Pre-trained Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-forgetting-for-pre-trained-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(i) For unwanted knowledge, efficient and effective deleting is crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-forgetting-for-pre-trained-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM^3:Large Language Model-based Task and Motion Planning with Motion Failure Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-3-large-language-model-based-task-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through a series of simulations in a box-packing domain, we quantitatively demonstrate the effectiveness of LLM^3 in solving TAMP problems and the efficiency in selecting action parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-3-large-language-model-based-task-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaVA-UHD: an LMM Perceiving Any Aspect Ratio and High-Resolution Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-uhd-an-lmm-perceiving-any-aspect-ratio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the challenges, we present LLaVA-UHD, a large multimodal model that can efficiently perceive images in any aspect ratio and high resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-uhd-an-lmm-perceiving-any-aspect-ratio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complete and Efficient Graph Transformers for Crystal Material Property Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complete-and-efficient-graph-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Crystal structures are characterized by atomic bases within a primitive unit cell that repeats along a regular lattice throughout 3D space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complete-and-efficient-graph-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Against Adversarial Attacks on No-Reference Image Quality Models with Gradient Norm Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defense-against-adversarial-attacks-on-no</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To be specific, we present theoretical evidence showing that the magnitude of score changes is related to the $\ell_1$ norm of the model's gradient with respect to the input image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defense-against-adversarial-attacks-on-no</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HVDistill: Transferring Knowledge from Images to Point Clouds via Unsupervised Hybrid-View Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hvdistill-transferring-knowledge-from-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a hybrid-view-based knowledge distillation framework, termed HVDistill, to guide the feature learning of a point cloud neural network with a pre-trained image network in an unsupervised man- ner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hvdistill-transferring-knowledge-from-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeisFusion: Constrained Diffusion Model with Input Guidance for 3D Seismic Data Interpolation and Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seisfusion-constrained-diffusion-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response to this challenge, we propose a novel diffusion model reconstruction framework tailored for 3D seismic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seisfusion-constrained-diffusion-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Multi-Source Inference for Text Conditioned Music Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-multi-source-inference-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-Source Diffusion Models (MSDM) allow for compositional musical generation tasks: generating a set of coherent sources, creating accompaniments, and performing source separation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-multi-source-inference-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartRefine: An Scenario-Adaptive Refinement Framework for Efficient Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartrefine-an-scenario-adaptive-refinement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Context information, such as road maps and surrounding agents' states, provides crucial geometric and semantic information for motion behavior prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartrefine-an-scenario-adaptive-refinement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Discriminative Knowledge Learning for Visible-Infrared Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-discriminative-knowledge-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel Implicit Discriminative Knowledge Learning (IDKL) network to uncover and leverage the implicit discriminative information contained within the modality-specific.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-discriminative-knowledge-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAD-Gaussians: Bundle Adjusted Deblur Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bad-gaussians-bundle-adjusted-deblur-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While neural rendering has demonstrated impressive capabilities in 3D scene reconstruction and novel view synthesis, it heavily relies on high-quality sharp images and accurate camera poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bad-gaussians-bundle-adjusted-deblur-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lie Group Approach to Riemannian Batch Normalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lie-group-approach-to-riemannian-batch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using the deformation concept, we generalize the existing Lie groups on SPD manifolds into three families of parameterized Lie groups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lie-group-approach-to-riemannian-batch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Aware Pseudo-Label Filtering for Source-Free Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-pseudo-label-filtering-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Source-free unsupervised domain adaptation (SFUDA) aims to enable the utilization of a pre-trained source model in an unlabeled target domain without access to source data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-pseudo-label-filtering-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MindEye2: Shared-Subject Models Enable fMRI-To-Image With 1 Hour of Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mindeye2-shared-subject-models-enable-fmri-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstructions of visual perception from brain activity have improved tremendously, but the practical utility of such methods has been limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mindeye2-shared-subject-models-enable-fmri-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quality-Aware Image-Text Alignment for Real-World Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quality-aware-image-text-alignment-for-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we introduce a quality-aware image-text alignment strategy to make CLIP generate representations that correlate with the inherent quality of the images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quality-aware-image-text-alignment-for-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised co-salient object detection via feature correspondence at multiple scales</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-co-salient-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on three CoSOD benchmark datasets show that our self-supervised model outperforms the corresponding state-of-the-art models by a huge margin (e. g. on the CoCA dataset, our model has a 13. 7% F-measure gain over the SOTA unsupervised CoSOD model).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-co-salient-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An SDP-based Branch-and-Cut Algorithm for Biclustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-sdp-based-branch-and-cut-algorithm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Biclustering, also called co-clustering, block clustering, or two-way clustering, involves the simultaneous clustering of both the rows and columns of a data matrix into distinct groups, such that the rows and columns within a group display similar patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-sdp-based-branch-and-cut-algorithm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JORA: JAX Tensor-Parallel LoRA Library for Retrieval Augmented Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jora-jax-tensor-parallel-lora-library-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The scaling of Large Language Models (LLMs) for retrieval-based tasks, particularly in Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG), faces significant memory constraints, especially when fine-tuning extensive prompt sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jora-jax-tensor-parallel-lora-library-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPA-Enhancer: Chain-of-Thought Prompted Adaptive Enhancer for Object Detection under Unknown Degradations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cpa-enhancer-chain-of-thought-prompted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object detection methods under known single degradations have been extensively investigated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cpa-enhancer-chain-of-thought-prompted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Markov Random Field for Stereo Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-markov-random-field-for-stereo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stereo matching is a core task for many computer vision and robotics applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-markov-random-field-for-stereo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian multi-exposure image fusion for robust high dynamic range preprocessing in ptychography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-multi-exposure-image-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image information is restricted by the dynamic range of the detector, which can be addressed using multi-exposure image fusion (MEF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-multi-exposure-image-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Makes Math Word Problems Challenging for LLMs?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-makes-math-word-problems-challenging-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the question of what makes math word problems (MWPs) challenging for large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-makes-math-word-problems-challenging-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOv9 for Fracture Detection in Pediatric Wrist Trauma X-ray Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov9-for-fracture-detection-in-pediatric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The introduction of YOLOv9, the latest version of the You Only Look Once (YOLO) series, has led to its widespread adoption across various scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov9-for-fracture-detection-in-pediatric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain-on-Switch: Towards Advanced Intelligent Network Data Plane via NN-Driven Traffic Analysis at Line-Speed</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-on-switch-towards-advanced-intelligent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many types of NNs (such as Recurrent Neural Network (RNN), and transformers) that are designed to work with sequential data have advantages over tree-based models, because they can take raw network data as input without complex feature computations on the fly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-on-switch-towards-advanced-intelligent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Source Prompt Disentangled Inversion for Boosting Image Editability with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/source-prompt-disentangled-inversion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-driven diffusion models have significantly advanced the image editing performance by using text prompts as inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/source-prompt-disentangled-inversion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customizing Visual-Language Foundation Models for Multi-modal Anomaly Detection and Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/customizing-visual-language-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we unify the input representation of multi-modality into a 2D image format, enabling multi-modal anomaly detection and reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/customizing-visual-language-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAG: Guidance-free Open-Vocabulary Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tag-guidance-free-open-vocabulary-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised and open-vocabulary segmentation, proposed to tackle these issues, faces challenges, including the inability to assign specific class labels to clusters and the necessity of user-provided text queries for guidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tag-guidance-free-open-vocabulary-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Data Diversity for Fine-Tuning Language Models in Human Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-data-diversity-for-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, the concept of diversity for prompts can be more complex than responses that are typically quantified by single digits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-data-diversity-for-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconstruct before Query: Continual Missing Modality Learning with Decomposed Prompt Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstruct-before-query-continual-missing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, our RebQ leverages extensive multi-modal knowledge from pre-trained LMMs to reconstruct the data of missing modality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstruct-before-query-continual-missing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Objective Evolutionary Neural Architecture Search for Recurrent Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-evolutionary-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial neural network (NN) architecture design is a nontrivial and time-consuming task that often requires a high level of human expertise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-evolutionary-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaskDiffusion: Exploiting Pre-trained Diffusion Models for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskdiffusion-exploiting-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation is essential in computer vision for various applications, yet traditional approaches face significant challenges, including the high cost of annotation and extensive training for supervised learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskdiffusion-exploiting-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
