<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:12:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>PsySafe: A Comprehensive Framework for Psychological-based Attack, Defense, and Evaluation of Multi-agent System Safety</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psysafe-a-comprehensive-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We anticipate that our framework and observations will provide valuable insights for further research into the safety of multi-agent systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psysafe-a-comprehensive-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUMBoost: Gradient Boosted Random Utility Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rumboost-gradient-boosted-random-utility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce additional constraints on the ensembles to ensure three crucial features of the utility specifications: (i) dependency of the utilities of each alternative on only the attributes of that alternative, (ii) monotonicity of marginal utilities, and (iii) an intrinsically interpretable functional form, where the exact response of the model is known throughout the entire input space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rumboost-gradient-boosted-random-utility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LightDiC: A Simple yet Effective Approach for Large-scale Digraph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightdic-a-simple-yet-effective-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing graph neural networks (GNNs) are limited to undirected graphs, whose restricted scope of the captured relational information hinders their expressive capabilities and deployments in real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightdic-a-simple-yet-effective-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Statistical Significance and Discriminative Power in Pattern Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-statistical-significance-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pattern discovery plays a central role in both descriptive and predictive tasks across multiple domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-statistical-significance-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VRMN-bD: A Multi-modal Natural Behavior Dataset of Immersive Human Fear Responses in VR Stand-up Interactive Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vrmn-bd-a-multi-modal-natural-behavior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding and recognizing emotions are important and challenging issues in the metaverse era.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vrmn-bd-a-multi-modal-natural-behavior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuroSynt: A Neuro-symbolic Portfolio Solver for Reactive Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurosynt-a-neuro-symbolic-portfolio-solver</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the core of the solver lies a seamless integration of neural and symbolic approaches to solving the reactive synthesis problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurosynt-a-neuro-symbolic-portfolio-solver</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Blind Spots in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-blind-spots-in-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we aim to investigate the underlying limitations of general-purpose LLMs when deployed for tasks that require a temporal understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-blind-spots-in-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Text-to-Image Diffusion: Recaptioning, Planning, and Generating with Multimodal LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mastering-text-to-image-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a brand new training-free text-to-image generation/editing framework, namely Recaption, Plan and Generate (RPG), harnessing the powerful chain-of-thought reasoning ability of multimodal LLMs to enhance the compositionality of text-to-image diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mastering-text-to-image-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TurboSVM-FL: Boosting Federated Learning through SVM Aggregation for Lazy Clients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/turbosvm-fl-boosting-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is a distributed collaborative machine learning paradigm that has gained strong momentum in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/turbosvm-fl-boosting-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Fair Evaluation of Various Deep Learning-Based Document Image Binarization Approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fair-evaluation-of-various-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate them on different Document Image Binarization Contest (DIBCO) datasets and obtain very heterogeneous results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fair-evaluation-of-various-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedGTA: Topology-aware Averaging for Federated Graph Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedgta-topology-aware-averaging-for-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing FGL studies fall into two categories: (i) FGL Optimization, which improves multi-client training in existing machine learning models; (ii) FGL Model, which enhances performance with complex local models and multi-client interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedgta-topology-aware-averaging-for-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broiler-Net: A Deep Convolutional Framework for Broiler Behavior Analysis in Poultry Houses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/broiler-net-a-deep-convolutional-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting anomalies in poultry houses is crucial for maintaining optimal chicken health conditions, minimizing economic losses and bolstering profitability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/broiler-net-a-deep-convolutional-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond TreeSHAP: Efficient Computation of Any-Order Shapley Interactions for Tree Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-treeshap-efficient-computation-of-any</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While shallow decision trees may be interpretable, larger ensemble models like gradient-boosted trees, which often set the state of the art in machine learning problems involving tabular data, still remain black box models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-treeshap-efficient-computation-of-any</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALMs: Authorial Language Models for Authorship Attribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alms-authorial-language-models-for-authorship</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce an authorship attribution method called Authorial Language Models (ALMs) that involves identifying the most likely author of a questioned document based on the perplexity of the questioned document calculated for a set of causal language models fine-tuned on the writings of a set of candidate author.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alms-authorial-language-models-for-authorship</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Machine Learning for the Classification of Astrophysical X-ray Sources</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-machine-learning-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide a catalog of probabilistic classes for 8, 756 sources, comprising a total of 14, 507 detections, and demonstrate the success of the method at identifying emission from young stellar objects, as well as distinguishing between small-scale and large-scale compact accretors with a significant level of confidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-machine-learning-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Neurons in GPT2 Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-neurons-in-gpt2-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In other words, are neural mechanisms universal across different models?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-neurons-in-gpt2-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointGL: A Simple Global-Local Framework for Efficient Point Cloud Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointgl-a-simple-global-local-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficient analysis of point clouds holds paramount significance in real-world 3D applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointgl-a-simple-global-local-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admission Prediction in Undergraduate Applications: an Interpretable Deep Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/admission-prediction-in-undergraduate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article addresses the challenge of validating the admission committee's decisions for undergraduate admissions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/admission-prediction-in-undergraduate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NLCG-Net: A Model-Based Zero-Shot Learning Framework for Undersampled Quantitative MRI Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlcg-net-a-model-based-zero-shot-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Typical quantitative MRI (qMRI) methods estimate parameter maps after image reconstructing, which is prone to biases and error propagation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlcg-net-a-model-based-zero-shot-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Navigation: Inferring the Interlocking Map of Knowledge from Research Trajectories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-navigation-inferring-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA["If I have seen further, it is by standing on the shoulders of giants," Isaac Newton's renowned statement hints that new knowledge builds upon existing foundations, which means there exists an interdependent relationship between knowledge, which, yet uncovered, is implied in the historical development of scientific systems for hundreds of years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-navigation-inferring-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Effective and General Graph Unlearning via Mutual Evolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-effective-and-general-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid advancement of AI applications, the growing needs for data privacy and model robustness have highlighted the importance of machine unlearning, especially in thriving graph-based scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-effective-and-general-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GI-PIP: Do We Require Impractical Auxiliary Dataset for Gradient Inversion Attacks?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gi-pip-do-we-require-impractical-auxiliary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep gradient inversion attacks expose a serious threat to Federated Learning (FL) by accurately recovering private data from shared gradients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gi-pip-do-we-require-impractical-auxiliary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subgroup analysis methods for time-to-event outcomes in heterogeneous randomized controlled trials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subgroup-analysis-methods-for-time-to-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identifying such heterogeneous treatment effects is key for precision medicine and many post-hoc analysis methods have been developed for that purpose.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subgroup-analysis-methods-for-time-to-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SFC: Shared Feature Calibration in Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfc-shared-feature-calibration-in-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we leverage the class prototypes that carry positive shared features and propose a Multi-Scaled Distribution-Weighted (MSDW) consistency loss for narrowing the gap between the CAMs generated through classifier weights and class prototypes during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfc-shared-feature-calibration-in-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Large Multimodal Models against Common Corruptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-multimodal-models-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This technical report aims to fill a deficiency in the assessment of large multimodal models (LMMs) by specifically examining the self-consistency of their outputs when subjected to common corruptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-multimodal-models-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less Could Be Better: Parameter-efficient Fine-tuning Advances Medical Vision Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-could-be-better-parameter-efficient-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parameter-efficient fine-tuning (PEFT) that was initially developed for exploiting pre-trained large language models has recently emerged as an effective approach to perform transfer learning on computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-could-be-better-parameter-efficient-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Labeling the Job Shop Scheduling Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-labeling-the-job-shop-scheduling-problem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by Semi- and Self-Supervised learning, we show that it is possible to easily train generative models by sampling multiple solutions and using the best one according to the problem objective as a pseudo-label.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-labeling-the-job-shop-scheduling-problem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VQC-Based Reinforcement Learning with Data Re-uploading: Performance and Trainability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vqc-based-reinforcement-learning-with-data-re</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work empirically studies the performance and trainability of such VQC-based Deep Q-Learning models in classic control benchmark environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vqc-based-reinforcement-learning-with-data-re</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models as Hierarchy Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-as-hierarchy-encoders</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interpreting hierarchical structures latent in language is a key limitation of current language models (LMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-as-hierarchy-encoders</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEBERTNets: Sequence Enhanced BERT Networks for Event Entity Extraction Tasks Oriented to the Finance Field</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sebertnets-sequence-enhanced-bert-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, motivated by recommendation system, we propose Hybrid Sequence Enhanced BERT Networks (HSEBERTNets for short), which uses a multi-channel recall method to recall all the corresponding event entity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sebertnets-sequence-enhanced-bert-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MolTailor: Tailoring Chemical Molecular Representation to Specific Tasks via Text Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moltailor-tailoring-chemical-molecular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The agent accentuates task-relevant features in the molecular representation by understanding the natural language description of the task, just as a tailor customizes clothes for clients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moltailor-tailoring-chemical-molecular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient local linearity regularization to overcome catastrophic overfitting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-local-linearity-regularization-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our regularization term can be theoretically linked to curvature of the loss function and is computationally cheaper than previous methods by avoiding Double Backpropagation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-local-linearity-regularization-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Reliable and Factual Response Generation: Detecting Unanswerable Questions in Information-Seeking Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-reliable-and-factual-response</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our proposed method employs a sentence-level classifier to detect if the answer is present, then aggregates these predictions on the passage level, and eventually across the top-ranked passages to arrive at a final answerability estimate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-reliable-and-factual-response</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Evaluation Measures for Evaluating Social Biases in Masked Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-evaluation-measures-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many evaluation measures are used to evaluate social biases in masked language models (MLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-evaluation-measures-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over-Reasoning and Redundant Calculation of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/over-reasoning-and-redundant-calculation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) can solve problems step-by-step.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/over-reasoning-and-redundant-calculation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear Alignment: A Closed-form Solution for Aligning Human Preferences without Tuning and Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-alignment-a-closed-form-solution-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This reliance limits the applicability of RLHF and hinders the development of professional assistants tailored to diverse human preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-alignment-a-closed-form-solution-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InferAligner: Inference-Time Alignment for Harmlessness through Cross-Model Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferaligner-inference-time-alignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid development of large language models (LLMs), they are not only used as general-purpose AI assistants but are also customized through further fine-tuning to meet the requirements of different applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferaligner-inference-time-alignment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Duality in Open Information Extraction with Predicate Prompt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-duality-in-open-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open information extraction (OpenIE) aims to extract the schema-free triplets in the form of (\emph{subject}, \emph{predicate}, \emph{object}) from a given sentence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-duality-in-open-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreeMIL: A Multi-instance Learning Framework for Time Series Anomaly Detection with Inexact Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treemil-a-multi-instance-learning-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, the subsequence features are extracted to determine the presence of collective anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treemil-a-multi-instance-learning-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Term Fair Decision Making through Deep Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-term-fair-decision-making-through-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies long-term fair machine learning which aims to mitigate group disparity over the long term in sequential decision-making systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-term-fair-decision-making-through-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Fusion of Multimodal Electronic Health Records for Better Medical Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-fusion-of-multimodal-electronic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The widespread adoption of Electronic Health Record (EHR) systems in healthcare institutes has generated vast amounts of medical data, offering significant opportunities for improving healthcare services through deep learning techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-fusion-of-multimodal-electronic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Argument Mining over Varying Rhetorical Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-argument-mining-over-varying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rhetorical Structure Theory implies no single discourse interpretation of a text, and the limitations of RST parsers further exacerbate inconsistent parsing of similar structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-argument-mining-over-varying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel-Wise Recognition for Holistic Surgical Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixel-wise-recognition-for-holistic-surgical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the Holistic and Multi-Granular Surgical Scene Understanding of Prostatectomies (GraSP) dataset, a curated benchmark that models surgical scene understanding as a hierarchy of complementary tasks with varying levels of granularity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixel-wise-recognition-for-holistic-surgical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Latent Vulnerabilities Hidden Gems for Software Vulnerability Prediction? An Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-latent-vulnerabilities-hidden-gems-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge these gaps, we conduct a large-scale study on the latent vulnerable functions in two commonly used SV datasets and their utilization for function-level and line-level SV predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-latent-vulnerabilities-hidden-gems-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedRKG: A Privacy-preserving Federated Recommendation Framework via Knowledge Graph Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedrkg-a-privacy-preserving-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) has emerged as a promising approach for preserving data privacy in recommendation systems by training models locally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedrkg-a-privacy-preserving-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VONet: Unsupervised Video Object Learning With Parallel U-Net Attention and Object-wise Sequential VAE</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vonet-unsupervised-video-object-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised video object learning seeks to decompose video scenes into structural object representations without any supervision from depth, optical flow, or segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vonet-unsupervised-video-object-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Global-Local Representation Learning and Selection for Cross-Domain Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-global-local-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the framework consists of separate global-local adversarial learning modules that learn domain-invariant global and local features independently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-global-local-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coevolving Artistic Images Using OMNIREP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coevolving-artistic-images-using-omnirep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We have recently developed OMNIREP, a coevolutionary algorithm to discover both a representation and an interpreter that solve a particular problem of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coevolving-artistic-images-using-omnirep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the Gap between TD Learning and Supervised Learning -- A Generalisation Point of View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-gap-between-td-learning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this analysis, we construct new datasets to explicitly test for this property, revealing that SL-based methods lack this stitching property and hence fail to perform combinatorial generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-gap-between-td-learning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Policy Distance for Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-policy-distance-for-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we extend MAPD to a customizable version, which can quantify differences among agent policies on specified aspects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-policy-distance-for-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
