<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 21:10:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Detect Multi-class Anomalies with Just One Normal Image Prompt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-detect-multi-class-anomalies-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these self-attention reconstruction models primarily operate on target features, which may result in perfect reconstruction for both normal and anomaly features due to high consistency with context, leading to failure in detecting anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-detect-multi-class-anomalies-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Train a Multi-Task Diffusion Policy on RLBench-18 in One Day with One GPU</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/train-a-multi-task-diffusion-policy-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a method for training multi-task vision-language robotic diffusion policies that reduces training time and memory usage by an order of magnitude.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/train-a-multi-task-diffusion-policy-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layered Unlearning for Adversarial Relearning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layered-unlearning-for-adversarial-relearning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our goal is to understand how post-training methods, such as fine-tuning, alignment, and unlearning, modify language model behavior and representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layered-unlearning-for-adversarial-relearning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARCANE -- Early Detection of Interplanetary Coronal Mass Ejections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arcane-early-detection-of-interplanetary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interplanetary coronal mass ejections (ICMEs) are major drivers of space weather disturbances, posing risks to both technological infrastructure and human activities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arcane-early-detection-of-interplanetary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaUAS: Universal Anomaly Segmentation with One-Prompt Meta-Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metauas-universal-anomaly-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paradigm enables us to leverage large-scale synthetic image pairs, featuring object-level and local region changes, derived from existing image datasets, which are independent of target anomaly datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metauas-universal-anomaly-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAKE: Multi-Aspect Knowledge-Enhanced Vision-Language Pretraining for Zero-shot Dermatological Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-multi-aspect-knowledge-enhanced-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dermatological diagnosis represents a complex multimodal challenge that requires integrating visual features with specialized clinical knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-multi-aspect-knowledge-enhanced-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spec2VolCAMU-Net: A Spectrogram-to-Volume Model for EEG-to-fMRI Reconstruction based on Multi-directional Time-Frequency Convolutional Attention Encoder and Vision-Mamba U-Net</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spec2volcamu-net-a-spectrogram-to-volume</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-resolution functional magnetic resonance imaging (fMRI) is essential for mapping human brain activity; however, it remains costly and logistically challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spec2volcamu-net-a-spectrogram-to-volume</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting butterfly species presence from satellite imagery using soft contrastive regularisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-butterfly-species-presence-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The growing demand for scalable biodiversity monitoring methods has fuelled interest in remote sensing data, due to its widespread availability and extensive coverage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-butterfly-species-presence-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APR-Transformer: Initial Pose Estimation for Localization in Complex Environments through Absolute Pose Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apr-transformer-initial-pose-estimation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Precise initialization plays a critical role in the performance of localization algorithms, especially in the context of robotics, autonomous driving, and computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apr-transformer-initial-pose-estimation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marigold: Affordable Adaptation of Diffusion-Based Image Generators for Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marigold-affordable-adaptation-of-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of deep learning in computer vision over the past decade has hinged on large labeled datasets and strong pretrained models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marigold-affordable-adaptation-of-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TopoDiT-3D: Topology-Aware Diffusion Transformer with Bottleneck Structure for 3D Point Cloud Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topodit-3d-topology-aware-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose TopoDiT-3D, a Topology-Aware Diffusion Transformer with a bottleneck structure for 3D point cloud generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topodit-3d-topology-aware-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Mixed Precision Quantization in Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-mixed-precision-quantization-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mixed precision quantization emerges as a promising solution to enhance the efficiency of GNN architectures without compromising prediction performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-mixed-precision-quantization-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAD Neural Networks: Divergent Gradient Flows and Asymptotic Optimality via o-minimal Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sad-neural-networks-divergent-gradient-flows</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that the gradient flow either converges to a critical point or diverges to infinity while the loss converges to an asymptotic critical value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sad-neural-networks-divergent-gradient-flows</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Point Cloud Patches Rendering via Splitting 2D Gaussians</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-point-cloud-patches-rendering-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, we introduce a novel point cloud rendering method by predicting 2D Gaussians from point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-point-cloud-patches-rendering-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Isolation Forest</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-isolation-forest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The anomaly detection literature is abundant with offline methods, which require repeated access to data in memory, and impose impractical assumptions when applied to a streaming context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-isolation-forest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Computations for Generalized Mixed Effects Models with Crossed Random Effects Using Krylov Subspace Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-computations-for-generalized-mixed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mixed effects models are widely used for modeling data with hierarchically grouped structures and high-cardinality categorical predictor variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-computations-for-generalized-mixed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLIP3-o: A Family of Fully Open Unified Multimodal Models-Architecture, Training and Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blip3-o-a-family-of-fully-open-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on our innovative model design, training recipe, and datasets, we develop BLIP3-o, a suite of state-of-the-art unified multimodal models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blip3-o-a-family-of-fully-open-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenLKA: An Open Dataset of Lane Keeping Assist from Recent Car Models under Real-world Driving Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openlka-an-open-dataset-of-lane-keeping-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lane Keeping Assist (LKA) is widely adopted in modern vehicles, yet its real-world performance remains underexplored due to proprietary systems and limited data access.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openlka-an-open-dataset-of-lane-keeping-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Prefix Tuning for Diverse and Accurate Code Summarization Using Pre-trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-prefix-tuning-for-diverse-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in source code summarization have leveraged transformer-based pre-trained models, including Large Language Models of Code (LLMCs), to automate and improve the generation of code summaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-prefix-tuning-for-diverse-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaFortiTran: An Adaptive Transformer Model for Robust OFDM Channel Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adafortitran-an-adaptive-transformer-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning models for channel estimation in Orthogonal Frequency Division Multiplexing (OFDM) systems often suffer from performance degradation under fast-fading channels and low-SNR scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adafortitran-an-adaptive-transformer-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EDBench: Large-Scale Electron Density Data for Molecular Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edbench-large-scale-electron-density-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing molecular machine learning force fields (MLFFs) generally focus on the learning of atoms, molecules, and simple quantum chemical properties (such as energy and force), but ignore the importance of electron density (ED) $\rho(r)$ in accurately understanding molecular force fields (MFFs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edbench-large-scale-electron-density-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ranking-Based At-Risk Student Prediction Using Federated Learning and Differential Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ranking-based-at-risk-student-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such textbooks yield learning log data that have been used in numerous educational data mining (EDM) studies for student behavior analysis and performance prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ranking-based-at-risk-student-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACTors: A New Dataset for Studying the Fact-checking Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factors-a-new-dataset-for-studying-the-fact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It contains 118, 112 claims from 117, 993 fact-checking reports in English (co-)authored by 1, 953 individuals and published during the period of 1995-2025 by 39 fact-checking organisations that are active signatories of the IFCN (International Fact-Checking Network) and/or EFCSN (European Fact-Checking Standards Network).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factors-a-new-dataset-for-studying-the-fact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atomic Consistency Preference Optimization for Long-Form Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomic-consistency-preference-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) frequently produce factoid hallucinations - plausible yet incorrect answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomic-consistency-preference-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focus, Merge, Rank: Improved Question Answering Based on Semi-structured Knowledge Bases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focus-merge-rank-improved-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many real-world settings, machine learning models and interactive systems have access to both structured knowledge, e. g., knowledge graphs or tables, and unstructured content, e. g., natural language documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focus-merge-rank-improved-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CXMArena: Unified Dataset to benchmark performance in realistic CXM Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cxmarena-unified-dataset-to-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) hold immense potential for revolutionizing Customer Experience Management (CXM), particularly in contact center operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cxmarena-unified-dataset-to-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UMotion: Uncertainty-driven Human Motion Estimation from Inertial and Ultra-wideband Units</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/umotion-uncertainty-driven-human-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse wearable inertial measurement units (IMUs) have gained popularity for estimating 3D human motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/umotion-uncertainty-driven-human-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WavReward: Spoken Dialogue Models With Generalist Reward Evaluators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavreward-spoken-dialogue-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we propose WavReward, a reward feedback model based on audio language models that can evaluate both the IQ and EQ of spoken dialogue systems with speech input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavreward-spoken-dialogue-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Robustness of Adversarial Defenses in Malware Detection Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-robustness-of-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarially trained defenses, including AT-rFGSM-k, AT-MaxMA, improves robustness under small budgets but remains vulnerable to unrestricted perturbations, with attack success rates of 99. 45% and 96. 62%, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-robustness-of-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Shot Anomaly-Driven Generation for Anomaly Classification and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-anomaly-driven-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experiments demonstrate that our generated anomalies effectively improve the model performance of both anomaly classification and segmentation tasks simultaneously, \eg, DRAEM and DseTSeg achieved a 5. 8\% and 1. 5\% improvement in AU-PR metric on segmentation task, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-anomaly-driven-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRRNet: Macro-Micro Feature Fusion and Dual Reverse Refinement for Camouflaged Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drrnet-macro-micro-feature-fusion-and-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the decoder, we also introduce a reverse refinement module that leverages spatial edge priors and frequency-domain noise suppression to perform a two-stage inverse refinement of the output.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drrnet-macro-micro-feature-fusion-and-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Fair Federated Learning under Demographic Disparities and Data Imbalance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-fair-federated-learning-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ensuring fairness is critical when applying artificial intelligence to high-stakes domains such as healthcare, where predictive models trained on imbalanced and demographically skewed data risk exacerbating existing disparities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-fair-federated-learning-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distance-aware Self-adaptive Graph Convolution for Fine-grained Hierarchical Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-aware-self-adaptive-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Convolutional Networks (GCNs) are widely used to improve recommendation accuracy and performance by effectively learning the representations of user and item nodes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-aware-self-adaptive-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable and Convexified Information Bottleneck Optimization via Symbolic Continuation and Entropy-Regularized Trajectories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-and-convexified-information-bottleneck</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Information Bottleneck (IB) method frequently suffers from unstable optimization, characterized by abrupt representation shifts near critical points of the IB trade-off parameter, beta.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-and-convexified-information-bottleneck</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUST: Multi-Scale Structural-Temporal Link Prediction Model for UAV Ad Hoc Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/must-multi-scale-structural-temporal-link</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In adversarial environments where the route information of UAVs is unavailable, predicting future links must rely solely on the observed historical topological information of UANETs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/must-multi-scale-structural-temporal-link</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformal Bounds on Full-Reference Image Quality for Imaging Inverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-bounds-on-full-reference-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In imaging inverse problems, we would like to know how close the recovered image is to the true image in terms of full-reference image quality (FRIQ) metrics like PSNR, SSIM, LPIPS, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-bounds-on-full-reference-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Multi-modal Large Language Model v.s. Supervised Deep Learning: A Comparative Study on CT-Based Intracranial Hemorrhage Subtyping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-multi-modal-large-language-model-v</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study evaluates the performance of zero-shot multi-modal large language models (MLLMs) compared to traditional deep learning methods in ICH binary classification and subtyping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-multi-modal-large-language-model-v</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Learning with Augmented Class via Forests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-learning-with-augmented-class-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we focus on learning with augmented class via forests, where an augmented class may appear in testing data yet not in training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-learning-with-augmented-class-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reproducibility Study of "Cooperate or Collapse: Emergence of Sustainable Cooperation in a Society of LLM Agents"</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducibility-study-of-cooperate-or</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study evaluates and extends the findings made by Piatti et al., who introduced GovSim, a simulation framework designed to assess the cooperative decision-making capabilities of large language models (LLMs) in resource-sharing scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducibility-study-of-cooperate-or</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contactless Cardiac Pulse Monitoring Using Event Cameras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contactless-cardiac-pulse-monitoring-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An end-to-end model is trained to extract the cardiac signal from a two-dimensional representation of the event stream, with model performance evaluated based on the accuracy of the calculated heart rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contactless-cardiac-pulse-monitoring-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAP-based Explanations are Sensitive to Feature Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shap-based-explanations-are-sensitive-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper examines the impact of data engineering choices on local feature-based explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shap-based-explanations-are-sensitive-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Social Robot with Inner Speech for Dietary Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-social-robot-with-inner-speech-for-dietary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore the use of inner speech as a mechanism to enhance transparency and trust in social robots for dietary advice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-social-robot-with-inner-speech-for-dietary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skeleton-Guided Diffusion Model for Accurate Foot X-ray Synthesis in Hallux Valgus Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-guided-diffusion-model-for-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image synthesis plays a crucial role in providing anatomically accurate images for diagnosis and treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-guided-diffusion-model-for-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judging the Judges: Can Large Vision-Language Models Fairly Evaluate Chart Comprehension and Reasoning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/judging-the-judges-can-large-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While using LVLMs as judges to assess the chart comprehension capabilities of other LVLMs could streamline evaluation processes, challenges like proprietary datasets, restricted access to powerful models, and evaluation costs hinder their adoption in industrial settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/judging-the-judges-can-large-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large-Scale Empirical Analysis of Custom GPTs' Vulnerabilities in the OpenAI Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-empirical-analysis-of-custom</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we analyze 14, 904 custom GPTs to assess their susceptibility to seven exploitable threats, such as roleplay-based attacks, system prompt leakage, phishing content generation, and malicious code synthesis, across various categories and popularity tiers within the OpenAI marketplace.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-empirical-analysis-of-custom</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSurgSAM2: Referring Segment Anything in Surgical Video via Credible Long-term Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resurgsam2-referring-segment-anything-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce ReSurgSAM2, a two-stage surgical referring segmentation framework that leverages Segment Anything Model 2 to perform text-referred target detection, followed by tracking with reliable initial frame identification and diversity-driven long-term memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resurgsam2-referring-segment-anything-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieving Scalable Robot Autonomy via neurosymbolic planning using lightweight local LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-scalable-robot-autonomy-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PDDL-based symbolic task planning remains pivotal for robot autonomy yet struggles with dynamic human-robot collaboration due to scalability, re-planning demands, and delayed plan availability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-scalable-robot-autonomy-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rejoining fragmented ancient bamboo slips with physics-driven deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rejoining-fragmented-ancient-bamboo-slips</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach enables the training of a matching network without requiring manually paired samples, providing ranked suggestions to facilitate the rejoining process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rejoining-fragmented-ancient-bamboo-slips</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model Psychometrics: A Systematic Review of Evaluation, Validation, and Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-psychometrics-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of large language models (LLMs) has outpaced traditional evaluation methodologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-psychometrics-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAT: Benchmark for Auto-bidding Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bat-benchmark-for-auto-bidding-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The optimization of bidding strategies for online advertising slot auctions presents a critical challenge across numerous digital marketplaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bat-benchmark-for-auto-bidding-task</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
