<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 09:12:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Chain-of-Thought Reasoning in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-chain-of-thought-reasoning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating the vision features in both stages, the model is able to generate effective rationales that contribute to answer inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-chain-of-thought-reasoning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-precision regressors for particle physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-precision-regressors-for-particle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the necessary number of data points per simulation is on the order of $10^9$ - $10^{12}$, machine learning regressors can be used in place of physics simulators to significantly reduce this computational burden.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-precision-regressors-for-particle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Collapse Inspired Feature-Classifier Alignment for Few-Shot Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-collapse-inspired-feature-classifier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we deal with this misalignment dilemma in FSCIL inspired by the recently discovered phenomenon named neural collapse, which reveals that the last-layer features of the same class will collapse into a vertex, and the vertices of all classes are aligned with the classifier prototypes, which are formed as a simplex equiangular tight frame (ETF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-collapse-inspired-feature-classifier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over-parameterised Shallow Neural Networks with Asymmetrical Node Scaling: Global Convergence Guarantees and Feature Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/over-parameterised-shallow-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the optimisation of large and shallow neural networks via gradient flow, where the output of each hidden node is scaled by some positive parameter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/over-parameterised-shallow-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuro Symbolic Continual Learning: Knowledge, Reasoning Shortcuts and Concept Rehearsal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-continual-learning-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Neuro-Symbolic Continual Learning, where a model has to solve a sequence of neuro-symbolic tasks, that is, it has to map sub-symbolic inputs to high-level concepts and compute predictions by reasoning consistently with prior knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-continual-learning-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$IC^3$: Image Captioning by Committee Consensus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ic-3-image-captioning-by-committee-consensus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[If you ask a human to describe an image, they might do so in a thousand different ways.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ic-3-image-captioning-by-committee-consensus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Metric Learning for Uncertainty Quantification in Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-metric-learning-for-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the first Bayesian encoder for metric learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-metric-learning-for-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paced-Curriculum Distillation with Prediction and Label Uncertainty for Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paced-curriculum-distillation-with-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Purpose: In curriculum learning, the idea is to train on easier samples first and gradually increase the difficulty, while in self-paced learning, a pacing function defines the speed to adapt the training progress.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paced-curriculum-distillation-with-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphReg: Dynamical Point Cloud Registration with Geometry-aware Graph Signal Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphreg-dynamical-point-cloud-registration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results demonstrate that our proposed method outperforms representative state-of-the-art approaches in terms of accuracy and is more suitable for registering large-scale point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphreg-dynamical-point-cloud-registration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empirical Analysis of the AdaBoost's Error Bound</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-analysis-of-the-adaboost-s-error</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the accuracy limits of machine learning algorithms is essential for data scientists to properly measure performance so they can continually improve their models' predictive capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-analysis-of-the-adaboost-s-error</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Coherence Markers for the Early Diagnosis of the Alzheimer Disease</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-coherence-markers-for-the-early</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we explore how language models can be employed to analyze language and discriminate between mentally impaired and healthy subjects through the perplexity metric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-coherence-markers-for-the-early</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Ensemble of Low-fidelity Experts: Mitigating NAS "Cold-Start"</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-ensemble-of-low-fidelity-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first step, we train different sub-predictors on different types of available low-fidelity information to extract beneficial knowledge as low-fidelity experts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-ensemble-of-low-fidelity-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KST-Mixer: Kinematic Spatio-Temporal Data Mixer For Colon Shape Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kst-mixer-kinematic-spatio-temporal-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Kinematic data of a colonoscope and the colon, including positions and directions of their centerlines, are obtained using electromagnetic and depth sensors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kst-mixer-kinematic-spatio-temporal-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laplacian Change Point Detection for Single and Multi-view Dynamic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplacian-change-point-detection-for-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[how to capture temporal dependencies, and iii).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplacian-change-point-detection-for-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exposing the CSI: A Systematic Investigation of CSI-based Wi-Fi Sensing Capabilities and Limitations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposing-the-csi-a-systematic-investigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We leverage our dataset to dissect the performance of a state-of-the-art sensing framework across different environments and individuals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposing-the-csi-a-systematic-investigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenSpike: An OpenRAM SNN Accelerator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openspike-an-openram-snn-accelerator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a spiking neural network (SNN) accelerator made using fully open-source EDA tools, process design kit (PDK), and memory macros synthesized using OpenRAM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openspike-an-openram-snn-accelerator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech Enhancement for Virtual Meetings on Cellular Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-enhancement-for-virtual-meetings-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study speech enhancement using deep learning (DL) for virtual meetings on cellular devices, where transmitted speech has background noise and transmission loss that affects speech quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-enhancement-for-virtual-meetings-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Baseline for Direct 2D Multi-Person Head Pose Estimation with Full-range Angles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-baseline-for-direct-2d-multi-person</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present comprehensive comparisons with state-of-the-art single HPE methods on public benchmarks, as well as superior baseline results on our constructed MPHPE datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-baseline-for-direct-2d-multi-person</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Efficacy of Differentially Private Few-shot Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-efficacy-of-differentially-private-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To understand under which conditions few-shot DP can be effective, we perform an exhaustive set of experiments that reveals how the accuracy and vulnerability to attack of few-shot DP image classification models are affected as the number of shots per class, privacy level, model architecture, dataset, and subset of learnable parameters in the model vary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-efficacy-of-differentially-private-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy Expansion for Bridging Offline-to-Online Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-expansion-for-bridging-offline-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With this approach, the policy previously learned offline is fully retained during online learning, thus mitigating the potential issues such as destroying the useful behaviors of the offline policy in the initial stage of online learning while allowing the offline policy participate in the exploration naturally in an adaptive manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-expansion-for-bridging-offline-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperspectral Image Classification Using Deep Matrix Capsules</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperspectral-image-classification-using-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperspectral image (HSI) classification is used in multiple domains like precision agriculture, mineral exploration, remote sensing, and others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperspectral-image-classification-using-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEPS: Joint Self-supervised Nighttime Image Enhancement and Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steps-joint-self-supervised-nighttime-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By fitting a bridge-shaped curve to the illumination map distribution, both regions are suppressed and two tasks are bridged naturally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steps-joint-self-supervised-nighttime-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tab2KG: Semantic Table Interpretation with Lightweight Semantic Profiles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tab2kg-semantic-table-interpretation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a one-shot learning approach that relies on these profiles to map a tabular dataset containing previously unseen instances to a domain ontology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tab2kg-semantic-table-interpretation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDJIR: Neural Direct and Joint Inverse Rendering for Geometry, Lights, and Materials of Real Object</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ndjir-neural-direct-and-joint-inverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of inverse rendering is to decompose geometry, lights, and materials given pose multi-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ndjir-neural-direct-and-joint-inverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No One Left Behind: Real-World Federated Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-one-left-behind-real-world-federated-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle the above issues, we propose a novel Local-Global Anti-forgetting (LGA) model to address local and global catastrophic forgetting on old categories, which is a pioneering work to explore a global class-incremental model in the FL feld.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-one-left-behind-real-world-federated-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADAPT: Action-aware Driving Caption Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapt-action-aware-driving-caption</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge the gap, we propose an end-to-end transformer-based architecture, ADAPT (Action-aware Driving cAPtion Transformer), which provides user-friendly natural language narrations and reasoning for each decision making step of autonomous vehicular control and action.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapt-action-aware-driving-caption</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deterministic equivalent and error universality of deep random features learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deterministic-equivalent-and-error</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Establishing this result requires proving a deterministic equivalent for traces of the deep random features sample covariance matrices which can be of independent interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deterministic-equivalent-and-error</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An automated, geometry-based method for the analysis of hippocampal thickness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-automated-geometry-based-method-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose an automated, geometry-based approach for the unfolding, point-wise correspondence, and local analysis of hippocampal shape features such as thickness and curvature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-automated-geometry-based-method-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster Convergence with Lexicase Selection in Tree-based Automated Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-convergence-with-lexicase-selection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many evolutionary computation systems, parent selection methods can affect, among other things, convergence to a solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-convergence-with-lexicase-selection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Power Laws for Hyperparameter Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-power-laws-for-hyperparameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperparameter optimization is an important subfield of machine learning that focuses on tuning the hyperparameters of a chosen algorithm to achieve peak performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-power-laws-for-hyperparameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HunSum-1: an Abstractive Summarization Dataset for Hungarian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunsum-1-an-abstractive-summarization-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce HunSum-1: a dataset for Hungarian abstractive summarization, consisting of 1. 14M news articles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunsum-1-an-abstractive-summarization-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Learning of Deep Random Networks of Extensive-width</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-learning-of-deep-random-networks-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of learning a target function corresponding to a deep, extensive-width, non-linear neural network with random Gaussian weights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-learning-of-deep-random-networks-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For the Underrepresented in Gender Bias Research: Chinese Name Gender Prediction with Heterogeneous Graph Attention Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/for-the-underrepresented-in-gender-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We open-source a more balanced multi-character dataset from an official source together with our code, hoping to help future research promoting gender equality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/for-the-underrepresented-in-gender-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AmbiCoref: Evaluating Human and Model Sensitivity to Ambiguous Coreference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambicoref-evaluating-human-and-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we construct AmbiCoref, a diagnostic corpus of minimal sentence pairs with ambiguous and unambiguous referents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambicoref-evaluating-human-and-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPIDE: A Purely Spike-based Method for Training Feedback Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spide-a-purely-spike-based-method-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study spike-based implicit differentiation on the equilibrium state (SPIDE) that extends the recently proposed training method, implicit differentiation on the equilibrium state (IDE), for supervised learning with purely spike-based computation, which demonstrates the potential for energy-efficient training of SNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spide-a-purely-spike-based-method-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe Interval Path Planning With Kinodynamic Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-interval-path-planning-with-kinodynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safe Interval Path Planning (SIPP) is a powerful algorithm for solving single-agent pathfinding problem when the agent is confined to a graph and certain vertices/edges of this graph are blocked at certain time intervals due to dynamic obstacles that populate the environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-interval-path-planning-with-kinodynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Lunch for Domain Adversarial Training: Environment Label Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-lunch-for-domain-adversarial-training-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A fundamental challenge for machine learning models is how to generalize learned models for out-of-distribution (OOD) data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-lunch-for-domain-adversarial-training-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Few-Shot Generalization by Exploring and Exploiting Auxiliary Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-few-shot-generalization-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we focus on Few-shot Learning with Auxiliary Data (FLAD), a training paradigm that assumes access to auxiliary data during few-shot learning in hopes of improving generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-few-shot-generalization-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Choice Functions with Gaussian Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-choice-functions-with-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a Gaussian Process model to learn choice functions from choice-data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-choice-functions-with-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W2SAT: Learning to generate SAT instances from Weighted Literal Incidence Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/w2sat-learning-to-generate-sat-instances-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Boolean Satisfiability (SAT) problem stands out as an attractive NP-complete problem in theoretic computer science and plays a central role in a broad spectrum of computing-related applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/w2sat-learning-to-generate-sat-instances-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Message Passing Neural Network for Crystal Material Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-message-passing-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic material discovery with desired properties is a fundamental challenge for material sciences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-message-passing-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Entity Alignment for Temporal Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-entity-alignment-for-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art time-aware EA studies have suggested that the temporal information of TKGs facilitates the performance of EA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-entity-alignment-for-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional Flow Matching: Simulation-Free Dynamic Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-flow-matching-simulation-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CFM features a stable regression objective like that used to train the stochastic flow in diffusion models but enjoys the efficient inference of deterministic flow models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-flow-matching-simulation-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dictionary-based Manifold Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dictionary-based-manifold-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a paradigm for interpretable Manifold Learning for scientific data analysis, whereby we parametrize a manifold with $d$ smooth functions from a scientist-provided dictionary of meaningful, domain-related functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dictionary-based-manifold-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distillation Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-policy-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Can we design an algorithm that can employ the off-policy data, while exploit the stable learning by sailing along the course of the on-policy walkway?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-policy-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compositional Prompt Tuning with Motion Cues for Open-vocabulary Video Relation Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-prompt-tuning-with-motion-cues</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Without bells and whistles, our RePro achieves a new state-of-the-art performance on two VidVRD benchmarks of not only the base training object and predicate categories, but also the unseen ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-prompt-tuning-with-motion-cues</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$\rm A^2Q$: Aggregation-Aware Quantization for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rm-a-2q-aggregation-aware-quantization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through an in-depth analysis of the topology of GNNs, we observe that the topology of the graph leads to significant differences between nodes, and most of the nodes in a graph appear to have a small aggregation value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rm-a-2q-aggregation-aware-quantization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertain Quality-Diversity: Evaluation methodology and new methods for Quality-Diversity in Uncertain Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertain-quality-diversity-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we propose a new methodology to evaluate Uncertain QD approaches, relying on a new per-generation sampling budget and a set of existing and new metrics specifically designed for Uncertain QD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertain-quality-diversity-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mPLUG-2: A Modularized Multi-modal Foundation Model Across Text, Image and Video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mplug-2-a-modularized-multi-modal-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to predominant paradigms of solely relying on sequence-to-sequence generation or encoder-based instance discrimination, mPLUG-2 introduces a multi-module composition network by sharing common universal modules for modality collaboration and disentangling different modality modules to deal with modality entanglement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mplug-2-a-modularized-multi-modal-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inference of Partial Colexifications from Multilingual Wordlists</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-of-partial-colexifications-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The past years have seen a drastic rise in studies devoted to the investigation of colexification patterns in individual languages families in particular and the languages of the world in specific.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-of-partial-colexifications-from</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
