<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 09:16:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Using Developer Discussions to Guide Fixing Bugs in Software</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-developer-discussions-to-guide-fixing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatically fixing software bugs is a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-developer-discussions-to-guide-fixing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Factual Consistency in Summarization with Compression-Based Post-Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-factual-consistency-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose to use sentence-compression data to train the post-editing model to take a summary with extrinsic entity errors marked with special tokens and output a compressed, well-formed summary with those errors removed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-factual-consistency-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physically-Based Face Rendering for NIR-VIS Face Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physically-based-face-rendering-for-nir-vis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we reconstruct 3D face shape and reflectance from a large 2D facial dataset and introduce a novel method of transforming the VIS reflectance to NIR reflectance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physically-based-face-rendering-for-nir-vis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Much Hate with #china? A Preliminary Analysis on China-related Hateful Tweets Two Years After the Covid Pandemic Began</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-much-hate-with-china-a-preliminary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We identify a hateful rate in #china tweets of 2. 5% in 2020 and 1. 9% in 2021.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-much-hate-with-china-a-preliminary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainability in Practice: Estimating Electrification Rates from Mobile Phone Data in Senegal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainability-in-practice-estimating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conclude our paper by pointing to the two main challenges we encountered during our work: data processing and model design that might be restricted by currently available XAI methods, and the importance of domain knowledge to interpret explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainability-in-practice-estimating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inverse Kernel Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverse-kernel-decomposition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To deal with very noisy data with weak correlations, we propose two solutions -- blockwise and geodesic -- to make use of locally correlated data points and provide better and numerically more stable latent estimations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverse-kernel-decomposition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining Multi-Fidelity Modelling and Asynchronous Batch Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-multi-fidelity-modelling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian Optimization is a useful tool for experiment design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-multi-fidelity-modelling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDFlow: Unsupervised Optical Flow Learning by Reliable Mutual Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdflow-unsupervised-optical-flow-learning-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To break the dilemma, we propose a novel mutual distillation framework to transfer reliable knowledge back and forth between the teacher and student networks for alternate improvement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdflow-unsupervised-optical-flow-learning-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Generative Approach for Production-Aware Industrial Network Traffic Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generative-approach-for-production-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze the traffic statistics, capture the dependencies between the internal states of the machine, and model the network traffic as a production state dependent stochastic process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generative-approach-for-production-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Distillation from Cross Teaching Teachers for Efficient Semi-Supervised Abdominal Organ Segmentation in CT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-distillation-from-cross-teaching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For more clinical applications of deep learning models for medical image segmentation, high demands on labeled data and computational resources must be addressed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-distillation-from-cross-teaching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phase-Shifting Coder: Predicting Accurate Orientation in Oriented Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phase-shifting-coder-predicting-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the vigorous development of computer vision, oriented object detection has gradually been featured.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phase-shifting-coder-predicting-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving word mover's distance by leveraging self-attention matrix</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-word-mover-s-distance-by-leveraging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method is based on the Fused Gromov-Wasserstein distance, which simultaneously considers the similarity of the word embedding and the SAM for calculating the optimal transport between two sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-word-mover-s-distance-by-leveraging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fleet Rebalancing for Expanding Shared e-Mobility Systems: A Multi-agent Deep Reinforcement Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fleet-rebalancing-for-expanding-shared-e</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is particularly challenging in the context of expanding systems, because i) the range of the EVs is limited while charging time is typically long, which constrain the viable rebalancing operations; and ii) the EV stations in the system are dynamically changing, i. e., the legitimate targets for rebalancing operations can vary over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fleet-rebalancing-for-expanding-shared-e</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Graph Node Classification Benchmark: Learning Structure from Histology Cell Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-graph-node-classification-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new benchmark dataset, Placenta, for node classification in an underexplored domain: predicting microanatomical tissue structures from cell graphs in placenta histology whole slide images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-graph-node-classification-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep equilibrium models as estimators for continuous latent variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-equilibrium-models-as-estimators-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider a generalised setting where the canonical parameters of the exponential family are a nonlinear transformation of the latents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-equilibrium-models-as-estimators-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiDAL: Inter-frame Uncertainty Based Active Learning for 3D LiDAR Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidal-inter-frame-uncertainty-based-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose LiDAL, a novel active learning method for 3D LiDAR semantic segmentation by exploiting inter-frame uncertainty among LiDAR frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidal-inter-frame-uncertainty-based-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dance of SNN and ANN: Solving binding problem by combining spike timing and reconstructive attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dance-of-snn-and-ann-solving-binding-problem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a brain-inspired hybrid neural network (HNN) that introduces temporal binding theory originated from neuroscience into ANNs by integrating spike timing dynamics (via spiking neural networks, SNNs) with reconstructive attention (by ANNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dance-of-snn-and-ann-solving-binding-problem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Condition Training for Target Source Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-condition-training-for-target-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research has shown remarkable performance in leveraging multiple extraneous conditional and non-mutually exclusive semantic concepts for sound source separation, allowing the flexibility to extract a given target source based on multiple different queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-condition-training-for-target-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LERT: A Linguistically-motivated Pre-trained Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lert-a-linguistically-motivated-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose LERT, a pre-trained language model that is trained on three types of linguistic features along with the original MLM pre-training task, using a linguistically-informed pre-training (LIP) strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lert-a-linguistically-motivated-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning in an Adaptable Chess Environment for Detecting Human-understandable Concepts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-in-an-adaptable-chess</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-trained autonomous agents developed using machine learning are showing great promise in a variety of control settings, perhaps most remarkably in applications involving autonomous vehicles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-in-an-adaptable-chess</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised learning of audio representations using angular contrastive loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-of-audio-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the discriminative ability of feature embeddings in SSL, we propose a new loss function called Angular Contrastive Loss (ACL), a linear combination of angular margin and contrastive loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-of-audio-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Transformers Reason in Fragments of Natural Language?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-transformers-reason-in-fragments-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art deep-learning-based approaches to Natural Language Processing (NLP) are credited with various capabilities that involve reasoning with natural language texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-transformers-reason-in-fragments-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmarking Dataset with 2440 Organic Molecules for Volume Distribution at Steady State</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmarking-dataset-with-2440-organic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conclusions: To the best of our knowledge, this is the largest dataset for VDss, which can be used as the benchmark for computational studies of VDss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmarking-dataset-with-2440-organic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneFormer: One Transformer to Rule Universal Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oneformer-one-transformer-to-rule-universal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, such panoptic architectures do not truly unify image segmentation because they need to be trained individually on the semantic, instance, or panoptic segmentation to achieve the best performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oneformer-one-transformer-to-rule-universal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMDialog: A Large-scale Multi-turn Dialogue Dataset Towards Multi-modal Open-domain Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmdialog-a-large-scale-multi-turn-dialogue</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, it is the largest multi-modal conversation dataset by the number of dialogues by 8x.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmdialog-a-large-scale-multi-turn-dialogue</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DisentQA: Disentangling Parametric and Contextual Knowledge with Counterfactual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentqa-disentangling-parametric-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Question answering models commonly have access to two sources of "knowledge" during inference time: (1) parametric knowledge - the factual knowledge encoded in the model weights, and (2) contextual knowledge - external knowledge (e. g., a Wikipedia passage) given to the model to generate a grounded answer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentqa-disentangling-parametric-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nano: Nested Human-in-the-Loop Reward Learning for Few-shot Language Model Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nano-nested-human-in-the-loop-reward-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing techniques for controlling the distribution of generated text only work with quantified distributions, which require pre-defined categories, proportions of the distribution, or an existing corpus following the desired distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nano-nested-human-in-the-loop-reward-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnimeRun: 2D Animation Visual Correspondence from Open Source 3D Movies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animerun-2d-animation-visual-correspondence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing correspondence datasets for two-dimensional (2D) cartoon suffer from simple frame composition and monotonic movements, making them insufficient to simulate real animations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animerun-2d-animation-visual-correspondence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleNAT: Giving Each Head a New Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylenat-giving-each-head-a-new-perspective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image generation has been a long sought-after but challenging task, and performing the generation task in an efficient manner is similarly difficult.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylenat-giving-each-head-a-new-perspective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiSC: Differential Spectral Clustering of Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disc-differential-spectral-clustering-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Selecting subsets of features that differentiate between two conditions is a key task in a broad range of scientific domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disc-differential-spectral-clustering-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Real Time Exploration and Optimization for Safety-Critical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-real-time-exploration-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of decision-making under uncertainty in an environment with safety constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-real-time-exploration-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Randomized Response for Differential Privacy in Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-randomized-response-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) are susceptible to privacy inference attacks (PIAs), given their ability to learn joint representation from features and edges among nodes in graph data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-randomized-response-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient brain age prediction from 3D MRI volumes using 2D projections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-brain-age-prediction-from-3d-mri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using 3D CNNs on high resolution medical volumes is very computationally demanding, especially for large datasets like the UK Biobank which aims to scan 100, 000 subjects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-brain-age-prediction-from-3d-mri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-shot Visual Commonsense Immorality Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-visual-commonsense-immorality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we propose a model that predicts visual commonsense immorality in a zero-shot manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-visual-commonsense-immorality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stay Home Safe with Starving Federated Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stay-home-safe-with-starving-federated-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the past few years, the field of adversarial attack received numerous attention from various researchers with the help of successful attack success rate against well-known deep neural networks that were acknowledged to achieve high classification ability in various tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stay-home-safe-with-starving-federated-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perfectly predicting ICU length of stay: too good to be true</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perfectly-predicting-icu-length-of-stay-too</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A paper of Alsinglawi et al was recently accepted and published in Scientific Reports.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perfectly-predicting-icu-length-of-stay-too</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness and bias correction in machine learning for depression prediction: results from four different study populations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-and-bias-correction-in-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A significant level of stigma and inequality exists in mental healthcare, especially in under-served populations, which spreads through collected data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-and-bias-correction-in-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Flow, Stereo and Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-flow-stereo-and-depth-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a unified formulation and model for three motion and 3D perception tasks: optical flow, rectified stereo matching and unrectified stereo depth estimation from posed images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-flow-stereo-and-depth-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Multi-scale Mean Teacher Network for Semi-supervised Infection Segmentation in Chest CT Volume for COVID-19</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-multi-scale-mean-teacher-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated detecting lung infections from computed tomography (CT) data plays an important role for combating COVID-19.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-multi-scale-mean-teacher-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSDT: Masked Language Model Scoring Defense in Text Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msdt-masked-language-model-scoring-defense-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such easily-downloaded language models from various websites empowered the public users as well as some major institutions to give a momentum to their real-life application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msdt-masked-language-model-scoring-defense-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystify Transformers &amp; Convolutions in Modern Image Deep Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystify-transformers-convolutions-in-modern</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the novel feature transformation designs are often claimed as the source of gain, some backbones may benefit from advanced engineering techniques, which makes it hard to identify the real gain from the key feature transformation operators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystify-transformers-convolutions-in-modern</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vis2Mus: Exploring Multimodal Representation Mapping for Controllable Music Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vis2mus-exploring-multimodal-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we explore the representation mapping from the domain of visual arts to the domain of music, with which we can use visual arts as an effective handle to control music generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vis2mus-exploring-multimodal-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer-Net BCa: Breast Cancer Pathologic Complete Response Prediction using Volumetric Deep Radiomic Features from Synthetic Correlated Diffusion Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cancer-net-bca-breast-cancer-pathologic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Breast cancer is the second most common type of cancer in women in Canada and the United States, representing over 25% of all new female cancer cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cancer-net-bca-breast-cancer-pathologic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternImage: Exploring Large-Scale Vision Foundation Models with Deformable Convolutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internimage-exploring-large-scale-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to the great progress of large-scale vision transformers (ViTs) in recent years, large-scale models based on convolutional neural networks (CNNs) are still in an early state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internimage-exploring-large-scale-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Set Automatic Target Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-set-automatic-target-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic Target Recognition (ATR) is a category of computer vision algorithms which attempts to recognize targets on data obtained from different sensors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-set-automatic-target-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Ramifications of Human Label Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-ramifications-of-human-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our evaluation of existing uncertainty estimation algorithms, with the presence of HLU, indicates the limitations of existing uncertainty metrics and algorithms themselves in response to HLU.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-ramifications-of-human-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can one hear the position of nodes?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-one-hear-the-position-of-nodes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wave propagation through nodes and links of a network forms the basis of spectral graph theory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-one-hear-the-position-of-nodes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Shot Character Understanding in Movies as an Assessment to Meta-Learning of Theory-of-Mind</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-character-understanding-in-movies-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When reading a story, humans can rapidly understand new fictional characters with a few observations, mainly by drawing analogy to fictional and real people they met before in their lives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-character-understanding-in-movies-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Aesthetic and Technical Effects for Video Quality Assessment of User Generated Content</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-aesthetic-and-technical-effects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better explain the quality perception mechanisms and learn more robust representations, we aim to disentangle the effects of aesthetic quality issues and technical quality issues risen by the complicated video generation processes in the UGC-VQA problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-aesthetic-and-technical-effects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks with Adaptive Readouts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-with-adaptive-readouts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that in some problems such as binding affinity prediction where molecules are typically presented in a canonical form it might be possible to relax the constraints on permutation invariance of the hypothesis space and learn a more effective model of the affinity by employing an adaptive readout function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-with-adaptive-readouts</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
