<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 21:09:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Pluggable Style Representation Learning for Multi-Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pluggable-style-representation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, for style modeling, we propose a style representation learning scheme to encode the style information into a compact representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pluggable-style-representation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextual Checkerboard Denoise -- A Novel Neural Network-Based Approach for Classification-Aware OCT Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-checkerboard-denoise-a-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to non-medical image denoising, where enhancing image clarity is the primary goal, medical image denoising warrants preservation of crucial features without introduction of new artifacts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-checkerboard-denoise-a-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handling irresolvable conflicts in the Semantic Web: an RDF-based conflict-tolerant version of the Deontic Traditional Scheme</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handling-irresolvable-conflicts-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new ontology that implements the well-known Deontic Traditional Scheme in RDFs and SPARQL, fit to handle irresolvable conflicts, i. e., situations in which two or more statements prescribe conflicting obligations, prohibitions, or permissions, with none of them being "stronger" than the other one(s).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handling-irresolvable-conflicts-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIDetx: a compression-based method for identification of machine-learning generated text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aidetx-a-compression-based-method-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces AIDetx, a novel method for detecting machine-generated text using data compression techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aidetx-a-compression-based-method-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feedback-driven object detection and iterative model improvement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feedback-driven-object-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present the development and evaluation of a platform designed to interactively improve object detection models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feedback-driven-object-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LDA-AQU: Adaptive Query-guided Upsampling via Local Deformable Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lda-aqu-adaptive-query-guided-upsampling-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we introduce local self-attention into the upsampling task and demonstrate that the majority of existing upsamplers can be regarded as special cases of upsamplers based on local self-attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lda-aqu-adaptive-query-guided-upsampling-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GuardSplat: Robust and Efficient Watermarking for 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guardsplat-robust-and-efficient-watermarking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, 1) We first propose a CLIP-guided Message Decoupling Optimization module for training the message decoder, leveraging CLIP's aligning capability and rich representations to achieve a high extraction accuracy with minimal optimization costs, presenting exceptional capability and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guardsplat-robust-and-efficient-watermarking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfake Media Generation and Detection in the Generative AI Era: A Survey and Outlook</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepfake-media-generation-and-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the recent advancements in generative modeling, the realism of deepfake content has been increasing at a steady pace, even reaching the point where people often fail to detect manipulated media content online, thus being deceived into various kinds of scams.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepfake-media-generation-and-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-RAG: Autonomous Retrieval-Augmented Generation for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-rag-autonomous-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Iterative retrieval refers to the process in which the model continuously queries the retriever during generation to enhance the relevance of the retrieved knowledge, thereby improving the performance of Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-rag-autonomous-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uniform Attention Maps: Boosting Image Fidelity in Reconstruction and Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniform-attention-maps-boosting-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study underscores the potential of uniform attention maps to enhance the fidelity and versatility of diffusion-based image processing methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniform-attention-maps-boosting-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Multimodal Large Language Models via Dynamic Visual-Token Exit and the Empirical Findings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-multimodal-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we reveal that visual tokens will stop contributing to reasoning when the text tokens receive enough image information, yielding obvious visual redundancy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-multimodal-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced anomaly detection in well log data through the application of ensemble GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-anomaly-detection-in-well-log-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study extends the ensemble GANs (EGANs) framework to capture the distribution of well log data and detect anomalies that fall outside of these distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-anomaly-detection-in-well-log-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURE-VQA: Systematic Understanding of Robustness Evaluation in Medical VQA Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sure-vqa-systematic-understanding-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-Language Models (VLMs) have great potential in medical tasks, like Visual Question Answering (VQA), where they could act as interactive assistants for both patients and clinicians.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sure-vqa-systematic-understanding-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCUCoder: Adaptive Bitrate Learned Video Compression for IoT Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcucoder-adaptive-bitrate-learned-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid growth of camera-based IoT devices demands the need for efficient video compression, particularly for edge applications where devices face hardware constraints, often with only 1 or 2 MB of RAM and unstable internet connections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcucoder-adaptive-bitrate-learned-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Loss Strategy for Vehicle Trajectory Prediction: Combining Off-Road, Diversity, and Directional Consistency Losses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-loss-strategy-for-vehicle-trajectory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trajectory prediction is essential for the safety and efficiency of planning in autonomous vehicles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-loss-strategy-for-vehicle-trajectory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELT: A Simple Diversity-driven EarlyLate Training for Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delt-a-simple-diversity-driven-earlylate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The conventional batch-to-batch matching mechanism is ideal for small-scale datasets and includes bi-level optimization methods on models and syntheses, such as FRePo, RCIG, and RaT-BPTT, as well as other methods like distribution matching, gradient matching, and weight trajectory matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delt-a-simple-diversity-driven-earlylate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Domain Recommendation Meets Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-recommendation-meets-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-domain recommendation (CDR) has emerged as a promising solution to the cold-start problem, faced by single-domain recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-recommendation-meets-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeMo: Decoupled Momentum Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demo-decoupled-momentum-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training large neural networks typically requires sharing gradients between accelerators through specialized high-speed interconnects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demo-decoupled-momentum-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensemble Watermarks for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-watermarks-for-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, we combine acrostica and sensorimotor norms with the established red-green watermark to achieve a 98% detection rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-watermarks-for-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Initialization using Update Approximation is a Silver Bullet for Extremely Efficient Low-Rank Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/initialization-using-update-approximation-is</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-rank adapters have become a standard approach for efficiently fine-tuning large language models (LLMs), but they often fall short of achieving the performance of full fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/initialization-using-update-approximation-is</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChineseWebText 2.0: Large-Scale High-quality Chinese Web Text with Multi-dimensional and fine-grained information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chinesewebtext-2-0-large-scale-high-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With this approach, we release the largest, high-quality and fine-grained Chinese text ChineseWebText2. 0, which consists of 3. 8TB and each text is associated with a quality score, domain labels, a toxicity label and a toxicity score, facilitating the LLM researchers to select data based on various types of fine-grained information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chinesewebtext-2-0-large-scale-high-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Risk Minimization: Towards Next-Level Robustness in Fine-tuning Zero-Shot Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-risk-minimization-towards-next-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning foundation models often compromises their robustness to distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-risk-minimization-towards-next-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T2Vid: Translating Long Text into Multi-Image is the Catalyst for Video-LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t2vid-translating-long-text-into-multi-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, our study of these approaches harvests an effective data augmentation method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t2vid-translating-long-text-into-multi-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Continual Graph Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-continual-graph-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we present a pioneering study on Federated Continual Graph Learning (FCGL), which adapts GNNs to multiple evolving graphs within decentralized settings while adhering to storage and privacy constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-continual-graph-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SADG: Segment Any Dynamic Gaussian Without Object Trackers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sadg-segment-any-dynamic-gaussian-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce SADG, Segment Any Dynamic Gaussian Without Object Trackers, a novel approach that combines dynamic Gaussian Splatting representation and semantic information without reliance on object IDs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sadg-segment-any-dynamic-gaussian-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning of Vision Transformers through Frequency-Based Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adapting vision transformer foundation models through parameter-efficient fine-tuning (PEFT) methods has become increasingly popular.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPrompter: reconceptualized segment anything model with multiprompt network for camouflaged object detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprompter-reconceptualized-segment-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this, we propose an edge gradient extraction module, which generates a mask containing gradient information regarding the boundaries of camouflaged objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprompter-reconceptualized-segment-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scale Invariance of Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-invariance-of-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address two fundamental challenges in Graph Neural Networks (GNNs): (1) the lack of theoretical support for invariance learning, a critical property in image processing, and (2) the absence of a unified model capable of excelling on both homophilic and heterophilic graph datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-invariance-of-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDHRA Bandersnatch: Training Neural Networks to Predict Parallel Realities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/andhra-bandersnatch-training-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the Many-Worlds Interpretation (MWI), this work introduces a novel neural network architecture that splits the same input signal into parallel branches at each layer, utilizing a Hyper Rectified Activation, referred to as ANDHRA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/andhra-bandersnatch-training-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEOBench-VLM: Benchmarking Vision-Language Models for Geospatial Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geobench-vlm-benchmarking-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap in the geospatial domain, we present GEOBench-VLM, a comprehensive benchmark specifically designed to evaluate VLMs on geospatial tasks, including scene understanding, object counting, localization, fine-grained categorization, and temporal analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geobench-vlm-benchmarking-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter-Efficient Transfer Learning for Music Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-transfer-learning-for-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Common ways of adapting music foundation models to downstream tasks are probing and fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-transfer-learning-for-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing Key Details to See Differences: A Novel Prototypical Perspective for Skeleton-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-key-details-to-see-differences-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In skeleton-based action recognition, a key challenge is distinguishing between actions with similar trajectories of joints due to the lack of image-level details in skeletal representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-key-details-to-see-differences-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detailed Object Description with Controllable Dimensions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detailed-object-description-with-controllable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, it can not only improve the quality of object details but also offer flexibility in including or excluding specific dimensions based on user preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detailed-object-description-with-controllable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Dream My Painting: Connecting MLLMs and Diffusion Models via Prompt Generation for Text-Guided Multi-Mask Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-dream-my-painting-connecting-mllms-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inpainting focuses on filling missing or corrupted regions of an image to blend seamlessly with its surrounding content and style.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-dream-my-painting-connecting-mllms-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMNI-DC: Highly Robust Depth Completion with Multiresolution Depth Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omni-dc-highly-robust-depth-completion-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate our model, we establish a new evaluation protocol named Robust-DC for zero-shot testing under various sparse depth patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omni-dc-highly-robust-depth-completion-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Det-SAM2:Technical Report on the Self-Prompting Segmentation Framework Based on Segment Anything Model 2</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/det-sam2-technical-report-on-the-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segment Anything Model 2 (SAM2) demonstrates exceptional performance in video segmentation and refinement of segmentation results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/det-sam2-technical-report-on-the-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUPE: Heuristic Underwater Perceptual Enhancement with Semantic Collaborative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hupe-heuristic-underwater-perceptual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To strike a balance between visual quality and application, we propose a heuristic invertible network for underwater perception enhancement, dubbed HUPE, which enhances visual quality and demonstrates flexibility in handling other downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hupe-heuristic-underwater-perceptual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Neural Networks Do Work with Pre-Defined Filters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-do-work-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel class of Convolutional Neural Networks called Pre-defined Filter Convolutional Neural Networks (PFCNNs), where all nxn convolution kernels with n>1 are pre-defined and constant during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-do-work-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helvipad: A Real-World Dataset for Omnidirectional Stereo Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helvipad-a-real-world-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite considerable progress in stereo depth estimation, omnidirectional imaging remains underexplored, mainly due to the lack of appropriate data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helvipad-a-real-world-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RL for Mitigating Cascading Failures: Targeted Exploration via Sensitivity Factors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-for-mitigating-cascading-failures-targeted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Electricity grid's resiliency and climate change strongly impact one another due to an array of technical and policy-related decisions that impact both.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-for-mitigating-cascading-failures-targeted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Surface Priors for Editable Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-surface-priors-for-editable-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike other methods, our pipeline allows modifications applied to the extracted mesh to be propagated to the proxy representation, from which we recover the updated parameters of the Gaussians.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-surface-priors-for-editable-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoLLM Knows When to Speak: Enhancing Time-Sensitive Video Comprehension with Video-Text Duet Interaction Format</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videollm-knows-when-to-speak-enhancing-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We construct MMDuetIT, a video-text training dataset designed to adapt VideoLLMs to video-text duet interaction format.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videollm-knows-when-to-speak-enhancing-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergence of Self-Identity in AI: A Mathematical Framework and Empirical Study with Generative Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-self-identity-in-ai-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a mathematical framework for defining and quantifying self-identity in artificial intelligence (AI) systems, addressing a critical gap in the theoretical foundations of artificial consciousness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-self-identity-in-ai-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monocular Obstacle Avoidance Based on Inverse PPO for Fixed-wing UAVs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-obstacle-avoidance-based-on-inverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After that, a reinforcement learning controller with a novel reward function is designed to balance the target approach and flight trajectory smoothness, satisfying the specific dynamic constraints and stability requirements of a fixed-wing UAV platform.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-obstacle-avoidance-based-on-inverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning optimal objective values for MILP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-optimal-objective-values-for-milp</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern Mixed Integer Linear Programming (MILP) solvers use the Branch-and-Bound algorithm together with a plethora of auxiliary components that speed up the search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-optimal-objective-values-for-milp</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Multispectral Object Detection: A Bag of Tricks and Comprehensive Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-multispectral-object-detection-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multispectral object detection, utilizing RGB and TIR (thermal infrared) modalities, is widely recognized as a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-multispectral-object-detection-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Learning for Deep Learning-based Prediction of Lattice Thermal Conductivity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-deep-learning-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interestingly, we also show that a much greater improvement is obtained when first fine-tuning it on a large datasets of low-quality approximations of LTC (based on the AGL model) and then applying a second phase of fine-tuning with our high-quality, smaller-scale datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-deep-learning-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuaLLM-Health: An Adaptation of an LLM-Based Framework for Quantitative Data Extraction from Online Health Discussions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quallm-health-an-adaptation-of-an-llm-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present an adapted framework from QuaLLM into QuaLLM-Health for extracting clinically relevant quantitative data from Reddit discussions about glucagon-like peptide-1 (GLP-1) receptor agonists using large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quallm-health-an-adaptation-of-an-llm-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Fourier-embedded Network for Bi-modal Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fourier-embedded-network-for-bi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of deep learning provides a significant improvement of salient object detection combining both RGB and thermal images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fourier-embedded-network-for-bi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Knowledge Concepts to Whole Slide Images for Precise Histopathology Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-knowledge-concepts-to-whole-slide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the large size and lack of fine-grained annotation, Whole Slide Images (WSIs) analysis is commonly approached as a Multiple Instance Learning (MIL) problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-knowledge-concepts-to-whole-slide</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
