<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 21:06:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DED: Diagnostic Evidence Distillation for acne severity grading on face images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ded-diagnostic-evidence-distillation-for-acne</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose an acne diagnosis method, Diagnostic Evidence Distillation (DED), that suitably adapts the characteristics of acne diagnosis and can be applied to diagnose under different acne criteria.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ded-diagnostic-evidence-distillation-for-acne</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network Alignment with Transferable Graph Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-alignment-with-transferable-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Network alignment is the task of establishing one-to-one correspondences between the nodes of different graphs and finds a plethora of applications in high-impact domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-alignment-with-transferable-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoLLIE: Annotation Guidelines improve Zero-Shot Information-Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gollie-annotation-guidelines-improve-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous attempts to leverage such information have failed, even with the largest models, as they are not able to follow the guidelines out-of-the-box.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gollie-annotation-guidelines-improve-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent Instructs Large Language Models to be General Zero-Shot Reasoners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-instructs-large-language-models-to-be</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For instance, our method boosts the performance of state-of-the-art large language models by a large margin, including Vicuna-13b (13. 3%), Llama-2-70b-chat (23. 2%), and GPT-3. 5 Turbo (17. 0%).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-instructs-large-language-models-to-be</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Text-to-Image Diffusion Models with Reward Backpropagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-text-to-image-diffusion-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to their unsupervised training, controlling their behavior in downstream tasks, such as maximizing human-perceived image quality, image-text alignment, or ethical image generation, is difficult.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-text-to-image-diffusion-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAPES: Learning to Sample Graphs for Scalable Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grapes-learning-to-sample-graphs-for-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) learn the representation of nodes in a graph by aggregating the neighborhood information in various ways.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grapes-learning-to-sample-graphs-for-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeaTMOSS: Mining Pre-Trained Models in Open-Source Software</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peatmoss-mining-pre-trained-models-in-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Developing and training deep learning models is expensive, so software engineers have begun to reuse pre-trained deep learning models (PTMs) and fine-tune them for downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peatmoss-mining-pre-trained-models-in-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MathCoder: Seamless Code Integration in LLMs for Enhanced Mathematical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathcoder-seamless-code-integration-in-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a method to fine-tune open-source language models, enabling them to use code for modeling and deriving math equations and, consequently, enhancing their mathematical reasoning abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathcoder-seamless-code-integration-in-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Large Language Models As AI Research Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-language-models-as-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Can we build AI research agents to perform these long-horizon tasks?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-language-models-as-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSPy: Compiling Declarative Language Model Calls into Self-Improving Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dspy-compiling-declarative-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ML community is rapidly exploring techniques for prompting language models (LMs) and for stacking them into pipelines that solve complex tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dspy-compiling-declarative-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Representation Learning via Asymmetric Negative Contrast and Reverse Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-representation-learning-via-asymmetric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks are vulnerable to adversarial noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-representation-learning-via-asymmetric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GENER: A Parallel Layer Deep Learning Network To Detect Gene-Gene Interactions From Gene Expression Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gener-a-parallel-layer-deep-learning-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting and discovering new gene interactions based on known gene expressions and gene interaction data presents a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gener-a-parallel-layer-deep-learning-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Personalized Story Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-personalized-story-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further develop a personalized story evaluation model PERSE to infer reviewer preferences and provide a personalized evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-personalized-story-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relational Convolutional Networks: A framework for learning representations of hierarchical relations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-convolutional-networks-a-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on the problem of learning representations of hierarchical relations, proposing an architectural framework we call "relational convolutional networks".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-convolutional-networks-a-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreshLLMs: Refreshing Large Language Models with Search Engine Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freshllms-refreshing-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce FreshQA, a novel dynamic QA benchmark encompassing a diverse range of question and answer types, including questions that require fast-changing world knowledge as well as questions with false premises that need to be debunked.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freshllms-refreshing-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Know2BIO: A Comprehensive Dual-View Benchmark for Evolving Biomedical Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/know2bio-a-comprehensive-dual-view-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge graphs (KGs) have emerged as a powerful framework for representing and integrating complex biomedical information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/know2bio-a-comprehensive-dual-view-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Energy-Based Prior Model with Diffusion-Amortized MCMC</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-energy-based-prior-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To remedy this sampling issue, in this paper we introduce a simple but effective diffusion-based amortization method for long-run MCMC sampling and develop a novel learning algorithm for the latent space EBM based on it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-energy-based-prior-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Good Are Synthetic Medical Images? An Empirical Study with Lung Ultrasound</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-good-are-synthetic-medical-images-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adding synthetic training data using generative models offers a low-cost method to deal effectively with the data scarcity challenge, and can also address data imbalance and patient privacy issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-good-are-synthetic-medical-images-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSI: Enhancing the Robustness of 3D Point Cloud Recognition against Corruption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csi-enhancing-the-robustness-of-3d-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we harness the inherent set property of point cloud data to introduce a novel critical subset identification (CSI) method, aiming to bolster recognition robustness in the face of data corruption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csi-enhancing-the-robustness-of-3d-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LESSON: Learning to Integrate Exploration Strategies for Reinforcement Learning via an Option Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesson-learning-to-integrate-exploration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, a unified framework for exploration in reinforcement learning (RL) is proposed based on an option-critic model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesson-learning-to-integrate-exploration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can pre-trained models assist in dataset distillation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-pre-trained-models-assist-in-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dataset Distillation (DD) is a prominent technique that encapsulates knowledge from a large-scale original dataset into a small synthetic dataset for efficient training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-pre-trained-models-assist-in-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Zero Level-Set Extraction from Unsigned Distance Fields Based on Double Covering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-zero-level-set-extraction-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the computed iso-surface is the boundary of the $r$-offset volume of the target zero level-set $S$, which is an orientable manifold, regardless of the topology of $S$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-zero-level-set-extraction-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-Based Radiance Fields for Controllable Human Motion Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-based-radiance-fields-for-controllable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel controllable human motion synthesis method for fine-level deformation based on static point-based radiance fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-based-radiance-fields-for-controllable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plug-and-Play Posterior Sampling under Mismatched Measurement and Prior Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-posterior-sampling-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Posterior sampling has been shown to be a powerful Bayesian approach for solving imaging inverse problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-posterior-sampling-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of learning a flow-based generative model from limited sample complexity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-learning-a-flow-based-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of training a flow-based generative model, parametrized by a two-layer autoencoder, to sample from a high-dimensional Gaussian mixture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-learning-a-flow-based-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Long Way to Go: Investigating Length Correlations in RLHF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-long-way-to-go-investigating-length</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we find that even running RLHF with a reward based solely on length can reproduce most of the downstream improvements over the initial policy model, showing that reward models in these settings have a long way to go.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-long-way-to-go-investigating-length</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-dimensional Bayesian Optimization with Group Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-bayesian-optimization-with-6</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a group testing approach to identify active variables to facilitate efficient optimization in these domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-bayesian-optimization-with-6</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoDA: Collaborative Novel Box Discovery and Cross-modal Alignment for Open-vocabulary 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coda-collaborative-novel-box-discovery-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-vocabulary 3D Object Detection (OV-3DDet) aims to detect objects from an arbitrary list of categories within a 3D scene, which remains seldom explored in the literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coda-collaborative-novel-box-discovery-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViFiT: Reconstructing Vision Trajectories from IMU and Wi-Fi Fine Time Measurements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vifit-reconstructing-vision-trajectories-from-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tracking subjects in videos is one of the most widely used functions in camera-based IoT applications such as security surveillance, smart city traffic safety enhancement, vehicle to pedestrian communication and so on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vifit-reconstructing-vision-trajectories-from-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magicremover: Tuning-free Text-guided Image inpainting with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magicremover-tuning-free-text-guided-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose MagicRemover, a tuning-free method that leverages the powerful diffusion models for text-guided image inpainting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magicremover-tuning-free-text-guided-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a time series of neural activity during a perceptual inference task, our framework finds (i) the neural representation of relevant latent variables, (ii) interactions between these variables that define the brain's internal model of the world, and (iii) message-functions specifying the inference algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-modeling the Sequential and Graphical Routes for Peptide Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-modeling-the-sequential-and-graphical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Peptides are formed by the dehydration condensation of multiple amino acids.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-modeling-the-sequential-and-graphical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBCL: Zero-shot Model Generation for Task Trade-offs in Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ibcl-zero-shot-model-generation-for-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Upon a new task, IBCL (1) updates a knowledge base in the form of a convex hull of model parameter distributions and (2) obtains particular models to address task trade-off preferences with zero-shot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ibcl-zero-shot-model-generation-for-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Bayes Estimators for Irregular Spatial Data using Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-bayes-estimators-for-irregular-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Bayes estimators are neural networks that approximate Bayes estimators in a fast and likelihood-free manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-bayes-estimators-for-irregular-spatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extracting Rules from Event Data for Study Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extracting-rules-from-event-data-for-study</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we examine how event data from campus management systems can be used to analyze the study paths of higher education students.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extracting-rules-from-event-data-for-study</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memoria: Hebbian Memory Architecture for Human-Like Sequential Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memoria-hebbian-memory-architecture-for-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have demonstrated their success in various domains and tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memoria-hebbian-memory-architecture-for-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoBEV: Elevating Roadside 3D Object Detection with Depth and Height Complementarity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cobev-elevating-roadside-3d-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Roadside camera-driven 3D object detection is a crucial task in intelligent transportation systems, which extends the perception range beyond the limitations of vision-centric vehicles and enhances road safety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cobev-elevating-roadside-3d-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>scHyena: Foundation Model for Full-Length Single-Cell RNA-Seq Analysis in Brain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/schyena-foundation-model-for-full-length</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Single-cell RNA sequencing (scRNA-seq) has made significant strides in unraveling the intricate cellular diversity within complex tissues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/schyena-foundation-model-for-full-length</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedNAR: Federated Optimization with Normalized Annealing Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fednar-federated-optimization-with-normalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we first explore the choices of weight decay and identify that weight decay value appreciably influences the convergence of existing FL algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fednar-federated-optimization-with-normalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlowFormer: Universal Adversarial Patch for Attack on Compute and Energy Efficiency of Inference Efficient Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slowformer-universal-adversarial-patch-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that such models can be vulnerable to a universal adversarial patch attack, where the attacker optimizes for a patch that when pasted on any image, can increase the compute and power consumption of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slowformer-universal-adversarial-patch-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast, Expressive SE$(n)$ Equivariant Networks through Weight-Sharing in Position-Orientation Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-expressive-se-n-equivariant-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The theory of homogeneous spaces tells us how to do group convolutions with feature maps over the homogeneous space of positions $\mathbb{R}^3$, position and orientations $\mathbb{R}^3 {\times} S^2$, and the group SE$(3)$ itself.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-expressive-se-n-equivariant-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCB-Dataset3: A Benchmark for Detecting Student Classroom Behavior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scb-dataset3-a-benchmark-for-detecting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The use of deep learning methods to automatically detect students' classroom behavior is a promising approach for analyzing their class performance and improving teaching effectiveness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scb-dataset3-a-benchmark-for-detecting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Search GFlowNets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-search-gflownets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative Flow Networks (GFlowNets) are amortized sampling methods that learn a distribution over discrete objects proportional to their rewards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-search-gflownets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P2CADNet: An End-to-End Reconstruction Network for Parametric 3D CAD Model from Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p2cadnet-an-end-to-end-reconstruction-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computer Aided Design (CAD), especially the feature-based parametric CAD, plays an important role in modern industry and society.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p2cadnet-an-end-to-end-reconstruction-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-PEFT: Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning for 3D Pre-trained Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-peft-parameter-efficient-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce Point-PEFT, a novel framework for adapting point cloud pre-trained models with minimal learnable parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-peft-parameter-efficient-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Max-Entropy and Free Energy Principles, Belief Diffusions and their Singularities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-max-entropy-and-free-energy-principles-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A comprehensive picture of three Bethe-Kikuchi variational principles including their relationship to belief propagation (BP) algorithms on hypergraphs is given.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-max-entropy-and-free-energy-principles-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Recipe for Improved Certifiable Robustness: Capacity and Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-recipe-for-improved-certifiable-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key challenge, supported both theoretically and empirically, is that robustness demands greater network capacity and more data than standard training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-recipe-for-improved-certifiable-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Prototype-Based Neural Network for Image Anomaly Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-prototype-based-neural-network-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes ProtoAD, a prototype-based neural network for image anomaly detection and localization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-prototype-based-neural-network-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Multi-Configuration Problems: A Performance Analysis with Choco Solver</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-multi-configuration-problems-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many scenarios, configurators support the configuration of a solution that satisfies the preferences of a single user.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-multi-configuration-problems-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Memorization in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-memorization-in-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Looking into this, we first observe that memorization behaviors tend to occur on smaller-sized datasets, which motivates our definition of effective model memorization (EMM), a metric measuring the maximum size of training data at which a learned diffusion model approximates its theoretical optimum.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-memorization-in-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
