<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 21:07:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling and renormalization in high-dimensional regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-and-renormalization-in-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a succinct derivation of the training and generalization performance of a variety of high-dimensional ridge regression models using the basic tools of random matrix theory and free probability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-and-renormalization-in-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characterizing Information Seeking Processes with Multiple Physiological Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-information-seeking-processes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Information access systems are getting complex, and our understanding of user behavior during information seeking processes is mainly drawn from qualitative methods, such as observational studies or surveys.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-information-seeking-processes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Positional Bias for Query-Agnostic Generative Content in Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-positional-bias-for-query-agnostic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate such defects by showing that non-relevant text--such as promotional content--can be easily injected into a document without adversely affecting its position in search results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-positional-bias-for-query-agnostic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global News Synchrony and Diversity During the Start of the COVID-19 Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-news-synchrony-and-diversity-during</link>
      <description><![CDATA[News coverage profoundly affects how countries and individuals behave in international relations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-news-synchrony-and-diversity-during</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Models Biased on Text without Gender-related Language?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-models-biased-on-text-without-gender</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key observation in prior work is that models reinforce stereotypes as a consequence of the gendered correlations that are present in the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-models-biased-on-text-without-gender</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predictive Accuracy-Based Active Learning for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictive-accuracy-based-active-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Active learning is considered a viable solution to alleviate the contradiction between the high dependency of deep learning-based segmentation methods on annotated data and the expensive pixel-level annotation cost of medical images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictive-accuracy-based-active-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iMTSP: Solving Min-Max Multiple Traveling Salesman Problem with Imperative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imtsp-solving-min-max-multiple-traveling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address these issues by reformulating MTSP as a bilevel optimization problem, using the concept of imperative learning (IL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imtsp-solving-min-max-multiple-traveling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Representation, No Trust: Connecting Representation, Collapse, and Trust Issues in PPO</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-representation-no-trust-connecting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We draw connections between representation collapse, performance collapse, and trust region issues in PPO, and present Proximal Feature Optimization (PFO), a novel auxiliary loss, that along with other interventions shows that regularizing the representation dynamics improves the performance of PPO agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-representation-no-trust-connecting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing the Power of Multiple Minds: Lessons Learned from LLM Routing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-the-power-of-multiple-minds</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid development of LLMs, it is natural to ask how to harness their capabilities efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-the-power-of-multiple-minds</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covariant spatio-temporal receptive fields for neuromorphic computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covariant-spatio-temporal-receptive-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we present a principled computational model for neuromorphic systems in terms of spatio-temporal receptive fields, based on affine Gaussian kernels over space and leaky-integrator and leaky integrate-and-fire models over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covariant-spatio-temporal-receptive-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrossMatch: Enhance Semi-Supervised Medical Image Segmentation with Perturbation Strategies and Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crossmatch-enhance-semi-supervised-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-supervised learning for medical image segmentation presents a unique challenge of efficiently using limited labeled data while leveraging abundant unlabeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crossmatch-enhance-semi-supervised-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Quantization and Hardware Acceleration for Vision Transformers: A Comprehensive Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-quantization-and-hardware-acceleration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model quantization, by converting high-precision numbers to lower-precision, reduces the computational demands and memory needs of ViTs, allowing the creation of hardware specifically optimized for these quantized algorithms, boosting efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-quantization-and-hardware-acceleration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Compose: Improving Object Centric Learning by Injecting Compositionality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-compose-improving-object-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning compositional representation is a key aspect of object-centric learning as it enables flexible systematic generalization and supports complex visual reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-compose-improving-object-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UWAFA-GAN: Ultra-Wide-Angle Fluorescein Angiography Transformation via Multi-scale Generation and Registration Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uwafa-gan-ultra-wide-angle-fluorescein</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fundus photography, in combination with the ultra-wide-angle fundus (UWF) techniques, becomes an indispensable diagnostic tool in clinical settings by offering a more comprehensive view of the retina.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uwafa-gan-ultra-wide-angle-fluorescein</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UCB-driven Utility Function Search for Multi-objective Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ucb-driven-utility-function-search-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Multi-objective Reinforcement Learning (MORL) agents are tasked with optimising decision-making behaviours that trade-off between multiple, possibly conflicting, objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ucb-driven-utility-function-search-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Bidirectional Displacement for Semi-Supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-bidirectional-displacement-for-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consistency learning is a central strategy to tackle unlabeled data in semi-supervised medical image segmentation (SSMIS), which enforces the model to produce consistent predictions under the perturbation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-bidirectional-displacement-for-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaMoLE: Fine-Tuning Large Language Models with Adaptive Mixture of Low-Rank Adaptation Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adamole-fine-tuning-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce AdaMoLE, a novel method for fine-tuning large language models (LLMs) through an Adaptive Mixture of Low-Rank Adaptation (LoRA) Experts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adamole-fine-tuning-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TFPred: Learning Discriminative Representations from Unlabeled Data for Few-Label Rotating Machinery Fault Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tfpred-learning-discriminative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in intelligent rotating machinery fault diagnosis have been enabled by the availability of massive labeled training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tfpred-learning-discriminative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Learning with Task Adaptation Pre-training for Speech Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-with-task-adaptation-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose an active learning (AL)-based fine-tuning framework for SER, called \textsc{After}, that leverages task adaptation pre-training (TAPT) and AL methods to enhance performance and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-with-task-adaptation-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Pre-training of Text Recognizers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-pre-training-of-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The evaluation shows that the self-supervised pre-training on data from the target domain is very effective, but it struggles to outperform transfer learning from closely related domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-pre-training-of-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectrally Pruned Gaussian Fields with Neural Compensation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectrally-pruned-gaussian-fields-with-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this comes with high memory consumption, e. g., a well-trained Gaussian field may utilize three million Gaussian primitives and over 700 MB of memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectrally-pruned-gaussian-fields-with-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arbitrary Time Information Modeling via Polynomial Approximation for Temporal Knowledge Graph Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbitrary-time-information-modeling-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Distinguished from traditional knowledge graphs (KGs), temporal knowledge graphs (TKGs) must explore and reason over temporally evolving facts adequately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbitrary-time-information-modeling-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAPIDFlow: Recurrent Adaptable Pyramids with Iterative Decoding for Efficient Optical Flow Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapidflow-recurrent-adaptable-pyramids-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extracting motion information from videos with optical flow estimation is vital in multiple practical robot applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapidflow-recurrent-adaptable-pyramids-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformal Risk Control for Ordinal Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-risk-control-for-ordinal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a natural extension to the standard conformal prediction method, several conformal risk control methods have been recently developed and applied to various learning problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-risk-control-for-ordinal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer-based Reasoning for Learning Evolutionary Chain of Events on Temporal Knowledge Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-reasoning-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then craft a mixed-context reasoning module based on the multi-layer perceptron (MLP) to learn the unified representations of inter-quadruples for ECE while accomplishing temporal knowledge reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-reasoning-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAM: A Universal Dual Attention Mechanism for Multimodal Timeseries Cryptocurrency Trend Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dam-a-universal-dual-attention-mechanism-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the distributed systems landscape, Blockchain has catalyzed the rise of cryptocurrencies, merging enhanced security and decentralization with significant investment opportunities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dam-a-universal-dual-attention-mechanism-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient-based Automatic Per-Weight Mixed Precision Quantization for Neural Networks On-Chip</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-based-automatic-per-weight-mixed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model size and inference speed at deployment time, are major challenges in many deep learning applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-based-automatic-per-weight-mixed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A First Look at Selection Bias in Preference Elicitation for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-first-look-at-selection-bias-in-preference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the fact that the extreme sparsity of preference elicitation interactions make them severely more prone to selection bias than natural interactions, the effect of selection bias in preference elicitation on the resulting recommendations has not been studied yet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-first-look-at-selection-bias-in-preference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASAM: Boosting Segment Anything Model with Adversarial Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asam-boosting-segment-anything-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the evolving landscape of computer vision, foundation models have emerged as pivotal tools, exhibiting exceptional adaptability to a myriad of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asam-boosting-segment-anything-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Be Aware of the Neighborhood Effect: Modeling Selection Bias under Interference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/be-aware-of-the-neighborhood-effect-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On this basis, we propose a novel ideal loss that can be used to deal with selection bias in the presence of neighborhood effect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/be-aware-of-the-neighborhood-effect-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Countering Reward Over-optimization in LLM with Demonstration-Guided Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/countering-reward-over-optimization-in-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Reinforcement Learning (RL) has been proven essential for tuning large language models (LLMs), it can lead to reward over-optimization (ROO).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/countering-reward-over-optimization-in-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGCBS: An Optimal and Efficient Algorithm for Solving Multi-Goal Multi-Agent Path Finding Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgcbs-an-optimal-and-efficient-algorithm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this paper demonstrates that the methods based on DVS cannot always obtain the optimal solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgcbs-an-optimal-and-efficient-algorithm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Network Approach to Semantic Type Detection in Tables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-network-approach-to-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study addresses the challenge of detecting semantic column types in relational tables, a key task in many real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-network-approach-to-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemiPL: A Semi-supervised Method for Event Sound Source Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semipl-a-semi-supervised-method-for-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, Event Sound Source Localization has been widely applied in various fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semipl-a-semi-supervised-method-for-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constrained Decoding for Secure Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-decoding-for-secure-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose new constrained decoding techniques to generate code that satisfies security and correctness constraints simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-decoding-for-secure-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Graph ODEs for Irregularly-Sampled Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-graph-odes-for-irregularly-sampled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern graph representation learning works mostly under the assumption of dealing with regularly sampled temporal graph snapshots, which is far from realistic, e. g., social networks and physical systems are characterized by continuous dynamics and sporadic observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-graph-odes-for-irregularly-sampled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAG and RAU: A Survey on Retrieval-Augmented Language Model in Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rag-and-rau-a-survey-on-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have catalyzed significant advancements in Natural Language Processing (NLP), yet they encounter challenges such as hallucination and the need for domain-specific knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rag-and-rau-a-survey-on-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Search Engine for Machines: Unified Ranking for Multiple Retrieval-Augmented Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-search-engine-for-machines-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This lays the groundwork for us to build a large-scale experimentation ecosystem consisting of 18 RAG systems that engage in training and 18 unknown RAG systems that use the uRAG as the new users of the search engine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-search-engine-for-machines-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complex contagions can outperform simple contagions for network reconstruction with dense networks or saturated dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-contagions-can-outperform-simple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Network scientists often use complex dynamic processes to describe network contagions, but tools for fitting contagion models typically assume simple dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-contagions-can-outperform-simple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATOMMIC: An Advanced Toolbox for Multitask Medical Imaging Consistency to facilitate Artificial Intelligence applications from acquisition to analysis in Magnetic Resonance Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atommic-an-advanced-toolbox-for-multitask</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We benchmark 25 DL models on eight publicly available datasets to present distinct applications of ATOMMIC on accelerated MRI reconstruction, image segmentation, quantitative parameter map estimation, and joint accelerated MRI reconstruction and image segmentation utilizing MTL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atommic-an-advanced-toolbox-for-multitask</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-Mamba: CLIP Pretrained Mamba Models with OOD and Hessian Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-mamba-clip-pretrained-mamba-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State space models and Mamba-based models have been increasingly applied across various domains, achieving state-of-the-art performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-mamba-clip-pretrained-mamba-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G2LTraj: A Global-to-Local Generation Approach for Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g2ltraj-a-global-to-local-generation-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, to ensure the optimal granularity of key steps, we design a selectable granularity strategy that caters to each predicted trajectory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g2ltraj-a-global-to-local-generation-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IgCONDA-PET: Implicitly-Guided Counterfactual Diffusion for Detecting Anomalies in PET Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/igconda-pet-implicitly-guided-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Minimizing the need for pixel-level annotated data for training PET anomaly segmentation networks is crucial, particularly due to time and cost constraints related to expert annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/igconda-pet-implicitly-guided-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroDreamer: Zero-shot 3D Generation in $\sim$20 Seconds by Score-based Iterative Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/microdreamer-zero-shot-3d-generation-in-sim</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce score-based iterative reconstruction (SIR), an efficient and general algorithm for 3D generation with a multi-view score-based diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/microdreamer-zero-shot-3d-generation-in-sim</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transforming Dutch: Debiasing Dutch Coreference Resolution Systems for Non-binary Pronouns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transforming-dutch-debiasing-dutch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further show that CDA remains effective in low-resource settings, in which a limited set of debiasing documents is used.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transforming-dutch-debiasing-dutch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnomalyXFusion: Multi-modal Anomaly Synthesis with Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalyxfusion-multi-modal-anomaly-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The AnomalyXFusion framework comprises two distinct yet synergistic modules: the Multi-modal In-Fusion (MIF) module and the Dynamic Dif-Fusion (DDF) module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalyxfusion-multi-modal-anomaly-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Real-World HDR Video Reconstruction: A Large-Scale Benchmark Dataset and A Two-Stage Alignment Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-hdr-video-reconstruction-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, to facilitate the development of real-world HDR video reconstruction, we present Real-HDRV, a large-scale real-world benchmark dataset for HDR video reconstruction, featuring various scenes, diverse motion patterns, and high-quality labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-hdr-video-reconstruction-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed Continuous and Categorical Flow Matching for 3D De Novo Molecule Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-continuous-and-categorical-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore the use of flow matching, a recently proposed generative modeling framework that generalizes diffusion models, for the task of de novo molecule generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-continuous-and-categorical-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Stage Open-Vocabulary Temporal Action Detection Leveraging Temporal Multi-scale and Action Label Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-stage-open-vocabulary-temporal-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Closed-vocab TAD is typically confined to localizing and classifying actions based on a predefined set of categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-stage-open-vocabulary-temporal-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PCA for Point Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pca-for-point-processes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By treating point process realizations as random measures, we adopt a functional analysis perspective and propose a form of functional Principal Component Analysis (fPCA) for point processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pca-for-point-processes</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
