<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:12:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>On the Importance of Feature Decorrelation for Unsupervised Representation Learning in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-importance-of-feature-decorrelation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel URL framework that causally predicts future states while increasing the dimension of the latent manifold by decorrelating the features in the latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-importance-of-feature-decorrelation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JABBERWOCK: A Tool for WebAssembly Dataset Generation and Its Application to Malicious Website Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jabberwock-a-tool-for-webassembly-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also conduct experimental evaluations of JABBERWOCK in terms of the processing time for dataset generation, comparison of the generated samples with actual WebAssembly samples gathered from the Internet, and an application for malicious website detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jabberwock-a-tool-for-webassembly-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group Equivariant Fourier Neural Operators for Partial Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/group-equivariant-fourier-neural-operators</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider solving partial differential equations (PDEs) with Fourier neural operators (FNOs), which operate in the frequency domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/group-equivariant-fourier-neural-operators</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prediction of Transportation Index for Urban Patterns in Small and Medium-sized Indian Cities using Hybrid RidgeGAN Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-of-transportation-index-for-urban</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These synthetic urban universes mimic global urban patterns and evaluating their landscape structures through spatial pattern analysis can aid in comprehending landscape dynamics, thereby enhancing sustainable urban planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-of-transportation-index-for-urban</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Independent Teachers are Better Role Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-independent-teachers-are-better-role</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address the above limitations by designing a new deep-learning model, called 3D-DenseUNet, which works as adaptable global aggregation blocks in down-sampling to solve the issue of spatial information loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-independent-teachers-are-better-role</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communication-Efficient Zeroth-Order Distributed Online Optimization: Algorithm, Theory, and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communication-efficient-zeroth-order</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper focuses on a multi-agent zeroth-order online optimization problem in a federated learning setting for target tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communication-efficient-zeroth-order</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair yet Asymptotically Equal Collaborative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-yet-asymptotically-equal-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In collaborative learning with streaming data, nodes (e. g., organizations) jointly and continuously learn a machine learning (ML) model by sharing the latest model updates computed from their latest streaming data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-yet-asymptotically-equal-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaping through tree space: continuous phylogenetic inference for rooted and unrooted trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leaping-through-tree-space-continuous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Phylogenetics is now fundamental in life sciences, providing insights into the earliest branches of life and the origins and spread of epidemics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leaping-through-tree-space-continuous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prodigy: An Expeditiously Adaptive Parameter-Free Learner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prodigy-an-expeditiously-adaptive-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of estimating the learning rate in adaptive methods, such as Adagrad and Adam.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prodigy-an-expeditiously-adaptive-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Model Comparison in Factor Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-model-comparison-in-factor-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian state and parameter estimation have been automated effectively in the literature, however, this has not yet been the case for model comparison, which therefore still requires error-prone and time-consuming manual derivations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-model-comparison-in-factor-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Can Recommender Systems Benefit from Large Language Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-can-recommender-systems-benefit-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the "WHERE" question, we discuss the roles that LLM could play in different stages of the recommendation pipeline, i. e., feature engineering, feature encoder, scoring/ranking function, and pipeline controller.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-can-recommender-systems-benefit-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Large Language Models Infer Causation from Correlation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-infer-causation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose the first benchmark dataset to test the pure causal inference skills of large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-infer-causation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Sparse Can We Prune A Deep Network: A Geometric Viewpoint</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-sparse-can-we-prune-a-deep-network-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, in this work we take a first principles approach, specifically, by merely enforcing the sparsity constraint on the original loss function, we're able to characterize the sharp phase transition point of pruning ratio, which corresponds to the boundary between the feasible and the infeasible, from the perspective of high-dimensional geometry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-sparse-can-we-prune-a-deep-network-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Contextual Perception: How to Generalize to New Backgrounds and Ambiguous Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-contextual-perception-how-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, to better understand the model properties contributing to OOD generalization, we use representational geometry analysis and our own probing methods to examine a population of models, and we discover that those with more factorized representations and appropriate feature weighting are more successful in handling Background-Invariance and Object-Disambiguation tests.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-contextual-perception-how-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Realistic Saliency Guided Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realistic-saliency-guided-image-enhancement-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We thus offer a viable solution for automating image enhancement and photo cleanup operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realistic-saliency-guided-image-enhancement-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Estimation of the Koopman Operator with Kolmogorov-Smirnov Indicator Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-estimation-of-the-koopman-operator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It has become common to perform kinetic analysis using approximate Koopman operators that transforms high-dimensional time series of observables into ranked dynamical modes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-estimation-of-the-koopman-operator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xiezhi: An Ever-Updating Benchmark for Holistic Domain Knowledge Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xiezhi-an-ever-updating-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[New Natural Langauge Process~(NLP) benchmarks are urgently needed to align with the rapid development of large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xiezhi-an-ever-updating-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Word sense extension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/word-sense-extension</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Humans often make creative use of words to express novel senses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/word-sense-extension</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dynamical Graph Prior for Relational Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamical-graph-prior-for-relational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a \textit{dynamical graph prior} (DYGR) for relational inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamical-graph-prior-for-relational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DetZero: Rethinking Offboard 3D Object Detection with Long-term Sequential Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detzero-rethinking-offboard-3d-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on Waymo Open Dataset show our DetZero outperforms all state-of-the-art onboard and offboard 3D detection methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detzero-rethinking-offboard-3d-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illumination Controllable Dehazing Network based on Unsupervised Retinex Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illumination-controllable-dehazing-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the one hand, the dehazing task is an illposedness problem, which means that no unique solution exists.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illumination-controllable-dehazing-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I run as fast as a rabbit, can you? A Multilingual Simile Dialogue Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-run-as-fast-as-a-rabbit-can-you-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, the MSD data can also be used on dialogue tasks to test the ability of dialogue systems when using similes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-run-as-fast-as-a-rabbit-can-you-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HRTF upsampling with a generative adversarial network using a gnomonic equiangular projection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrtf-upsampling-with-a-generative-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An individualised head-related transfer function (HRTF) is essential for creating realistic virtual reality (VR) and augmented reality (AR) environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrtf-upsampling-with-a-generative-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GMS-3DQA: Projection-based Grid Mini-patch Sampling for 3D Model Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gms-3dqa-projection-based-grid-mini-patch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model-based 3DQA methods extract features directly from the 3D models, which are characterized by their high degree of complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gms-3dqa-projection-based-grid-mini-patch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Error Feedback Can Accurately Compress Preconditioners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/error-feedback-can-accurately-compress</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on deep neural networks for vision show that this approach can compress full-matrix preconditioners by up to two orders of magnitude without impact on accuracy, effectively removing the memory overhead of full-matrix preconditioning for implementations of full-matrix Adagrad (GGT) and natural gradient (M-FAC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/error-feedback-can-accurately-compress</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Boosted Model Ensembling Approach to Ball Action Spotting in Videos: The Runner-Up Solution to CVPR'23 SoccerNet Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-boosted-model-ensembling-approach-to-ball</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first generated several variants of the E2E-Spot model, resulting in a candidate model set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-boosted-model-ensembling-approach-to-ball</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extending Kernel PCA through Dualization: Sparsity, Robustness and Fast Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-kernel-pca-through-dualization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of this paper is to revisit Kernel Principal Component Analysis (KPCA) through dualization of a difference of convex functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-kernel-pca-through-dualization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expectation-Complete Graph Representations with Homomorphisms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expectation-complete-graph-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate novel random graph embeddings that can be computed in expected polynomial time and that are able to distinguish all non-isomorphic graphs in expectation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expectation-complete-graph-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explaining Reinforcement Learning with Shapley Values</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-reinforcement-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For reinforcement learning systems to be widely adopted, their users must understand and trust them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-reinforcement-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying the Knowledge in GNNs for Reliable Distillation into MLPs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-the-knowledge-in-gnns-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge the gaps between topology-aware Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) and inference-efficient Multi-Layer Perceptron (MLPs), GLNN proposes to distill knowledge from a well-trained teacher GNN into a student MLP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-the-knowledge-in-gnns-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ModeT: Learning Deformable Image Registration via Motion Decomposition Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modet-learning-deformable-image-registration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Transformer structures have been widely used in computer vision and have recently made an impact in the area of medical image registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modet-learning-deformable-image-registration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Path Neural Networks: Expressive and Accurate Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/path-neural-networks-expressive-and-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We derive three different variants of the PathNN model that aggregate single shortest paths, all shortest paths and all simple paths of length up to K. We prove that two of these variants are strictly more powerful than the 1-WL algorithm, and we experimentally validate our theoretical results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/path-neural-networks-expressive-and-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDLP: Unsupervised Object-Centric Video Prediction with Deep Dynamic Latent Particles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddlp-unsupervised-object-centric-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new object-centric video prediction algorithm based on the deep latent particle (DLP) representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddlp-unsupervised-object-centric-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinGPT: Open-Source Financial Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fingpt-open-source-financial-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While proprietary models like BloombergGPT have taken advantage of their unique data accumulation, such privileged access calls for an open-source alternative to democratize Internet-scale financial data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fingpt-open-source-financial-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptivity Complexity for Causal Graph Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptivity-complexity-for-causal-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this problem, we provide a $r$-adaptive algorithm that achieves $O(\min\{r,\log n\} \cdot n^{1/\min\{r,\log n\}})$ approximation with respect to the verification number, a well-known lower bound for adaptive algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptivity-complexity-for-causal-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Private Sharpness-Aware Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-sharpness-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training deep learning models with differential privacy (DP) results in a degradation of performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-sharpness-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AircraftVerse: A Large-Scale Multimodal Dataset of Aerial Vehicle Designs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aircraftverse-a-large-scale-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present AircraftVerse, a publicly available aerial vehicle design dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aircraftverse-a-large-scale-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the Loop: Testing ChatGPT to Generate Model Explanations to Improve Human Labelling of Sponsored Content on Social Media</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-loop-testing-chatgpt-to-generate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve annotation accuracy and, thus, the detection of sponsored content, we propose using chatGPT to augment the annotation process with phrases identified as relevant features and brief explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-loop-testing-chatgpt-to-generate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yet Another ICU Benchmark: A Flexible Multi-Center Framework for Clinical ML</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yet-another-icu-benchmark-a-flexible-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Datasets and code are not always published, and cohort definitions, preprocessing pipelines, and training setups are difficult to reproduce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yet-another-icu-benchmark-a-flexible-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ART of Conversation: Measuring Phonetic Convergence and Deliberate Imitation in L2-Speech with a Siamese RNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-art-of-conversation-measuring-phonetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Phonetic convergence describes the automatic and unconscious speech adaptation of two interlocutors in a conversation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-art-of-conversation-measuring-phonetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster Approximation Algorithms for Parameterized Graph Clustering and Edge Labeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-approximation-algorithms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph clustering is a fundamental task in network analysis where the goal is to detect sets of nodes that are well-connected to each other but sparsely connected to the rest of the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-approximation-algorithms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed-TD: Efficient Neural Network Accelerator with Layer-Specific Tensor Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-td-efficient-neural-network-accelerator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The deployment of neural networks to such dataflow architecture accelerators is usually hindered by the available on-chip memory as it is desirable to preload the weights of neural networks on-chip to maximise the system performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-td-efficient-neural-network-accelerator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PandaLM: An Automatic Evaluation Benchmark for LLM Instruction Tuning Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pandalm-an-automatic-evaluation-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To ensure the reliability of PandaLM, we collect a diverse human-annotated test dataset, where all contexts are generated by humans and labels are aligned with human preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pandalm-an-automatic-evaluation-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subject clustering by IF-PCA and several recent methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subject-clustering-by-if-pca-and-several</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also find that IF-PCA is quite competitive, which slightly outperforms Seurat and SC3 over the $8$ single-cell data sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subject-clustering-by-if-pca-and-several</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIXIU: A Large Language Model, Instruction Data and Evaluation Benchmark for Finance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixiu-a-large-language-model-instruction-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces PIXIU, a comprehensive framework including the first financial LLM based on fine-tuning LLaMA with instruction data, the first instruction data with 136K data samples to support the fine-tuning, and an evaluation benchmark with 5 tasks and 9 datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixiu-a-large-language-model-instruction-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Time in Causal Algorithmic Recourse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-importance-of-time-in-causal-algorithmic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The application of Algorithmic Recourse in decision-making is a promising field that offers practical solutions to reverse unfavorable decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-importance-of-time-in-causal-algorithmic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Closed-form Equations for Subgrid-scale Closures from High-fidelity Data: Promises and Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-closed-form-equations-for-subgrid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is growing interest in discovering interpretable, closed-form equations for subgrid-scale (SGS) closures/parameterizations of complex processes in Earth system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-closed-form-equations-for-subgrid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and Equivariant Graph Networks for Predicting Quantum Hamiltonian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-equivariant-graph-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the prediction of the Hamiltonian matrix, which finds use in quantum chemistry and condensed matter physics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-equivariant-graph-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stratification of uncertainties recalibrated by isotonic regression and its impact on calibration error statistics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stratification-of-uncertainties-recalibrated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Partitioning of the resulting data into equal-sized bins introduces an aleatoric component to the estimation of bin-based calibration statistics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stratification-of-uncertainties-recalibrated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InvPT++: Inverted Pyramid Multi-Task Transformer for Visual Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invpt-inverted-pyramid-multi-task-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[And then, we design a transformer decoder to establish spatial and cross-task interaction globally, and a novel UP-Transformer block is devised to increase the resolutions of multi-task features gradually and establish cross-task interaction at different scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invpt-inverted-pyramid-multi-task-transformer</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
