<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 21:08:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Can LLMs Beat Humans in Debating? A Dynamic Multi-agent Framework for Competitive Debate</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llms-beat-humans-in-debating-a-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we introduce Agent for Debate (Agent4Debate), a dynamic, multi-agent framework based on LLMs designed to enhance their capabilities in competitive debate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llms-beat-humans-in-debating-a-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMTeC: A Corpus of Eye Movements on Machine-Generated Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emtec-a-corpus-of-eye-movements-on-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, the corpus includes the language models' internals that underlie the generation of the stimulus texts: the transition scores, the attention scores, and the hidden states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emtec-a-corpus-of-eye-movements-on-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Molecular Machine (Learned) Representations with Stereoelectronics-Infused Molecular Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-molecular-machine-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the explicit addition of stereoelectronic interactions significantly improves the performance of molecular machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-molecular-machine-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Reasoning Biases in Large Language Models Through Syllogism: Insights from the NeuBAROCO Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-reasoning-biases-in-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also present experimental results and in-depth analysis using a new Chain-of-Thought prompting method, which asks LLMs to translate syllogisms into abstract logical expressions and then explain their reasoning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-reasoning-biases-in-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Language Model Math Reasoning via Grounding in Educational Curricula</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-language-model-math-reasoning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work presents a novel angle for evaluating language models' (LMs) mathematical abilities, by investigating whether they can discern skills and concepts enabled by math content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-language-model-math-reasoning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Locally Private Sparse Estimation Given Multiple Samples Per User</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-locally-private-sparse-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous studies yielded discouraging results for item-level locally differentially private linear regression with $s^*$-sparsity assumption, where the minimax rate for $nm$ samples is $\mathcal{O}(s^{*}d / nm\varepsilon^2)$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-locally-private-sparse-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMRole: A Comprehensive Framework for Developing and Evaluating Multimodal Role-Playing Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmrole-a-comprehensive-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce the concept of Multimodal Role-Playing Agents (MRPAs), and propose a comprehensive framework, MMRole, for their development and evaluation, which comprises a personalized multimodal dataset and a robust evaluation method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmrole-a-comprehensive-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Data Addition Dilemma</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-data-addition-dilemma</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many machine learning for healthcare tasks, standard datasets are constructed by amassing data across many, often fundamentally dissimilar, sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-data-addition-dilemma</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listwise Reward Estimation for Offline Preference-based Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/listwise-reward-estimation-for-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Listwise Reward Estimation (LiRE), a novel approach for offline PbRL that leverages second-order preference information by constructing a Ranked List of Trajectories (RLT), which can be efficiently built by using the same ternary feedback type as traditional methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/listwise-reward-estimation-for-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Approximate Characterization of Single-Cell Heterogeneity in Microbial Growth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-approximate-characterization-of-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Live-cell microscopy allows to go beyond measuring average features of cellular populations to observe, quantify and explain biological heterogeneity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-approximate-characterization-of-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiDAR-Event Stereo Fusion with Hallucinations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidar-event-stereo-fusion-with-hallucinations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event stereo matching is an emerging technique to estimate depth from neuromorphic cameras; however, events are unlikely to trigger in the absence of motion or the presence of large, untextured regions, making the correspondence problem extremely challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidar-event-stereo-fusion-with-hallucinations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Fine-Grained Grounded Citations for Attributed Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-fine-grained-grounded-citations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the impressive performance on information-seeking tasks, large language models (LLMs) still struggle with hallucinations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-fine-grained-grounded-citations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Guided Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-guided-language-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For auto-regressive language models, existing guidance methods are prone to decoding errors that cascade during generation and degrade performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-guided-language-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mbrs: A Library for Minimum Bayes Risk Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbrs-a-library-for-minimum-bayes-risk</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We published our mbrs as an MIT-licensed open-source project, and the code is available on GitHub.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbrs-a-library-for-minimum-bayes-risk</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HydraFormer: One Encoder For All Subsampling Rates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hydraformer-one-encoder-for-all-subsampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In automatic speech recognition, subsampling is essential for tackling diverse scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hydraformer-one-encoder-for-all-subsampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TheGlueNote: Learned Representations for Robust and Flexible Note Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thegluenote-learned-representations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Note alignment refers to the task of matching individual notes of two versions of the same symbolically encoded piece.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thegluenote-learned-representations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Img-Diff: Contrastive Data Synthesis for Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/img-diff-contrastive-data-synthesis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, we investigate alternative methods for generating image difference data through "object removal" and conduct thorough evaluation to confirm the dataset's diversity, quality, and robustness, presenting several insights on synthesis of such contrastive dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/img-diff-contrastive-data-synthesis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inference with the Upper Confidence Bound Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-with-the-upper-confidence-bound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that in such a case the arms are stable when $\frac{\log K}{\log T} \rightarrow 0$, and the number of near-optimal arms are large.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-with-the-upper-confidence-bound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Exposure Bias in Online Learning to Rank Recommendation: A Novel Reward Model for Cascading Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-exposure-bias-in-online-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study exposure bias in a class of well-known contextual bandit algorithms known as Linear Cascading Bandits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-exposure-bias-in-online-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Algorithm for Estimation of Sparse Gaussian Graphical Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dc-algorithm-for-estimation-of-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we formulate the sparse estimation problem for Gaussian graphical models using the $\ell_0$ norm and propose a method to solve this problem using the Difference of Convex functions Algorithm (DCA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dc-algorithm-for-estimation-of-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Review of 3D Reconstruction Techniques for Deformable Tissues in Robotic Surgery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-3d-reconstruction-techniques-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a crucial and intricate task in robotic minimally invasive surgery, reconstructing surgical scenes using stereo or monocular endoscopic video holds immense potential for clinical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-3d-reconstruction-techniques-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Transformer for High Dimensional Multivariate Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-transformer-for-high-dimensional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the number of channels in real-world applications outpaces the capabilities of existing channel-dependent models, and contrary to common expectations, some models underperform the channel-independent models in handling high-dimensional data, which raises questions about the performance of channel-dependent models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-transformer-for-high-dimensional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Forecast: A Multimodal Approach to Temporal Event Forecasting with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-forecast-a-multimodal-approach-to-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study an emerging and intriguing problem of multimodal temporal event forecasting with large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-forecast-a-multimodal-approach-to-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Power of Sparse Neural Networks for Feature Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-power-of-sparse-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse Neural Networks (SNNs) have emerged as powerful tools for efficient feature selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-power-of-sparse-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans-Tokenization and Cross-lingual Vocabulary Transfers: Language Adaptation of LLMs for Low-Resource NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trans-tokenization-and-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By lowering the data and time requirements for training high-quality models, our trans-tokenization strategy allows for the development of LLMs for a wider range of languages, especially those with limited resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trans-tokenization-and-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bias-Aware Low-Rank Adaptation: Mitigating Catastrophic Inheritance of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bias-aware-low-rank-adaptation-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have exhibited remarkable proficiency across a diverse array of natural language processing (NLP) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bias-aware-low-rank-adaptation-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Noisy Clients in Federated Learning with End-to-end Label Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-noisy-clients-in-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intuitively, the performance degradation is dominated by clients with higher noise rates since their trained models contain more misinformation from data, thus it is necessary to devise an effective optimization scheme to mitigate the negative impacts of these noisy clients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-noisy-clients-in-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-View Meets Diffusion: Aerial Image Synthesis with Geometry and Text Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-view-meets-diffusion-aerial-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel Geometric Preserving Ground-to-Aerial (G2A) image synthesis (GPG2A) model that can generate realistic aerial images from ground images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-view-meets-diffusion-aerial-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and Accurate Pneumonia Detection Using a Novel Multi-Scale Transformer Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-accurate-pneumonia-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By employing our specialized transformer, we attain superior results with significantly fewer parameters compared to common transformer models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-accurate-pneumonia-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Translations for Children: Iterative Simplification Considering Age of Acquisition with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-translations-for-children</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a method that replaces words with high Age of Acquisitions (AoA) in translations with simpler words to match the translations to the user's level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-translations-for-children</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ungrounded Alignment Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ungrounded-alignment-problem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper examines a simplified version of the general problem, where an unsupervised learner is presented with a sequence of images for the characters in a text corpus, and this learner is later evaluated on its ability to recognize specific (possibly rare) sequential patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ungrounded-alignment-problem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantics or spelling? Probing contextual word embeddings with orthographic noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantics-or-spelling-probing-contextual-word</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pretrained language model (PLM) hidden states are frequently employed as contextual word embeddings (CWE): high-dimensional representations that encode semantic information given linguistic context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantics-or-spelling-probing-contextual-word</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FacialPulse: An Efficient RNN-based Depression Detection via Temporal Facial Landmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facialpulse-an-efficient-rnn-based-depression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Depression is a prevalent mental health disorder that significantly impacts individuals' lives and well-being.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facialpulse-an-efficient-rnn-based-depression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AEye: A Visualization Tool for Image Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aeye-a-visualization-tool-for-image-datasets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image datasets serve as the foundation for machine learning models in computer vision, significantly influencing model capabilities, performance, and biases alongside architectural considerations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aeye-a-visualization-tool-for-image-datasets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PaveCap: The First Multimodal Framework for Comprehensive Pavement Condition Assessment with Dense Captioning and PCI Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pavecap-the-first-multimodal-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The framework consists of two main parts: a Single-Shot PCI Estimation Network and a Dense Captioning Network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pavecap-the-first-multimodal-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring RAG-based Vulnerability Augmentation with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-rag-based-vulnerability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conducted an extensive evaluation of our proposed approach on three vulnerability datasets and three DLVD models, using two LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-rag-based-vulnerability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Multimodal Large Language Models with Quantization-Aware Scale Learning for Efficient Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-multimodal-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method is grounded in two key innovations: (1) The learning of group-wise scale factors for quantized LLM weights to mitigate the quantization error arising from activation outliers and achieve more effective vision-language instruction tuning; (2) The implementation of a multimodal warmup that progressively integrates linguistic and multimodal training samples, thereby preventing overfitting of the quantized model to multimodal data while ensuring stable adaptation of multimodal large language models to downstream vision-language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-multimodal-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D2Styler: Advancing Arbitrary Style Transfer with Discrete Diffusion Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d2styler-advancing-arbitrary-style-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This makes it easy to move features from the style image to the content image without bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d2styler-advancing-arbitrary-style-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BeeManc at the PLABA Track of TAC-2023: Investigating LLMs and Controllable Attributes for Improving Biomedical Text Readability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beemanc-at-the-plaba-track-of-tac-2023</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the official human evaluation, our model BART-w-CTs ranks 2nd on Sentence-Simplicity (score 92. 84), 3rd on Term-Simplicity (score 82. 33) among all 7 evaluated systems; It also produced a high score 91. 57 on Fluency in comparison to the highest score 93. 53.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beemanc-at-the-plaba-track-of-tac-2023</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time is Not Enough: Time-Frequency based Explanation for Time-Series Black-Box Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-is-not-enough-time-frequency-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct extensive experiments in the generated synthetic dataset and various UCR Time-Series datasets to first compare the explanation performance of FIA and other existing perturbation-based XAI methods in both time-domain and time-frequency domain, and then show the superiority of our FIA in the time-frequency domain with the SpectralX framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-is-not-enough-time-frequency-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image-to-LaTeX Converter for Mathematical Formulas and Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-to-latex-converter-for-mathematical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this project, we train a vision encoder-decoder model to generate LaTeX code from images of mathematical formulas and text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-to-latex-converter-for-mathematical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgformer: Surgical Transformer with Hierarchical Temporal Attention for Surgical Phase Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgformer-surgical-transformer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we propose a novel Hierarchical Temporal Attention (HTA) to capture both global and local information within varied temporal resolutions from a target frame-centric perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgformer-surgical-transformer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Non-Native Language Context Limitation: Native Language Prompting Facilitates Knowledge Elicitation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-non-native-language-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multilingual large language models (MLLMs) struggle to answer questions posed in non-dominant languages, even though they have already acquired the relevant knowledge from their dominant language corpus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-non-native-language-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WalledEval: A Comprehensive Safety Evaluation Toolkit for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/walledeval-a-comprehensive-safety-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[WalledEval is a comprehensive AI safety testing toolkit designed to evaluate large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/walledeval-a-comprehensive-safety-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech-MASSIVE: A Multilingual Speech Dataset for SLU and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-massive-a-multilingual-speech-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Speech-MASSIVE, a multilingual Spoken Language Understanding (SLU) dataset comprising the speech counterpart for a portion of the MASSIVE textual corpus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-massive-a-multilingual-speech-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Generation Scheme for Thermal Modality with Edge-Guided Adversarial Conditional Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-generation-scheme-for-thermal-modality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This framework aims to produce meticulously aligned pseudo thermal images at the pixel level, leveraging edge information extracted from visible images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-generation-scheme-for-thermal-modality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pick of the Bunch: Detecting Infrared Small Targets Beyond Hit-Miss Trade-Offs via Selective Rank-Aware Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pick-of-the-bunch-detecting-infrared-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Infrared small target detection faces the inherent challenge of precisely localizing dim targets amidst complex background clutter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pick-of-the-bunch-detecting-infrared-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM2-PATH: A better segment anything model for semantic segmentation in digital pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam2-path-a-better-segment-anything-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The semantic segmentation task in pathology plays an indispensable role in assisting physicians in determining the condition of tissue lesions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam2-path-a-better-segment-anything-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relevance meets Diversity: A User-Centric Framework for Knowledge Exploration through Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relevance-meets-diversity-a-user-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use diversity as a surrogate of the amount of knowledge obtained by the user while interacting with the system, and we seek to maximize diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relevance-meets-diversity-a-user-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Output Diversity Improves Conjugate Gradient-based Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-output-diversity-improves-conjugate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hypothesized that increasing the distance between two consecutive search points would enhance the output diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-output-diversity-improves-conjugate</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
