<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:08:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Identity-Aware Cross-Modal Retrieval: a Dataset and a Baseline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-identity-aware-cross-modal-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in deep learning have significantly enhanced content-based retrieval methods, notably through models like CLIP that map images and texts into a shared embedding space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-identity-aware-cross-modal-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReFlow6D: Refraction-Guided Transparent Object 6D Pose Estimation via Intermediate Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reflow6d-refraction-guided-transparent-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve this, we present ReFlow6D, a novel method for transparent object 6D pose estimation that harnesses the refractive-intermediate representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reflow6d-refraction-guided-transparent-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Intelligent and Secure Cloud: Large Language Model Empowered Proactive Defense</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-intelligent-and-secure-cloud-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid evolution of cloud computing technologies and the increasing number of cloud applications have provided a large number of benefits in daily lives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-intelligent-and-secure-cloud-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TangoFlux: Super Fast and Faithful Text to Audio Generation with Flow Matching and Clap-Ranked Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tangoflux-super-fast-and-faithful-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce TangoFlux, an efficient Text-to-Audio (TTA) generative model with 515M parameters, capable of generating up to 30 seconds of 44. 1kHz audio in just 3. 7 seconds on a single A40 GPU.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tangoflux-super-fast-and-faithful-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Visual Representation for Text-based Person Searching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-visual-representation-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior works adopt image and text encoders pre-trained on unimodal data to extract global and local features from image and text respectively, and then global-local alignment is achieved explicitly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-visual-representation-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Software Engineering Agents and Verifiers with SWE-Gym</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-software-engineering-agents-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When combined with our fine-tuned SWE agents, we achieve 32. 0% and 26. 0% on SWE-Bench Verified and Lite, respectively, reflecting a new state-of-the-art for open-weight SWE agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-software-engineering-agents-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Vision-Language Models Truly Understanding Multi-vision Sensor?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-vision-language-models-truly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we introduce Diverse Negative Attributes (DNA) optimization to enable VLMs to perform deep reasoning on multi-vision sensor tasks, helping to bridge the core information gap between images and sensor data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-vision-language-models-truly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TiGDistill-BEV: Multi-view BEV 3D Object Detection via Target Inner-Geometry Learning Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tigdistill-bev-multi-view-bev-3d-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers have consistently aimed to leverage LiDAR's precise spatial information to enhance camera-based detectors through methods like depth supervision and bird-eye-view (BEV) feature distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tigdistill-bev-multi-view-bev-3d-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MapQaTor: A System for Efficient Annotation of Map Query Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapqator-a-system-for-efficient-annotation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mapping and navigation services like Google Maps, Apple Maps, Openstreet Maps, are essential for accessing various location-based data, yet they often struggle to handle natural language geospatial queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapqator-a-system-for-efficient-annotation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency-Masked Embedding Inference: A Non-Contrastive Approach for Time Series Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-masked-embedding-inference-a-non</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fundamentally overcome the limitations of contrastive learning, this paper introduces Frequency-masked Embedding Inference (FEI), a novel non-contrastive method that completely eliminates the need for positive and negative samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-masked-embedding-inference-a-non</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sample Correlation for Fingerprinting Deep Face Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-correlation-for-fingerprinting-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Face recognition has witnessed remarkable advancements in recent years, thanks to the development of deep learning techniques. However, an off-the-shelf face recognition model as a commercial service could be stolen by model stealing attacks, posing great threats to the rights of the model owner. Model fingerprinting, as a model stealing detection method, aims to verify whether a suspect model is stolen from the victim model, gaining more and more attention nowadays. Previous methods always utilize transferable adversarial examples as the model fingerprint, but this method is known to be sensitive to adversarial defense and transfer learning techniques. To address this issue, we consider the pairwise relationship between samples instead and propose a novel yet simple model stealing detection method based on SAmple Correlation (SAC). Specifically, we present SAC-JC that selects JPEG compressed samples as model inputs and calculates the correlation matrix among their model outputs. Extensive results validate that SAC successfully defends against various model stealing attacks in deep face recognition, encompassing face verification and face emotion recognition, exhibiting the highest performance in terms of AUC, p-value and F1 score. Furthermore, we extend our evaluation of SAC-JC to object recognition datasets including Tiny-ImageNet and CIFAR10, which also demonstrates the superior performance of SAC-JC to previous methods. The code will be available at \url{https://github. com/guanjiyang/SAC_JC}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-correlation-for-fingerprinting-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Parallel External-Memory Bidirectional Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-parallel-external-memory-bidirectional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parallelization and External Memory (PEM) techniques have significantly enhanced the capabilities of search algorithms when solving large-scale problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-parallel-external-memory-bidirectional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Style Prompt Learning Using Diffusion Models for Blind Face Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-style-prompt-learning-using-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Blind face restoration aims to recover high-quality facial images from various unidentified sources of degradation, posing significant challenges due to the minimal information retrievable from the degraded images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-style-prompt-learning-using-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plancraft: an evaluation dataset for planning with LLM agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plancraft-an-evaluation-dataset-for-planning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Plancraft, a multi-modal evaluation dataset for LLM agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plancraft-an-evaluation-dataset-for-planning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMix: Improving Text-to-Image Diffusion Model with Cross-Attention Mixing Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vmix-improving-text-to-image-diffusion-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While diffusion models show extraordinary talents in text-to-image generation, they may still fail to generate highly aesthetic images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vmix-improving-text-to-image-diffusion-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftPatch+: Fully Unsupervised Anomaly Classification and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softpatch-fully-unsupervised-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the performance of SoftPatch and SoftPatch+ is comparable to that of the noise-free methods in conventional unsupervised AD setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softpatch-fully-unsupervised-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Two Imperatives: Privacy and Explainability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tale-of-two-imperatives-privacy-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning's preponderance across scientific domains has reshaped high-stakes decision-making, making it essential to follow rigorous operational frameworks that include both Right-to-Privacy (RTP) and Right-to-Explanation (RTE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tale-of-two-imperatives-privacy-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Parallel Genetic Algorithm for Perturbed Substructure Optimization in Complex Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-parallel-genetic-algorithm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, GAPA includes an extensible library that optimizes and accelerates 10 PSSO algorithms, covering 4 crucial tasks for graph mining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-parallel-genetic-algorithm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vinci: A Real-time Embodied Smart Assistant based on Egocentric Vision-Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vinci-a-real-time-embodied-smart-assistant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Vinci, a real-time embodied smart assistant built upon an egocentric vision-language model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vinci-a-real-time-embodied-smart-assistant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisionReward: Fine-Grained Multi-Dimensional Human Preference Learning for Image and Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visionreward-fine-grained-multi-dimensional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a general strategy to aligning visual generation models -- both image and video generation -- with human preference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visionreward-fine-grained-multi-dimensional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyG-SSL: A Graph Self-Supervised Learning Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyg-ssl-a-graph-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Self-Supervised Learning (SSL) has emerged as a pivotal area of research in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyg-ssl-a-graph-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Heads Are Better Than One: Averaging along Fine-Tuning to Improve Targeted Transferability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-heads-are-better-than-one-averaging-along</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the proposed method with existing fine-tuning schemes by integrating them with state-of-the-art targeted attacks in various attacking scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-heads-are-better-than-one-averaging-along</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributed Mixture-of-Agents for Edge Inference with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributed-mixture-of-agents-for-edge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, we demonstrate through experiments, leveraging open-source LLMs for the implementation of distributed MoA, that certain MoA configurations produce higher-quality responses compared to others, as evaluated on AlpacaEval 2. 0 benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributed-mixture-of-agents-for-edge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Hangover Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-hangover-effects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We are interested to see if teams exhibit a decline in performance the day following a game in a city with active nightlife; we call this a "hangover effect".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-hangover-effects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edicho: Consistent Image Editing in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edicho-consistent-image-editing-in-the-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a verified need, consistent editing across in-the-wild images remains a technical challenge arising from various unmanageable factors, like object poses, lighting conditions, and photography environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edicho-consistent-image-editing-in-the-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Aggregation and Segregation of Representations for Domain Adaptive Human Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-aggregation-and-segregation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To cope with the label deficiency issue, one common solution is to train the HPE models with easily available synthetic datasets (source) and apply them to real-world data (target) through domain adaptation (DA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-aggregation-and-segregation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact of Data Distribution on Fairness Guarantees in Equitable Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-data-distribution-on-fairness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a comprehensive theoretical framework analyzing the relationship between data distributions and fairness guarantees in equitable deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-data-distribution-on-fairness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReTaKe: Reducing Temporal and Knowledge Redundancy for Long Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retake-reducing-temporal-and-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[we introduce a training-free method, $\textbf{ReTaKe}$, containing two novel modules DPSelect and PivotKV, to jointly model and reduce both temporal visual redundancy and knowledge redundancy for long video understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retake-reducing-temporal-and-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Sora: Democratizing Efficient Video Production for All</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-sora-democratizing-efficient-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate the development and accessibility of artificial visual intelligence, we created Open-Sora, an open-source video generation model designed to produce high-fidelity video content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-sora-democratizing-efficient-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to SFT, NLFT does not increase the algorithmic complexity, maintaining O(n).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Current Video LLMs Have Strong OCR Abilities? A Preliminary Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-current-video-llms-have-strong-ocr</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rise of multimodal large language models, accurately extracting and understanding textual information from video content, referred to as video based optical character recognition (Video OCR), has become a crucial capability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-current-video-llms-have-strong-ocr</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion Transfer-Driven intra-class data augmentation for Finger Vein Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-transfer-driven-intra-class-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel motion transfer (MT) model for finger vein image data augmentation via modeling the actual finger posture and rotational movements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-transfer-driven-intra-class-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Hybrid Policy in Reinforcement Learning for Interpretable Temporal Logic Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-hybrid-policy-in-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these challenges, we propose a Temporal-Logic-guided Hybrid policy framework (HyTL) which leverages three-level decision layers to improve the agent's performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-hybrid-policy-in-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Conditional Alignment based on Label Shift Calibration for Imbalanced Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-conditional-alignment-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we propose contrastive conditional alignment based on label shift calibration (CCA-LSC) for IDA, to address both covariate shift and label shift.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-conditional-alignment-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Impact of Prompt Programming on Function-Level Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-impact-of-prompt-programming-on-function</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce CodePromptEval, a dataset of 7072 prompts designed to evaluate five prompt techniques (few-shot, persona, chain-of-thought, function signature, list of packages) and their effect on the correctness, similarity, and quality of complete functions generated by three LLMs (GPT-4o, Llama3, and Mistral).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-impact-of-prompt-programming-on-function</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FairDiffusion: Enhancing Equity in Latent Diffusion Models via Fair Bayesian Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairdiffusion-enhancing-equity-in-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this critical concern, we present the first comprehensive study on the fairness of medical text-to-image diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairdiffusion-enhancing-equity-in-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calibre: Towards Fair and Accurate Personalized Federated Learning with Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibre-towards-fair-and-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of personalized federated learning, existing approaches train a global model to extract transferable representations, based on which any client could train personalized models with a limited number of data samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibre-towards-fair-and-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneKE: A Dockerized Schema-Guided LLM Agent-based Knowledge Extraction System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oneke-a-dockerized-schema-guided-llm-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce OneKE, a dockerized schema-guided knowledge extraction system, which can extract knowledge from the Web and raw PDF Books, and support various domains (science, news, etc.).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oneke-a-dockerized-schema-guided-llm-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imitation Learning from Suboptimal Demonstrations via Meta-Learning An Action Ranker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imitation-learning-from-suboptimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To make more effective use of supplementary demonstrations, we introduce meta-goal in ILMAR to optimize the functional of the advantage function by explicitly minimizing the distance between the current policy and the expert policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imitation-learning-from-suboptimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Contrastive Pretrain Model with Prompt Tuning for Multi-center Medication Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-contrastive-pretrain-model-with-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a novel conTrastive prEtrain Model with Prompt Tuning (TEMPT) for multi-center medication recommendation, which includes two stages of pretraining and finetuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-contrastive-pretrain-model-with-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MobileNetV2: A lightweight classification model for home-based sleep apnea screening</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobilenetv2-a-lightweight-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For sleep stage classification, in UCDDB dataset, the ROC-AUC exceeded 0. 85 across all stages, with recall for Sleep reaching 0. 906 and specificity for REM and Wake states at 0. 956 and 0. 937, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobilenetv2-a-lightweight-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M-MAD: Multidimensional Multi-Agent Debate Framework for Fine-grained Machine Translation Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-mad-multidimensional-multi-agent-debate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) have given rise to the LLM-as-a-judge paradigm, showcasing their potential to deliver human-like judgments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-mad-multidimensional-multi-agent-debate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEGSTalk: Decomposed Per-Embedding Gaussian Fields for Hair-Preserving Talking Face Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/degstalk-decomposed-per-embedding-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these challenges in existing methods, we propose a decomposed per-embedding Gaussian fields (DEGSTalk), a 3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS)-based talking face synthesis method for generating realistic talking faces with long hairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/degstalk-decomposed-per-embedding-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeLU Activation Function for Fast and Stable Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/telu-activation-function-for-fast-and-stable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the Hyperbolic Tangent Exponential Linear Unit (TeLU), a neural network hidden activation function defined as TeLU(x)=xtanh(exp(x)).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/telu-activation-function-for-fast-and-stable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Compositional Generalization of Multimodal LLMs for Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-compositional-generalization-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal large language models (MLLMs) hold significant potential in the medical field, but their capabilities are often limited by insufficient data in certain medical domains, highlighting the need for understanding what kinds of images can be used by MLLMs for generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-compositional-generalization-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniRestorer: Universal Image Restoration via Adaptively Estimating Image Degradation at Proper Granularity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unirestorer-universal-image-restoration-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to existing degradation-agnostic and -aware methods, UniRestorer can leverage degradation estimation to benefit degradationspecific restoration, and use granularity estimation to make the model robust to degradation estimation error.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unirestorer-universal-image-restoration-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invariant debiasing learning for recommendation via biased imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-debiasing-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we experimentally demonstrate that invariant learning causes information loss by directly discarding the variant information, which reduces the generalization ability and results in the degradation of model performance in unbiased recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-debiasing-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Visual Grounding: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-visual-grounding-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we outline the challenges confronting visual grounding and propose valuable directions for future research, which may serve as inspiration for subsequent researchers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-visual-grounding-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GSplatLoc: Ultra-Precise Camera Localization via 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gsplatloc-ultra-precise-camera-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present GSplatLoc, a camera localization method that leverages the differentiable rendering capabilities of 3D Gaussian splatting for ultra-precise pose estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gsplatloc-ultra-precise-camera-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VELoRA: A Low-Rank Adaptation Approach for Efficient RGB-Event based Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/velora-a-low-rank-adaptation-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the successful application of large models, the introduction of such large models can also be considered to further enhance the performance of multi-modal tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/velora-a-low-rank-adaptation-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
