<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 21:07:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SimAM: A Simple, Parameter-Free Attention Module for Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simam-a-simple-parameter-free-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Another advantage of the module is that most of the operators are selected based on the solution to the defined energy function, avoiding too many efforts for structure tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simam-a-simple-parameter-free-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Modeling of Future Context for Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-modeling-of-future-context-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing approaches to image captioning usually generate the sentence word-by-word from left to right, with the constraint of conditioned on local context including the given image and history generated words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-modeling-of-future-context-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Ensemble Approach for Multiple Emotion Descriptors Estimation Using Multi-task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ensemble-approach-for-multiple-emotion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper illustrates our submission method to the fourth Affective Behavior Analysis in-the-Wild (ABAW) Competition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ensemble-approach-for-multiple-emotion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FairGRAPE: Fairness-aware GRAdient Pruning mEthod for Face Attribute Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairgrape-fairness-aware-gradient-pruning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing pruning techniques preserve deep neural networks' overall ability to make correct predictions but may also amplify hidden biases during the compression process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairgrape-fairness-aware-gradient-pruning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Respecting Time Series Properties Makes Deep Time Series Forecasting Perfect</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/respecting-time-series-properties-makes-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to the core idea of respecting time series properties, no matter in which forecasting format, RTNet shows obviously superior forecasting performances compared with dozens of other SOTA time series forecasting baselines in three real-world benchmark datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/respecting-time-series-properties-makes-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Image Compression via Joint Learning with Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-image-compression-via-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key is to transform the original noisy images to noise-free bits by eliminating the undesired noise during compression, where the bits are later decompressed as clean images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-image-compression-via-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Soft Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-soft-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning has recently achieved great success in representation learning without human annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-soft-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoupled Adversarial Contrastive Learning for Self-supervised Adversarial Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-adversarial-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial training (AT) for robust representation learning and self-supervised learning (SSL) for unsupervised representation learning are two active research fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-adversarial-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My View is the Best View: Procedure Learning from Egocentric Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/my-view-is-the-best-view-procedure-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead, we propose to use the signal provided by the temporal correspondences between key-steps across videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/my-view-is-the-best-view-procedure-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Reference-based Distinctive Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-reference-based-distinctive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, reference images used by existing Ref-DIC works are easy to distinguish: these reference images only resemble the target image at scene-level and have few common objects, such that a Ref-DIC model can trivially generate distinctive captions even without considering the reference images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-reference-based-distinctive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Testing of Deep Neural Networks via Decision Boundary Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-testing-of-deep-neural-networks-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In practice, the de facto standard to assess the quality of DNNs in industry is to check their performance (accuracy) on a collected set of labeled test data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-testing-of-deep-neural-networks-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototype-Guided Continual Adaptation for Class-Incremental Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-guided-continual-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[2) Prototype-based alignment and replay: based on the identified label prototypes, we align both domains and enforce the model to retain previous knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-guided-continual-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeVIS: Making Deformable Transformers Work for Video Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/devis-making-deformable-transformers-work-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reason about all VIS subtasks jointly over multiple frames, we present temporal multi-scale deformable attention with instance-aware object queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/devis-making-deformable-transformers-work-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Interacting Hand Pose Estimation by Hand De-occlusion and Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-interacting-hand-pose-estimation-by-hand</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike most previous works that directly predict the 3D poses of two interacting hands simultaneously, we propose to decompose the challenging interacting hand pose estimation task and estimate the pose of each hand separately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-interacting-hand-pose-estimation-by-hand</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RealFlow: EM-based Realistic Optical Flow Dataset Generation from Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realflow-em-based-realistic-optical-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we first estimate optical flow between a pair of video frames, and then synthesize a new image from this pair based on the predicted flow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realflow-em-based-realistic-optical-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-tailed Instance Segmentation using Gumbel Optimized Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-instance-segmentation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Major advancements have been made in the field of object detection and segmentation recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-instance-segmentation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scale dependant layer for self-supervised nuclei encoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-dependant-layer-for-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent developments in self-supervised learning give us the possibility to further reduce human intervention in multi-step pipelines where the focus evolves around particular objects of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-dependant-layer-for-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-Temporal Deformable Attention Network for Video Deblurring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-deformable-attention-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key success factor of the video deblurring methods is to compensate for the blurry pixels of the mid-frame with the sharp pixels of the adjacent video frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-deformable-attention-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POP: Mining POtential Performance of new fashion products via webly cross-modal query expansion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pop-mining-potential-performance-of-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a data-centric pipeline able to generate exogenous observation data for the New Fashion Product Performance Forecasting (NFPPF) problem, i. e., predicting the performance of a brand-new clothing probe with no available past observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pop-mining-potential-performance-of-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning Hyperparameter Optimization for Breast Mass Detection in Mammograms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-hyperparameter-optimization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate breast cancer diagnosis through mammography has the potential to save millions of lives around the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-hyperparameter-optimization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MobileDenseNet: A new approach to object detection on mobile devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobiledensenet-a-new-approach-to-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also developed a light neck FCPNLite for mobile devices that will aid with the detection of small objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobiledensenet-a-new-approach-to-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiface: A Dataset for Neural Face Rendering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiface-a-dataset-for-neural-face-rendering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Along with the release of the dataset, we conduct ablation studies on the influence of different model architectures toward the model's interpolation capacity of novel viewpoint and expressions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiface-a-dataset-for-neural-face-rendering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Faceted Distillation of Base-Novel Commonality for Few-shot Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-faceted-distillation-of-base-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most of existing methods for few-shot object detection follow the fine-tuning paradigm, which potentially assumes that the class-agnostic generalizable knowledge can be learned and transferred implicitly from base classes with abundant samples to novel classes with limited samples via such a two-stage training strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-faceted-distillation-of-base-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physiology-based simulation of the retinal vasculature enables annotation-free segmentation of OCT angiographs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physiology-based-simulation-of-the-retinal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Encouraged by our method's competitive quantitative and superior qualitative performance, we believe that it constitutes a versatile tool to advance the quantitative analysis of OCTA images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physiology-based-simulation-of-the-retinal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom Structure Preservation in Face Aging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/custom-structure-preservation-in-face-aging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel architecture for face age editing that can produce structural modifications while maintaining relevant details present in the original image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/custom-structure-preservation-in-face-aging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimization of Forcemyography Sensor Placement for Arm Movement Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-of-forcemyography-sensor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To study the effectiveness of our optimization algorithm, a dataset for mechanical maintenance tasks using FMG armbands with 16 sensors is collected.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-of-forcemyography-sensor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verifying Fairness in Quantum Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifying-fairness-in-quantum-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we define a formal framework for the fairness verification and analysis of quantum machine learning decision models, where we adopt one of the most popular notions of fairness in the literature based on the intuition -- any two similar individuals must be treated similarly and are thus unbiased.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifying-fairness-in-quantum-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's in the laundromat? Mapping and characterising offshore owned domestic property in London</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-s-in-the-laundromat-mapping-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We perform an in-depth analysis of the offshore domestic property in London, comparing the price, distribution and entropy/concentration with Airbnb property, low-use/empty property and conventional domestic property.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-s-in-the-laundromat-mapping-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fact sheet: Automatic Self-Reported Personality Recognition Track</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fact-sheet-automatic-self-reported</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an informed baseline to help disentangle the various contextual factors of influence in this type of case studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fact-sheet-automatic-self-reported</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Dilated Spatio-Temporal Synchronous Graph Modeling for Traffic Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-dilated-spatio-temporal-synchronous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, we propose an automated dilated spatio-temporal synchronous graph network, named Auto-DSTSGN for traffic prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-dilated-spatio-temporal-synchronous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster VoxelPose: Real-time 3D Human Pose Estimation by Orthographic Projection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-voxelpose-real-time-3d-human-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the voxel-based methods have achieved promising results for multi-person 3D pose estimation from multi-cameras, they suffer from heavy computation burdens, especially for large scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-voxelpose-real-time-3d-human-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilabel Prototype Generation for Data Reduction in k-Nearest Neighbour classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilabel-prototype-generation-for-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prototype Generation (PG) methods are typically considered for improving the efficiency of the $k$-Nearest Neighbour ($k$NN) classifier when tackling high-size corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilabel-prototype-generation-for-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layer-refined Graph Convolutional Networks for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layer-refined-graph-convolutional-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, these models usually aggregate all layer embeddings for node updating and achieve their best recommendation performance within a few layers because of over-smoothing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layer-refined-graph-convolutional-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panoptic Scene Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panoptic-scene-graph-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing research addresses scene graph generation (SGG) -- a critical technology for scene understanding in images -- from a detection perspective, i. e., objects are detected using bounding boxes followed by prediction of their pairwise relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panoptic-scene-graph-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer with Implicit Edges for Particle-based Physics Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-with-implicit-edges-for-particle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consequently, in this paper we propose a novel Transformer-based method, dubbed as Transformer with Implicit Edges (TIE), to capture the rich semantics of particle interactions in an edge-free manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-with-implicit-edges-for-particle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Controller Tuning with Time-Varying Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-controller-tuning-with-time-varying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current TVBO methods do not explicitly account for these properties, resulting in poor tuning performance and many unstable controllers through over-exploration of the parameter space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-controller-tuning-with-time-varying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dense Material Segmentation Dataset for Indoor and Outdoor Scene Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dense-material-segmentation-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key algorithm for understanding the world is material segmentation, which assigns a label (metal, glass, etc.)]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dense-material-segmentation-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic ELF: Image Deraining Meets Association Learning and Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magic-elf-image-deraining-meets-association</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convolutional neural network (CNN) and Transformer have achieved great success in multimedia applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magic-elf-image-deraining-meets-association</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised pre-training of graph transformers on patient population graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-pre-training-of-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that our proposed pre-training methods help in modeling the data at a patient and population level and improve performance in different fine-tuning tasks on all datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-pre-training-of-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniFed: A Benchmark for Federated Learning Frameworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifed-a-benchmark-for-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) has become a practical and popular paradigm in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifed-a-benchmark-for-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi Resolution Analysis (MRA) for Approximate Self-Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-resolution-analysis-mra-for-approximate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have emerged as a preferred model for many tasks in natural langugage processing and vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-resolution-analysis-mra-for-approximate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeedFormer: Patch Seeds based Point Cloud Completion with Upsample Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seedformer-patch-seeds-based-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Point cloud completion has become increasingly popular among generation tasks of 3D point clouds, as it is a challenging yet indispensable problem to recover the complete shape of a 3D object from its partial observation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seedformer-patch-seeds-based-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Unsupervised Hierarchies of Audio Concepts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-unsupervised-hierarchies-of-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we adapt concept learning to the realm of music, with its particularities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-unsupervised-hierarchies-of-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Domain Adaptation for Semantic Segmentation in Ever-Changing Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-domain-adaptation-for-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised Domain Adaptation (UDA) aims at reducing the domain gap between training and testing data and is, in most cases, carried out in offline manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-domain-adaptation-for-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human Trajectory Prediction via Neural Social Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-trajectory-prediction-via-neural-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our new model (Neural Social Physics or NSP) is a deep neural network within which we use an explicit physics model with learnable parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-trajectory-prediction-via-neural-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEVIANT: Depth EquiVarIAnt NeTwork for Monocular 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deviant-depth-equivariant-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, DEVIANT is equivariant to the depth translations in the projective manifold whereas vanilla networks are not.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deviant-depth-equivariant-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Supervised Learning of Optical Flow by Flow Supervisor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-learning-of-optical-flow-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A training pipeline for optical flow CNNs consists of a pretraining stage on a synthetic dataset followed by a fine tuning stage on a target dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-learning-of-optical-flow-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable AI Algorithms for Vibration Data-based Fault Detection: Use Case-adadpted Methods and Critical Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-ai-algorithms-for-vibration-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This allows to assess the saliency given to features which depend on the rotation speed and those with constant frequency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-ai-algorithms-for-vibration-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LocVTP: Video-Text Pre-training for Temporal Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locvtp-video-text-pre-training-for-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further enhance the temporal reasoning ability of the learned feature, we propose a context projection head and a temporal aware contrastive loss to perceive the contextual relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locvtp-video-text-pre-training-for-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPIN: An Empirical Evaluation on Sharing Parameters of Isotropic Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spin-an-empirical-evaluation-on-sharing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we perform an empirical evaluation on methods for sharing parameters in isotropic networks (SPIN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spin-an-empirical-evaluation-on-sharing</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
