<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 21:07:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Modal-Invariant and Temporal-Memory for Video-based Visible-Infrared Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-modal-invariant-and-temporal-memory-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our constructed dataset, we prove that with the increase of frames in a tracklet, the performance does meet more enhancement, demonstrating the significance of video-to-video matching in RGB-IR person Re-ID.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-modal-invariant-and-temporal-memory-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P2P: Tuning Pre-trained Image Models for Point Cloud Analysis with Point-to-Pixel Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p2p-tuning-pre-trained-image-models-for-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nowadays, pre-training big models on large-scale datasets has become a crucial topic in deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p2p-tuning-pre-trained-image-models-for-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expanding Language-Image Pretrained Models for General Video Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expanding-language-image-pretrained-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate that our approach is effective and can be generalized to different video recognition scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expanding-language-image-pretrained-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Tuning for Generative Multimodal Pretrained Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-tuning-for-generative-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompt tuning has become a new paradigm for model tuning and it has demonstrated success in natural language pretraining and even vision pretraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-tuning-for-generative-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Per-Clip Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/per-clip-video-object-segmentation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this per-clip inference scheme, we update the memory with an interval and simultaneously process a set of consecutive frames (i. e. clip) between the memory updates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/per-clip-video-object-segmentation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Object Manipulation Skills from Video via Approximate Differentiable Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-object-manipulation-skills-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our approach on a 3D reconstruction task that consists of 54 video demonstrations sourced from 9 actions such as pull something from right to left or put something in front of something.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-object-manipulation-skills-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SC6D: Symmetry-agnostic and Correspondence-free 6D Object Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sc6d-symmetry-agnostic-and-correspondence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pose estimation is decomposed into three sub-tasks: a) object 3D rotation representation learning and matching; b) estimation of the 2D location of the object center; and c) scale-invariant distance estimation (the translation along the z-axis) via classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sc6d-symmetry-agnostic-and-correspondence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Generative Neural Temporal Point Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-generative-neural-temporal-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While lots of previous works have focused on `goodness-of-fit' of TPP models by maximizing the likelihood, their predictive performance is unsatisfactory, which means the timestamps generated by models are far apart from true observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-generative-neural-temporal-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Graph Neural Networks using Weighted Graph Laplacian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-graph-neural-networks-using-weighted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For demonstration, the experiments are conducted with Graph convolutional neural network(GCNN) architecture, however, the proposed framework is easily amenable to any existing GNN architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-graph-neural-networks-using-weighted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSformer: A Lightweight Transformer for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssformer-a-lightweight-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is well believed that Transformer performs better in semantic segmentation compared to convolutional neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssformer-a-lightweight-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Convolutional Persistence Transform</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-convolutional-persistence-transform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider a new topological feauturization of $d$-dimensional images, obtained by convolving images with various filters before computing persistence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-convolutional-persistence-transform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EgPDE-Net: Building Continuous Neural Networks for Time Series Prediction with Exogenous Variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egpde-net-building-continuous-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While exogenous variables have a major impact on performance improvement in time series analysis, inter-series correlation and time dependence among them are rarely considered in the present continuous methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egpde-net-building-continuous-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KD-SCFNet: Towards More Accurate and Efficient Salient Object Detection via Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kd-scfnet-towards-more-accurate-and-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing salient object detection (SOD) models are difficult to apply due to the complex and huge model structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kd-scfnet-towards-more-accurate-and-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XCon: Learning with Experts for Fine-grained Category Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xcon-learning-with-experts-for-fine-grained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the problem of generalized category discovery (GCD) in this paper, i. e. clustering the unlabeled images leveraging the information from a set of seen classes, where the unlabeled images could contain both seen classes and unseen classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xcon-learning-with-experts-for-fine-grained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dilated Context Integrated Network with Cross-Modal Consensus for Temporal Emotion Localization in Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilated-context-integrated-network-with-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a new task, named Temporal Emotion Localization in videos~(TEL), which aims to detect human emotions and localize their corresponding temporal boundaries in untrimmed videos with aligned subtitles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilated-context-integrated-network-with-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient-based Uncertainty for Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-based-uncertainty-for-monocular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To avoid relying on ground-truth information for the loss definition, we present an auxiliary loss function based on the correspondence of the depth prediction for an image and its horizontally flipped counterpart.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-based-uncertainty-for-monocular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Feature-space Multimodal Data Augmentation Technique for Text-video Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-feature-space-multimodal-data-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data augmentation techniques were introduced to increase the performance on unseen test examples by creating new training samples with the application of semantics-preserving techniques, such as color space or geometric transformations on images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-feature-space-multimodal-data-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaCat: Adaptive Categorical Discretization for Autoregressive Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adacat-adaptive-categorical-discretization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoregressive generative models can estimate complex continuous data distributions, like trajectory rollouts in an RL environment, image intensities, and audio.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adacat-adaptive-categorical-discretization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geometric analysis enables biological insight from complex non-identifiable models using simple surrogates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-analysis-enables-biological-insight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To draw insights from the complex, non-identifiable models that incorporate key biological mechanisms of interest, we study the geometry of a map in parameter space from the complex model to a simple, identifiable, surrogate model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-analysis-enables-biological-insight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flow Annealed Importance Sampling Bootstrap</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-annealed-importance-sampling-bootstrap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We target with AIS the minimum variance distribution for the estimation of the $\alpha$-divergence via importance sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-annealed-importance-sampling-bootstrap</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Fine-Grained Classification with Self-Supervised Target Relation Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-fine-grained-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such target coding schemes are less flexible to model inter-class correlation and are sensitive to sparse and imbalanced data distribution as well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-fine-grained-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Feature Vision Transformer via Self-Supervised Representation Learning for Improvement of COVID-19 Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-feature-vision-transformer-via-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the diagnostic performance of CXR imaging a growing number of studies have investigated whether supervised deep learning methods can provide additional support.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-feature-vision-transformer-via-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLO-FaceV2: A Scale and Occlusion Aware Face Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo-facev2-a-scale-and-occlusion-aware-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a real-time face detector based on the one-stage detector YOLOv5, named YOLO-FaceV2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo-facev2-a-scale-and-occlusion-aware-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RealPatch: A Statistical Matching Framework for Model Patching with Real Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realpatch-a-statistical-matching-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the effectiveness of RealPatch on three benchmark datasets, CelebA, Waterbirds and a subset of iWildCam, showing improvements in worst-case subgroup performance and in subgroup performance gap in binary classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realpatch-a-statistical-matching-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAHiTrA: Damage Assessment Using a Novel Hierarchical Transformer Architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dahitra-damage-assessment-using-a-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we introduce a new high-resolution satellite imagery dataset, Ida-BD (related to the 2021 Hurricane Ida in Louisiana in 2021, for domain adaptation to further evaluate the capability of the model to be applied to newly damaged areas with scarce data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dahitra-damage-assessment-using-a-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmented Learning for Class-of-Service Network Traffic Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmented-learning-for-class-of-service</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The commonality of statistical features among the network flow segments motivates us to propose novel segmented learning that includes essential vector representation and a simple-segment method of classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmented-learning-for-class-of-service</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MinVIS: A Minimal Video Instance Segmentation Framework without Video-based Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minvis-a-minimal-video-instance-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By only training a query-based image instance segmentation model, MinVIS outperforms the previous best result on the challenging Occluded VIS dataset by over 10% AP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minvis-a-minimal-video-instance-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequence Model Imitation Learning with Unobserved Contexts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequence-model-imitation-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider imitation learning problems where the expert has access to a per-episode context that is hidden from the learner, both in the demonstrations and at test-time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequence-model-imitation-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperLine3D: Self-supervised Line Segmentation and Description for LiDAR Point Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superline3d-self-supervised-line-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To repetitively extract them as features and perform association between discrete LiDAR frames for registration, we propose the first learning-based feature segmentation and description model for 3D lines in LiDAR point cloud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superline3d-self-supervised-line-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Discovery of Semantic Concepts in Satellite Imagery with Style-based Wavelet-driven Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-discovery-of-semantic-concepts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, considerable advancements have been made in the area of Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs), particularly with the advent of style-based architectures that address many key shortcomings - both in terms of modeling capabilities and network interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-discovery-of-semantic-concepts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable bilinear attention network with domain adaptation improves drug-target prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-bilinear-attention-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent deep learning-based methods show promising performance but two challenges remain: (i) how to explicitly model and learn local interactions between drugs and targets for better prediction and interpretation; (ii) how to generalize prediction performance on novel drug-target pairs from different distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-bilinear-attention-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PalQuant: Accelerating High-precision Networks on Low-precision Accelerators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/palquant-accelerating-high-precision-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the PArallel Low-precision Quantization (PalQuant) method that approximates high-precision computations via learning parallel low-precision representations from scratch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/palquant-accelerating-high-precision-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Re-Attention Transformer for Weakly Supervised Object Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-attention-transformer-for-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly supervised object localization is a challenging task which aims to localize objects with coarse annotations such as image categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-attention-transformer-for-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subject-Specific Lesion Generation and Pseudo-Healthy Synthesis for Multiple Sclerosis Brain Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subject-specific-lesion-generation-and-pseudo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a novel foreground-based generative method for modelling the local lesion characteristics that can both generate synthetic lesions on healthy images and synthesize subject-specific pseudo-healthy images from pathological images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subject-specific-lesion-generation-and-pseudo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pedestrian-Robot Interactions on Autonomous Crowd Navigation: Reactive Control Methods and Evaluation Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pedestrian-robot-interactions-on-autonomous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous navigation in highly populated areas remains a challenging task for robots because of the difficulty in guaranteeing safe interactions with pedestrians in unstructured situations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pedestrian-robot-interactions-on-autonomous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Negative Frames Matter in Egocentric Visual Query 2D Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/negative-frames-matter-in-egocentric-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The repeated gradient computation of the same object lead to an inefficient training; (2) The false positive rate is high on background frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/negative-frames-matter-in-egocentric-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Prior Feature and Attention Enhanced Image Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-prior-feature-and-attention-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, this paper incorporates the pre-training based Masked AutoEncoder (MAE) into the inpainting model, which enjoys richer informative priors to enhance the inpainting process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-prior-feature-and-attention-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Lingual Knowledge Transfer for Clinical Phenotyping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-knowledge-transfer-for-clinical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clinical phenotyping enables the automatic extraction of clinical conditions from patient records, which can be beneficial to doctors and clinics worldwide.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-knowledge-transfer-for-clinical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silo NLP's Participation at WAT2022</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/silo-nlp-s-participation-at-wat2022</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper provides the system description of "Silo NLP's" submission to the Workshop on Asian Translation (WAT2022).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/silo-nlp-s-participation-at-wat2022</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T4DT: Tensorizing Time for Learning Temporal 3D Visual Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t4dt-tensorizing-time-for-learning-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that low-rank tensor compression is extremely compact to store and query time-varying signed distance functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t4dt-tensorizing-time-for-learning-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Reinforcement Learning for Multi-Agent Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-reinforcement-learning-for-multi-agent-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of autonomous agents which can interact with other agents to accomplish a given task is a core area of research in artificial intelligence and machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-reinforcement-learning-for-multi-agent-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic Deep Networks with Linear Competing Units for Model-Agnostic Meta-Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-deep-networks-with-linear-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work addresses meta-learning (ML) by considering deep networks with stochastic local winner-takes-all (LWTA) activations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-deep-networks-with-linear-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GaitGL: Learning Discriminative Global-Local Feature Representations for Gait Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaitgl-learning-discriminative-global-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GFR extractor aims to extract contextual information, e. g., the relationship among various body parts, and the mask-based LFR extractor is presented to exploit the detailed posture changes of local regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaitgl-learning-discriminative-global-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Variable Selection in a Million Dimensions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-variable-selection-in-a-million</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian variable selection is a powerful tool for data analysis, as it offers a principled method for variable selection that accounts for prior information and uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-variable-selection-in-a-million</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIPCaD-Bench: Continuous Industrial Process datasets for benchmarking Causal Discovery methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cipcad-bench-continuous-industrial-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces two novel public datasets for CD in continuous manufacturing processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cipcad-bench-continuous-industrial-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Late Fusion Multi-view Clustering via Global and Local Alignment Maximization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/late-fusion-multi-view-clustering-via-global</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It optimally fuses multiple source information in partition level from each individual view, and maximally aligns the consensus partition with these weighted base ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/late-fusion-multi-view-clustering-via-global</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Cluster Validity Measures (In)valid?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-cluster-validity-measures-in-valid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Internal cluster validity measures (such as the Calinski-Harabasz, Dunn, or Davies-Bouldin indices) are frequently used for selecting the appropriate number of partitions a dataset should be split into.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-cluster-validity-measures-in-valid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEMO: Coverage-guided Model Generation For Deep Learning Library Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memo-coverage-guided-model-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In view of the limitations of existing DL library testing techniques, we propose MEMO to efficiently generate diverse DL models by exploring layer types, layer pairs, and layer parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memo-coverage-guided-model-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label Sleuth: From Unlabeled Text to a Classifier in a Few Hours</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-sleuth-from-unlabeled-text-to-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text classification can be useful in many real-world scenarios, saving a lot of time for end users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-sleuth-from-unlabeled-text-to-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Individual Decision-Making Style: Exploring Behavioral Stylometry in Chess</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-individual-decision-making-style-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a transformer-based approach to behavioral stylometry in the context of chess, where one attempts to identify the player who played a set of games.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-individual-decision-making-style-1</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
