<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 21:09:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ASANet: Asymmetric Semantic Aligning Network for RGB and SAR image land cover classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asanet-asymmetric-semantic-aligning-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing studies on cross-modal fusion assume that consistent feature information is necessary between the two modalities, and as a result, they construct networks without adequately addressing the unique characteristics of each modality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asanet-asymmetric-semantic-aligning-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trajectory-based Road Autolabeling with Lidar-Camera Fusion in Winter Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajectory-based-road-autolabeling-with-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust road segmentation in all road conditions is required for safe autonomous driving and advanced driver assistance systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajectory-based-road-autolabeling-with-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoCo: Low-Contrast-Enhanced Contrastive Learning for Semi-Supervised Endoscopic Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loco-low-contrast-enhanced-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The segmentation of endoscopic images plays a vital role in computer-aided diagnosis and treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loco-low-contrast-enhanced-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Negative Loss: A Robust Framework for Learning with Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-negative-loss-a-robust-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By replacing MAE in APL with our proposed NNLFs, we enhance APL and present a new framework called Active Negative Loss (ANL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-negative-loss-a-robust-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HERO: Hint-Based Efficient and Reliable Query Optimizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hero-hint-based-efficient-and-reliable-query</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model addresses the three key challenges in learned hint-based query optimization: reliable hint recommendation (ensuring non-degradation of query latency), efficient hint exploration, and fast inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hero-hint-based-efficient-and-reliable-query</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Diffusion Priors under Sparse Views?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-use-diffusion-priors-under-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the diffusion model, as an external prior that can directly provide visual supervision, has always underperformed in sparse-view 3D reconstruction using Score Distillation Sampling (SDS) due to the low information entropy of sparse views compared to text, leading to optimization challenges caused by mode deviation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-use-diffusion-priors-under-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RG-SAN: Rule-Guided Spatial Awareness Network for End-to-End 3D Referring Expression Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rg-san-rule-guided-spatial-awareness-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The RG-SAN consists of the Text-driven Localization Module (TLM) and the Rule-guided Weak Supervision (RWS) strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rg-san-rule-guided-spatial-awareness-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Sensing Temporal Vision-Language Models: A Comprehensive Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remote-sensing-temporal-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This survey fills a critical gap in the literature by providing an integrated overview of RSTVLM, offering a foundation for further advancements in remote sensing temporal image understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remote-sensing-temporal-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noisy Ostracods: A Fine-Grained, Imbalanced Real-World Dataset for Benchmarking Robust Machine Learning and Label Correction Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisy-ostracods-a-fine-grained-imbalanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Noisy Ostracods, a noisy dataset for genus and species classification of crustacean ostracods with specialists' annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisy-ostracods-a-fine-grained-imbalanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AccDiffusion v2: Towards More Accurate Higher-Resolution Diffusion Extrapolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accdiffusion-v2-towards-more-accurate-higher</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, our analysis indicates that global semantic information is conducive to suppressing both repetitive generation and local distortion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accdiffusion-v2-towards-more-accurate-higher</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Weisfeiler-Lehman Kernels to Subgraphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-weisfeiler-lehman-kernels-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subgraph representation learning has been effective in solving various real-world problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-weisfeiler-lehman-kernels-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wasserstein Markets for Differentially-Private Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasserstein-markets-for-differentially</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data is an increasingly vital component of decision making processes across industries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasserstein-markets-for-differentially</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class-wise Autoencoders Measure Classification Difficulty And Detect Label Mistakes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-wise-autoencoders-measure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new framework for analyzing classification datasets based on the ratios of reconstruction errors between autoencoders trained on individual classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-wise-autoencoders-measure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gracefully Filtering Backdoor Samples for Generative Large Language Models without Retraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gracefully-filtering-backdoor-samples-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Backdoor attacks remain significant security threats to generative large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gracefully-filtering-backdoor-samples-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoICL: Confidence-based Iterative In-context Learning for Out-of-Distribution Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videoicl-confidence-based-iterative-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose VideoICL, a novel video in-context learning framework for OOD tasks that introduces a similarity-based relevant example selection strategy and a confidence-based iterative inference approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videoicl-confidence-based-iterative-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast LiDAR Data Generation with Rectified Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-lidar-data-generation-with-rectified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building LiDAR generative models holds promise as powerful data priors for restoration, scene manipulation, and scalable simulation in autonomous mobile robots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-lidar-data-generation-with-rectified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copy-Move Forgery Detection and Question Answering for Remote Sensing Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copy-move-forgery-detection-and-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the task of Remote Sensing Copy-Move Question Answering (RSCMQA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copy-move-forgery-detection-and-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BN-AuthProf: Benchmarking Machine Learning for Bangla Author Profiling on Social Media Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bn-authprof-benchmarking-machine-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper focuses on author profiling in the Bangla language, aiming to extract valuable insights about anonymous authors based on their writing style on social media.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bn-authprof-benchmarking-machine-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Image Tokenizers with Grouped Spherical Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-image-tokenizers-with-grouped</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision tokenizers have gained a lot of attraction due to their scalability and compactness; previous works depend on old-school GAN-based hyperparameters, biased comparisons, and a lack of comprehensive analysis of the scaling behaviours.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-image-tokenizers-with-grouped</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Transformers for Weakly-Supervised Microorganism Enumeration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-transformers-for-weakly-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This comparative study contributes to the field of microbial image analysis by presenting innovative approaches to the recurring challenge of microorganism enumeration and by highlighting the capabilities of ViTs in the task of regression counting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-transformers-for-weakly-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Rich Emotions in 3D Avatars: A Text-to-3D Avatar Generation Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-rich-emotions-in-3d-avatars-a-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[T3DEM is the most crucial step in determining the quality of Emo3D generation and encompasses three key challenges: Expression Diversity, Emotion-Content Consistency, and Expression Fluidity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-rich-emotions-in-3d-avatars-a-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saliency Maps Give a False Sense of Explanability to Image Classifiers: An Empirical Evaluation across Methods and Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saliency-maps-give-a-false-sense-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The interpretability of deep neural networks (DNNs) has emerged as a crucial area of research, particularly in image classification tasks where decisions often lack transparency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saliency-maps-give-a-false-sense-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANER: Boundary-Aware LLMs for Few-Shot Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/baner-boundary-aware-llms-for-few-shot-named</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an approach called Boundary-Aware LLMs for Few-Shot Named Entity Recognition to address these issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/baner-boundary-aware-llms-for-few-shot-named</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Learning via Classifier Impact and Greedy Selection for Interactive Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-via-classifier-impact-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we assess our performance for the interactive content-based image retrieval task on several benchmarks and demonstrate its superiority over existing approaches and common baselines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-via-classifier-impact-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Critical Scenarios for Testing Automated Driving Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-critical-scenarios-for-testing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose AVASTRA, a Reinforcement Learning (RL)-based approach to generate realistic critical scenarios for testing ADSs in simulation environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-critical-scenarios-for-testing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HumanRig: Learning Automatic Rigging for Humanoid Character in a Large Scale Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humanrig-learning-automatic-rigging-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid evolution of 3D generation algorithms, the cost of producing 3D humanoid character models has plummeted, yet the field is impeded by the lack of a comprehensive dataset for automatic rigging, which is a pivotal step in character animation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humanrig-learning-automatic-rigging-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimuScope: Realistic Endoscopic Synthetic Dataset Generation through Surgical Simulation and Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simuscope-realistic-endoscopic-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This simulator generates a wide set of annotations that surpass those available in public synthetic datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simuscope-realistic-endoscopic-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShadowHack: Hacking Shadows via Luminance-Color Divide and Conquer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadowhack-hacking-shadows-via-luminance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Shadows introduce challenges such as reduced brightness, texture deterioration, and color distortion in images, complicating a holistic solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadowhack-hacking-shadows-via-luminance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROVER: A Multi-Season Dataset for Visual SLAM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rover-a-multi-season-dataset-for-visual-slam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we present ROVER, a comprehensive benchmark dataset tailored for evaluating visual SLAM algorithms under diverse environmental conditions and spatial configurations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rover-a-multi-season-dataset-for-visual-slam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agri-LLaVA: Knowledge-Infused Large Multimodal Assistant on Agricultural Pests and Diseases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agri-llava-knowledge-infused-large-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By open-sourcing our dataset and model, we aim to promote research and development in LMMs within the agricultural domain and make significant contributions to tackle the challenges of agricultural pests and diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agri-llava-knowledge-infused-large-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLM-4-Voice: Towards Intelligent and Human-Like End-to-End Spoken Chatbot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glm-4-voice-towards-intelligent-and-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We continue pre-training from the pre-trained text language model GLM-4-9B with a combination of unsupervised speech data, interleaved speech-text data, and supervised speech-text data, scaling up to 1 trillion tokens, achieving state-of-the-art performance in both speech language modeling and spoken question answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glm-4-voice-towards-intelligent-and-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCR Hinders RAG: Evaluating the Cascading Impact of OCR on Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ocr-hinders-rag-evaluating-the-cascading</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce OHRBench, the first benchmark for understanding the cascading impact of OCR on RAG systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ocr-hinders-rag-evaluating-the-cascading</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-based Visual Anagram as Multi-task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-visual-anagram-as-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual anagrams are images that change appearance upon transformation, like flipping or rotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-visual-anagram-as-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GSOT3D: Towards Generic 3D Single Object Tracking in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gsot3d-towards-generic-3d-single-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel benchmark, GSOT3D, that aims at facilitating development of generic 3D single object tracking (SOT) in the wild.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gsot3d-towards-generic-3d-single-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Scale Representation Learning for Protein Fitness Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-representation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing novel functional proteins crucially depends on accurately modeling their fitness landscape.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-representation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable fault and severity classification for rolling element bearings using Kolmogorov-Arnold networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-fault-and-severity-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By training shallow network architectures and minimizing the number of selected features, the framework produces lightweight models that deliver explainable results through feature attribution and symbolic representations of their activation functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-fault-and-severity-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShowHowTo: Generating Scene-Conditioned Step-by-Step Visual Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/showhowto-generating-scene-conditioned-step</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of this work is to generate step-by-step visual instructions in the form of a sequence of images, given an input image that provides the scene context and the sequence of textual instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/showhowto-generating-scene-conditioned-step</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstantSwap: Fast Customized Concept Swapping across Sharp Shape Differences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instantswap-fast-customized-concept-swapping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[They struggle to maintain consistency in both the foreground and background during concept swapping, especially when the shape difference is large between objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instantswap-fast-customized-concept-swapping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RGBDS-SLAM: A RGB-D Semantic Dense SLAM Based on 3D Multi Level Pyramid Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgbds-slam-a-rgb-d-semantic-dense-slam-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose RGBDS-SLAM, a RGB-D semantic dense SLAM system based on 3D multi-level pyramid gaussian splatting, which enables high-quality dense reconstruction of scene RGB, depth, and semantics. In this system, we introduce a 3D multi-level pyramid gaussian splatting method that restores scene details by extracting multi-level image pyramids for gaussian splatting training, ensuring consistency in RGB, depth, and semantic reconstructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgbds-slam-a-rgb-d-semantic-dense-slam-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SfM-Free 3D Gaussian Splatting via Hierarchical Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfm-free-3d-gaussian-splatting-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel SfM-Free 3DGS (SFGS) method for video input, eliminating the need for known camera poses and SfM preprocessing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfm-free-3d-gaussian-splatting-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concept Based Continuous Prompts for Interpretable Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-based-continuous-prompts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continuous prompts have become widely adopted for augmenting performance across a wide range of natural language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-based-continuous-prompts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphOTTER: Evolving LLM-based Graph Reasoning for Complex Table Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphotter-evolving-llm-based-graph-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite considerable progress having been made in the LLM era, the reasoning processes of existing methods are often implicit, feeding the entire table into prompts, making it difficult to effectively filter out irrelevant information in the table.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphotter-evolving-llm-based-graph-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuoCast: Duo-Probabilistic Meteorology-Aware Model for Extended Precipitation Nowcasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/duocast-duo-probabilistic-meteorology-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, extended short-term precipitation nowcasting struggles with decreasing precision because of insufficient consideration of meteorological knowledge, such as weather fronts which significantly influence precipitation intensity, duration, and spatial distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/duocast-duo-probabilistic-meteorology-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MBA-RAG: a Bandit Approach for Adaptive Retrieval-Augmented Generation through Question Complexity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mba-rag-a-bandit-approach-for-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) has proven to be highly effective in boosting the generative performance of language model in knowledge-intensive tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mba-rag-a-bandit-approach-for-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morphological-Symmetry-Equivariant Heterogeneous Graph Neural Network for Robotic Dynamics Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphological-symmetry-equivariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a morphological-symmetry-equivariant heterogeneous graph neural network, namely MS-HGNN, for robotic dynamics learning, that integrates robotic kinematic structures and morphological symmetries into a single graph network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphological-symmetry-equivariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Much Can Time-related Features Enhance Time Series Forecasting?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-much-can-time-related-features-enhance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in long-term time series forecasting (LTSF) have primarily focused on capturing cross-time and cross-variate (channel) dependencies within historical data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-much-can-time-related-features-enhance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedPAW: Federated Learning with Personalized Aggregation Weights for Urban Vehicle Speed Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedpaw-federated-learning-with-personalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to variations in drivers' driving styles and vehicle types, speed predictions for different target vehicles may significantly differ.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedpaw-federated-learning-with-personalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextSSR: Diffusion-based Data Synthesis for Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textssr-diffusion-based-data-synthesis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments show that models trained on added TextSSR-F data exhibit better accuracy compared to models trained on 4 million existing synthetic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textssr-diffusion-based-data-synthesis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-Prompt: Towards Universal In-Context Image Generation in Auto-Regressive Vision Language Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-prompt-towards-universal-in-context-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments validate the model's performance across diverse seen image generation tasks and its capacity to generalize to previously unseen tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-prompt-towards-universal-in-context-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinyFusion: Diffusion Transformers Learned Shallow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyfusion-diffusion-transformers-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present TinyFusion, a depth pruning method designed to remove redundant layers from diffusion transformers via end-to-end learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyfusion-diffusion-transformers-learned</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
