<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 09:12:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Avicenna: a challenge dataset for natural language generation toward commonsense syllogistic reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avicenna-a-challenge-dataset-for-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Avicenna corpus was developed as a benchmark for syllogistic NLG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avicenna-a-challenge-dataset-for-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring Your Own View: Graph Neural Networks for Link Prediction with Personalized Subgraph Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bring-your-own-view-graph-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge the gap, we introduce a Personalized Subgraph Selector (PS2) as a plug-and-play framework to automatically, personally, and inductively identify optimal subgraphs for different edges when performing GNNLP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bring-your-own-view-graph-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rule Learning by Modularity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rule-learning-by-modularity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a modular methodology that combines state-of-the-art methods in (stochastic) machine learning with traditional methods in rule learning to provide efficient and scalable algorithms for the classification of vast data sets, while remaining explainable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rule-learning-by-modularity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAC-Net: A Hybrid Attention-Based Convolutional Neural Network for Highly Accurate Protein-Ligand Binding Affinity Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hac-net-a-hybrid-attention-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applying deep learning concepts from image detection and graph theory has greatly advanced protein-ligand binding affinity prediction, a challenge with enormous ramifications for both drug discovery and protein engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hac-net-a-hybrid-attention-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroBERT: Effective Training of Low-resource Monolingual BERTs through Parameter Reduction and Multitask Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/microbert-effective-training-of-low-resource</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer language models (TLMs) are critical for most NLP tasks, but they are difficult to create for low-resource languages because of how much pretraining data they require.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/microbert-effective-training-of-low-resource</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmark for Uncertainty &amp; Robustness in Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-for-uncertainty-robustness-in-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-Supervised Learning (SSL) is crucial for real-world applications, especially in data-hungry domains such as healthcare and self-driving cars.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-for-uncertainty-robustness-in-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using MM principles to deal with incomplete data in K-means clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-mm-principles-to-deal-with-incomplete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Among many clustering algorithms, the K-means clustering algorithm is widely used because of its simple algorithm and fast convergence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-mm-principles-to-deal-with-incomplete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NARS vs. Reinforcement learning: ONA vs. Q-Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nars-vs-reinforcement-learning-ona-vs-q</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the realistic scenarios is taking a sequence of optimal actions to do a task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nars-vs-reinforcement-learning-ona-vs-q</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precise Location Matching Improves Dense Contrastive Learning in Digital Pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precise-location-matching-improves-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method outperforms previous dense matching methods by up to 7. 2 % in average precision for detection and 5. 6 % in average precision for instance segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precise-location-matching-improves-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finetuning for Sarcasm Detection with a Pruned Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finetuning-for-sarcasm-detection-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sarcasm is usually conveyed through tone of voice, facial expressions, or other forms of nonverbal communication, but it can also be indicated by the use of certain words or phrases that are typically associated with irony or humor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finetuning-for-sarcasm-detection-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Unfolding-based Weighted Averaging for Federated Learning under Heterogeneous Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-unfolding-based-weighted-averaging-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is a collaborative model training method by iterating model updates at multiple clients and aggregation of the updates at a central server.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-unfolding-based-weighted-averaging-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Survival of Tongue Cancer Patients by Machine Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-survival-of-tongue-cancer-patients</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prognostic factors identified by our method are consistent with previous clinical studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-survival-of-tongue-cancer-patients</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProgNet: A Transferable Deep Network for Aircraft Engine Damage Propagation Prognosis under Real Flight Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prognet-a-transferable-deep-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, ProgNet is transferred to the target domain of obtained degradation features for fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prognet-a-transferable-deep-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The choice of scaling technique matters for classification performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-choice-of-scaling-technique-matters-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we execute a broad experiment comparing the impact of 5 scaling techniques on the performances of 20 classification algorithms among monolithic and ensemble models, applying them to 82 publicly available datasets with varying imbalance ratios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-choice-of-scaling-technique-matters-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Classification with Small Datasets: Overview and Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-classification-with-small-datasets-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, as research in this scope is still in its infancy, two key ingredients are missing for ensuring reliable and truthful progress: a systematic and extensive overview of the state of the art, and a common benchmark to allow for objective comparisons between published methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-classification-with-small-datasets-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Meta-Representation Learning via Global Label Inference and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-meta-representation-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirically, MeLa outperforms existing methods across a diverse range of benchmarks, in particular under a more challenging setting where the number of training tasks is limited and labels are task-specific.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-meta-representation-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Adaptive Computation for Iterative Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-adaptive-computation-for-iterative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Recurrent Interface Network (RIN), a neural net architecture that allocates computation adaptively to the input according to the distribution of information, allowing it to scale to iterative generation of high-dimensional data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-adaptive-computation-for-iterative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electromagnetic Based Communication Model for Dynamic Metasurface Antennas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/electromagnetic-based-communication-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic metasurface antennas (DMAs) arise as a promising technology in the field of massive multiple-input multiple-output (mMIMO) systems, offering the possibility of integrating a large number of antennas in a limited -- and potentially large -- aperture while keeping the required number of radio-frequency (RF) chains under control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/electromagnetic-based-communication-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Causal Credit Assignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-causal-credit-assignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this setting, we propose a variant of Hindsight Credit Assignment that effectively exploits a given causal structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-causal-credit-assignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confidence-Aware Paced-Curriculum Learning by Label Smoothing for Surgical Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-aware-paced-curriculum-learning-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we design a paced curriculum by label smoothing (P-CBLS) using paced learning with uniform label smoothing (ULS) for classification tasks and fuse uniform and spatially varying label smoothing (SVLS) for semantic segmentation tasks in a curriculum manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-aware-paced-curriculum-learning-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certified Policy Smoothing for Cooperative Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certified-policy-smoothing-for-cooperative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results show that our method produces meaningful guaranteed robustness for all models and environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certified-policy-smoothing-for-cooperative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind Your Heart: Stealthy Backdoor Attack on Dynamic Deep Neural Network in Edge Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-your-heart-stealthy-backdoor-attack-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transforming off-the-shelf deep neural network (DNN) models into dynamic multi-exit architectures can achieve inference and transmission efficiency by fragmenting and distributing a large DNN model in edge computing scenarios (e. g., edge devices and cloud servers).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-your-heart-stealthy-backdoor-attack-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graphs for Conversational Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-reasoning-over-incomplete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a variational Bayesian method to approximate posterior distributions over dialogue-specific subgraphs, which not only leverages the dialogue corpus for restructuring missing entity relations but also dynamically selects knowledge based on the dialogue context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-reasoning-over-incomplete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransPath: Learning Heuristics For Grid-Based Pathfinding via Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transpath-learning-heuristics-for-grid-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we suggest learning the instance-dependent heuristic proxies that are supposed to notably increase the efficiency of the search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transpath-learning-heuristics-for-grid-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically Annotating Indoor Images with CAD Models via RGB-D Scans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatically-annotating-indoor-images-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an automatic method for annotating images of indoor scenes with the CAD models of the objects by relying on RGB-D scans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatically-annotating-indoor-images-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamdani Motif Generation using Conditional GAN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jamdani-motif-generation-using-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental results of the pix2pix model on this dataset show satisfactory outputs of computer-generated images of Jamdani motifs and we believe that our work will open a new avenue for further research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jamdani-motif-generation-using-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predictive Coding Based Multiscale Network with Encoder-Decoder LSTM for Video Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictive-coding-based-multiscale-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a predictive coding model, it is updated by a combination of bottom-up and top-down information flows, which is different from traditional bottom-up training style.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictive-coding-based-multiscale-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renormalization in the neural network-quantum field theory correspondence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/renormalization-in-the-neural-network-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A statistical ensemble of neural networks can be described in terms of a quantum field theory (NN-QFT correspondence).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/renormalization-in-the-neural-network-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-queue Momentum Contrast for Microvideo-Product Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-queue-momentum-contrast-for-microvideo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The booming development and huge market of micro-videos bring new e-commerce channels for merchants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-queue-momentum-contrast-for-microvideo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-shot human motion prediction for heterogeneous sensors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-human-motion-prediction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human motion prediction is a complex task as it involves forecasting variables over time on a graph of connected sensors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-human-motion-prediction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Colorization of Structured Mobile Web Pages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-colorization-of-structured-mobile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The web page colorization problem is then formalized as a task of estimating plausible color styles for a given web page content with a given hierarchical structure of the elements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-colorization-of-structured-mobile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHLE: Devices Tracking and Depth Filtering for Stereo-based Height Limit Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shle-devices-tracking-and-depth-filtering-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In stage 1, a novel devices detection and tracking scheme is introduced, which accurately locate the height limit devices in the left or right image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shle-devices-tracking-and-depth-filtering-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-High-Definition Low-Light Image Enhancement: A Benchmark and Transformer-Based Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-high-definition-low-light-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we consider the task of low-light image enhancement (LLIE) and introduce a large-scale database consisting of images at 4K and 8K resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-high-definition-low-light-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual News Location Detection using an Entity-Based Siamese Network with Semi-Supervised Contrastive Learning and Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-news-location-detection-using-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the effectiveness of our approach, and due to the lack of datasets in this area, we also contribute to the research community with a gold-standard multilingual news-location dataset, NewsLOC.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-news-location-detection-using-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MN-DS: A Multilabeled News Dataset for News Articles Hierarchical Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mn-ds-a-multilabeled-news-dataset-for-news</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article presents a dataset of 10, 917 news articles with hierarchical news categories collected between January 1st 2019, and December 31st 2019.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mn-ds-a-multilabeled-news-dataset-for-news</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SiteFerret: beyond simple pocket identification in proteins</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siteferret-beyond-simple-pocket</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel method for the automatic detection of pockets on protein molecular surfaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siteferret-beyond-simple-pocket</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When and Why Test Generators for Deep Learning Produce Invalid Inputs: an Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-and-why-test-generators-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate to what extent TIGs can generate valid inputs, according to both automated and human validators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-and-why-test-generators-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperparameters in Contextual RL are Highly Situational</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameters-in-contextual-rl-are-highly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although Reinforcement Learning (RL) has shown impressive results in games and simulation, real-world application of RL suffers from its instability under changing environment conditions and hyperparameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameters-in-contextual-rl-are-highly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Emotion Modelling in Written Stories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-emotion-modelling-in-written</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Telling stories is an integral part of human communication which can evoke emotions and influence the affective states of the audience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-emotion-modelling-in-written</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Supervised Learning of Monocular Depth Estimation via Consistency Regularization with K-way Disjoint Masking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-learning-of-monocular-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-Supervised Learning (SSL) has recently accomplished successful achievements in various fields such as image classification, object detection, and semantic segmentation, which typically require a lot of labour to construct ground-truth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-learning-of-monocular-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Semantic Modeling for Structural Data Source with the Prior Knowledge from Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-semantic-modeling-for-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, an automatic approach for learning the semantics of a data source is desirable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-semantic-modeling-for-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Poison: Machine Unlearning Enables Camouflaged Poisoning Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-poison-machine-unlearning-enables</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce camouflaged data poisoning attacks, a new attack vector that arises in the context of machine unlearning and other settings when model retraining may be induced.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-poison-machine-unlearning-enables</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Content Relationships for Distilling Efficient GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-content-relationships-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a content relationship distillation (CRD) to tackle the over-parameterized generative adversarial networks (GANs) for the serviceability in cutting-edge devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-content-relationships-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighboring state-based RL Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neighboring-state-based-rl-exploration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning is a powerful tool to model decision-making processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neighboring-state-based-rl-exploration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Residual Networks for Adversarial Robustness: An Architectural Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-residual-networks-for-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, little attention was devoted to analyzing the role of architectural elements (such as topology, depth, and width) on adversarial robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-residual-networks-for-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entropy- and Distance-Based Predictors From GPT-2 Attention Patterns Predict Reading Times Over and Above GPT-2 Surprisal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropy-and-distance-based-predictors-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based large language models are trained to make predictions about the next word by aggregating representations of previous tokens through their self-attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropy-and-distance-based-predictors-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Highlighter: Localizing Regions on 3D Shapes via Text Descriptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-highlighter-localizing-regions-on-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key feature of our system is the ability to interpret "out-of-domain" localizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-highlighter-localizing-regions-on-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Linguistic Syntactic Difference in Multilingual BERT: How Good is It and How Does It Affect Transfer?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-linguistic-syntactic-difference-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that the distance between the distributions of different languages is highly consistent with the syntactic difference in terms of linguistic formalisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-linguistic-syntactic-difference-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Narrative Relationship Embeddings by Training with Additional Inverse-Relationship Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-narrative-relationship-embeddings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of embedding character-entity relationships from the reduced semantic space of narratives, proposing and evaluating the assumption that these relationships hold under a reflection operation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-narrative-relationship-embeddings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuAT: Dual-Aggregation Transformer Network for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/duat-dual-aggregation-transformer-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The GLSA has the ability to aggregate and represent both global and local spatial features, which are beneficial for locating large and small objects, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/duat-dual-aggregation-transformer-network-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
