<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 09:23:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Map-free Visual Relocalization: Metric Pose Relative to a Single Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-free-visual-relocalization-metric-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Can we relocalize in a scene represented by a single reference image?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-free-visual-relocalization-metric-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixture of Attention Heads: Selecting Attention Heads Per Token</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-attention-heads-selecting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes the Mixture of Attention Heads (MoA), a new architecture that combines multi-head attention with the MoE mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-attention-heads-selecting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Failure of Batch Normalization for Transformers in NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-failure-of-batch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Batch Normalization (BN) is a core and prevalent technique in accelerating the training of deep neural networks and improving the generalization on Computer Vision (CV) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-failure-of-batch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP: Modality-Agnostic Uncertainty-Aware Vision-Language Pre-training Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-modality-agnostic-uncertainty-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal semantic understanding often has to deal with uncertainty, which means the obtained message tends to refer to multiple targets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-modality-agnostic-uncertainty-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion Aware Self-Supervision for Generic Event Boundary Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-aware-self-supervision-for-generic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address this issue by revisiting a simple and effective self-supervised method and augment it with a differentiable motion feature learning module to tackle the spatial and temporal diversities in the GEBD task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-aware-self-supervision-for-generic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-Fields: Weakly Supervised Semantic Fields for Robotic Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-fields-weakly-supervised-semantic-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose CLIP-Fields, an implicit scene model that can be trained with no direct human supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-fields-weakly-supervised-semantic-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IsoVec: Controlling the Relative Isomorphism of Word Embedding Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isovec-controlling-the-relative-isomorphism</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to extract high-quality translation dictionaries from monolingual word embedding spaces depends critically on the geometric similarity of the spaces -- their degree of "isomorphism."]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isovec-controlling-the-relative-isomorphism</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregating Layers for Deepfake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aggregating-layers-for-deepfake-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Crucially, most work in this domain assume that the Deepfakes in the test set come from the same Deepfake algorithms that were used for training the network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aggregating-layers-for-deepfake-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markup-to-Image Diffusion Models with Scheduled Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/markup-to-image-diffusion-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These experiments each verify the effectiveness of the diffusion process and the use of scheduled sampling to fix generation issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/markup-to-image-diffusion-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Training of Language Models for Few-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-training-of-language-models-for-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work on applying large language models (LMs) achieves impressive performance in many NLP applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-training-of-language-models-for-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Well Do Multi-hop Reading Comprehension Models Understand Date Information?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-well-do-multi-hop-reading-comprehension-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Other results reveal that our probing questions can help to improve the performance of the models (e. g., by +10. 3 F1) on the main QA task and our dataset can be used for data augmentation to improve the robustness of the models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-well-do-multi-hop-reading-comprehension-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ME-D2N: Multi-Expert Domain Decompositional Network for Cross-Domain Few-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/me-d2n-multi-expert-domain-decompositional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, to solve the data imbalance problem between the source data with sufficient examples and the auxiliary target data with limited examples, we build our model under the umbrella of multi-expert learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/me-d2n-multi-expert-domain-decompositional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Kernel-Based View of Language Model Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-kernel-based-view-of-language-model-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It has become standard to solve NLP tasks by fine-tuning pre-trained language models (LMs), especially in low-data settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-kernel-based-view-of-language-model-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACRNet: Attention Cube Regression Network for Multi-view Real-time 3D Human Pose Estimation in Telemedicine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acrnet-attention-cube-regression-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel multi-view Attention Cube Regression Network (ACRNet), which regresses the 3D position of joints in real time by aggregating informative attention points on each cube surface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acrnet-attention-cube-regression-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19-related Nepali Tweets Classification in a Low Resource Setting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covid-19-related-nepali-tweets-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Billions of people across the globe have been using social media platforms in their local languages to voice their opinions about the various topics related to the COVID-19 pandemic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covid-19-related-nepali-tweets-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Model Combination: An Instance-wise Approach to Unsupervised Ensemble Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-model-combination-an-instance-wise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consider making a prediction over new test data without any opportunity to learn from a training set of labelled data - instead given access to a set of expert models and their predictions alongside some limited information about the dataset used to train them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-model-combination-an-instance-wise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAgNet: Mesh Agnostic Neural PDE Solver</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magnet-mesh-agnostic-neural-pde-solver</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The computational complexity of classical numerical methods for solving Partial Differential Equations (PDE) scales significantly as the resolution increases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magnet-mesh-agnostic-neural-pde-solver</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Causal Effects from Sets of Interventions in the Presence of Unobserved Confounders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-causal-effects-from-sets-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address this challenge by aiming to learn the effect of a single-intervention from both observational data and sets of interventions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-causal-effects-from-sets-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EOCSA: Predicting Prognosis of Epithelial Ovarian Cancer with Whole Slide Histopathological Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eocsa-predicting-prognosis-of-epithelial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, we developed a survival prediction model, named DeepConvAttentionSurv (DCAS), which was able to extract patch-level features, removed less discriminative clusters and predicted the EOC survival precisely.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eocsa-predicting-prognosis-of-epithelial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Misspecified Phase Retrieval with Generative Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/misspecified-phase-retrieval-with-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study phase retrieval under model misspecification and generative priors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/misspecified-phase-retrieval-with-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-NeRF: Explicit Neural Radiance Field for Multi-Scene 360$^{\circ} $ Insufficient RGB-D Views</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-nerf-explicit-neural-radiance-field-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on a rarely discussed but important setting: can we train one model that can represent multiple scenes, with 360$^\circ $ insufficient views and RGB-D images?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-nerf-explicit-neural-radiance-field-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreGAN: Exploiting Frequency Components for Training GANs under Limited Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fregan-exploiting-frequency-components-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training GANs under limited data often leads to discriminator overfitting and memorization issues, causing divergent training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fregan-exploiting-frequency-components-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoHNAS: A Neural Architecture Search Framework with Conjoint Optimization for Adversarial Robustness and Hardware Efficiency of Convolutional and Capsule Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rohnas-a-neural-architecture-search-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Architecture Search (NAS) algorithms aim at finding efficient Deep Neural Network (DNN) architectures for a given application under given system constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rohnas-a-neural-architecture-search-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Event Coding Pipeline with Prompt Entailment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-event-coding-pipeline-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose PR-ENT, a new event coding approach that is more flexible and resource-efficient, while maintaining competitive accuracy: first, we extend an event description such as "Military injured two civilians'' by a template, e. g. "People were [Z]" and prompt a pre-trained (cloze) language model to fill the slot Z.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-event-coding-pipeline-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-Training for Robots: Offline RL Enables Learning New Tasks from a Handful of Trials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-for-robots-offline-rl-enables</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, PTR is the first offline RL method that succeeds at learning new tasks in a new domain on a real WidowX robot with as few as 10 task demonstrations, by effectively leveraging an existing dataset of diverse multi-task robot data collected in a variety of toy kitchens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-for-robots-offline-rl-enables</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency-Aware Self-Supervised Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-aware-self-supervised-monocular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present two versatile methods to generally enhance self-supervised monocular depth estimation (MDE) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-aware-self-supervised-monocular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Learning with Self-Improving Momentum Target</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-with-self-improving-momentum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The idea of using a separately trained target model (or teacher) to improve the performance of the student model has been increasingly popular in various machine learning domains, and meta-learning is no exception; a recent discovery shows that utilizing task-wise target models can significantly boost the generalization performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-with-self-improving-momentum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoxTeacher: Exploring High-Quality Pseudo Labels for Weakly Supervised Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boxteacher-exploring-high-quality-pseudo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing methods for weakly supervised instance segmentation focus on designing heuristic losses with priors from bounding boxes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boxteacher-exploring-high-quality-pseudo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Pretrained Multilingual Models Equally Fair Across Languages?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-pretrained-multilingual-models-equally-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pretrained multilingual language models can help bridge the digital language divide, enabling high-quality NLP models for lower resourced languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-pretrained-multilingual-models-equally-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SGD with large step sizes learns sparse features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgd-with-large-step-sizes-learns-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, these observations unveil how, through the step size schedules, both gradient and noise drive together the SGD dynamics through the loss landscape of neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgd-with-large-step-sizes-learns-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIGAT: Modeling News Recommendation with Dual-Graph Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/digat-modeling-news-recommendation-with-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, existing graph-based NR methods are promising but lack effective news-user feature interaction, rendering the graph-based recommendation suboptimal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/digat-modeling-news-recommendation-with-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant 3D-Conditional Diffusion Models for Molecular Linker Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-3d-conditional-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, the model automatically determines the number of atoms in the linker and its attachment points to the input fragments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-3d-conditional-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Human Matting via Semantic Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-human-matting-via-semantic-guidance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike previous works, our framework is data efficient, which requires a small amount of matting ground-truth to learn to estimate high quality object mattes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-human-matting-via-semantic-guidance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Win-win Deal: Towards Sparse and Robust Pre-trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-win-win-deal-towards-sparse-and-robust-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response to the efficiency problem, recent studies show that dense PLMs can be replaced with sparse subnetworks without hurting the performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-win-win-deal-towards-sparse-and-robust-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEE-Few: Seed, Expand and Entail for Few-shot Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/see-few-seed-expand-and-entail-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current few-shot NER methods focus on leveraging existing datasets in the rich-resource domains which might fail in a training-from-scratch setting where no source-domain data is used.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/see-few-seed-expand-and-entail-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASAPose: Class-Adaptive and Semantic-Aware Multi-Object Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/casapose-class-adaptive-and-semantic-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applications in the field of augmented reality or robotics often require joint localisation and 6d pose estimation of multiple objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/casapose-class-adaptive-and-semantic-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capturing Global Structural Information in Long Document Question Answering with Compressive Graph Selector Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/capturing-global-structural-information-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the proposed model consists of three modules: local graph network, global graph network and evidence memory network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/capturing-global-structural-information-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Sharpness-Aware Minimization with Fisher Mask for Better Generalization on Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-sharpness-aware-minimization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning large pretrained language models on a limited training corpus usually suffers from poor generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-sharpness-aware-minimization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CD-FSOD: A Benchmark for Cross-domain Few-shot Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cd-fsod-a-benchmark-for-cross-domain-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although few-shot object detection (FSOD) has attracted great research attention, no work yet exists that studies FSOD across the different domains seen in real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cd-fsod-a-benchmark-for-cross-domain-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EnsembleMOT: A Step towards Ensemble Learning of Multiple Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemblemot-a-step-towards-ensemble-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiple Object Tracking (MOT) has rapidly progressed in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemblemot-a-step-towards-ensemble-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer Vision based inspection on post-earthquake with UAV synthetic dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computer-vision-based-inspection-on-post</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The area affected by the earthquake is vast and often difficult to entirely cover, and the earthquake itself is a sudden event that causes multiple defects simultaneously, that cannot be effectively traced using traditional, manual methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computer-vision-based-inspection-on-post</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCL-Net: Deep Correspondence Learning Network for 6D Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcl-net-deep-correspondence-learning-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Establishment of point correspondence between camera and object coordinate systems is a promising way to solve 6D object poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcl-net-deep-correspondence-learning-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Long-tailed Object Detection with Image-Level Supervision by Multi-Task Collaborative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-long-tailed-object-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, there are an object detection task (consisting of an instance-classification task and a localization task) and an image-classification task in our framework, responsible for utilizing the two types of supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-long-tailed-object-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intrinsic Dimension for Large-Scale Geometric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsic-dimension-for-large-scale-geometric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the present work, we derive a computationally feasible method for determining said axiomatic ID functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsic-dimension-for-large-scale-geometric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAN You Hear Me? Reclaiming Unconditional Speech Synthesis from Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gan-you-hear-me-reclaiming-unconditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As in the StyleGAN family of image synthesis models, ASGAN maps sampled noise to a disentangled latent vector which is then mapped to a sequence of audio features so that signal aliasing is suppressed at every layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gan-you-hear-me-reclaiming-unconditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cluster-level pseudo-labelling for source-free cross-domain facial expression recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-level-pseudo-labelling-for-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatically understanding emotions from visual data is a fundamental task for human behaviour understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-level-pseudo-labelling-for-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Embodied Reference with Touch-Line Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-embodied-reference-with-touch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human studies have revealed that objects referred to or pointed to do not lie on the elbow-wrist line, a common misconception; instead, they lie on the so-called virtual touch line.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-embodied-reference-with-touch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained Image Style Transfer with Visual Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-image-style-transfer-with-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such a design usually destroys the spatial information of the input images and fails to transfer fine-grained style patterns into style transfer results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-image-style-transfer-with-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Segmentation under Adverse Conditions: A Weather and Nighttime-aware Synthetic Data-based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-segmentation-under-adverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent semantic segmentation models perform well under standard weather conditions and sufficient illumination but struggle with adverse weather conditions and nighttime.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-segmentation-under-adverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototypical VoteNet for Few-Shot 3D Point Cloud Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-votenet-for-few-shot-3d-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing 3D point cloud object detection approaches heavily rely on large amounts of labeled training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-votenet-for-few-shot-3d-point</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
