<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 21:06:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Long-term Conversation Analysis: Exploring Utility and Privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-term-conversation-analysis-exploring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The analysis of conversations recorded in everyday life requires privacy protection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-term-conversation-analysis-exploring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Regularization in Optimal Time Variable Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-regularization-in-optimal-time-variable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, optimal time variable learning in deep neural networks (DNNs) was introduced in arXiv:2204. 08528.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-regularization-in-optimal-time-variable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributional Modeling for Location-Aware Adversarial Patches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-modeling-for-location-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the Distribution-Optimized Adversarial Patch (DOPatch), a novel method that optimizes a multimodal distribution of adversarial locations instead of individual ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-modeling-for-location-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBBQ: A Chinese Bias Benchmark Dataset Curated with Human-AI Collaboration for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbbq-a-chinese-bias-benchmark-dataset-curated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a Chinese Bias Benchmark dataset that consists of over 100K questions jointly constructed by human experts and generative language models, covering stereotypes and societal biases in 14 social dimensions related to Chinese culture and values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbbq-a-chinese-bias-benchmark-dataset-curated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural directional distance field object representation for uni-directional path-traced rendering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-directional-distance-field-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Faster rendering of synthetic images is a core problem in the field of computer graphics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-directional-distance-field-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model as Attributed Training Data Generator: A Tale of Diversity and Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-as-attributed-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we present a comprehensive empirical study on data generation encompassing vital aspects like bias, diversity, and efficiency, and highlight three key observations: firstly, synthetic datasets generated by simple prompts exhibit significant biases, such as regional bias; secondly, attribute diversity plays a pivotal role in enhancing model performance; lastly, attributed prompts achieve the performance of simple class-conditional prompts while utilizing only 5\% of the querying cost of ChatGPT associated with the latter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-as-attributed-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiZoo &amp; MultiBench: A Standardized Toolkit for Multimodal Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multizoo-multibench-a-standardized-toolkit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning multimodal representations involves integrating information from multiple heterogeneous sources of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multizoo-multibench-a-standardized-toolkit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatLaw: Open-Source Legal Large Language Model with Integrated External Knowledge Bases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatlaw-open-source-legal-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose a self-attention method to enhance the ability of large models to overcome errors present in reference data, further optimizing the issue of model hallucinations at the model level and improving the problem-solving capabilities of large models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatlaw-open-source-legal-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating the Accuracy-Robustness Trade-off via Multi-Teacher Adversarial Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-the-accuracy-robustness-trade-off</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial training is a practical approach for improving the robustness of deep neural networks against adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-the-accuracy-robustness-trade-off</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Individual and Structural Graph Information Bottlenecks for Out-of-Distribution Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individual-and-structural-graph-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To remove class spurious feature caused by distribution shifts, we propose Individual Graph Information Bottleneck (I-GIB) which discards irrelevant information by minimizing the mutual information between the input graph and its embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individual-and-structural-graph-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Separable Physics-Informed Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/separable-physics-informed-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The number of training points (collocation points) required on these challenging PDEs grows substantially, but it is severely limited due to the expensive computational costs and heavy memory overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/separable-physics-informed-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Open Vocabulary Learning: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-open-vocabulary-learning-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our knowledge, this is the first comprehensive literature review of open vocabulary learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-open-vocabulary-learning-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is ChatGPT a Biomedical Expert? -- Exploring the Zero-Shot Performance of Current GPT Models in Biomedical Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-chatgpt-a-biomedical-expert-exploring-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We assessed the performance of commercial Large Language Models (LLMs) GPT-3. 5-Turbo and GPT-4 on tasks from the 2023 BioASQ challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-chatgpt-a-biomedical-expert-exploring-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MyDigitalFootprint: an extensive context dataset for pervasive computing applications at the edge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mydigitalfootprint-an-extensive-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demonstrate the dataset's effectiveness, we present three context-aware applications utilizing various machine learning tasks: (i) a social link prediction algorithm based on physical proximity data, (ii) daily-life activity recognition using smartphone-embedded sensors data, and (iii) a pervasive context-aware recommender system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mydigitalfootprint-an-extensive-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Pan-sharpening with Memories of Spatial Details</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-pan-sharpening-with-memories-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, in this paper, we observe that the spatial details from PAN images are mainly high-frequency cues, i. e., the edges reflect the contour of input PAN images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-pan-sharpening-with-memories-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On information captured by neural networks: connections with memorization and generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-information-captured-by-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the popularity and success of deep learning, there is limited understanding of when, how, and why neural networks generalize to unseen examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-information-captured-by-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Systematic analysis of the impact of label noise correction on ML Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/systematic-analysis-of-the-impact-of-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply the methodology to analyze six label noise correction methods according to several fairness metrics on standard OpenML datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/systematic-analysis-of-the-impact-of-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Sampling and Aggregation Operations in GNN Frameworks with GPU Initiated Direct Storage Accesses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-sampling-and-aggregation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose the GPU Initiated Direct Storage Access (GIDS) dataloader, to enable GPU-oriented GNN training for large-scale graphs while efficiently utilizing all hardware resources, such as CPU memory, storage, and GPU memory with a hybrid data placement strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-sampling-and-aggregation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More efficient manual review of automatically transcribed tabular data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-efficient-manual-review-of-automatically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We allocated those 90, 000 codes to human reviewers, who used our annotation tool to review the codes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-efficient-manual-review-of-automatically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RL$^3$: Boosting Meta Reinforcement Learning via RL inside RL$^2$</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-3-boosting-meta-reinforcement-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meta reinforcement learning (meta-RL) methods such as RL$^2$ have emerged as promising approaches for learning data-efficient RL algorithms tailored to a given task distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-3-boosting-meta-reinforcement-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Points for Energy Renovation (PointER): A LiDAR-Derived Point Cloud Dataset of One Million English Buildings Linked to Energy Characteristics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/points-for-energy-renovation-pointer-a-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building point clouds in new regions can be generated with the open-source code published alongside the paper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/points-for-energy-renovation-pointer-a-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Language Models can be Poets too: An AI Writing Assistant and Constrained Text Generation Studio</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/most-language-models-can-be-poets-too-an-ai-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a simple and universally applicable technique for modifying the output of a language model by compositionally applying filter functions to the language models vocabulary before a unit of text is generated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/most-language-models-can-be-poets-too-an-ai-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S2SNet: A Pretrained Neural Network for Superconductivity Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s2snet-a-pretrained-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, S2SNet is the first work to predict superconductivity with only information of crystal structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s2snet-a-pretrained-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Land Cover Segmentation with Sparse Annotations from Sentinel-2 Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/land-cover-segmentation-with-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Land cover (LC) segmentation plays a critical role in various applications, including environmental analysis and natural disaster management.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/land-cover-segmentation-with-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curious Replay for Model-based Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curious-replay-for-model-based-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Agents must be able to adapt quickly as an environment changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curious-replay-for-model-based-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empirical Loss Landscape Analysis of Neural Network Activation Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-loss-landscape-analysis-of-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Activation functions play a significant role in neural network design by enabling non-linearity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-loss-landscape-analysis-of-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Path-Controllable Deep Unfolding Network for Compressive Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-path-controllable-deep-unfolding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep unfolding network (DUN) that unfolds the optimization algorithm into a deep neural network has achieved great success in compressive sensing (CS) due to its good interpretability and high performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-path-controllable-deep-unfolding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIPD: A Federated Learning Person Detection Benchmark Based on Real-World Non-IID Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nipd-a-federated-learning-person-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we open source a non-IID IoT person detection (NIPD) data set, which is collected from five different cameras.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nipd-a-federated-learning-person-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reduce Computational Complexity for Convolutional Layers by Skipping Zeros</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduce-computational-complexity-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper gives C-K-S algorithm (ConvV2, KS-deconv, Sk-dilated), which skips these 0s in two ways: trim the filters to exclude padded 0s; transform sparse tensors to dense tensors, to avoid inserted 0s in deconvolution and dilated-convolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduce-computational-complexity-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Surgical Instruments Segmentation to Unseen Domains with One-to-Many Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-surgical-instruments</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we mitigate data-related issues by efficiently leveraging minimal source images to generate synthetic surgical instrument segmentation datasets and achieve outstanding generalization performance on unseen real domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-surgical-instruments</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taqyim: Evaluating Arabic NLP Tasks Using ChatGPT Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taqyim-evaluating-arabic-nlp-tasks-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated impressive performance on various downstream tasks without requiring fine-tuning, including ChatGPT, a chat-based model built on top of LLMs such as GPT-3. 5 and GPT-4.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taqyim-evaluating-arabic-nlp-tasks-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Framework for Identifying Depression on Social Media: MentalRiskES@IberLEF 2023</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-identifying-depression-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes our participation in the MentalRiskES task at IberLEF 2023.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-identifying-depression-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAE-GEBD:Winning the CVPR'2023 LOVEU-GEBD Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mae-gebd-winning-the-cvpr-2023-loveu-gebd</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Generic Event Boundary Detection (GEBD) task aims to build a model for segmenting videos into segments by detecting general event boundaries applicable to various classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mae-gebd-winning-the-cvpr-2023-loveu-gebd</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning normal asymmetry representations for homologous brain structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-normal-asymmetry-representations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel method to learn normal asymmetry patterns in homologous brain structures based on anomaly detection and representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-normal-asymmetry-representations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Annealed Importance Sampling with Constant Rate Progress</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-annealed-importance-sampling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This algorithm relies on a sequence of interpolating distributions bridging the target to an initial tractable distribution such as the well-known geometric mean path of unnormalized distributions which is assumed to be suboptimal in general.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-annealed-importance-sampling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Re] Double Sampling Randomized Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-double-sampling-randomized-smoothing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper is a contribution to the reproducibility challenge in the field of machine learning, specifically addressing the issue of certifying the robustness of neural networks (NNs) against adversarial perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-double-sampling-randomized-smoothing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIPA-v2: Scaling CLIP Training with 81.1% Zero-shot ImageNet Accuracy within a \$10,000 Budget; An Extra \$4,000 Unlocks 81.8% Accuracy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clipa-v2-scaling-clip-training-with-81-1-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent work CLIPA presents an inverse scaling law for CLIP training -- whereby the larger the image/text encoders used, the shorter the sequence length of image/text tokens that can be applied in training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clipa-v2-scaling-clip-training-with-81-1-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-supervised Multimodal Representation Learning through a Global Workspace</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-multimodal-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent deep learning models can efficiently combine inputs from different modalities (e. g., images and text) and learn to align their latent representations, or to translate signals from one domain to another (as in image captioning, or text-to-image generation).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-multimodal-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Inferential Structure in Neural Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-inferential-structure-in-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Processes (NPs) are appealing due to their ability to perform fast adaptation based on a context set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-inferential-structure-in-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCID: Deep Canonical Information Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcid-deep-canonical-information-decomposition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Canonical Correlation Analysis (CCA)-based methods have traditionally been used to identify shared variables, however, they were designed for multivariate targets and only offer trivial solutions for univariate cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcid-deep-canonical-information-decomposition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly Detection in Networks via Score-Based Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomaly-detection-in-networks-via-score-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Node outlier detection in attributed graphs is a challenging problem for which there is no method that would work well across different datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomaly-detection-in-networks-via-score-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KnowPrefix-Tuning: A Two-Stage Prefix-Tuning Framework for Knowledge-Grounded Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowprefix-tuning-a-two-stage-prefix-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Knowledgeable Prefix Tuning (KnowPrefix-Tuning), a two-stage tuning framework, bypassing the retrieval process in a knowledge-grounded conversation system by injecting prior knowledge into the lightweight knowledge prefix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowprefix-tuning-a-two-stage-prefix-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UTRNet: High-Resolution Urdu Text Recognition In Printed Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utrnet-high-resolution-urdu-text-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the limitations of previous works, which struggle to generalize to the intricacies of the Urdu script and the lack of sufficient annotated real-world data, we have introduced the UTRSet-Real, a large-scale annotated real-world dataset comprising over 11, 000 lines and UTRSet-Synth, a synthetic dataset with 20, 000 lines closely resembling real-world and made corrections to the ground truth of the existing IIITH dataset, making it a more reliable resource for future research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utrnet-high-resolution-urdu-text-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Can Mask More For Extremely Low-Bitrate Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-can-mask-more-for-extremely-low-bitrate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments have demonstrated that our approach outperforms recent state-of-the-art methods in R-D performance, visual quality, and downstream applications, at very low bitrates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-can-mask-more-for-extremely-low-bitrate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easing Color Shifts in Score-Based Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easing-color-shifts-in-score-based-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This network architecture substantially improves the resulting spatial means of the generated images, and we show that the improvement is approximately independent of the size of the generated images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easing-color-shifts-in-score-based-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Annotation of Direct Speech in Written French Narratives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-annotation-of-direct-speech-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The automatic annotation of direct speech (AADS) in written text has been often used in computational narrative understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-annotation-of-direct-speech-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PANet: LiDAR Panoptic Segmentation with Sparse Instance Proposal and Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panet-lidar-panoptic-segmentation-with-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we propose a non-learning Sparse Instance Proposal (SIP) module with the ``sampling-shifting-grouping" scheme to directly group thing points into instances from the raw point cloud efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panet-lidar-panoptic-segmentation-with-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross Spectral Image Reconstruction Using a Deep Guided Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-spectral-image-reconstruction-using-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since only little cross spectral data is available for training, this neural network is highly regularized.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-spectral-image-reconstruction-using-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating The Impact Of Species Specialisation On Ecological Network Robustness Using Analytic Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-impact-of-species</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We have also extended the model to predict scenarios in which secondary extinctions occur once species lose a certain percentage of interaction strength, and to model the loss of interactions as opposed to just species extinction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-impact-of-species</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-class systems seamlessly fit in the forward-forward algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-class-systems-seamlessly-fit-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The forward-forward algorithm presents a new method of training neural networks by updating weights during an inference, performing parameter updates for each layer individually.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-class-systems-seamlessly-fit-in-the</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
