<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 09:15:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Toroidal Probabilistic Spherical Discriminant Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toroidal-probabilistic-spherical-discriminant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It extends PSDA with the ability to model within and between-speaker variabilities in toroidal submanifolds of the hypersphere.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toroidal-probabilistic-spherical-discriminant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A few-shot learning approach with domain adaptation for personalized real-life stress detection in close relationships</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-few-shot-learning-approach-with-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed metric learning is based on a Siamese neural network (SNN) that learns the relative difference between pairs of samples from a target user and non-target users, thus being able to address the scarcity of labelled data from the target.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-few-shot-learning-approach-with-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmentation of Multiple Sclerosis Lesions across Hospitals: Learn Continually or Train from Scratch?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-of-multiple-sclerosis-lesions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segmentation of Multiple Sclerosis (MS) lesions is a challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-of-multiple-sclerosis-lesions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Adaptive Object Detection for Autonomous Driving under Foggy Weather</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-object-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel domain adaptive object detection framework for autonomous driving under foggy weather.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-object-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Convolutional Neural Networks for Multi-Target Tracking: A Transfer Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-convolutional-neural-networks-for-multi-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We represent the target states and sensor measurements as images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-convolutional-neural-networks-for-multi-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COCO-DR: Combating Distribution Shifts in Zero-Shot Dense Retrieval with Contrastive and Distributionally Robust Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coco-dr-combating-distribution-shifts-in-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new zero-shot dense retrieval (ZeroDR) method, COCO-DR, to improve the generalization ability of dense retrieval by combating the distribution shifts between source training tasks and target scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coco-dr-combating-distribution-shifts-in-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Inter-Dependence Between Time and Mark in Multivariate Temporal Point Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-inter-dependence-between-time-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we model the conditional inter-dependence of time and mark to overcome the limitations of conditionally independent models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-inter-dependence-between-time-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening the Black Box of wav2vec Feature Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opening-the-black-box-of-wav2vec-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised models, namely, wav2vec and its variants, have shown promising results in various downstream tasks in the speech domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opening-the-black-box-of-wav2vec-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and Effective Augmentation Strategy for Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-effective-augmentation-strategy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first explain this contrasting behavior by viewing augmentation during training as a problem of domain generalization, and further propose Diverse Augmentation-based Joint Adversarial Training (DAJAT) to use data augmentations effectively in adversarial training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-effective-augmentation-strategy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A knowledge-driven vowel-based approach of depression classification from speech using data augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-knowledge-driven-vowel-based-approach-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Following that, the depression is classified at the global-level from a group of vowel CNN embeddings that serve as the input of another 1D CNN ("depression CNN").]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-knowledge-driven-vowel-based-approach-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Complex Backgrounds: A Unified Difference-Aware Decoder for Binary Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-complex-backgrounds-a-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Stage A, the first branch decoder of the difference-aware decoder is used to obtain a guide map.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-complex-backgrounds-a-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dictionary-Assisted Supervised Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dictionary-assisted-supervised-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text analysis in the social sciences often involves using specialized dictionaries to reason with abstract concepts, such as perceptions about the economy or abuse on social media.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dictionary-assisted-supervised-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HRTF Field: Unifying Measured HRTF Magnitude Representation with Neural Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrtf-field-unifying-measured-hrtf-magnitude</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose to use neural fields, a differentiable representation of functions through neural networks, to model HRTFs with arbitrary spatial sampling schemes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrtf-field-unifying-measured-hrtf-magnitude</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Severity Assessment of Dysarthric speech by using Self-supervised Model with Multi-task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-severity-assessment-of-dysarthric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle the problem, we propose a novel automatic severity assessment method for dysarthric speech, using the self-supervised model in conjunction with multi-task learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-severity-assessment-of-dysarthric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dial2vec: Self-Guided Contrastive Learning of Unsupervised Dialogue Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dial2vec-self-guided-contrastive-learning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce the task of learning unsupervised dialogue embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dial2vec-self-guided-contrastive-learning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deformable Temporal Convolutional Networks for Monaural Noisy Reverberant Speech Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deformable-temporal-convolutional-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work deformable convolution is proposed as a solution to allow TCN models to have dynamic RFs that can adapt to various reverberation times for reverberant speech separation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deformable-temporal-convolutional-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Multi-Person Body Detection and Orientation Estimation via One Unified Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-multi-person-body-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the paper, we propose a single-stage end-to-end trainable framework for tackling the HBOE problem with multi-persons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-multi-person-body-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeVC: Towards High-Quality Text-Free One-Shot Voice Conversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freevc-towards-high-quality-text-free-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Voice conversion (VC) can be achieved by first extracting source content information and target speaker information, and then reconstructing waveform with these information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freevc-towards-high-quality-text-free-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Audio Inverse Problems with a Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-audio-inverse-problems-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents CQT-Diff, a data-driven generative audio model that can, once trained, be used for solving various different audio inverse problems in a problem-agnostic setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-audio-inverse-problems-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Data2vec: Noise-robust Speech Representation Learning for ASR by Combining Regression and Improved Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-data2vec-noise-robust-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised pre-training methods based on contrastive learning or regression tasks can utilize more unlabeled data to improve the performance of automatic speech recognition (ASR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-data2vec-noise-robust-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusion-based Few-Shot Morphing Attack Detection and Fingerprinting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusion-based-few-shot-morphing-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our technical contributions include: 1) We propose a fusion-based few-shot learning (FSL) method to learn discriminative features that can generalize to unseen morphing attack types from predefined presentation attacks; 2) The proposed FSL based on the fusion of the PRNU model and Noiseprint network is extended from binary MAD to multiclass morphing attack fingerprinting (MAF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusion-based-few-shot-morphing-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting modality-invariant feature for robust multimodal emotion recognition with missing modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-modality-invariant-feature-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal emotion recognition leverages complementary information across modalities to gain performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-modality-invariant-feature-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-Voxel Adaptive Feature Abstraction for Robust Point Cloud Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-voxel-adaptive-feature-abstraction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the proposed framework iteratively voxelize the point cloud and extract point-voxel feature with shared local encoding and Transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-voxel-adaptive-feature-abstraction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How well can Text-to-Image Generative Models understand Ethical Natural Language Interventions?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-well-can-text-to-image-generative-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce an Ethical NaTural Language Interventions in Text-to-Image GENeration (ENTIGEN) benchmark dataset to evaluate the change in image generations conditional on ethical interventions across three social axes -- gender, skin color, and culture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-well-can-text-to-image-generative-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformers meet Stochastic Block Models: Attention with Data-Adaptive Sparsity and Cost</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-meet-stochastic-block-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The forward and backward cost are thus linear to the number of edges, which each attention head can also choose flexibly based on the input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-meet-stochastic-block-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Feature Distillation via Projector Ensemble</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-feature-distillation-via-projector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the positive effect of the projector in feature distillation, we propose an ensemble of projectors to further improve the quality of student features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-feature-distillation-via-projector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truncation Sampling as Language Model Desmoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truncation-sampling-as-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this light, truncation algorithms aim to perform desmoothing, estimating a subset of the support of the true distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truncation-sampling-as-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Language Model to Train if You Have One Million GPU Hours?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-language-model-to-train-if-you-have-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[All our models and code are open-sourced at https://huggingface. co/bigscience .]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-language-model-to-train-if-you-have-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too Brittle To Touch: Comparing the Stability of Quantization and Distillation Towards Developing Lightweight Low-Resource MT Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/too-brittle-to-touch-comparing-the-stability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging shared learning through Massively Multilingual Models, state-of-the-art machine translation models are often able to adapt to the paucity of data for low-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/too-brittle-to-touch-comparing-the-stability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TASA: Deceiving Question Answering Models by Twin Answer Sentences Attack</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tasa-deceiving-question-answering-models-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Twin Answer Sentences Attack (TASA), an adversarial attack method for question answering (QA) models that produces fluent and grammatical adversarial contexts while maintaining gold answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tasa-deceiving-question-answering-models-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep-MDS Framework for Recovering the 3D Shape of 2D Landmarks from a Single Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-mds-framework-for-recovering-the-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, a low parameter deep learning framework utilizing the Non-metric Multi-Dimensional scaling (NMDS) method, is proposed to recover the 3D shape of 2D landmarks on a human face, in a single input image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-mds-framework-for-recovering-the-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACES: Translation Accuracy Challenge Sets for Evaluating Machine Translation Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aces-translation-accuracy-challenge-sets-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As machine translation (MT) metrics improve their correlation with human judgement every year, it is crucial to understand the limitations of such metrics at the segment level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aces-translation-accuracy-challenge-sets-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards High-Quality Neural TTS for Low-Resource Languages by Learning Compact Speech Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-high-quality-neural-tts-for-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we optimize the training strategy by leveraging more audio to learn MSMCRs better for low-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-high-quality-neural-tts-for-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Visual Attention and Distraction During Visual Search Using Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-visual-attention-and-distraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our second approach is object-based and predicts the distractor and target objects during visual search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-visual-attention-and-distraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Reverse-engineering of Trojan Triggers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-reverse-engineering-of-trojan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On average, the detection accuracy of our method is 93\%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-reverse-engineering-of-trojan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Wikidata's edit history in knowledge graph refinement tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-wikidata-s-edit-history-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A number of solutions have been proposed to that end, ranging from rule-based approaches to the use of probabilistic methods, but there is an element that has not been considered yet: the edit history of the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-wikidata-s-edit-history-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Decoding: Open-ended Text Generation as Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-decoding-open-ended-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose contrastive decoding (CD), a more reliable search objective that returns the difference between likelihood under a large LM (called the expert, e. g. OPT-13b) and a small LM (called the amateur, e. g. OPT-125m).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-decoding-open-ended-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GaitMixer: skeleton-based gait representation learning via wide-spectrum multi-axial mixer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaitmixer-skeleton-based-gait-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing gait recognition methods are appearance-based, which rely on the silhouettes extracted from the video data of human walking activities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaitmixer-skeleton-based-gait-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structuring User-Generated Content on Social Media with Multimodal Aspect-Based Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structuring-user-generated-content-on-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[People post their opinions and experiences on social media, yielding rich databases of end users' sentiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structuring-user-generated-content-on-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He Said, She Said: Style Transfer for Shifting the Perspective of Dialogues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/he-said-she-said-style-transfer-for-shifting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a sample application, we demonstrate that applying perspective shifting to a dialogue summarization dataset (SAMSum) substantially improves the zero-shot performance of extractive news summarization models on this data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/he-said-she-said-style-transfer-for-shifting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Graph Is More Than Its Nodes: Towards Structured Uncertainty-Aware Learning on Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-graph-is-more-than-its-nodes-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current graph neural networks (GNNs) that tackle node classification on graphs tend to only focus on nodewise scores and are solely evaluated by nodewise metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-graph-is-more-than-its-nodes-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving abstractive summarization with energy-based re-ranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-abstractive-summarization-with-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current abstractive summarization systems present important weaknesses which prevent their deployment in real-world applications, such as the omission of relevant information and the generation of factual inconsistencies (also known as hallucinations).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-abstractive-summarization-with-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Articulation GAN: Unsupervised modeling of articulatory learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/articulation-gan-unsupervised-modeling-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Articulatory analysis of the generated EMA representations suggests that the network learns to control articulators in a manner that closely follows human articulators during speech production.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/articulation-gan-unsupervised-modeling-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MorphTE: Injecting Morphology in Tensorized Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphte-injecting-morphology-in-tensorized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the era of deep learning, word embeddings are essential when dealing with text tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphte-injecting-morphology-in-tensorized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working Alliance Transformer for Psychotherapy Dialogue Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/working-alliance-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a predictive measure of the treatment outcome in psychotherapy, the working alliance measures the agreement of the patient and the therapist in terms of their bond, task and goal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/working-alliance-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COST-EFF: Collaborative Optimization of Spatial and Temporal Efficiency with Slenderized Multi-exit Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-eff-collaborative-optimization-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by such considerations, we propose a collaborative optimization for PLMs that integrates static model compression and dynamic inference acceleration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-eff-collaborative-optimization-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Vision-Language Transformer in Fashion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-vision-language-transformer-in-fashion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a masked vision-language transformer (MVLT) for fashion-specific multi-modal representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-vision-language-transformer-in-fashion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermarking for Out-of-distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watermarking-for-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-distribution (OOD) detection aims to identify OOD data based on representations extracted from well-trained deep models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watermarking-for-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Networks with Quantization Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-with-quantization-constraints</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we show that dual variables indicate the sensitivity of the objective with respect to constraint perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-with-quantization-constraints</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Automatically Extracting UML Class Diagrams from Natural Language Specifications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-automatically-extracting-uml-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To develop our approach, we create a dataset of UML class diagrams and their English specifications with the help of volunteers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-automatically-extracting-uml-class</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
