<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 09:12:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study on Compliance with Ranking Transparency in the Software Documentation of EU Online Platforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-compliance-with-ranking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compliance with the European Union's Platform-to-Business (P2B) Regulation is challenging for online platforms, and assessing their compliance can be difficult for public authorities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-compliance-with-ranking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Latent Multi-view Subspace Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-latent-multi-view-subspace</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we stack the data matrices from various views into the block-diagonal locations of the augmented matrix to exploit the complementary information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-latent-multi-view-subspace</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inverse Transfer Multiobjective Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverse-transfer-multiobjective-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel concept of inverse transfer in multiobjective optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverse-transfer-multiobjective-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PC-Conv: Unifying Homophily and Heterophily with Two-fold Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pc-conv-unifying-homophily-and-heterophily</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is attributed to their neglect of homophily in heterophilic graphs, and vice versa.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pc-conv-unifying-homophily-and-heterophily</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacking Byzantine Robust Aggregation in High Dimensions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attacking-byzantine-robust-aggregation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing such aggregators is challenging when dealing with high dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attacking-byzantine-robust-aggregation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Diffusion Models for Visual Perception with Meta Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-diffusion-models-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our key insight is to introduce learnable embeddings (meta prompts) to the pre-trained diffusion models to extract proper features for perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-diffusion-models-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Covariate Gait Recognition: A Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-covariate-gait-recognition-a-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to existing datasets, CCGR has both population and individual-level diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-covariate-gait-recognition-a-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuaLight: Enhancing Traffic Signal Control by Leveraging Scenario-Specific and Scenario-Shared Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dualight-enhancing-traffic-signal-control-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we implement a scenario-shared Co-Train module to facilitate the learning of generalizable dynamics information across different scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dualight-enhancing-traffic-signal-control-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quality-Diversity Generative Sampling for Learning with Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quality-diversity-generative-sampling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[QDGS is a model-agnostic framework that uses prompt guidance to optimize a quality objective across measures of diversity for synthetically generated data, without fine-tuning the generative model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quality-diversity-generative-sampling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balancing the Style-Content Trade-Off in Sentiment Transfer Using Polarity-Aware Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-the-style-content-trade-off-in-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text sentiment transfer aims to flip the sentiment polarity of a sentence (positive to negative or vice versa) while preserving its sentiment-independent content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-the-style-content-trade-off-in-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating the Design of Multigrid Methods with Evolutionary Program Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-the-design-of-multigrid-methods</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this purpose, we develop a novel context-free grammar that enables the automated generation of multigrid methods in a symbolically-manipulable formal language, based on which we can apply the same multigrid-based solver to problems of different sizes without having to adapt its internal structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-the-design-of-multigrid-methods</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part to Whole: Collaborative Prompting for Surgical Instrument Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/part-to-whole-collaborative-prompting-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, in this paper, we investigate text promptable surgical instrument segmentation and propose SP-SAM (SurgicalPart-SAM), a novel efficient-tuning approach that integrates surgical instrument structure knowledge with the generic segmentation knowledge of SAM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/part-to-whole-collaborative-prompting-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Learning Neuronal Skeleton and Brain Circuit Topology with Permutation Invariant Encoders for Neuron Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-learning-neuronal-skeleton-and-brain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Skeleton Encoder integrates the local information of neurons in a bottom-up manner, with a one-dimensional convolution in neural skeleton's point data; Connectome Encoder uses a graph neural network to capture the topological information of neural circuit; finally, Readout Layer fuses the above two information and outputs classification results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-learning-neuronal-skeleton-and-brain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasons to Reject? Aligning Language Models with Judgments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasons-to-reject-aligning-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As humans, we consistently engage in interactions with our peers and receive feedback in the form of natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasons-to-reject-aligning-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUMA: Efficient Continual Graph Learning with Graph Condensation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puma-efficient-continual-graph-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our prior work, CaT is a replay-based framework with a balanced continual learning procedure, which designs a small yet effective memory bank for replaying data by condensing incoming graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puma-efficient-continual-graph-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TACO: Topics in Algorithmic COde generation dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taco-topics-in-algorithmic-code-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, each TACO problem includes several fine-grained labels such as task topics, algorithms, programming skills, and difficulty levels, providing a more precise reference for the training and evaluation of code generation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taco-topics-in-algorithmic-code-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Effectiveness of Unlearning in Session-Based Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-unlearning-in-session</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the one hand, these approaches cannot achieve satisfying unlearning effects due to the collaborative correlations and sequential connections between the unlearning item and the remaining items in the session.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-unlearning-in-session</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSAP: Analyzing Bias Through Demographic Comparison of Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsap-analyzing-bias-through-demographic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Often, these biases can be traced back to the data used for training, where large uncurated datasets have become the norm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsap-analyzing-bias-through-demographic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCUNet++: Assessment of Pulmonary Embolism CT Image Segmentation Leveraging Swin-UNet and CNN Bottleneck Hybrid Architecture with Multi-Fusion Dense Skip Connection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scunet-assessment-of-pulmonary-embolism-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These findings demonstrate that our method exhibits strong performance in PE segmentation tasks, potentially enhancing the accuracy of automatic segmentation of PE and providing a powerful diagnostic tool for clinical physicians.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scunet-assessment-of-pulmonary-embolism-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Token-Level Contrastive Learning with Modality-Aware Prompting for Multimodal Intent Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-level-contrastive-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To establish an optimal multimodal semantic environment for text modality, we develop a modality-aware prompting module (MAP), which effectively aligns and fuses features from text, video and audio modalities with similarity-based modality alignment and cross-modality attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-level-contrastive-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aurora:Activating Chinese chat capability for Mistral-8x7B sparse Mixture-of-Experts through Instruction-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aurora-activating-chinese-chat-capability-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work is pioneering in the execution of instruction fine-tuning on a sparse expert-mixed model, marking a significant breakthrough in enhancing the capabilities of this model architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aurora-activating-chinese-chat-capability-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Stage Adaptive Feature Fusion Neural Network for Multimodal Gait Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-stage-adaptive-feature-fusion-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, by considering the temporal and spatial characteristics of gait data, we propose a multi-stage feature fusion strategy (MSFFS), which performs multimodal fusions at different stages in the feature extraction process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-stage-adaptive-feature-fusion-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Images in Discrete Choice Modeling: Addressing Data Isomorphism in Multi-Modality Inputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/images-in-discrete-choice-modeling-addressing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose and benchmark two methodologies to address this challenge: architectural design adjustments to segregate redundant information, and isomorphic information mitigation through source information masking and inpainting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/images-in-discrete-choice-modeling-addressing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Occlusion-Aware Transformer for Robust Stereo Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-occlusion-aware-transformer-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the remarkable progress facilitated by learning-based stereo-matching algorithms, the performance in the ill-conditioned regions, such as the occluded regions, remains a bottleneck.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-occlusion-aware-transformer-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning via Input-Output Collaborative Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-via-input-output</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) is a machine learning paradigm in which distributed local nodes collaboratively train a central model without sharing individually held private data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-via-input-output</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from higher-order statistics, efficiently: hypothesis tests, random features, and neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-higher-order-statistics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that neural networks extract information from higher-order correlations in the spiked cumulant model efficiently, and reveal a large gap in the amount of data required by neural networks and random features to learn from higher-order cumulants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-higher-order-statistics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argue with Me Tersely: Towards Sentence-Level Counter-Argument Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/argue-with-me-tersely-towards-sentence-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results show the competitiveness of our proposed framework and evaluator in counter-argument generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/argue-with-me-tersely-towards-sentence-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards More Faithful Natural Language Explanation Using Multi-Level Contrastive Learning in VQA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-more-faithful-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above issues, we propose a novel self-supervised \textbf{M}ulti-level \textbf{C}ontrastive \textbf{L}earning based natural language \textbf{E}xplanation model (MCLE) for VQA with semantic-level, image-level, and instance-level factual and counterfactual samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-more-faithful-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Visual Supervision for Array-based Active Speaker Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-visual-supervision-for-array-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The multichannel audio ``student'' network is trained to generate the same results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-visual-supervision-for-array-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HGE: Embedding Temporal Knowledge Graphs in a Product Space of Heterogeneous Geometric Subspaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hge-embedding-temporal-knowledge-graphs-in-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal knowledge graphs may exhibit static temporal patterns at distinct points in time and dynamic temporal patterns between different timestamps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hge-embedding-temporal-knowledge-graphs-in-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entropic Open-set Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropic-open-set-active-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Active Learning (AL) aims to enhance the performance of deep models by selecting the most informative samples for annotation from a pool of unlabeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropic-open-set-active-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaussian Splatting with NeRF-based Color and Opacity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-splitting-algorithm-with-color-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the caveats of both models, we propose a hybrid model that uses GS representation of the 3D object's shape and NeRF-based encoding of color and opacity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-splitting-algorithm-with-color-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Semantic Space is Worth 256 Language Descriptions: Make Stronger Segmentation Models with Descriptive Properties</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semantic-space-is-worth-256-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of relying solely on category-specific annotations, ProLab uses descriptive properties grounded in common sense knowledge for supervising segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semantic-space-is-worth-256-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HD-Painter: High-Resolution and Prompt-Faithful Text-Guided Image Inpainting with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hd-painter-high-resolution-and-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in text-guided image inpainting, based on the unprecedented success of text-to-image diffusion models, has led to exceptionally realistic and visually plausible results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hd-painter-high-resolution-and-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geo2SigMap: High-Fidelity RF Signal Mapping Using Geographic Databases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geo2sigmap-high-fidelity-rf-signal-mapping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we develop an automated framework that seamlessly integrates three open-source tools: OpenStreetMap (geographic databases), Blender (computer graphics), and Sionna (ray tracing), enabling the efficient generation of large-scale 3D building maps and ray tracing models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geo2sigmap-high-fidelity-rf-signal-mapping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angle of Arrival and Centimeter Distance Estimation on a Smart UWB Sensor Node</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/angle-of-arrival-and-centimeter-distance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate and low-power indoor localization is becoming more and more of a necessity to empower novel consumer and industrial applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/angle-of-arrival-and-centimeter-distance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk-Sensitive Stochastic Optimal Control as Rao-Blackwellized Markovian Score Climbing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-sensitive-stochastic-optimal-control-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stochastic optimal control of dynamical systems is a crucial challenge in sequential decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-sensitive-stochastic-optimal-control-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MFABA: A More Faithful and Accelerated Boundary-based Attribution Method for Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mfaba-a-more-faithful-and-accelerated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better understand the output of deep neural networks (DNN), attribution based methods have been an important approach for model interpretability, which assign a score for each input dimension to indicate its importance towards the model outcome.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mfaba-a-more-faithful-and-accelerated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-Eval: Evaluating the Tool Utilization Capability Step by Step</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-eval-evaluating-the-tool-utilization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to previous works that evaluate models holistically, we comprehensively decompose the tool utilization into multiple sub-processes, including instruction following, planning, reasoning, retrieval, understanding, and review.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-eval-evaluating-the-tool-utilization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Point Cloud Diffusion for Disentangled 3D Shape and Appearance Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-point-cloud-diffusion-for-disentangled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, none of the existing models enable disentangled generation to control the shape and appearance separately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-point-cloud-diffusion-for-disentangled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian optimized physics-informed neural network for estimating wave propagation velocities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-optimized-physics-informed-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The inverse estimation capability of the proposed approach is tested in three different isotropic media with different wave velocities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-optimized-physics-informed-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SE(3)-Equivariant and Noise-Invariant 3D Motion Tracking in Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/se-3-equivariant-and-noise-invariant-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we propose EquiTrack, the first method that uses recent steerable SE(3)-equivariant CNNs (E-CNN) for motion tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/se-3-equivariant-and-noise-invariant-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Few-Shot Recommender Systems with Large Language Models -- Enhanced Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-few-shot-recommender-systems-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommender systems utilizing explicit feedback have witnessed significant advancements and widespread applications over the past years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-few-shot-recommender-systems-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structured Probabilistic Coding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-probabilistic-coding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By extracting compact and informative representations from input related to the target task, SPC can enhance the generalization ability of pre-trained language models for better language understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-probabilistic-coding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable 3D Face Generation with Conditional Style Code Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-3d-face-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For 3D GAN inversion, we introduce two methods which aim to enhance the representation of style codes and alleviate 3D inconsistencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-3d-face-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invariant Anomaly Detection under Distribution Shifts: A Causal Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-anomaly-detection-under-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, by leveraging tools from causal inference we attempt to increase the resilience of anomaly detection models to different kinds of distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-anomaly-detection-under-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchoring Path for Inductive Relation Prediction in Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anchoring-path-for-inductive-relation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose Anchoring Path Sentence Transformer (APST) by introducing Anchoring Paths (APs) to alleviate the reliance of CPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anchoring-path-for-inductive-relation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive End-to-End Computer Vision Framework for Restoration and Recognition of Low-Quality Engineering Drawings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-end-to-end-computer-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing computer vision approaches for digitizing engineering drawings typically assume the input drawings have high quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-end-to-end-computer-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DriveLM: Driving with Graph Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivelm-driving-with-graph-visual-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experiments demonstrate that Graph VQA provides a simple, principled framework for reasoning about a driving scene, and DriveLM-Data provides a challenging benchmark for this task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivelm-driving-with-graph-visual-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhysRFANet: Physics-Guided Neural Network for Real-Time Prediction of Thermal Effect During Radiofrequency Ablation Treatment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physrfanet-physics-guided-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Radiofrequency ablation (RFA) is a widely used minimally invasive technique for ablating solid tumors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physrfanet-physics-guided-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
