<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 21:07:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>McUDI: Model-Centric Unsupervised Degradation Indicator for Failure Prediction AIOps Solutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcudi-model-centric-unsupervised-degradation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the continuous change in operational data, AIOps solutions suffer from performance degradation over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcudi-model-centric-unsupervised-degradation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Modular Approach to Automatic Cyber Threat Attribution using Opinion Pools</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modular-approach-to-automatic-cyber-threat</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An experimental validation suggests that the modular approach does not result in decreased performance and can even enhance precision and recall compared to monolithic alternatives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modular-approach-to-automatic-cyber-threat</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MambaMorph: a Mamba-based Backbone with Contrastive Feature Learning for Deformable MR-CT Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambamorph-a-mamba-based-backbone-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deformable image registration is an essential approach for medical image analysis. This paper introduces MambaMorph, an innovative multi-modality deformable registration network, specifically designed for Magnetic Resonance (MR) and Computed Tomography (CT) image alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambamorph-a-mamba-based-backbone-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Pseudo-labelling and Enhancing Robustness for Semi-Supervised Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-pseudo-labelling-and-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key challenge, faced by the best-performing SSL-based SSDG methods, is selecting accurate pseudo-labels under multiple domain shifts and reducing overfitting to source domains under limited labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-pseudo-labelling-and-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Double Trouble? Impact and Detection of Duplicates in Face Image Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/double-trouble-impact-and-detection-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additional steps based on face recognition and face image quality assessment models reduce false positives, and facilitate the deduplication of the face images both for intra- and inter-subject duplicate sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/double-trouble-impact-and-detection-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Extensible Framework for Open Heterogeneous Collaborative Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-extensible-framework-for-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a new open heterogeneous problem: how to accommodate continually emerging new heterogeneous agent types into collaborative perception, while ensuring high perception performance and low integration cost?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-extensible-framework-for-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BayesPrompt: Prompting Large-Scale Pre-Trained Language Models on Few-shot Inference via Debiased Domain Abstraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesprompt-prompting-large-scale-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From the perspective of distribution analyses, we disclose that the intrinsic issues behind the phenomenon are the over-multitudinous conceptual knowledge contained in PLMs and the abridged knowledge for target downstream domains, which jointly result in that PLMs mis-locate the knowledge distributions corresponding to the target domains in the universal knowledge embedding space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesprompt-prompting-large-scale-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smooth Ranking SVM via Cutting-Plane Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smooth-ranking-svm-via-cutting-plane-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The most popular classification algorithms are designed to maximize classification accuracy during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smooth-ranking-svm-via-cutting-plane-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimation of partially known Gaussian graphical models with score-based structural priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimation-of-partially-known-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel algorithm for the support estimation of partially known Gaussian graphical models that incorporates prior information about the underlying graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimation-of-partially-known-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inconsistency Masks: Removing the Uncertainty from Input-Pseudo-Label Pairs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inconsistency-masks-removing-the-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By integrating IM with other methods, we demonstrate remarkable binary segmentation performance on the ISIC 2018 dataset, starting with just 10% labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inconsistency-masks-removing-the-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIFI: MultI-camera Feature Integration for Roust 3D Distracted Driver Activity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mifi-multi-camera-feature-integration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Distracted driver activity recognition plays a critical role in risk aversion-particularly beneficial in intelligent transportation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mifi-multi-camera-feature-integration-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConstraintChecker: A Plugin for Large Language Models to Reason on Commonsense Knowledge Bases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constraintchecker-a-plugin-for-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When considering a new knowledge instance, ConstraintChecker employs a rule-based module to produce a list of constraints, then it uses a zero-shot learning module to check whether this knowledge instance satisfies all constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constraintchecker-a-plugin-for-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Manipulate Artistic Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-manipulate-artistic-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancement in computer vision has significantly lowered the barriers to artistic creation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-manipulate-artistic-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Pathway: Improve Transformers with Irrelevant Data from Other Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-pathway-improve-transformers-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose to improve transformers of a specific modality with irrelevant data from other modalities, e. g., improve an ImageNet model with audio or point cloud datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-pathway-improve-transformers-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProCNS: Progressive Prototype Calibration and Noise Suppression for Weakly-Supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procns-progressive-prototype-calibration-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly-supervised segmentation (WSS) has emerged as a solution to mitigate the conflict between annotation cost and model performance by adopting sparse annotation formats (e. g., point, scribble, block, etc.).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procns-progressive-prototype-calibration-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Multi-task Anti-Noise Learning and Distilling Frameworks for Fine-grained Vehicle Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-multi-task-anti-noise-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The PMAL framework achieves high recognition accuracy by treating image denoising as an additional task in image recognition and progressively forcing a model to learn noise invariance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-multi-task-anti-noise-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter-Efficient Conversational Recommender System as a Language Processing Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-conversational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational recommender systems (CRS) aim to recommend relevant items to users by eliciting user preference through natural language conversation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-conversational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleviating Structural Distribution Shift in Graph Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alleviating-structural-distribution-shift-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph anomaly detection (GAD) is a challenging binary classification problem due to its different structural distribution between anomalies and normal nodes -- abnormal nodes are a minority, therefore holding high heterophily and low homophily compared to normal nodes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alleviating-structural-distribution-shift-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Natural Language Capability of Code Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-natural-language-capability-of-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Code large language models (Code LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable performance in code generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-natural-language-capability-of-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CreativeSynth: Creative Blending and Synthesis of Visual Arts based on Multimodal Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creativesynth-creative-blending-and-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale text-to-image generative models have made impressive strides, showcasing their ability to synthesize a vast array of high-quality images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creativesynth-creative-blending-and-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Long-Term Time-Series Forecasting via Meta Transformer Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-long-term-time-series-forecasting-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A slow learner tailors suitable representations to fast learners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-long-term-time-series-forecasting-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pix2gestalt: Amodal Segmentation by Synthesizing Wholes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pix2gestalt-amodal-segmentation-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce pix2gestalt, a framework for zero-shot amodal segmentation, which learns to estimate the shape and appearance of whole objects that are only partially visible behind occlusions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pix2gestalt-amodal-segmentation-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Domain Few-Shot Learning via Adaptive Transformer Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-few-shot-learning-via-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most few-shot learning works rely on the same domain assumption between the base and the target tasks, hindering their practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-few-shot-learning-via-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leeroo Orchestrator: Elevating LLMs Performance Through Model Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leeroo-orchestrator-elevating-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an architecture to harness the collective knowledge of multiple trained LLMs to create a new state-of-the-art.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leeroo-orchestrator-elevating-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy-Based Concept Bottleneck Models: Unifying Prediction, Concept Intervention, and Conditional Interpretations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-based-concept-bottleneck-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our ECBMs address both limitations of existing CBMs, providing higher accuracy and richer concept interpretations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-based-concept-bottleneck-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUMP: A joint multimodal registration pipeline for neuroimaging with minimal preprocessing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jump-a-joint-multimodal-registration-pipeline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a pipeline for unbiased and robust multimodal registration of neuroimaging modalities with minimal pre-processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jump-a-joint-multimodal-registration-pipeline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unitxt: Flexible, Shareable and Reusable Data Preparation and Evaluation for Generative AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitxt-flexible-shareable-and-reusable-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the dynamic landscape of generative NLP, traditional text processing pipelines limit research flexibility and reproducibility, as they are tailored to specific dataset, task, and model combinations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitxt-flexible-shareable-and-reusable-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation of Fractional Brownian Motion and Related Stochastic Processes in Practice: A Straightforward Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-of-fractional-brownian-motion-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fractional Brownian motion, with its long-time correlated increments, has been applied in many fields in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-of-fractional-brownian-motion-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Independent Dynamic Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-independent-dynamic-programming-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We experimentally compare our DIDP solvers with commercial MIP and CP solvers (solving MIP and CP models, respectively) on common benchmark instances of eleven combinatorial optimization problem classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-independent-dynamic-programming-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Producing Plankton Classifiers that are Robust to Dataset Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/producing-plankton-classifiers-that-are</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, a MobileNet with a 92% nominal test accuracy shows a 77% OOD accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/producing-plankton-classifiers-that-are</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Range-Agnostic Multi-View Depth Estimation With Keyframe Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/range-agnostic-multi-view-depth-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods for 3D reconstruction from posed frames require prior knowledge about the scene metric range, usually to recover matching cues along the epipolar lines and narrow the search range.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/range-agnostic-multi-view-depth-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modular Adaptation of Multilingual Encoders to Written Swiss German Dialect</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modular-adaptation-of-multilingual-encoders</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Creating neural text encoders for written Swiss German is challenging due to a dearth of training data combined with dialectal variation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modular-adaptation-of-multilingual-encoders</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Analysis of Noise Reduction Methods in Sentiment Analysis on Noisy Bengali Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-analysis-of-noise-reduction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a dataset (NC-SentNoB) that we annotated manually to identify ten different types of noise found in a pre-existing sentiment analysis dataset comprising of around 15K noisy Bengali texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-analysis-of-noise-reduction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>True Knowledge Comes from Practice: Aligning LLMs with Embodied Environments via Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/true-knowledge-comes-from-practice-aligning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the impressive performance across numerous tasks, large language models (LLMs) often fail in solving simple decision-making tasks due to the misalignment of the knowledge in LLMs with environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/true-knowledge-comes-from-practice-aligning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Cost-Sensitive Meta-Learning Strategy for Fair Provider Exposure in Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cost-sensitive-meta-learning-strategy-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When devising recommendation services, it is important to account for the interests of all content providers, encompassing not only newcomers but also minority demographic groups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cost-sensitive-meta-learning-strategy-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QAGait: Revisit Gait Recognition from a Quality Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qagait-revisit-gait-recognition-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gait recognition is a promising biometric method that aims to identify pedestrians from their unique walking patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qagait-revisit-gait-recognition-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFMatch: Aligning Automated Answer Equivalence Evaluation with Expert Judgments For Open-Domain Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfmatch-aligning-automated-answer-equivalence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Question answering (QA) can only make progress if we know if an answer is correct, but for many of the most challenging and interesting QA examples, current evaluation metrics to determine answer equivalence (AE) often do not align with human judgments, particularly more verbose, free-form answers from large language models (LLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfmatch-aligning-automated-answer-equivalence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentBoard: An Analytical Evaluation Board of Multi-turn LLM Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentboard-an-analytical-evaluation-board-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating large language models (LLMs) as general-purpose agents is essential for understanding their capabilities and facilitating their integration into practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentboard-an-analytical-evaluation-board-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Explainable Harmful Meme Detection through Multimodal Debate between Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explainable-harmful-meme-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then we propose to fine-tune a small language model as the debate judge for harmfulness inference, to facilitate multimodal fusion between the harmfulness rationales and the intrinsic multimodal information within memes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explainable-harmful-meme-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robustness in Fairness against Edge-level Perturbations in GNN-based Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-in-fairness-against-edge-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efforts in the recommendation community are shifting from the sole emphasis on utility to considering beyond-utility factors, such as fairness and robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-in-fairness-against-edge-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning Model Reuse in the HuggingFace Community: Challenges, Benefit and Trends</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-model-reuse-in-the-huggingface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our qualitative analysis, we present a taxonomy of the challenges and benefits associated with PTM reuse within this community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-model-reuse-in-the-huggingface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpeechGPT-Gen: Scaling Chain-of-Information Speech Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechgpt-gen-scaling-chain-of-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It comprises an autoregressive model based on LLM for semantic information modeling and a non-autoregressive model employing flow matching for perceptual information modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechgpt-gen-scaling-chain-of-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Synthetic Health Sensor Data for Privacy-Preserving Wearable Stress Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-synthetic-health-sensor-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Smartwatch health sensor data is increasingly utilized in smart health applications and patient monitoring, including stress detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-synthetic-health-sensor-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Definitive Guide to Policy Gradients in Deep Reinforcement Learning: Theory, Algorithms and Implementations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-definitive-guide-to-policy-gradients-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, various powerful policy gradient algorithms have been proposed in deep reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-definitive-guide-to-policy-gradients-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can GPT-3.5 Generate and Code Discharge Summaries?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-gpt-3-5-generate-and-code-discharge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural coding models were trained on baseline and augmented data and evaluated on a MIMIC-IV test set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-gpt-3-5-generate-and-code-discharge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Forget Clients in Federated Online Learning to Rank?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-forget-clients-in-federated-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a FOLTR system, a ranker is learned by aggregating local updates to the global ranking model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-forget-clients-in-federated-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructDoc: A Dataset for Zero-Shot Generalization of Visual Document Understanding with Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructdoc-a-dataset-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of completing various visual document understanding (VDU) tasks, e. g., question answering and information extraction, on real-world documents through human-written instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructdoc-a-dataset-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debiased Sample Selection for Combating Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiased-sample-selection-for-combating-noisy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose a noIse-Tolerant Expert Model (ITEM) for debiased learning in sample selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiased-sample-selection-for-combating-noisy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compositional Generative Inverse Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-generative-inverse-design</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an N-body interaction task and a challenging 2D multi-airfoil design task, we demonstrate that by composing the learned diffusion model at test time, our method allows us to design initial states and boundary shapes that are more complex than those in the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-generative-inverse-design</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatterBox: Multi-round Multimodal Referring and Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatterbox-multi-round-multimodal-referring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we establish a baseline for a new task named multimodal multi-round referring and grounding (MRG), opening up a promising direction for instance-level multimodal dialogues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatterbox-multi-round-multimodal-referring</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
