<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 09:12:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>On the Relation between Sharpness-Aware Minimization and Adversarial Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-relation-between-sharpness-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel understanding of Sharpness-Aware Minimization (SAM) in the context of adversarial robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-relation-between-sharpness-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling Script Knowledge from Large Language Models for Constrained Language Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-script-knowledge-from-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In everyday life, humans often plan their actions by following step-by-step instructions in the form of goal-oriented scripts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-script-knowledge-from-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Rule-based LTLf Process Specifications: A Probabilistic Data-driven Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-rule-based-ltlf-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a mining context, these specifications are inferred from, and checked on, multi-sets of runs recorded by information systems (namely, event logs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-rule-based-ltlf-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DietCNN: Multiplication-free Inference for Quantized CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dietcnn-multiplication-free-inference-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rising demand for networked embedded systems with machine intelligence has been a catalyst for sustained attempts by the research community to implement Convolutional Neural Networks (CNN) based inferencing on embedded resource-limited devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dietcnn-multiplication-free-inference-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Generative AI Models for Synthetic Data Generation in Healthcare: Balancing Research and Privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-generative-ai-models-for-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The widespread adoption of electronic health records and digital healthcare data has created a demand for data-driven insights to enhance patient outcomes, diagnostics, and treatments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-generative-ai-models-for-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TPS++: Attention-Enhanced Thin-Plate Spline for Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tps-attention-enhanced-thin-plate-spline-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce TPS++, an attention-enhanced TPS transformation that incorporates the attention mechanism to text rectification for the first time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tps-attention-enhanced-thin-plate-spline-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Good Intentions: Reporting the Research Landscape of NLP for Social Good</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-good-intentions-reporting-the-research</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using state-of-the-art NLP models, we address each of these tasks and use them on the entire ACL Anthology, resulting in a visualization workspace that gives researchers a comprehensive overview of the field of NLP4SG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-good-intentions-reporting-the-research</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models Need Holistically Thought in Medical Conversational QA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-need-holistically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The medical conversational question answering (CQA) system aims at providing a series of professional medical services to improve the efficiency of medical care.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-need-holistically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detection of depression on social networks using transformers and ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-of-depression-on-social-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the impact of technology on our lives is increasing, we witness increased use of social media that became an essential tool not only for communication but also for sharing information with community about our thoughts and feelings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-of-depression-on-social-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC3DCD: unsupervised learning for multiclass 3D point cloud change detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dc3dcd-unsupervised-learning-for-multiclass</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an unsupervised method, called DeepCluster 3D Change Detection (DC3DCD), to detect and categorize multiclass changes at point level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dc3dcd-unsupervised-learning-for-multiclass</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PET-NeuS: Positional Encoding Tri-Planes for Neural Surfaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pet-neus-positional-encoding-tri-planes-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first component is to borrow the tri-plane representation from EG3D and represent signed distance fields as a mixture of tri-planes and MLPs instead of representing it with MLPs only.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pet-neus-positional-encoding-tri-planes-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMIL: Context-Aware Multiple Instance Learning for Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camil-context-aware-multiple-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly supervised approaches often use image subsections or tiles as input, with the overall classification of the WSI based on attention scores assigned to each tile.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camil-context-aware-multiple-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Mountain-Shaped Single-Stage Network for Accurate Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mountain-shaped-single-stage-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image restoration is the task of aiming to obtain a high-quality image from a corrupt input image, such as deblurring and deraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mountain-shaped-single-stage-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Pseudo Image Captions for Multimodal Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-pseudo-image-captions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-modal contrastive learning in vision language pretraining (VLP) faces the challenge of (partial) false negatives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-pseudo-image-captions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dialogue Planning via Brownian Bridge Stochastic Process for Goal-directed Proactive Dialogue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialogue-planning-via-brownian-bridge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key to achieving this task lies in planning dialogue paths that smoothly and coherently direct conversations towards the target.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialogue-planning-via-brownian-bridge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Building the Federated GPT: Federated Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-building-the-federated-gpt-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This repository offers a foundational framework for exploring federated fine-tuning of LLMs using heterogeneous instructions across diverse categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-building-the-federated-gpt-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eiffel Tower: A Deep-Sea Underwater Dataset for Long-Term Visual Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eiffel-tower-a-deep-sea-underwater-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new deep-sea dataset to benchmark underwater long-term visual localization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eiffel-tower-a-deep-sea-underwater-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architectural Vision for Quantum Computing in the Edge-Cloud Continuum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/architectural-vision-for-quantum-computing-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discuss the necessity, challenges, and solution approaches for extending existing work on classical edge computing to integrate QPUs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/architectural-vision-for-quantum-computing-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Granularity Denoising and Bidirectional Alignment for Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-denoising-and-bidirectional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly supervised semantic segmentation (WSSS) models relying on class activation maps (CAMs) have achieved desirable performance comparing to the non-CAMs-based counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-denoising-and-bidirectional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedNoRo: Towards Noise-Robust Federated Learning by Addressing Class Imbalance and Label Noise Heterogeneity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fednoro-towards-noise-robust-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated noisy label learning (FNLL) is emerging as a promising tool for privacy-preserving multi-source decentralized learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fednoro-towards-noise-robust-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E2TIMT: Efficient and Effective Modal Adapter for Text Image Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e2timt-efficient-and-effective-modal-adapter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the ablation studies verify the generalization of our method, where the proposed modal adapter is effective to bridge various OCR and MT models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e2timt-efficient-and-effective-modal-adapter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLA: Contextualized Commonsense Causal Reasoning from the Causal Inference Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cola-contextualized-commonsense-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a new task to detect commonsense causation between two events in an event sequence (i. e., context), called contextualized commonsense causal reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cola-contextualized-commonsense-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplicial Hopfield networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplicial-hopfield-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hopfield networks are artificial neural networks which store memory patterns on the states of their neurons by choosing recurrent connection weights and update rules such that the energy landscape of the network forms attractors around the memories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplicial-hopfield-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimal Learning Machine for Multi-Label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimal-learning-machine-for-multi-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Distance-based supervised method, the minimal learning machine, constructs a predictive model from data by learning a mapping between input and output distance matrices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimal-learning-machine-for-multi-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShapeCoder: Discovering Abstractions for Visual Programs from Unstructured Primitives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapecoder-discovering-abstractions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The discovered abstractions capture common patterns (both structural and parametric) across the dataset, so that programs rewritten with these abstractions are more compact, and expose fewer degrees of freedom.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapecoder-discovering-abstractions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Representation Learning for Person or Entity-centric Knowledge Graphs: an application in Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-learning-for-person-or-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[KGs are used to discover diagnoses or prioritize genes relevant to disease, but they often rely on schemas that are not centred around a node or entity of interest, such as a person.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-learning-for-person-or-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ImageBind: One Embedding Space To Bind Them All</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagebind-one-embedding-space-to-bind-them</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that all combinations of paired data are not necessary to train such a joint embedding, and only image-paired data is sufficient to bind the modalities together.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagebind-one-embedding-space-to-bind-them</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSVQ: Self-Supervised Learning with Multiple Sample Views and Queues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msvq-self-supervised-learning-with-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Let the student mimic the similar relationship between the samples, thus giving the student a more flexible ability to identify false negative samples in the dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msvq-self-supervised-learning-with-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributional Multi-Objective Decision Making</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-multi-objective-decision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For effective decision support in scenarios with conflicting objectives, sets of potentially optimal solutions can be presented to the decision maker.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-multi-objective-decision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linguistic More: Taking a Further Step toward Efficient and Accurate Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linguistic-more-taking-a-further-step-toward</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision model have gained increasing attention due to their simplicity and efficiency in Scene Text Recognition (STR) task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linguistic-more-taking-a-further-step-toward</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised dense representation learning for live-cell microscopy with time arrow prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-dense-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we present a self-supervised method based on time arrow prediction pre-training that learns dense image representations from raw, unlabeled live-cell microscopy videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-dense-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the Corruption Robustness of Image Classifiers with Random Lp-norm Corruptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-corruption-robustness-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the fields of adversarial robustness and formal robustness verification of image classification models, robustness is commonly defined as the stability to all input variations within an Lp-norm distance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-corruption-robustness-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Forecasting on New Roads Unseen in the Training Data Using Spatial Contrastive Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-forecasting-on-new-roads-unseen-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During inference, the spatial encoder only requires two days of traffic data on the new roads and does not require any re-training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-forecasting-on-new-roads-unseen-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Holistic and Local Information to Estimate Emotional Reaction Intensity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-holistic-and-local-information-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We handle variable video length with a regression token that accumulates information from all frames into a fixed-dimensional vector independent of video length.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-holistic-and-local-information-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Implicit Feedback-Based Recommendation through Multi-Behavior Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-implicit-feedback-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommender systems that learn from implicit feedback often use large volumes of a single type of implicit user feedback, such as clicks, to enhance the prediction of sparse target behavior such as purchases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-implicit-feedback-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flexible Job Shop Scheduling via Dual Attention Network Based Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-job-shop-scheduling-via-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The complex relationships between operations and machines are represented precisely and concisely, for which a dual-attention network (DAN) comprising several interconnected operation message attention blocks and machine message attention blocks is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-job-shop-scheduling-via-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popularity Debiasing from Exposure to Interaction in Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/popularity-debiasing-from-exposure-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new criterion for popularity debiasing, i. e., in an unbiased recommender system, both popular and unpopular items should receive Interactions Proportional to the number of users who Like it, namely IPL criterion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/popularity-debiasing-from-exposure-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternChat: Solving Vision-Centric Tasks by Interacting with Chatbots Beyond Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internchat-solving-vision-centric-tasks-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from existing interactive systems that rely on pure language, by incorporating pointing instructions, the proposed iChat significantly improves the efficiency of communication between users and chatbots, as well as the accuracy of chatbots in vision-centric tasks, especially in complicated visual scenarios where the number of objects is greater than 2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internchat-solving-vision-centric-tasks-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time instance segmentation with polygons using an Intersection-over-Union loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-instance-segmentation-with-polygons</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we improve over CenterPoly by enhancing the classical regression L1 loss with a novel region-based loss and a novel order loss, as well as with a new training process for the vertices prediction head.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-instance-segmentation-with-polygons</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recursions Are All You Need: Towards Efficient Deep Unfolding Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recursions-are-all-you-need-towards-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, we randomize the number of recursions during training to decrease the overall training time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recursions-are-all-you-need-towards-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style-A-Video: Agile Diffusion for Arbitrary Text-based Video Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/style-a-video-agile-diffusion-for-arbitrary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale text-to-video diffusion models have demonstrated an exceptional ability to synthesize diverse videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/style-a-video-agile-diffusion-for-arbitrary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Energy System Scheduling Using A Constraint-Aware Reinforcement Learning Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-energy-system-scheduling-using-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this, in this paper, a DRL algorithm (namely MIP-DQN) is proposed, capable of \textit{strictly} enforcing all operational constraints in the action space, ensuring the feasibility of the defined schedule in real-time operation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-energy-system-scheduling-using-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiModal-GPT: A Vision and Language Model for Dialogue with Humans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-gpt-a-vision-and-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further enhance the ability to chat with humans of the MultiModal-GPT, we utilize language-only instruction-following data to train the MultiModal-GPT jointly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-gpt-a-vision-and-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSGCL: Community-Strength-Enhanced Graph Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csgcl-community-strength-enhanced-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Contrastive Learning (GCL) is an effective way to learn generalized graph representations in a self-supervised manner, and has grown rapidly in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csgcl-community-strength-enhanced-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HistAlign: Improving Context Dependency in Language Generation by Aligning with History</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histalign-improving-context-dependency-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cache-LMs, which augment LMs with a memory of recent history, can increase context dependency and have shown remarkable performance in diverse language generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histalign-improving-context-dependency-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompted LLMs as Chatbot Modules for Long Open-domain Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompted-llms-as-chatbot-modules-for-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose MPC (Modular Prompted Chatbot), a new approach for creating high-quality conversational agents without the need for fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompted-llms-as-chatbot-modules-for-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Autoregressive Math Word Problem Solver with Unified Tree Structure</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-autoregressive-math-word-problem-solver</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the second issue, to handle the variants in evaluation, we propose to match the unified tree and design a path-based metric to evaluate the partial accuracy of expression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-autoregressive-math-word-problem-solver</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pedestrian Behavior Maps for Safety Advisories: CHAMP Framework and Real-World Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pedestrian-behavior-maps-for-safety</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is critical for vehicles to prevent any collisions with pedestrians.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pedestrian-behavior-maps-for-safety</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Masked Autoencoder for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-masked-autoencoder-for-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While some powerful neural network architectures (e. g., Transformer, Graph Neural Networks) have achieved improved performance in sequential recommendation with high-order item dependency modeling, they may suffer from poor representation capability in label scarcity scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-masked-autoencoder-for-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnomalyBERT: Self-Supervised Transformer for Time Series Anomaly Detection using Data Degradation Scheme</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalybert-self-supervised-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mechanical defects in real situations affect observation values and cause abnormalities in multivariate time series, such as sensor values or network data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalybert-self-supervised-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
