<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 09:15:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Online Game Level Generation from Music</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-game-level-generation-from-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Game consists of multiple types of content, while the harmony of different content types play an essential role in game design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-game-level-generation-from-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HelixFold: An Efficient Implementation of AlphaFold2 using PaddlePaddle</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helixfold-an-efficient-implementation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the complex model architecture and large memory consumption, it requires lots of computational resources and time to implement the training and inference of AlphaFold2 from scratch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helixfold-an-efficient-implementation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DGPO: Discovering Multiple Strategies with Diversity-Guided Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgpo-discovering-multiple-strategies-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent algorithms designed for reinforcement learning tasks focus on finding a single optimal solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgpo-discovering-multiple-strategies-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Behavior Hypergraph-Enhanced Transformer for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-behavior-hypergraph-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further ablation studies validate the effectiveness of our model design and benefits of the new MBHT framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-behavior-hypergraph-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniNet: Unified Architecture Search with Convolution, Transformer, and MLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uninet-unified-architecture-search-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we integrate configurable operators and DSMs into a unified search space and search with a Reinforcement Learning-based search algorithm to fully explore the optimal combination of the operators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uninet-unified-architecture-search-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency Domain Model Augmentation for Adversarial Attack</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-domain-model-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we apply a spectrum transformation to the input and thus perform the model augmentation in the frequency domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-domain-model-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modality-Aware Contrastive Instance Learning with Self-Distillation for Weakly-Supervised Audio-Visual Violence Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modality-aware-contrastive-instance-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we analyze the modality asynchrony and undifferentiated instances phenomena of the multiple instance learning (MIL) procedure, and further investigate its negative impact on weakly-supervised audio-visual learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modality-aware-contrastive-instance-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCPL: Contrastive Coherence Preserving Loss for Versatile Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccpl-contrastive-coherence-preserving-loss</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CCPL can preserve the coherence of the content source during style transfer without degrading stylization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccpl-contrastive-coherence-preserving-loss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradual Domain Adaptation without Indexed Intermediate Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradual-domain-adaptation-without-indexed-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This coarse domain sequence then undergoes a fine indexing step via a novel cycle-consistency loss, which encourages the next intermediate domain to preserve sufficient discriminative knowledge of the current intermediate domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradual-domain-adaptation-without-indexed-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Language Left Behind: Scaling Human-Centered Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-language-left-behind-scaling-human-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driven by the goal of eradicating language barriers on a global scale, machine translation has solidified itself as a key focus of artificial intelligence research today.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-language-left-behind-scaling-human-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cosmic Graph: Optimal Information Extraction from Large-Scale Structure using Catalogues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-cosmic-graph-optimal-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We a) demonstrate the high sensitivity of modular graph structure to the underlying cosmology in the noise-free limit, b) show that networks automatically combine mass and clustering information through comparisons to traditional statistics, c) demonstrate that graph neural networks can still extract information when catalogues are subject to noisy survey cuts, and d) illustrate how nonlinear IMNN summaries can be used as asymptotically optimal compressed statistics for Bayesian implicit likelihood inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-cosmic-graph-optimal-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio-Visual Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-visual-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To deal with the AVS problem, we propose a novel method that uses a temporal pixel-wise audio-visual interaction module to inject audio semantics as guidance for the visual segmentation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-visual-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Robust is your Fair Model? Exploring the Robustness of Diverse Fairness Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-robust-is-your-fair-model-exploring-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies have shown that robustness (the ability for a model to perform well on unseen data) plays a significant role in the type of strategy that should be used when approaching a new problem and, hence, measuring the robustness of these strategies has become a fundamental problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-robust-is-your-fair-model-exploring-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing Ranking and Effectiveness of Evolutionary Algorithm Hyperparameters Using Global Sensitivity Analysis Methodologies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-ranking-and-effectiveness-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a comprehensive global sensitivity analysis of two single-objective and two multi-objective state-of-the-art global optimization evolutionary algorithms as an algorithm configuration problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-ranking-and-effectiveness-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intra-Modal Constraint Loss For Image-Text Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intra-modal-constraint-loss-for-image-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-modal retrieval has drawn much attention in both computer vision and natural language processing domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intra-modal-constraint-loss-for-image-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Scale-Aware, Robust, and Generalizable Unsupervised Monocular Depth Estimation by Integrating IMU Motion Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-scale-aware-robust-and-generalizable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised monocular depth and ego-motion estimation has drawn extensive research attention in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-scale-aware-robust-and-generalizable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embedding Recycling for Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embedding-recycling-for-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training and inference with large neural models is expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embedding-recycling-for-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slot Filling for Extracting Reskilling and Upskilling Options from the Web</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slot-filling-for-extracting-reskilling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Disturbances in the job market such as advances in science and technology, crisis and increased competition have triggered a surge in reskilling and upskilling programs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slot-filling-for-extracting-reskilling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMS: An Annotated Corpus for Causal Analysis of Mental Health Issues in Social Media Posts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cams-an-annotated-corpus-for-causal-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new dataset for Causal Analysis of Mental health issues in Social media posts (CAMS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cams-an-annotated-corpus-for-causal-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Multi-objective Optimization: Comparative Study of the State-of-the-Art</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-multi-objective-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal multi-objective problems (MMOPs) commonly arise in real-world problems where distant solutions in decision space correspond to very similar objective values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-multi-objective-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance Shadow Detection with A Single-Stage Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-shadow-detection-with-a-single-stage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper formulates a new problem, instance shadow detection, which aims to detect shadow instance and the associated object instance that cast each shadow in the input image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-shadow-detection-with-a-single-stage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Federated Cox Model with Non-Proportional Hazards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-federated-cox-model-with-non-proportional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research has shown the potential for neural networks to improve upon classical survival models such as the Cox model, which is widely used in clinical practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-federated-cox-model-with-non-proportional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Penalty Approach for Normalizing Feature Distributions to Build Confounder-Free Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-penalty-approach-for-normalizing-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we extend the MDN method by applying a Penalty approach (referred to as PDMN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-penalty-approach-for-normalizing-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-term Reproducibility for Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-term-reproducibility-for-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is a sad reflection of modern academia that code is often ignored after publication -- there is no academic 'kudos' for bug fixes / maintenance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-term-reproducibility-for-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Baselined Gated Attention Recurrent Network for Request Prediction in Ridesharing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-baselined-gated-attention-recurrent-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ridesharing has received global popularity due to its convenience and cost efficiency for both drivers and passengers and its strong potential to contribute to the implementation of the UN Sustainable Development Goals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-baselined-gated-attention-recurrent-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDFEst: Categorical Pose and Shape Estimation of Objects from RGB-D using Signed Distance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdfest-categorical-pose-and-shape-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rich geometric understanding of the world is an important component of many robotic applications such as planning and manipulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdfest-categorical-pose-and-shape-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Latent Structure for Multi-Modal Vehicle Trajectory Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-latent-structure-for-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that a similar problem, in which the generated trajectory is located between adjacent lanes, often arises in VAE-based trajectory forecasting models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-latent-structure-for-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Study Boosting: Theoretical Considerations for Merging vs. Ensembling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-study-boosting-theoretical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the regression setting, we provide theoretical guidelines based on an analytical transition point to determine whether it is more beneficial to merge or to ensemble for boosting with linear learners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-study-boosting-theoretical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSP-HDRI$+$: A Synthetic Dataset Generator for Pre-Training of Human-Centric Computer Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psp-hdri-a-synthetic-dataset-generator-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new synthetic data generator PSP-HDRI$+$ that proves to be a superior pre-training alternative to ImageNet and other large-scale synthetic data counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psp-hdri-a-synthetic-dataset-generator-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-vision-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dual-ViT is henceforth able to reduce the computational complexity without compromising much accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-vision-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wave-ViT: Unifying Wavelet and Transformers for Visual Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wave-vit-unifying-wavelet-and-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the wavelet theory, we construct a new Wavelet Vision Transformer (\textbf{Wave-ViT}) that formulates the invertible down-sampling with wavelet transforms and self-attention learning in a unified way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wave-vit-unifying-wavelet-and-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistency is the key to further mitigating catastrophic forgetting in continual learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-is-the-key-to-further-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we examine the role of consistency regularization in ER framework under various continual learning scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-is-the-key-to-further-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start Small, Think Big: On Hyperparameter Optimization for Large-Scale Knowledge Graph Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/start-small-think-big-on-hyperparameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge graph embedding (KGE) models are an effective and popular approach to represent and reason with multi-relational data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/start-small-think-big-on-hyperparameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCCF: Deep Comprehensible Color Filter Learning Framework for High-Resolution Image Harmonization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dccf-deep-comprehensible-color-filter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image color harmonization algorithm aims to automatically match the color distribution of foreground and background images captured in different conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dccf-deep-comprehensible-color-filter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TASKOGRAPHY: Evaluating robot task planning over large 3D scene graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskography-evaluating-robot-task-planning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D scene graphs (3DSGs) are an emerging description; unifying symbolic, topological, and metric scene representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskography-evaluating-robot-task-planning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-modal Prototype Driven Network for Radiology Report Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-prototype-driven-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Radiology report generation (RRG) aims to describe automatically a radiology image with human-like language and could potentially support the work of radiologists, reducing the burden of manual reporting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-prototype-driven-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COO: Comic Onomatopoeia Dataset for Recognizing Arbitrary or Truncated Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coo-comic-onomatopoeia-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To encourage research on this topic, we provide a novel comic onomatopoeia dataset (COO), which consists of onomatopoeia texts in Japanese comics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coo-comic-onomatopoeia-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Contextual Relationships for Cervical Abnormal Cell Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-contextual-relationships-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, both contextual relationships between cells and cell-to-global images are exploited to enhance features of each region of interest (RoI) proposals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-contextual-relationships-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A clinically motivated self-supervised approach for content-based image retrieval of CT liver images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-clinically-motivated-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address these limitations by (1) proposing a self-supervised learning framework that incorporates domain-knowledge into the training procedure and (2) providing the first representation learning explainability analysis in the context of CBIR of CT liver images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-clinically-motivated-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast-Vid2Vid: Spatial-Temporal Compression for Video-to-Video Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-vid2vid-spatial-temporal-compression-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a spatial-temporal compression framework, \textbf{Fast-Vid2Vid}, which focuses on data aspects of generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-vid2vid-spatial-temporal-compression-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Functional Generalized Empirical Likelihood Estimation for Conditional Moment Restrictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/functional-generalized-empirical-likelihood</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Important problems in causal inference, economics, and, more generally, robust machine learning can be expressed as conditional moment restrictions, but estimation becomes challenging as it requires solving a continuum of unconditional moment restrictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/functional-generalized-empirical-likelihood</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalizing Federated Medical Image Segmentation via Local Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalizing-federated-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized FL tackles this issue by only utilizing partial model parameters shared from global server, while keeping the rest to adapt to its own data distribution in the local training of each site.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalizing-federated-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning Sequential Tasks on Contact Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planning-sequential-tasks-on-contact-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We devise a 3D scene graph representation, contact graph+ (cg+), for efficient sequential task planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planning-sequential-tasks-on-contact-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel students beget Nobel professors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nobel-students-beget-nobel-professors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is unclear whether the hierarchy in the economics profession is the result of the agglomeration of excellence or of nepotism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nobel-students-beget-nobel-professors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiomics-Guided Global-Local Transformer for Weakly Supervised Pathology Localization in Chest X-Rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radiomics-guided-global-local-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RGT consists of an image Transformer branch, a radiomics Transformer branch, and fusion layers that aggregate image and radiomic information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radiomics-guided-global-local-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2DPASS: 2D Priors Assisted Semantic Segmentation on LiDAR Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2dpass-2d-priors-assisted-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As camera and LiDAR sensors capture complementary information used in autonomous driving, great efforts have been made to develop semantic segmentation algorithms through multi-modality data fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2dpass-2d-priors-assisted-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual Persuasion Detection: Video Games as an Invaluable Data Source for NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-persuasion-detection-video-games</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Role-playing games (RPGs) have a considerable amount of text in video game dialogues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-persuasion-detection-video-games</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Detection of Papilledema in Pediatric Fundus Images with Explainable Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-detection-of-papilledema-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Papilledema is an ophthalmic neurologic disorder in which increased intracranial pressure leads to swelling of the optic nerves.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-detection-of-papilledema-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Pairwise Re-ranking with Pre-trained Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-pairwise-re-ranking-with-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pairwise re-ranking models predict which of two documents is more relevant to a query and then aggregate a final ranking from such preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-pairwise-re-ranking-with-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Proper Contrastive Self-supervised Learning Strategies For Music Audio Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-proper-contrastive-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The common research goal of self-supervised learning is to extract a general representation which an arbitrary downstream task would benefit from.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-proper-contrastive-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
