<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 21:06:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing detection of left bundle branch block by means of electrocardiogram’s signals using Machine Learning algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-detection-of-left-bundle-branch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LBBB is a cardiovascular disease that affects the heart’s electrical conduction system and may indicate the presence of underlying diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-detection-of-left-bundle-branch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Myopia: Learning from Positive and Unlabeled Data through Holistic Predictive Trends</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-myopia-learning-from-positive-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning binary classifiers from positive and unlabeled data (PUL) is vital in many real-world applications, especially when verifying negative examples is difficult.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-myopia-learning-from-positive-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Neuron Segmentation with Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-neuron-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By extracting semantic information from unlabeled data, self-supervised methods can improve the performance of downstream tasks, among which the mask image model (MIM) has been widely used due to its simplicity and effectiveness in recovering original information from masked images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-neuron-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Agent Tree Search Unifies Reasoning Acting and Planning in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-agent-tree-search-unifies-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated impressive performance on a range of decision-making tasks, they rely on simple acting processes and fall short of broad deployment as autonomous agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-agent-tree-search-unifies-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Graph Inference with Limited Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-graph-inference-with-limited</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We begin by defining the pivotal nodes as $k$-hop starved nodes, which can be identified based on a given adjacency matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-graph-inference-with-limited</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding, Predicting and Better Resolving Q-Value Divergence in Offline-RL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-predicting-and-better-resolving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first identify a fundamental pattern, self-excitation, as the primary cause of Q-value estimation divergence in offline RL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-predicting-and-better-resolving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saliency-Guided Hidden Associative Replay for Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saliency-guided-hidden-associative-replay-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual Learning is a burgeoning domain in next-generation AI, focusing on training neural networks over a sequence of tasks akin to human learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saliency-guided-hidden-associative-replay-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning with Fast and Forgetful Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-with-fast-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nearly all real world tasks are inherently partially observable, necessitating the use of memory in Reinforcement Learning (RL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-with-fast-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Aspect Extraction from Scientific Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-aspect-extraction-from-scientific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Being able to extract from scientific papers their main points, key insights, and other important information, referred to here as aspects, might facilitate the process of conducting a scientific literature review.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-aspect-extraction-from-scientific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asymptotically free sketched ridge ensembles: Risks, cross-validation, and tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymptotically-free-sketched-ridge-ensembles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose an "ensemble trick" whereby the risk for unsketched ridge regression can be efficiently estimated via GCV using small sketched ridge ensembles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymptotically-free-sketched-ridge-ensembles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dementia Assessment Using Mandarin Speech with an Attention-based Speech Recognition Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dementia-assessment-using-mandarin-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, we extracted the encoder from the speech recognition model and added a linear layer for dementia assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dementia-assessment-using-mandarin-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedConv: Enhancing Convolutional Neural Networks for Handling Data Heterogeneity in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedconv-enhancing-convolutional-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) is an emerging paradigm in machine learning, where a shared model is collaboratively learned using data from multiple devices to mitigate the risk of data leakage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedconv-enhancing-convolutional-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Degradation-Aware Self-Attention Based Transformer for Blind Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/degradation-aware-self-attention-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we integrate both CNN and Transformer components into the SR network, where we first use the CNN modulated by the degradation information to extract local features, and then employ the degradation-aware Transformer to extract global semantic features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/degradation-aware-self-attention-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Do We Need Weight Decay in Modern Deep Learning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-do-we-need-weight-decay-in-modern-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we highlight that the role of weight decay in modern deep learning is different from its regularization effect studied in classical learning theory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-do-we-need-weight-decay-in-modern-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Financial Sentiment Analysis via Retrieval Augmented Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-financial-sentiment-analysis-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Financial sentiment analysis is critical for valuation and investment decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-financial-sentiment-analysis-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Attribution Stability Indicator: a Measure for Time Series XAI Attributions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introducing-the-attribution-stability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the increasing amount and general complexity of time series data in domains such as finance, weather forecasting, and healthcare, there is a growing need for state-of-the-art performance models that can provide interpretable insights into underlying patterns and relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introducing-the-attribution-stability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Foundational Models for Molecular Learning on Large-Scale Multi-Task Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-foundational-models-for-molecular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, pre-trained foundation models have enabled significant advancements in multiple fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-foundational-models-for-molecular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whole Slide Multiple Instance Learning for Predicting Axillary Lymph Node Metastasis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whole-slide-multiple-instance-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Breast cancer is a major concern for women's health globally, with axillary lymph node (ALN) metastasis identification being critical for prognosis evaluation and treatment guidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whole-slide-multiple-instance-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aorta Segmentation from 3D CT in MICCAI SEG.A. 2023 Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aorta-segmentation-from-3d-ct-in-miccai-seg-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we describe our solution to the Segmentation of the Aorta (SEG. A. 231) from 3D CT challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aorta-segmentation-from-3d-ct-in-miccai-seg-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated 3D Segmentation of Kidneys and Tumors in MICCAI KiTS 2023 Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-3d-segmentation-of-kidneys-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Kidney and Kidney Tumor Segmentation Challenge (KiTS) 2023 offers a platform for researchers to compare their solutions to segmentation from 3D CT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-3d-segmentation-of-kidneys-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the Blink of an Eye: Event-based Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-the-blink-of-an-eye-event-based-emotion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, our method is the first eye-based emotion recognition method that leverages event-based cameras and spiking neural network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-the-blink-of-an-eye-event-based-emotion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Projection Learning and Tensor Decomposition Based Incomplete Multi-view Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-projection-learning-and-tensor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further consider the graph noise of projected data caused by missing samples and use a tensor-decomposition based graph filter for robust clustering. JPLTD decomposes the original tensor into an intrinsic tensor and a sparse tensor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-projection-learning-and-tensor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TiC: Exploring Vision Transformer in Convolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tic-exploring-vision-transformer-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While models derived from Vision Transformers (ViTs) have been phonemically surging, pre-trained models cannot seamlessly adapt to arbitrary resolution images without altering the architecture and configuration, such as sampling the positional encoding, limiting their flexibility for various vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tic-exploring-vision-transformer-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Camouflaged Object Detection: A Large-Scale Dataset and Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-camouflaged-object-detection-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide a comprehensive study on a new task called collaborative camouflaged object detection (CoCOD), which aims to simultaneously detect camouflaged objects with the same properties from a group of relevant images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-camouflaged-object-detection-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hermes: Unlocking Security Analysis of Cellular Network Protocols by Synthesizing Finite State Machines from Natural Language Specifications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hermes-unlocking-security-analysis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present Hermes, an end-to-end framework to automatically generate formal representations from natural language cellular specifications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hermes-unlocking-security-analysis-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Consistency Models: Synthesizing High-Resolution Images with Few-Step Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-consistency-models-synthesizing-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by Consistency Models (song et al.), we propose Latent Consistency Models (LCMs), enabling swift inference with minimal steps on any pre-trained LDMs, including Stable Diffusion (rombach et al).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-consistency-models-synthesizing-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bivariate Estimation-of-Distribution Algorithms Can Find an Exponential Number of Optima</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bivariate-estimation-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the bivariate EDA mutual-information-maximizing input clustering, without any problem-specific modification, quickly generates a model that behaves very similarly to a theoretically ideal model for EBOM, which samples each of the exponentially many optima with the same maximal probability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bivariate-estimation-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can pre-trained models assist in dataset distillation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-pre-trained-models-assist-in-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dataset Distillation (DD) is a prominent technique that encapsulates knowledge from a large-scale original dataset into a small synthetic dataset for efficient training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-pre-trained-models-assist-in-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Zero Level-Set Extraction from Unsigned Distance Fields Based on Double Covering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-zero-level-set-extraction-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the computed iso-surface is the boundary of the $r$-offset volume of the target zero level-set $S$, which is an orientable manifold, regardless of the topology of $S$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-zero-level-set-extraction-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-dimensional Bayesian Optimization with Group Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-bayesian-optimization-with-6</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a group testing approach to identify active variables to facilitate efficient optimization in these domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-bayesian-optimization-with-6</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSI: Enhancing the Robustness of 3D Point Cloud Recognition against Corruption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csi-enhancing-the-robustness-of-3d-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we harness the inherent set property of point cloud data to introduce a novel critical subset identification (CSI) method, aiming to bolster recognition robustness in the face of data corruption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csi-enhancing-the-robustness-of-3d-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plug-and-Play Posterior Sampling under Mismatched Measurement and Prior Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-posterior-sampling-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Posterior sampling has been shown to be a powerful Bayesian approach for solving imaging inverse problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-posterior-sampling-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FNOSeg3D: Resolution-Robust 3D Image Segmentation with Fourier Neural Operator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fnoseg3d-resolution-robust-3d-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the computational complexity of 3D medical image segmentation, training with downsampled images is a common remedy for out-of-memory errors in deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fnoseg3d-resolution-robust-3d-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeReg: Image-to-Point Cloud Registration Leveraging Pretrained Diffusion Models and Monocular Depth Estimators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freereg-image-to-point-cloud-registration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Matching cross-modality features between images and point clouds is a fundamental problem for image-to-point cloud registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freereg-image-to-point-cloud-registration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Functional data learning using convolutional neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/functional-data-learning-using-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show how convolutional neural networks (CNN) can be used in regression and classification learning problems of noisy and non-noisy functional data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/functional-data-learning-using-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LESSON: Learning to Integrate Exploration Strategies for Reinforcement Learning via an Option Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesson-learning-to-integrate-exploration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, a unified framework for exploration in reinforcement learning (RL) is proposed based on an option-critic model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesson-learning-to-integrate-exploration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of learning a flow-based generative model from limited sample complexity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-learning-a-flow-based-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of training a flow-based generative model, parametrized by a two-layer autoencoder, to sample from a high-dimensional Gaussian mixture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-learning-a-flow-based-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Long Way to Go: Investigating Length Correlations in RLHF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-long-way-to-go-investigating-length</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we find that even running RLHF with a reward based solely on length can reproduce most of the downstream improvements over the initial policy model, showing that reward models in these settings have a long way to go.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-long-way-to-go-investigating-length</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextualized Structural Self-supervised Learning for Ontology Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextualized-structural-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ontology matching (OM) entails the identification of semantic relationships between concepts within two or more knowledge graphs (KGs) and serves as a critical step in integrating KGs from various sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextualized-structural-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreshLLMs: Refreshing Large Language Models with Search Engine Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freshllms-refreshing-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce FreshQA, a novel dynamic QA benchmark encompassing a diverse range of question and answer types, including questions that require fast-changing world knowledge as well as questions with false premises that need to be debunked.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freshllms-refreshing-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provable benefits of annealing for estimating normalizing constants: Importance Sampling, Noise-Contrastive Estimation, and beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provable-benefits-of-annealing-for-estimating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we find that using the geometric path brings down the estimation error from an exponential to a polynomial function of the parameter distance between the target and proposal distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provable-benefits-of-annealing-for-estimating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certifiably Robust Graph Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certifiably-robust-graph-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on real-world datasets demonstrate the effectiveness of our proposed method in providing effective certifiable robustness and enhancing the robustness of any GCL model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certifiably-robust-graph-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kandinsky: an Improved Text-to-Image Synthesis with Image Prior and Latent Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kandinsky-an-improved-text-to-image-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image generation is a significant domain in modern computer vision and has achieved substantial improvements through the evolution of generative architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kandinsky-an-improved-text-to-image-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Text-to-Image Diffusion Models with Reward Backpropagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-text-to-image-diffusion-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to their unsupervised training, controlling their behavior in downstream tasks, such as maximizing human-perceived image quality, image-text alignment, or ethical image generation, is difficult.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-text-to-image-diffusion-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent Instructs Large Language Models to be General Zero-Shot Reasoners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-instructs-large-language-models-to-be</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For instance, our method boosts the performance of state-of-the-art large language models by a large margin, including Vicuna-13b (13. 3%), Llama-2-70b-chat (23. 2%), and GPT-3. 5 Turbo (17. 0%).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-instructs-large-language-models-to-be</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unbiased estimation of sampling variance for Simpson's diversity index</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-estimation-of-sampling-variance-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantification of measurement uncertainty is a cornerstone of scientific inquiry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-estimation-of-sampling-variance-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-Based Radiance Fields for Controllable Human Motion Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-based-radiance-fields-for-controllable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel controllable human motion synthesis method for fine-level deformation based on static point-based radiance fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-based-radiance-fields-for-controllable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RL-based Stateful Neural Adaptive Sampling and Denoising for Real-Time Path Tracing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-based-stateful-neural-adaptive-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monte-Carlo path tracing is a powerful technique for realistic image synthesis but suffers from high levels of noise at low sample counts, limiting its use in real-time applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-based-stateful-neural-adaptive-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characterizing the Features of Mitotic Figures Using a Conditional Diffusion Probabilistic Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-the-features-of-mitotic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, our goal is to shed light on the inherent uncertainty of mitosis labels and characterize the mitotic figure classification task in a human interpretable manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-the-features-of-mitotic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MathCoder: Seamless Code Integration in LLMs for Enhanced Mathematical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathcoder-seamless-code-integration-in-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a method to fine-tune open-source language models, enabling them to use code for modeling and deriving math equations and, consequently, enhancing their mathematical reasoning abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathcoder-seamless-code-integration-in-llms</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
