<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:12:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Vulnerable Nodes in Urban Infrastructure Interdependent Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-vulnerable-nodes-in-urban</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding and characterizing the vulnerability of urban infrastructures, which refers to the engineering facilities essential for the regular running of cities and that exist naturally in the form of networks, is of great value to us.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-vulnerable-nodes-in-urban</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch out Venomous Snake Species: A Solution to SnakeCLEF2023</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watch-out-venomous-snake-species-a-solution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The SnakeCLEF2023 competition aims to the development of advanced algorithms for snake species identification through the analysis of images and accompanying metadata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watch-out-venomous-snake-species-a-solution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DialogStudio: Towards Richest and Most Diverse Unified Dataset Collection for Conversational AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialogstudio-towards-richest-and-most-diverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite advancements in conversational AI, language models encounter challenges to handle diverse conversational tasks, and existing dialogue dataset collections often lack diversity and comprehensiveness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialogstudio-towards-richest-and-most-diverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Distribution Matching for Dataset Condensation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-distribution-matching-for-dataset-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel dataset condensation method based on distribution matching, which is more efficient and promising.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-distribution-matching-for-dataset-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISA: DIfferentiable Similarity Approximation for Universal Multimodal Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disa-differentiable-similarity-approximation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method is several orders of magnitude faster than local patch-based metrics and can be directly applied in clinical settings by replacing the similarity measure with the proposed one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disa-differentiable-similarity-approximation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSDM: Background Suppression Diffusion Model for Hyperspectral Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bsdm-background-suppression-diffusion-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel solution BSDM (background suppression diffusion model) for HAD, which can simultaneously learn latent background distributions and generalize to different datasets for suppressing complex background.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bsdm-background-suppression-diffusion-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longitudinal Data and a Semantic Similarity Reward for Chest X-Ray Report Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longitudinal-data-and-a-semantic-similarity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results indicate that longitudinal data improves CXR report generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longitudinal-data-and-a-semantic-similarity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FABRIC: Personalizing Diffusion Models with Iterative Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fabric-personalizing-diffusion-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an era where visual content generation is increasingly driven by machine learning, the integration of human feedback into generative models presents significant opportunities for enhancing user experience and output quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fabric-personalizing-diffusion-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Grained Multimodal Interaction Network for Entity Linking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-grained-multimodal-interaction-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, to derive the similarity matching score for each mention-entity pair, we device three interaction units to comprehensively explore the intra-modal interaction and inter-modal fusion among features of entities and mentions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-grained-multimodal-interaction-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RaTE: a Reproducible automatic Taxonomy Evaluation by Filling the Gap</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rate-a-reproducible-automatic-taxonomy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Taxonomies are an essential knowledge representation, yet most studies on automatic taxonomy construction (ATC) resort to manual evaluation to score proposed algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rate-a-reproducible-automatic-taxonomy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyTAG: Challenges and Opportunities for Reinforcement Learning in Tabletop Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytag-challenges-and-opportunities-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce PyTAG, a Python API for interacting with the Tabletop Games framework (TAG).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytag-challenges-and-opportunities-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Reliable Rare Category Analysis on Graphs via Individual Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-reliable-rare-category-analysis-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, to quantify the uncertainties in RCA, we develop a node-level uncertainty quantification algorithm to model the overlapping support regions with high uncertainty; to handle the rarity of minority classes in miscalibration calculation, we generalize the distribution-based calibration metric to the instance level and propose the first individual calibration measurement on graphs named Expected Individual Calibration Error (EICE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-reliable-rare-category-analysis-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Potential Based Rewards for Learning Humanoid Locomotion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-potential-based-rewards-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although several studies have explored the use of potential based reward shaping to accelerate learning convergence, most have been limited to grid-worlds and low-dimensional systems, and RL in robotics has predominantly relied on standard forms of reward shaping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-potential-based-rewards-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entropy regularization in probabilistic clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropy-regularization-in-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed estimator is equivalent to a post-processing procedure that reduces the number of sparsely-populated clusters and enhances interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropy-regularization-in-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Aware Dual Contrastive Learning for Multi-label Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-dual-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we leverage semantic-aware representation learning to extract category-related local discriminative features and construct category prototypes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-dual-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android in the Wild: A Large-Scale Dataset for Android Device Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/android-in-the-wild-a-large-scale-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dataset contains human demonstrations of device interactions, including the screens and actions, and corresponding natural language instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/android-in-the-wild-a-large-scale-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting Early with Meta Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-early-with-meta-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the early observation period of a time series, there might be only a few historic observations available to learn a model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-early-with-meta-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep unrolling Shrinkage Network for Dynamic MR imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-unrolling-shrinkage-network-for-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we put forward a novel deep unrolling shrinkage network (DUS-Net) by unrolling the alternating direction method of multipliers (ADMM) for optimizing the transformed $l_1$ norm dynamic MR reconstruction model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-unrolling-shrinkage-network-for-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Saner Deep Image Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-saner-deep-image-registration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we derive a set of theoretical guarantees for our sanity-checked image registration method, with experimental results supporting our theoretical findings and their effectiveness in increasing the sanity of models without sacrificing any performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-saner-deep-image-registration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Source-Free Domain Adaptation for Medical Image Segmentation via Prototype-Anchored Feature Alignment and Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/source-free-domain-adaptation-for-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle the source data-absent problem, we present a novel two-stage source-free domain adaptation (SFDA) framework for medical image segmentation, where only a well-trained source segmentation model and unlabeled target data are available during domain adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/source-free-domain-adaptation-for-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CValues: Measuring the Values of Chinese Large Language Models from Safety to Responsibility</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cvalues-measuring-the-values-of-chinese-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present CValues, the first Chinese human values evaluation benchmark to measure the alignment ability of LLMs in terms of both safety and responsibility criteria.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cvalues-measuring-the-values-of-chinese-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenKL: An Iterative Framework for Resolving Label Ambiguity and Label Non-conformity in Web Images Via a New Generalized KL Divergence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genkl-an-iterative-framework-for-resolving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle the limitation of entropy maximization, we propose $(\alpha, \beta)$-generalized KL divergence, $\mathcal{D}_{\text{KL}}^{\alpha, \beta}(p\|q)$, which can be used to identify significantly more NC instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genkl-an-iterative-framework-for-resolving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From West to East: Who can understand the music of the others better?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-west-to-east-who-can-understand-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This leads to research questions on whether these models can be used to learn representations for different music cultures and styles, or whether we can build similar music audio embedding models trained on data from different cultures or styles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-west-to-east-who-can-understand-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVA2023 Small Object Detection Challenge for Spotting Birds: Dataset, Methods, and Results</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mva2023-small-object-detection-challenge-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Small Object Detection (SOD) is an important machine vision topic because (i) a variety of real-world applications require object detection for distant objects and (ii) SOD is a challenging task due to the noisy, blurred, and less-informative image appearances of small objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mva2023-small-object-detection-challenge-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Machine Learning for Extraction of Theorems and Proofs in the Scientific Literature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-machine-learning-for-extraction-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, a simple CRF-based approach uses the features of the multimodal model along with information on block sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-machine-learning-for-extraction-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alioth: A Machine Learning Based Interference-Aware Performance Monitor for Multi-Tenancy Applications in Public Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alioth-a-machine-learning-based-interference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-tenancy in public clouds may lead to co-location interference on shared resources, which possibly results in performance degradation of cloud applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alioth-a-machine-learning-based-interference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Network Slicing Architectures with Machine Learning, Security, Sustainability and Experimental Networks Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-network-slicing-architectures-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Network Slicing (NS) is an essential technique extensively used in 5G networks computing strategies, mobile edge computing, mobile cloud computing, and verticals like the Internet of Vehicles and industrial IoT, among others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-network-slicing-architectures-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Llama 2: Open Foundation and Fine-Tuned Chat Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-2-open-foundation-and-fine-tuned-chat</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop and release Llama 2, a collection of pretrained and fine-tuned large language models (LLMs) ranging in scale from 7 billion to 70 billion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-2-open-foundation-and-fine-tuned-chat</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OnlineRefer: A Simple Online Baseline for Referring Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onlinerefer-a-simple-online-baseline-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Referring video object segmentation (RVOS) aims at segmenting an object in a video following human instruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onlinerefer-a-simple-online-baseline-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object-aware Gaze Target Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-aware-gaze-target-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gaze target detection aims to predict the image location where the person is looking and the probability that a gaze is out of the scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-aware-gaze-target-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Can Simple Arithmetic Operations Do for Temporal Modeling?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-can-simple-arithmetic-operations-do-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct comprehensive ablation studies on the instantiation of ATMs and demonstrate that this module provides powerful temporal modeling capability at a low computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-can-simple-arithmetic-operations-do-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedDefender: Client-Side Attack-Tolerant Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddefender-client-side-attack-tolerant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluations of real-world scenarios across multiple datasets show that the proposed method enhances the robustness of federated learning against model poisoning attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddefender-client-side-attack-tolerant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EigenTrajectory: Low-Rank Descriptors for Multi-Modal Trajectory Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigentrajectory-low-rank-descriptors-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present EigenTrajectory ($\mathbb{ET}$), a trajectory prediction approach that uses a novel trajectory descriptor to form a compact space, known here as $\mathbb{ET}$ space, in place of Euclidean space, for representing pedestrian movements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigentrajectory-low-rank-descriptors-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constraining Depth Map Geometry for Multi-View Stereo: A Dual-Depth Approach with Saddle-shaped Depth Cells</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constraining-depth-map-geometry-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning-based multi-view stereo (MVS) methods deal with predicting accurate depth maps to achieve an accurate and complete 3D representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constraining-depth-map-geometry-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluate Fine-tuning Strategies for Fetal Head Ultrasound Image Segmentation with U-Net</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluate-fine-tuning-strategies-for-fetal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method addresses the challenges associated with training a CNN network from scratch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluate-fine-tuning-strategies-for-fetal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel-wise Graph Attention Networks for Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixel-wise-graph-attention-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on these two modules, we consulted the ResNet and design a pixel-wise graph attention network (PGANet).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixel-wise-graph-attention-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a performance analysis on pre-trained Visual Question Answering models for autonomous driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-performance-analysis-on-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This short paper presents a preliminary analysis of three popular Visual Question Answering (VQA) models, namely ViLBERT, ViLT, and LXMERT, in the context of answering questions relating to driving scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-performance-analysis-on-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Region-Aware Neural Radiance Fields for High-Fidelity Talking Portrait Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-region-aware-neural-radiance-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents ER-NeRF, a novel conditional Neural Radiance Fields (NeRF) based architecture for talking portrait synthesis that can concurrently achieve fast convergence, real-time rendering, and state-of-the-art performance with small model size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-region-aware-neural-radiance-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overthinking the Truth: Understanding how Language Models Process False Demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overthinking-the-truth-understanding-how</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first phenomenon, overthinking, appears when we decode predictions from intermediate layers, given correct vs. incorrect few-shot demonstrations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overthinking-the-truth-understanding-how</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Select SAT Encodings for Pseudo-Boolean and Linear Integer Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-select-sat-encodings-for-pseudo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that it is possible to select encodings effectively using a standard set of features for constraint problems; however we obtain better performance with a new set of features specifically designed for the pseudo-Boolean and linear constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-select-sat-encodings-for-pseudo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Self-Supervised Thermal Water Segmentation for Aerial Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-self-supervised-thermal-water</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new method to adapt an RGB-trained water segmentation network to target-domain aerial thermal imagery using online self-supervision by leveraging texture and motion cues as supervisory signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-self-supervised-thermal-water</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PatchCT: Aligning Patch Set and Label Set with Conditional Transport for Multi-Label Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchct-aligning-patch-set-and-label-set-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that by formulating the multi-label classification as a CT problem, we can exploit the interactions between the image and label efficiently by minimizing the bidirectional CT cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchct-aligning-patch-set-and-label-set-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency-mixed Single-source Domain Generalization for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-mixed-single-source-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consequently, domain generalization (DG) is developed to boost the performance of segmentation models on unseen domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-mixed-single-source-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accuracy versus time frontiers of semi-supervised and self-supervised learning on medical images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accuracy-versus-time-frontiers-of-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study contributes a carefully-designed benchmark to help answer a practitioner's key question: given a small labeled dataset and a limited budget of hours to spend on training, what gains from additional unlabeled images are possible and which methods best achieve them?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accuracy-versus-time-frontiers-of-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RepViT: Revisiting Mobile CNN From ViT Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repvit-revisiting-mobile-cnn-from-vit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On ImageNet, RepViT achieves over 80\% top-1 accuracy with nearly 1ms latency on an iPhone 12, which is the first time for a lightweight model, to the best of our knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repvit-revisiting-mobile-cnn-from-vit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTK-approximating MLP Fusion for Efficient Language Model Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntk-approximating-mlp-fusion-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning a pre-trained language model (PLM) emerges as the predominant strategy in many natural language processing applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntk-approximating-mlp-fusion-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OxfordVGG Submission to the EGO4D AV Transcription Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oxfordvgg-submission-to-the-ego4d-av</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report presents the technical details of our submission on the EGO4D Audio-Visual (AV) Automatic Speech Recognition Challenge 2023 from the OxfordVGG team.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oxfordvgg-submission-to-the-ego4d-av</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Neural Network Training for Hyperbox-Based Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-neural-network-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperbox-based classification has been seen as a promising technique in which decisions on the data are represented as a series of orthogonal, multidimensional boxes (i. e., hyperboxes) that are often interpretable and human-readable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-neural-network-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application of BERT in Wind Power Forecasting-Teletraan's Solution in Baidu KDD Cup 2022</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-bert-in-wind-power-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nowadays, wind energy has drawn increasing attention as its important role in carbon neutrality and sustainable development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-bert-in-wind-power-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using the IBM Analog In-Memory Hardware Acceleration Kit for Neural Network Training and Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-the-ibm-analog-in-memory-hardware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analog In-Memory Computing (AIMC) is a promising approach to reduce the latency and energy consumption of Deep Neural Network (DNN) inference and training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-the-ibm-analog-in-memory-hardware</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
