<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 09:12:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Complexity of Why-Provenance for Datalog Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-complexity-of-why-provenance-for-datalog</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Towards this end, we pinpoint the data complexity of why-provenance for Datalog queries and key subclasses thereof.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-complexity-of-why-provenance-for-datalog</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaskCon: Masked Contrastive Learning for Coarse-Labelled Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskcon-masked-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More specifically, within the contrastive learning framework, for each sample our method generates soft-labels with the aid of coarse labels against other samples and another augmented view of the sample in question.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskcon-masked-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LSTM-based Video Quality Prediction Accounting for Temporal Distortions in Videoconferencing Calls</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lstm-based-video-quality-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using these features together with VMAF core features, our proposed model achieves a PCC of 0. 99 on the validation set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lstm-based-video-quality-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EasyDGL: Encode, Train and Interpret for Continuous-time Dynamic Graph Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easydgl-encode-train-and-interpret-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic graphs arise in various real-world applications, and it is often welcomed to model the dynamics directly in continuous time domain for its flexibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easydgl-encode-train-and-interpret-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MI-SegNet: Mutual Information-Based US Segmentation for Unseen Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mi-segnet-mutual-information-based-us</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We validate the generalizability of the proposed domain-independent segmentation approach on several datasets with varying parameters and machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mi-segnet-mutual-information-based-us</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Split-Et-Impera: A Framework for the Design of Distributed Deep Learning Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/split-et-impera-a-framework-for-the-design-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many recent pattern recognition applications rely on complex distributed architectures in which sensing and computational nodes interact together through a communication network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/split-et-impera-a-framework-for-the-design-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spherical Transformer for LiDAR-based 3D Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spherical-transformer-for-lidar-based-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study the varying-sparsity distribution of LiDAR points and present SphereFormer to directly aggregate information from dense close points to the sparse distant ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spherical-transformer-for-lidar-based-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformal Prediction for Time Series with Modern Hopfield Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-prediction-for-time-series-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To quantify uncertainty, conformal prediction methods are gaining continuously more interest and have already been successfully applied to various domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-prediction-for-time-series-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Implicit Relation Reasoning and Aligning for Text-to-Image Person Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-implicit-relation-reasoning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate these issues, we present IRRA: a cross-modal Implicit Relation Reasoning and Aligning framework that learns relations between local visual-textual tokens and enhances global image-text matching without requiring additional prior supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-implicit-relation-reasoning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiCro: Noisy Correspondence Rectification for Multi-modality Data via Bi-directional Cross-modal Similarity Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bicro-noisy-correspondence-rectification-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As one of the most fundamental techniques in multimodal learning, cross-modal matching aims to project various sensory modalities into a shared feature space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bicro-noisy-correspondence-rectification-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Transformer Models and Human Behaviors on Chinese Character Naming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-transformer-models-and-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These results suggested that the transformer models can well capture human's character naming behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-transformer-models-and-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reveal to Revise: An Explainable AI Life Cycle for Iterative Bias Correction of Deep Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reveal-to-revise-an-explainable-ai-life-cycle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, we propose Reveal to Revise (R2R), a framework entailing the entire eXplainable Artificial Intelligence (XAI) life cycle, enabling practitioners to iteratively identify, mitigate, and (re-)evaluate spurious model behavior with a minimal amount of human interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reveal-to-revise-an-explainable-ai-life-cycle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIMP: Medical Images and Prompts for renal transplant representation learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medimp-medical-images-and-prompts-for-renal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our goal is to learn meaningful manifolds of renal transplant DCE MRI, interesting for the prognosis of the transplant or patient status (2, 3, and 4 years after the transplant), fully exploiting the available multi-modal data in the most efficient way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medimp-medical-images-and-prompts-for-renal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel-wise Agricultural Image Time Series Classification: Comparisons and a Deformable Prototype-based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixel-wise-agricultural-image-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Improvements in Earth observation by satellites allow for imagery of ever higher temporal and spatial resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixel-wise-agricultural-image-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExBEHRT: Extended Transformer for Electronic Health Records to Predict Disease Subtypes &amp; Progressions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exbehrt-extended-transformer-for-electronic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce ExBEHRT, an extended version of BEHRT (BERT applied to electronic health records), and apply different algorithms to interpret its results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exbehrt-extended-transformer-for-electronic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wasserstein Auto-encoded MDPs: Formal Verification of Efficiently Distilled RL Policies with Many-sided Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasserstein-auto-encoded-mdps-formal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach yields bisimulation guarantees while learning the distilled policy, allowing concrete optimization of the abstraction and representation model quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasserstein-auto-encoded-mdps-formal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tube-Link: A Flexible Cross Tube Baseline for Universal Video Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tube-link-a-flexible-cross-tube-baseline-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our framework is a near-online approach that takes a short subclip as input and outputs the corresponding spatial-temporal tube masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tube-link-a-flexible-cross-tube-baseline-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHERF: Generalizable Human NeRF from a Single Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sherf-generalizable-human-nerf-from-a-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a bank of 3D-aware hierarchical features, including global, point-level, and pixel-aligned features, to facilitate informative encoding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sherf-generalizable-human-nerf-from-a-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dense Distinct Query for End-to-End Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-distinct-query-for-end-to-end-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, we first lay dense queries like traditional detectors and then select distinct ones for one-to-one assignments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-distinct-query-for-end-to-end-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-source Frame Semantic Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-frame-semantic-parsing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the state-of-the-art for frame semantic parsing has progressed dramatically in recent years, it is still difficult for end-users to apply state-of-the-art models in practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-frame-semantic-parsing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A multi-functional simulation platform for on-demand ride service operations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-functional-simulation-platform-for-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, the existing simulators still face many challenges, ranging from their closeness to real environments of ride-sourcing systems, to the completeness of different tasks they can implement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-functional-simulation-platform-for-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CiCo: Domain-Aware Sign Language Retrieval via Cross-Lingual Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cico-domain-aware-sign-language-retrieval-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our framework, termed as domain-aware sign language retrieval via Cross-lingual Contrastive learning or CiCo for short, outperforms the pioneering method by large margins on various datasets, e. g., +22. 4 T2V and +28. 0 V2T R@1 improvements on How2Sign dataset, and +13. 7 T2V and +17. 1 V2T R@1 improvements on PHOENIX-2014T dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cico-domain-aware-sign-language-retrieval-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edge Deep Learning Model Protection via Neuron Authorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge-deep-learning-model-protection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the development of deep learning processors and accelerators, deep learning models have been widely deployed on edge devices as part of the Internet of Things.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge-deep-learning-model-protection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Video Representation Learning with Unaligned Text for Sequential Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-video-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sequential video understanding, as an emerging video understanding task, has driven lots of researchers' attention because of its goal-oriented nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-video-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unbiased Multiple Instance Learning for Weakly Supervised Video Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-multiple-instance-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At each MIL training iteration, we use the current detector to divide the samples into two groups with different context biases: the most confident abnormal/normal snippets and the rest ambiguous ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-multiple-instance-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encoding Binary Concepts in the Latent Space of Generative Models for Enhancing Data Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/encoding-binary-concepts-in-the-latent-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel binarized regularization to facilitate learning of binary concepts to improve the quality of data generation in autoencoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/encoding-binary-concepts-in-the-latent-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Re-thinking Federated Active Learning based on Inter-class Diversity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-thinking-federated-active-learning-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we first demonstrate that the superiority of two selector models depends on the global and local inter-class diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-thinking-federated-active-learning-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balanced Spherical Grid for Egocentric View Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balanced-spherical-grid-for-egocentric-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the na\"ive spherical grid suffers from irregularities at two poles, and also cannot represent unbounded scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balanced-spherical-grid-for-egocentric-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Reasoning in the Presence of Latent Confounders via Neural ADMG Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-reasoning-in-the-presence-of-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we further extend the existing body of work and develop a novel gradient-based approach to learning an ADMG with non-linear functional relations from observational data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-reasoning-in-the-presence-of-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstract Visual Reasoning: An Algebraic Approach for Solving Raven's Progressive Matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstract-visual-reasoning-an-algebraic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce algebraic machine reasoning, a new reasoning framework that is well-suited for abstract reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstract-visual-reasoning-an-algebraic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Two Circuits: Grokking as Competition of Sparse and Dense Subnetworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tale-of-two-circuits-grokking-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Grokking is a phenomenon where a model trained on an algorithmic task first overfits but, then, after a large amount of additional training, undergoes a phase transition to generalize perfectly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tale-of-two-circuits-grokking-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difficulty in learning chirality for Transformer fed with SMILES</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difficulty-in-learning-chirality-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have seen development of descriptor generation based on representation learning of extremely diverse molecules, especially those that apply natural language processing (NLP) models to SMILES, a literal representation of molecular structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difficulty-in-learning-chirality-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MV-MR: multi-views and multi-representations for self-supervised learning and knowledge distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mv-mr-multi-views-and-multi-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new method of self-supervised learning and knowledge distillation based on the multi-views and multi-representations (MV-MR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mv-mr-multi-views-and-multi-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSTFormer: Motion Inspired Spatial-temporal Transformer with Dynamic-aware Attention for long-term Vessel Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mstformer-motion-inspired-spatial-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Against this background, we propose MSTFormer, a motion inspired vessel trajectory prediction method based on Transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mstformer-motion-inspired-spatial-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monocular Visual-Inertial Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-visual-inertial-depth-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate on the TartanAir and VOID datasets, observing up to 30% reduction in inverse RMSE with dense scale alignment relative to performing just global alignment alone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-visual-inertial-depth-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Vertex Replacement Grammars</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-vertex-replacement-grammars</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Context-free graph grammars have shown a remarkable ability to model structures in real-world relational data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-vertex-replacement-grammars</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wearing Masks Implies Refuting Trump?: Towards Target-specific User Stance Prediction across Events in COVID-19 and US Election 2020</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wearing-masks-implies-refuting-trump-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[People who share similar opinions towards controversial topics could form an echo chamber and may share similar political views toward other topics as well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wearing-masks-implies-refuting-trump-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Understanding Differences in Attribution Methods via Systematic Evaluations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-understanding-differences-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we propose a post-processing smoothing step that significantly improves the performance of some attribution methods, and discuss its applicability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-understanding-differences-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoRCoN-LO: Long-term Recurrent Convolutional Network-based LiDAR Odometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lorcon-lo-long-term-recurrent-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a deep learning-based LiDAR odometry estimation method called LoRCoN-LO that utilizes the long-term recurrent convolutional network (LRCN) structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lorcon-lo-long-term-recurrent-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fix the Noise: Disentangling Source Feature for Controllable Domain Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fix-the-noise-disentangling-source-feature-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This allows our method to smoothly control the degree to which it preserves source features while generating images from an entirely new domain using only a single model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fix-the-noise-disentangling-source-feature-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural networks trained on synthetically generated crystals can extract structural information from ICSD powder X-ray diffractograms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-trained-on-synthetically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, training directly on simulated diffractograms from databases such as the ICSD is challenging due to its limited size, class-inhomogeneity, and bias toward certain structure types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-trained-on-synthetically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DG-Trans: Dual-level Graph Transformer for Spatiotemporal Incident Impact Prediction on Traffic Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dg-trans-dual-level-graph-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, DG-Trans is equipped with dual abilities that extract spatiotemporal dependency and identify anomaly nodes affected by incidents while removing noise introduced by benign nodes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dg-trans-dual-level-graph-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Context-aware Classifier for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-context-aware-classifier-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation is still a challenging task for parsing diverse contexts in different scenes, thus the fixed classifier might not be able to well address varying feature distributions during testing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-context-aware-classifier-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are uGLAD? Time will tell!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-uglad-time-will-tell</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segmentation of multivariate time series data is a technique for identifying meaningful patterns or changes in the time series that can signal a shift in the system's behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-uglad-time-will-tell</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Optical Flow and Scene Flow with Bidirectional Camera-LiDAR Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-optical-flow-and-scene-flow-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fuse dense image features and sparse point features, we propose a learnable operator named bidirectional camera-LiDAR fusion module (Bi-CLFM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-optical-flow-and-scene-flow-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Optimization for Function Compositions with Applications to Dynamic Pricing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-optimization-for-function</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian Optimization (BO) is used to find the global optima of black box functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-optimization-for-function</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-efficient Large Scale Place Recognition with Graded Similarity Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-efficient-large-scale-place-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the fact that two images of the same place only partially share visual cues due to camera pose differences, we deploy an automatic re-annotation strategy to re-label VPR datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-efficient-large-scale-place-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALOFT: A Lightweight MLP-like Architecture with Dynamic Low-frequency Transform for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aloft-a-lightweight-mlp-like-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the local operation of the convolution kernel makes the model focus too much on local representations (e. g., texture), which inherently causes the model more prone to overfit to the source domains and hampers its generalization ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aloft-a-lightweight-mlp-like-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Neural Representation for Cooperative Low-light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-neural-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, extensive experiments demonstrate the robustness and superior effectiveness of our proposed NeRCo.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-neural-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Healthcare Embeddings for Improving Patient Care</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-healthcare-embeddings-for-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we propose DECENT, an auto-encoding heterogeneous co-evolving dynamic neural network, for learning heterogeneous dynamic embeddings of patients, doctors, rooms, and medications from diverse data streams.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-healthcare-embeddings-for-improving</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
