<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 09:12:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>PanopticNeRF-360: Panoramic 3D-to-2D Label Transfer in Urban Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panopticnerf-360-panoramic-3d-to-2d-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, PanopticNeRF-360 enables omnidirectional rendering of high-fidelity, multi-view and spatiotemporally consistent appearance, semantic and instance labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panopticnerf-360-panoramic-3d-to-2d-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-stage coarse-to-fine image anomaly segmentation and detection model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stage-coarse-to-fine-image-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In both stages of TASAD, we train our model on a mixture of normal and abnormal training samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stage-coarse-to-fine-image-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPL-SFDA: Uncertainty-aware Pseudo Label Guided Source-Free Domain Adaptation for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/upl-sfda-uncertainty-aware-pseudo-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The different predictions in these duplicated heads are used to obtain pseudo labels for unlabeled target-domain images and their uncertainty to identify reliable pseudo labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/upl-sfda-uncertainty-aware-pseudo-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Point-wise Abstaining Penalty for Point Cloud Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-point-wise-abstaining-penalty-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that learning different abstaining penalties, apart from point-wise penalty, for different types of (synthesized) outliers can further improve the performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-point-wise-abstaining-penalty-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TensorCodec: Compact Lossy Compression of Tensors without Strong Data Assumptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensorcodec-compact-lossy-compression-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While many tensor compression algorithms are available, many of them rely on strong data assumptions regarding its order, sparsity, rank, and smoothness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensorcodec-compact-lossy-compression-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baichuan 2: Open Large-scale Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/baichuan-2-open-large-scale-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable performance on a variety of natural language tasks based on just a few examples of natural language instructions, reducing the need for extensive feature engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/baichuan-2-open-large-scale-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Unified Controllable Text Generation via Regular Expression Instruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-unified-controllable-text-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Controllable text generation is a fundamental aspect of natural language generation, with numerous methods proposed for different constraint types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-unified-controllable-text-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Adaptive Safety for Multi-Agent Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-adaptive-safety-for-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ensuring safety in dynamic multi-agent systems is challenging due to limited information about the other agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-adaptive-safety-for-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KFC: Kinship Verification with Fair Contrastive Loss and Multi-Task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kfc-kinship-verification-with-fair</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Kinship verification is an emerging task in computer vision with multiple potential applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kfc-kinship-verification-with-fair</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAMS: Platform for Artificial Market Simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pams-platform-for-artificial-market</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new artificial market simulation platform, PAMS: Platform for Artificial Market Simulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pams-platform-for-artificial-market</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oracle Complexity Reduction for Model-free LQR: A Stochastic Variance-Reduced Policy Gradient Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oracle-complexity-reduction-for-model-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the problem of learning an $\epsilon$-approximate solution for the discrete-time Linear Quadratic Regulator (LQR) problem via a Stochastic Variance-Reduced Policy Gradient (SVRPG) approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oracle-complexity-reduction-for-model-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NusaWrites: Constructing High-Quality Corpora for Underrepresented and Extremely Low-Resource Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nusawrites-constructing-high-quality-corpora</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the effectiveness of online scraping, human translation, and paragraph writing by native speakers in constructing datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nusawrites-constructing-high-quality-corpora</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PGDiff: Guiding Diffusion Models for Versatile Face Restoration via Partial Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgdiff-guiding-diffusion-models-for-versatile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When combined with a diffusion prior, this partial guidance can deliver appealing results across a range of restoration tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgdiff-guiding-diffusion-models-for-versatile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Configurable Library for Generating and Manipulating Maze Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-configurable-library-for-generating-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding how machine learning models respond to distributional shifts is a key research challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-configurable-library-for-generating-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Contrastive Learning Meets Graph Meta Learning: A Unified Method for Few-shot Node Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-contrastive-learning-meets-graph-meta</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our study, we first identify two crucial advantages of contrastive learning compared to meta learning, including (1) the comprehensive utilization of graph nodes and (2) the power of graph augmentations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-contrastive-learning-meets-graph-meta</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGIC-TBR: Multiview Attention Fusion for Transformer-based Bodily Behavior Recognition in Group Settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magic-tbr-multiview-attention-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bodily behavioral language is an important social cue, and its automated analysis helps in enhancing the understanding of artificial intelligence systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magic-tbr-multiview-attention-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Shot Panoptic Segmentation With Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-panoptic-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concurrently, recent breakthroughs in visual representation learning have sparked a paradigm shift leading to the advent of large foundation models that can be trained with completely unlabeled images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-panoptic-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial-Assistant Encoder-Decoder Network for Real Time Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-assistant-encoder-decoder-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To ascertain the effectiveness of our approach, our SANet model achieved competitive results on the real-time CamVid and cityscape datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-assistant-encoder-decoder-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flash-LLM: Enabling Cost-Effective and Highly-Efficient Large Generative Model Inference with Unstructured Sparsity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flash-llm-enabling-cost-effective-and-highly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose Flash-LLM for enabling low-cost and highly-efficient large generative model inference with the sophisticated support of unstructured sparsity on high-performance but highly restrictive Tensor Cores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flash-llm-enabling-cost-effective-and-highly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Stain Self-Attention Graph Multiple Instance Learning Pipeline for Histopathology Whole Slide Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stain-self-attention-graph-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach is highly modular and can easily be modified to suit different clinical datasets, as it only requires a patient-level label without annotations and accepts WSI sets of different sizes, as the graphs can be of varying sizes and structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stain-self-attention-graph-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AV-SUPERB: A Multi-Task Evaluation Benchmark for Audio-Visual Representation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/av-superb-a-multi-task-evaluation-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Audio-visual representation learning aims to develop systems with human-like perception by utilizing correlation between auditory and visual information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/av-superb-a-multi-task-evaluation-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised speech enhancement with diffusion-based generative models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-speech-enhancement-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we introduce an alternative approach that operates in an unsupervised manner, leveraging the generative power of diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-speech-enhancement-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenBA: An Open-sourced 15B Bilingual Asymmetric seq2seq Model Pre-trained from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openba-an-open-sourced-15b-bilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report provides the main details to pre-train an analogous model, including pre-training data processing, Bilingual Flan data collection, the empirical observations that inspire our model architecture design, training objectives of different stages, and other enhancement techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openba-an-open-sourced-15b-bilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Generative Modeling of Urban Flow through Knowledge-enhanced Denoising Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-generative-modeling-of-urban-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To capture the effect of multiple factors on urban flow, such as region features and urban environment, we employ diffusion model to generate urban flow for regions under different conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-generative-modeling-of-urban-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoSE: Efficient Context Window Extension of LLMs via Positional Skip-wise Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-efficient-context-window-extension-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, we select several short chunks from a long input sequence, and introduce distinct skipping bias terms to modify the position indices of each chunk.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-efficient-context-window-extension-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully automated landmarking and facial segmentation on 3D photographs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-automated-landmarking-and-facial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The training dataset was used to train the deep learning networks, whereas the test dataset was used to evaluate the performance of the automated workflow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-automated-landmarking-and-facial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Landmark Discovery Using Consistency Guided Bottleneck</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-landmark-discovery-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the current work, we introduce a consistency-guided bottleneck in an image reconstruction-based pipeline that leverages landmark consistency, a measure of compatibility score with the pseudo-ground truth to generate adaptive heatmaps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-landmark-discovery-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOT: Scalable 3D Pre-training via Occupancy Prediction for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spot-scalable-3d-pre-training-via-occupancy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our contributions are threefold: (1) Occupancy prediction is shown to be promising for learning general representations, which is demonstrated by extensive experiments on plenty of datasets and tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spot-scalable-3d-pre-training-via-occupancy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forgedit: Text Guided Image Editing via Learning and Forgetting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forgedit-text-guided-image-editing-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text guided image editing on real images given only the image and the target text prompt as inputs, is a very general and challenging problem, which requires the editing model to reason by itself which part of the image should be edited, to preserve the characteristics of original image, and also to perform complicated non-rigid editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forgedit-text-guided-image-editing-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPTFUZZER : Red Teaming Large Language Models with Auto-Generated Jailbreak Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gptfuzzer-red-teaming-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, even starting with suboptimal seed templates, \fuzzer maintains over 90\% attack success rate against ChatGPT and Llama-2 models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gptfuzzer-red-teaming-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM Platform Security: Applying a Systematic Evaluation Framework to OpenAI's ChatGPT Plugins</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-platform-security-applying-a-systematic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a framework that lays a foundation for LLM platform designers to analyze and improve the security, privacy, and safety of current and future plugin-integrated LLM platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-platform-security-applying-a-systematic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AstroPortal: An ontology repository concept for astronomy, astronautics and other space topics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/astroportal-an-ontology-repository-concept</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes a repository for ontologies of astronomy, astronautics, and other space-related topics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/astroportal-an-ontology-repository-concept</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Embedded Programs for Hybrid Language Symbolic Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-embedded-programs-for-hybrid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How can we perform computations over natural language representations to solve tasks that require symbolic and numeric reasoning?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-embedded-programs-for-hybrid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MelodyGLM: Multi-task Pre-training for Symbolic Melody Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melodyglm-multi-task-pre-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, subjective evaluations show that, on the melody continuation task, MelodyGLM achieves average improvements of 0. 82, 0. 87, 0. 78, and 0. 94 in consistency, rhythmicity, structure, and overall quality, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melodyglm-multi-task-pre-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guide Your Agent with Adaptive Multimodal Rewards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guide-your-agent-with-adaptive-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Developing an agent capable of adapting to unseen environments remains a difficult challenge in imitation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guide-your-agent-with-adaptive-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating large language models' ability to understand metaphor and sarcasm using a screening test for Asperger syndrome</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-large-language-models-ability-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Metaphors and sarcasm are precious fruits of our highly-evolved social communication skills.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-large-language-models-ability-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenMSD: Towards Multilingual Scientific Documents Similarity Measurement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openmsd-towards-multilingual-scientific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the first multilingual scientific documents dataset, Open-access Multilingual Scientific Documents (OpenMSD), which has 74M papers in 103 languages and 778M citation pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openmsd-towards-multilingual-scientific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sample-adaptive Augmentation for Point Cloud Recognition Against Real-world Corruptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-adaptive-augmentation-for-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust 3D perception under corruption has become an essential task for the realm of 3D vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-adaptive-augmentation-for-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-dimension Queried and Interacting Network for Stereo Image Deraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dimension-queried-and-interacting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This module leverages dimension-wise queries that are independent of the input features and employs global context-aware attention (GCA) to capture essential features while avoiding the entanglement of redundant or irrelevant information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dimension-queried-and-interacting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter-Efficient Long-Tailed Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-long-tailed-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose PEL, a fine-tuning method that can effectively adapt pre-trained models to long-tailed recognition tasks in fewer than 20 epochs without the need for extra data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-long-tailed-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Kernel Density Integral Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-kernel-density-integral-transformation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that, without hyperparameter tuning, the kernel density integral transformation can be used as a simple drop-in replacement for either method, offering robustness to the weaknesses of each.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-kernel-density-integral-transformation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEDepth: Ground Embedding for Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gedepth-ground-embedding-for-monocular-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monocular depth estimation is an ill-posed problem as the same 2D image can be projected from infinite 3D scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gedepth-ground-embedding-for-monocular-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Gender Bias of Pre-trained Language Models in Natural Language Inference by Considering All Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-gender-bias-of-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the experiment, we propose a meta-evaluation method for NLI bias measures, and then use it to confirm that our measure can evaluate bias more accurately than the baseline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-gender-bias-of-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is a Fair Diffusion Model? Designing Generative Text-To-Image Models to Incorporate Various Worldviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-is-a-fair-diffusion-model-designing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative text-to-image (GTI) models produce high-quality images from short textual descriptions and are widely used in academic and creative domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-is-a-fair-diffusion-model-designing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaT: Balanced Continual Graph Learning with Graph Condensation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-balanced-continual-graph-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent replay-based methods intend to solve this problem by updating the model using both (1) the entire new-coming data and (2) a sampling-based memory bank that stores replayed graphs to approximate the distribution of historical data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-balanced-continual-graph-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drawing the Same Bounding Box Twice? Coping Noisy Annotations in Object Detection with Repeated Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drawing-the-same-bounding-box-twice-coping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The reliability of supervised machine learning systems depends on the accuracy and availability of ground truth labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drawing-the-same-bounding-box-twice-coping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Text-to-Image Diffusion with Soft Latent Direction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-text-to-image-diffusion-with-soft</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In spite of the rapidly evolving landscape of text-to-image generation, the synthesis and manipulation of multiple entities while adhering to specific relational constraints pose enduring challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-text-to-image-diffusion-with-soft</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CATR: Combinatorial-Dependence Audio-Queried Transformer for Audio-Visual Video Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/catr-combinatorial-dependence-audio-queried</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing methods exhibit two limitations: 1) they address video temporal features and audio-visual interactive features separately, disregarding the inherent spatial-temporal dependence of combined audio and video, and 2) they inadequately introduce audio constraints and object-level information during the decoding stage, resulting in segmentation outcomes that fail to comply with audio directives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/catr-combinatorial-dependence-audio-queried</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFormer: Rethinking RGBD Representation Learning for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dformer-rethinking-rgbd-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present DFormer, a novel RGB-D pretraining framework to learn transferable representations for RGB-D segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dformer-rethinking-rgbd-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Coarse-to-Fine Alignment for Video-Text Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-coarse-to-fine-alignment-for-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our model captures the cross-modal similarity information at different granularity levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-coarse-to-fine-alignment-for-video</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
