<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 09:11:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DNNShifter: An Efficient DNN Pruning System for Edge Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dnnshifter-an-efficient-dnn-pruning-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to sparse models, the pruned model variants are up to 5. 14x smaller and have a 1. 67x inference latency speedup, with no compromise to sparse model accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dnnshifter-an-efficient-dnn-pruning-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniBrain: Universal Brain MRI Diagnosis with Hierarchical Knowledge-enhanced Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unibrain-universal-brain-mri-diagnosis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Magnetic resonance imaging~(MRI) have played a crucial role in brain disease diagnosis, with which a range of computer-aided artificial intelligence methods have been proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unibrain-universal-brain-mri-diagnosis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPI-Flow: Learning Realistic Optical Flow with Multiplane Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpi-flow-learning-realistic-optical-flow-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The accuracy of learning-based optical flow estimation models heavily relies on the realism of the training datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpi-flow-learning-realistic-optical-flow-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sight Beyond Text: Multi-Modal Training Enhances LLMs in Truthfulness and Ethics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sight-beyond-text-multi-modal-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal large language models (MLLMs) are trained based on large language models (LLM), with an enhanced capability to comprehend multi-modal inputs and generate textual responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sight-beyond-text-multi-modal-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable JPEG: The Devil is in the Details</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-jpeg-the-devil-is-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[the input image, the JPEG quality, the quantization tables, and the color conversion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-jpeg-the-devil-is-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Reinforcement Learning for Jumping Monopods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-reinforcement-learning-for-jumping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we consider the complex control problem of making a monopod reach a target with a jump.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-reinforcement-learning-for-jumping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Résumé Parsing as Hierarchical Sequence Labeling: An Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resume-parsing-as-hierarchical-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extracting information from r\'esum\'es is typically formulated as a two-stage problem, where the document is first segmented into sections and then each section is processed individually to extract the target entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resume-parsing-as-hierarchical-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTD: Multi-Timestep Detector for Delayed Streaming Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtd-multi-timestep-detector-for-delayed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous driving systems require real-time environmental perception to ensure user safety and experience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtd-multi-timestep-detector-for-delayed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transparent Object Tracking with Enhanced Fusion Module</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transparent-object-tracking-with-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, with the existing fusion techniques, the addition of new features causes a change in the latent space making it impossible to incorporate transparency awareness on trackers with fixed latent spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transparent-object-tracking-with-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLSlice: Interactive Vision-and-Language Slice Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlslice-interactive-vision-and-language-slice</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work in vision-and-language demonstrates that large-scale pretraining can learn generalizable models that are efficiently transferable to downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlslice-interactive-vision-and-language-slice</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Fatigue Crack Growth via Path Slicing and Re-Weighting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-fatigue-crack-growth-via-path</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting potential risks associated with the fatigue of key structural components is crucial in engineering design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-fatigue-crack-growth-via-path</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConR: Contrastive Regularizer for Deep Imbalanced Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conr-contrastive-regularizer-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ConR minds the continuous nature of label space with two main strategies in a contrastive manner: incorrect proximities are penalized proportionate to the label similarities and the correct ones are encouraged to model local similarities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conr-contrastive-regularizer-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCSPNet-Joint: Efficient Joint Training Method for Traffic Sihn Detection Under Extreme Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccspnet-joint-efficient-joint-training-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traffic sign detection is an important research direction in intelligent driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccspnet-joint-efficient-joint-training-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Hallucinations and Off-target Machine Translation with Source-Contrastive and Language-Contrastive Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-hallucinations-and-off-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hallucinations and off-target translation remain unsolved problems in machine translation, especially for low-resource languages and massively multilingual models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-hallucinations-and-off-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregating Long-term Sharp Features via Hybrid Transformers for Video Deblurring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aggregating-long-term-sharp-features-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To aggregate long-term sharp features from detected sharp frames, we utilize a global Transformer with multi-scale matching capability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aggregating-long-term-sharp-features-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SupFusion: Supervised LiDAR-Camera Fusion for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supfusion-supervised-lidar-camera-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel training strategy called SupFusion, which provides an auxiliary feature level supervision for effective LiDAR-Camera fusion and significantly boosts detection performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supfusion-supervised-lidar-camera-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effect of hyperparameters on variable selection in random forests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-hyperparameters-on-variable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In conclusion, the default values of the hyperparameters will not always be suitable for identifying important variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-hyperparameters-on-variable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PILOT: A Pre-Trained Model-Based Continual Learning Toolbox</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pilot-a-pre-trained-model-based-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While traditional machine learning can effectively tackle a wide range of problems, it primarily operates within a closed-world setting, which presents limitations when dealing with streaming data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pilot-a-pre-trained-model-based-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Infringement Detection via Feature Disentanglement and Mutual Information Maximization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-infringement-detection-via-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We theoretically analyzed the mutual information between the label and the disentangled features, arriving at a loss that maximizes the extraction of task-relevant information from the original feature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-infringement-detection-via-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Refined Large Language Model as Automated Reward Function Designer for Deep Reinforcement Learning in Robotics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-refined-large-language-model-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, the performance of the reward function is assessed, and the results are presented back to the LLM for guiding its self-refinement process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-refined-large-language-model-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cognitive Mirage: A Review of Hallucinations in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cognitive-mirage-a-review-of-hallucinations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our contribution are threefold: (1) We provide a detailed and complete taxonomy for hallucinations appearing in text generation tasks; (2) We provide theoretical analyses of hallucinations in LLMs and provide existing detection and improvement methods; (3) We propose several research directions that can be developed in the future.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cognitive-mirage-a-review-of-hallucinations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards the TopMost: A Topic Modeling System Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-topmost-a-topic-modeling-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topic models have been proposed for decades with various applications and recently refreshed by the neural variational inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-topmost-a-topic-modeling-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Image Dataset for Benchmarking Recommender Systems with Raw Pixels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-image-dataset-for-benchmarking-recommender</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, to show the effectiveness of the dataset's image features, we substitute the itemID embeddings (from IDNet) with a powerful vision encoder that represents items using their raw image pixels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-image-dataset-for-benchmarking-recommender</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMUS: Adapting Segment Anything Model for Clinically-Friendly and Generalizable Ultrasound Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samus-adapting-segment-anything-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segment anything model (SAM), an eminent universal image segmentation model, has recently gathered considerable attention within the domain of medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samus-adapting-segment-anything-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedDIP: Federated Learning with Extreme Dynamic Pruning and Incremental Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddip-federated-learning-with-extreme</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) has been successfully adopted for distributed training and inference of large-scale Deep Neural Networks (DNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddip-federated-learning-with-extreme</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging SE(3) Equivariance for Learning 3D Geometric Shape Assembly</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-se-3-equivariance-for-learning-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Shape assembly aims to reassemble parts (or fragments) into a complete object, which is a common task in our daily life.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-se-3-equivariance-for-learning-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OWL Reasoners still useable in 2023</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/owl-reasoners-still-useable-in-2023</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a systematic literature and software review over 100 OWL reasoners/systems were analyzed to see if they would still be usable in 2023.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/owl-reasoners-still-useable-in-2023</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ungar $\unicode{x2013}$ A C++ Framework for Real-Time Optimal Control Using Template Metaprogramming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ungar-unicode-x2013-a-c-framework-for-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Ungar, an open-source library to aid the implementation of high-dimensional optimal control problems (OCPs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ungar-unicode-x2013-a-c-framework-for-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Procedural Language Understanding for Low-Resource Languages: A Case Study on Turkish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-procedural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these tasks, we implement strong baseline models via fine-tuning large language-specific models such as TR-BART and BERTurk, as well as multilingual models such as mBART, mT5, and XLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-procedural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Native Language Identification with Big Bird Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/native-language-identification-with-big-bird</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Native Language Identification (NLI) intends to classify an author's native language based on their writing in another language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/native-language-identification-with-big-bird</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond original Research Articles Categorization via NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-original-research-articles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes a novel approach to text categorization -- for unknown categories -- in the context of scientific literature, using Natural Language Processing techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-original-research-articles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can large-scale vocoded spoofed data improve speech spoofing countermeasure with a self-supervised front end?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-scale-vocoded-spoofed-data-improve</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While many datasets use spoofed data generated by speech synthesis systems, it was recently found that data vocoded by neural vocoders were also effective as the spoofed training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-scale-vocoded-spoofed-data-improve</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models as Black-Box Optimizers for Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-as-black-box-optimizers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language models (VLMs) pre-trained on web-scale datasets have demonstrated remarkable capabilities across a variety of vision and multimodal tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-as-black-box-optimizers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plasticity-Optimized Complementary Networks for Unsupervised Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plasticity-optimized-complementary-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the second phase, we combine this new knowledge with the previous network in an adaptation-retrospection phase to avoid forgetting and initialize a new expert with the knowledge of the old network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plasticity-optimized-complementary-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from History: Task-agnostic Model Contrastive Learning for Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-history-task-agnostic-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, models retrained with SPNIR outperform the original FFANet and DehazeFormer by 3. 41 dB and 0. 57 dB on the RESIDE indoor dataset for image dehazing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-history-task-agnostic-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commands as AI Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/commands-as-ai-conversations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Developers and data scientists often struggle to write command-line inputs, even though graphical interfaces or tools like ChatGPT can assist.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/commands-as-ai-conversations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Sparse PCA via Positive Semidefinite Projection for Unsupervised Feature Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-sparse-pca-via-positive-semidefinite</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A standard convex SPCA-based model with PSD constraint for unsupervised feature selection is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-sparse-pca-via-positive-semidefinite</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstaFlow: One Step is Enough for High-Quality Diffusion-Based Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instaflow-one-step-is-enough-for-high-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging our new pipeline, we create, to the best of our knowledge, the first one-step diffusion-based text-to-image generator with SD-level image quality, achieving an FID (Frechet Inception Distance) of $23. 3$ on MS COCO 2017-5k, surpassing the previous state-of-the-art technique, progressive distillation, by a significant margin ($37. 2$ $\rightarrow$ $23. 3$ in FID).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instaflow-one-step-is-enough-for-high-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Benefits of Differentially Private Pre-training and Parameter-Efficient Fine-tuning for Table Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-benefits-of-differentially</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For machine learning with tabular data, Table Transformer (TabTransformer) is a state-of-the-art neural network model, while Differential Privacy (DP) is an essential component to ensure data privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-benefits-of-differentially</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can we predict the Most Replayed data of video streaming platforms?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-predict-the-most-replayed-data-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we curate a large video benchmark, the YTMR500 dataset, which comprises 500 YouTube videos with MR data annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-predict-the-most-replayed-data-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certified Robust Models with Slack Control and Large Lipschitz Constants</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certified-robust-models-with-slack-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Calibrated Lipschitz-Margin Loss (CLL) that addresses this issue and improves certified robustness by tackling two problems: Firstly, commonly used margin losses do not adjust the penalties to the shrinking output distribution; caused by minimizing the Lipschitz constant $K$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certified-robust-models-with-slack-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epistemic Modeling Uncertainty of Rapid Neural Network Ensembles for Adaptive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epistemic-modeling-uncertainty-of-rapid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, a new type of emulator embedded neural network is presented using the rapid neural network paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epistemic-modeling-uncertainty-of-rapid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATTA: Anomaly-aware Test-Time Adaptation for Out-of-Distribution Detection in Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atta-anomaly-aware-test-time-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in dense out-of-distribution (OOD) detection have primarily focused on scenarios where the training and testing datasets share a similar domain, with the assumption that no domain shift exists between them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atta-anomaly-aware-test-time-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MatSciML: A Broad, Multi-Task Benchmark for Solid-State Materials Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matsciml-a-broad-multi-task-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose MatSci ML, a novel benchmark for modeling MATerials SCIence using Machine Learning (MatSci ML) methods focused on solid-state materials with periodic crystal structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matsciml-a-broad-multi-task-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quality-Agnostic Deepfake Detection with Intra-model Collaborative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quality-agnostic-deepfake-detection-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, detecting low quality as well as simultaneously detecting different qualities of deepfakes still remains a grave challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quality-agnostic-deepfake-detection-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Memory Management for Large Language Model Serving with PagedAttention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2309-06180</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On top of it, we build vLLM, an LLM serving system that achieves (1) near-zero waste in KV cache memory and (2) flexible sharing of KV cache within and across requests to further reduce memory usage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2309-06180</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Normality Learning-based Graph Anomaly Detection via Multi-Scale Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2309-06034</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, the model is refined with the only input of reliable normal nodes and learns a more accurate estimate of normality so that anomalous nodes can be more easily distinguished.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2309-06034</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Predict Concept Ordering for Common Sense Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2309-06363</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior work has shown that the ordering in which concepts are shown to a commonsense generator plays an important role, affecting the quality of the generated sentence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2309-06363</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Reed-Muller Codes for Classification with Rejection and Recovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2309-06359</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When deploying classifiers in the real world, users expect them to respond to inputs appropriately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2309-06359</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAMUR: Hyper Adapter for Multi-Domain Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2309-06217</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, due to the distribution differences among domains, the utilization of static parameters in existing methods limits their flexibility to adapt to diverse domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2309-06217</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
