<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 09:15:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Marker and source-marker reprogramming of Most Permissive Boolean networks and ensembles with BoNesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marker-and-source-marker-reprogramming-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we demonstrate how the software BoNesis can be employed to exhaustively identify combinations of perturbations which enforce properties on their fixed points and attractors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marker-and-source-marker-reprogramming-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camouflaged Object Detection via Context-aware Cross-level Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camouflaged-object-detection-via-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose a novel Context-aware Cross-level Fusion Network (C2F-Net), which fuses context-aware cross-level features for accurately identifying camouflaged objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camouflaged-object-detection-via-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Trimap Video Matting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-trimap-video-matting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key of OTVM is the joint modeling of trimap propagation and alpha prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-trimap-video-matting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoTransition: Learning to Recommend Video Transition Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autotransition-learning-to-recommend-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First we learn the embedding of video transitions through a video transition classification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autotransition-learning-to-recommend-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight and Progressively-Scalable Networks for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-and-progressively-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we thoroughly analyze the design of convolutional blocks (the type of convolutions and the number of channels in convolutions), and the ways of interactions across multiple scales, all from lightweight standpoint for semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-and-progressively-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Driven Sample Average Approximation with Covariate Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-sample-average-approximation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study optimization for data-driven decision-making when we have observations of the uncertain parameters within the optimization model together with concurrent observations of covariates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-sample-average-approximation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransNorm: Transformer Provides a Strong Spatial Normalization Mechanism for a Deep Segmentation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transnorm-transformer-provides-a-strong</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the past few years, convolutional neural networks (CNNs), particularly U-Net, have been the prevailing technique in the medical image processing era.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transnorm-transformer-provides-a-strong</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generator Knows What Discriminator Should Learn in Unconditional GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generator-knows-what-discriminator-should</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we explore the efficacy of dense supervision in unconditional generation and find generator feature maps can be an alternative of cost-expensive semantic label maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generator-knows-what-discriminator-should</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PASTA-GAN++: A Versatile Framework for High-Resolution Unpaired Virtual Try-on</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pasta-gan-a-versatile-framework-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we take a step forwards to explore versatile virtual try-on solutions, which we argue should possess three main properties, namely, they should support unsupervised training, arbitrary garment categories, and controllable garment editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pasta-gan-a-versatile-framework-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards the Neuroevolution of Low-level Artificial General Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-neuroevolution-of-low-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate a method to evolve a biologically-inspired artificial neural network that learns from environment reactions named Neuroevolution of Artificial General Intelligence (NAGI), a framework for low-level AGI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-neuroevolution-of-low-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardly Perceptible Trojan Attack against Neural Networks with Bit Flips</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardly-perceptible-trojan-attack-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The security of deep neural networks (DNNs) has attracted increasing attention due to their widespread use in various applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardly-perceptible-trojan-attack-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifying Hard Noise in Long-Tailed Sample Distribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-hard-noise-in-long-tailed-sample</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such imbalanced training data makes a classifier less discriminative for the tail classes, whose previously "easy" noises are now turned into "hard" ones -- they are almost as outliers as the clean tail samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-hard-noise-in-long-tailed-sample</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factorial User Modeling with Hierarchical Graph Neural Network for Enhanced Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factorial-user-modeling-with-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most sequential recommendation (SR) systems employing graph neural networks (GNNs) only model a user's interaction sequence as a flat graph without hierarchy, overlooking diverse factors in the user's preference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factorial-user-modeling-with-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe and Robust Experience Sharing for Deterministic Policy Gradient Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-and-robust-experience-sharing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning in high dimensional continuous tasks is challenging, mainly when the experience replay memory is very limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-and-robust-experience-sharing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mid-level Representation Enhancement and Graph Embedded Uncertainty Suppressing for Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mid-level-representation-enhancement-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, GUS is introduced to suppress the feature ambiguity in the representation space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mid-level-representation-enhancement-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolutionary Multiparty Distance Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-multiparty-distance-minimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of evolutionary multiobjective optimization, the decision maker (DM) concerns conflicting objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-multiparty-distance-minimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Pix2Vox++ for 3D Cardiac Reconstruction from 2D echo views</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-pix2vox-for-3d-cardiac</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate geometric quantification of the human heart is a key step in the diagnosis of numerous cardiac diseases, and in the management of cardiac patients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-pix2vox-for-3d-cardiac</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SiRi: A Simple Selective Retraining Mechanism for Transformer-based Visual Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siri-a-simple-selective-retraining-mechanism</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, SiRi conveys a significant principle to the research of visual grounding, i. e., a better initialized vision-language encoder would help the model converge to a better local minimum, advancing the performance accordingly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siri-a-simple-selective-retraining-mechanism</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALBench: A Framework for Evaluating Active Learning in Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/albench-a-framework-for-evaluating-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate the research in this field, this paper contributes an active learning benchmark framework named as ALBench for evaluating active learning in object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/albench-a-framework-for-evaluating-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concurrent Subsidiary Supervision for Unsupervised Source-Free Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concurrent-subsidiary-supervision-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prime challenge in unsupervised domain adaptation (DA) is to mitigate the domain shift between the source and target domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concurrent-subsidiary-supervision-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging GAN Priors for Few-Shot Part Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-gan-priors-for-few-shot-part</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, this work is an attempt to explore the internal relevance between generation tasks and perception tasks by prompt designing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-gan-priors-for-few-shot-part</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast expansion into harmonics on the disk: a steerable basis with fast radial convolutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-expansion-into-harmonics-on-the-disk-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a fast and numerically accurate method for expanding digitized $L \times L$ images representing functions on $[-1, 1]^2$ supported on the disk $\{x \in \mathbb{R}^2 : |x|<1\}$ in the harmonics (Dirichlet Laplacian eigenfunctions) on the disk.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-expansion-into-harmonics-on-the-disk-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atomic structure generation from reconstructing structural fingerprints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomic-structure-generation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These methods would help identify or, in the case of generative models, even create novel crystal structures of materials with a set of specified functional properties to then be synthesized or isolated in the laboratory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomic-structure-generation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstracting Sketches through Simple Primitives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstracting-sketches-through-simple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Toward equipping machines with such capabilities, we propose the Primitive-based Sketch Abstraction task where the goal is to represent sketches using a fixed set of drawing primitives under the influence of a budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstracting-sketches-through-simple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Video Deblurring Guided by Motion Magnitude</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-video-deblurring-guided-by-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video deblurring is a highly under-constrained problem due to the spatially and temporally varying blur.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-video-deblurring-guided-by-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AADG: Automatic Augmentation for Domain Generalization on Retinal Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aadg-automatic-augmentation-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a data manipulation based domain generalization method, called Automated Augmentation for Domain Generalization (AADG).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aadg-automatic-augmentation-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Vizier: Distributed Infrastructure and API for Reliable and Flexible Blackbox Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-vizier-distributed-infrastructure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vizier is the de-facto blackbox and hyperparameter optimization service across Google, having optimized some of Google's largest products and research efforts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-vizier-distributed-infrastructure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaKo: Knowledge-driven Visual Question Answering via Late Knowledge-to-Text Injection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lako-knowledge-driven-visual-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual question answering (VQA) often requires an understanding of visual concepts and language semantics, which relies on external knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lako-knowledge-driven-visual-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-shot Learning with Class-Covariance Metric for Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-learning-with-class-covariance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, embedding and metric-based few-shot learning (FSL) has been introduced into hyperspectral image classification (HSIC) and achieved impressive progress.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-learning-with-class-covariance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPAIC: A Spike-based Artificial Intelligence Computing Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spaic-a-spike-based-artificial-intelligence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a Python based spiking neural network (SNN) simulation and training framework, aka SPAIC that aims to support brain-inspired model and algorithm researches integrated with features from both deep learning and neuroscience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spaic-a-spike-based-artificial-intelligence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Visual Representation from Modality-Shared Contrastive Language-Image Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-visual-representation-from-modality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale multi-modal contrastive pre-training has demonstrated great utility to learn transferable features for a range of downstream tasks by mapping multiple modalities into a shared embedding space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-visual-representation-from-modality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CENet: Toward Concise and Efficient LiDAR Semantic Segmentation for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cenet-toward-concise-and-efficient-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate and fast scene understanding is one of the challenging task for autonomous driving, which requires to take full advantage of LiDAR point clouds for semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cenet-toward-concise-and-efficient-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compositional Human-Scene Interaction Synthesis with Semantic Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-human-scene-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, inspired by the compositional nature of interactions that humans can simultaneously interact with multiple objects, we define interaction semantics as the composition of varying numbers of atomic action-object pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-human-scene-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Series-Parallel Lookup Tables for Efficient Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-series-parallel-lookup-tables-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, we propose a parallel network which includes two branches of cascaded lookup tables which process different components of the input low-resolution images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-series-parallel-lookup-tables-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TINYCD: A (Not So) Deep Learning Model For Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinycd-a-not-so-deep-learning-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To compose the features extracted from the two images, we introduce a novel, economical in terms of parameters, mixing block capable of cross correlating features in both space and time domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinycd-a-not-so-deep-learning-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Learning under Latent Label Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-under-latent-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus motivated, we introduce a practical algorithm that leverages domain-discriminative models as follows: (i) push examples through domain discriminator $p(d|\mathbf{x})$; (ii) discretize the data by clustering examples in $p(d|\mathbf{x})$ space; (iii) perform non-negative matrix factorization on the discrete data; (iv) combine the recovered $p(y|d)$ with the discriminator outputs $p(d|\mathbf{x})$ to compute $p_d(y|x) \; \forall d$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-under-latent-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Protein Representations via Complete 3D Graph Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-protein-representations-via-complete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our ProNet is very flexible and can be used to compute protein representations at different levels of granularity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-protein-representations-via-complete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S-Prompts Learning with Pre-trained Transformers: An Occam's Razor for Domain Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-prompts-learning-with-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose one simple paradigm (named as S-Prompting) and two concrete approaches to highly reduce the forgetting degree in one of the most typical continual learning scenarios, i. e., domain increment learning (DIL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-prompts-learning-with-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Probabilistic U-Net for medical image segementation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-probabilistic-u-net-for-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the Generalized Probabilistic U-Net, which extends the Probabilistic U-Net by allowing more general forms of the Gaussian distribution as the latent space distribution that can better approximate the uncertainty in the reference segmentations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-probabilistic-u-net-for-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modality Image Registration using a Training-Time Privileged Third Modality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modality-image-registration-using-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we consider the task of pairwise cross-modality image registration, which may benefit from exploiting additional images available only at training time from an additional modality that is different to those being registered.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modality-image-registration-using-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bilateral Self-unbiased Learning from Biased Implicit Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilateral-self-unbiased-learning-from-biased</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implicit feedback has been widely used to build commercial recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilateral-self-unbiased-learning-from-biased</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repeated Environment Inference for Invariant Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repeated-environment-inference-for-invariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The EI step uses a reference model which focuses on spurious correlations to efficiently reach a good environment partition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repeated-environment-inference-for-invariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-displacement 3D Object Tracking with Hybrid Non-local Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-displacement-3d-object-tracking-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimization-based 3D object tracking is known to be precise and fast, but sensitive to large inter-frame displacements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-displacement-3d-object-tracking-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Representing Random Utility Choice Models with Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representing-random-utility-choice-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the successes of deep learning, we propose a class of neural network-based discrete choice models, called RUMnets, which is inspired by the random utility maximization (RUM) framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representing-random-utility-choice-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Hierarchy Aware Features for Reducing Mistake Severity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-hierarchy-aware-features-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach for learning Hierarchy Aware Features (HAF) that leverages classifiers at each level of the hierarchy that are constrained to generate predictions consistent with the label hierarchy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-hierarchy-aware-features-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProposalContrast: Unsupervised Pre-training for LiDAR-based 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proposalcontrast-unsupervised-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing approaches for unsupervised point cloud pre-training are constrained to either scene-level or point/voxel-level instance discrimination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proposalcontrast-unsupervised-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-supervised 3D Object Detection with Proficient Teachers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-3d-object-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reduce the dependence on large supervision, semi-supervised learning (SSL) based approaches have been proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-3d-object-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criteria Comparative Learning for Real-scene Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/criteria-comparative-learning-for-real-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the observation that the contrastive relationship could also exist between the criteria, in this work, we propose a novel training paradigm for RealSR, named Criteria Comparative Learning (Cria-CL), by developing contrastive losses defined on criteria instead of image patches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/criteria-comparative-learning-for-real-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visually explaining 3D-CNN predictions for video classification with an adaptive occlusion sensitivity analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visually-explaining-3d-cnn-predictions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key idea here is to occlude a specific volume of data by a 3D mask in an input 3D temporal-spatial data space and then measure the change degree in the output score.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visually-explaining-3d-cnn-predictions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Adaptation under Open Set Label Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptation-under-open-set-label-shift</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the problem of domain adaptation under Open Set Label Shift (OSLS) where the label distribution can change arbitrarily and a new class may arrive during deployment, but the class-conditional distributions p(x|y) are domain-invariant.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptation-under-open-set-label-shift</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
