<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 21:06:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>BitsFusion: 1.99 bits Weight Quantization of Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitsfusion-1-99-bits-weight-quantization-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion-based image generation models have achieved great success in recent years by showing the capability of synthesizing high-quality content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitsfusion-1-99-bits-weight-quantization-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batch-in-Batch: a new adversarial training framework for initial perturbation and sample selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batch-in-batch-a-new-adversarial-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial training methods commonly generate independent initial perturbation for adversarial samples from a simple uniform distribution, and obtain the training batch for the classifier without selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batch-in-batch-a-new-adversarial-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSNet: A Novel Way to Use Atrous Convolutions in Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsnet-a-novel-way-to-use-atrous-convolutions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Following these guidelines, we propose DSNet, a Dual-Branch CNN architecture, which incorporates atrous convolutions in the shallow layers of the model architecture, as well as pretraining the nearly entire encoder on ImageNet to achieve better performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsnet-a-novel-way-to-use-atrous-convolutions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMEmbed: Rethinking Lightweight LLM's Genuine Function in Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmembed-rethinking-lightweight-llm-s-genuine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the booming of Large Language Models (LLMs), prompt-learning has become a promising method mainly researched in various research areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmembed-rethinking-lightweight-llm-s-genuine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Language Models Understand Morality? Towards a Robust Detection of Moral Content</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-language-models-understand-morality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Davinci model as a state-of-the-art zero-shot unsupervised moral values classifier, pushing the boundaries of moral value detection without the need for explicit training on labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-language-models-understand-morality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jailbreak Vision Language Models via Bi-Modal Adversarial Prompt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jailbreak-vision-language-models-via-bi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, this paper introduces the Bi-Modal Adversarial Prompt Attack (BAP), which executes jailbreaks by optimizing textual and visual prompts cohesively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jailbreak-vision-language-models-via-bi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-temporal Early Prediction based on Multi-objective Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-early-prediction-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accuracy and timeliness are indeed often conflicting goals in prediction tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-early-prediction-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReST-MCTS*: LLM Self-Training via Process Reward Guided Tree Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rest-mcts-llm-self-training-via-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first show that the tree-search policy in ReST-MCTS* achieves higher accuracy compared with prior LLM reasoning baselines such as Best-of-N and Tree-of-Thought, within the same search budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rest-mcts-llm-self-training-via-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoTetris: Towards Compositional Text-to-Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videotetris-towards-compositional-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have demonstrated great success in text-to-video (T2V) generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videotetris-towards-compositional-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VISTA: Visualized Text Embedding For Universal Multi-Modal Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vista-visualized-text-embedding-for-universal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thirdly, we introduce a multi-stage training algorithm, which first aligns the visual token embedding with the text encoder using massive weakly labeled data, and then develops multi-modal representation capability using the generated composed image-text data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vista-visualized-text-embedding-for-universal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering Limitations of Large Language Models in Information Seeking from Tables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-limitations-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Seeking information from tables (TIS) is a crucial capability for Large Language Models (LLMs), serving as the foundation of knowledge-based Q&A systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-limitations-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentGym: Evolving Large Language Model-based Agents across Diverse Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentgym-evolving-large-language-model-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building generalist agents that can handle diverse tasks and evolve themselves across different environments is a long-term goal in the AI community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentgym-evolving-large-language-model-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos with Keywords: Exposing Large Language Models Sycophancy to Misleading Keywords and Evaluating Defense Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chaos-with-keywords-exposing-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study explores the sycophantic tendencies of Large Language Models (LLMs), where these models tend to provide answers that match what users want to hear, even if they are not entirely correct.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chaos-with-keywords-exposing-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reassessing How to Compare and Improve the Calibration of Machine Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reassessing-how-to-compare-and-improve-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A machine learning model is calibrated if its predicted probability for an outcome matches the observed frequency for that outcome conditional on the model prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reassessing-how-to-compare-and-improve-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compressible Dynamics in Deep Overparameterized Low-Rank Learning &amp; Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compressible-dynamics-in-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In practice, we demonstrate the effectiveness of this approach for deep low-rank matrix completion as well as fine-tuning language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compressible-dynamics-in-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantically Diverse Language Generation for Uncertainty Estimation in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantically-diverse-language-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current LLMs generate text in an autoregressive fashion by predicting and appending text tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantically-diverse-language-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIGMARK: A Black-Box Approach for Enhancing Image Watermarks against Diffusion Model Edits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jigmark-a-black-box-approach-for-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we investigate the vulnerability of image watermarks to diffusion-model-based image editing, a challenge exacerbated by the computational cost of accessing gradient information and the closed-source nature of many diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jigmark-a-black-box-approach-for-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow and Light: Digitally Reconstructed Radiographs for Disease Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadow-and-light-digitally-reconstructed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, CheXnet trained on the CheXpert dataset can accurately identify several pathologies, even when operating out of distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadow-and-light-digitally-reconstructed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Batched Linear Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-batched-linear-bandits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the E$^4$ algorithm for the batched linear bandit problem, incorporating an Explore-Estimate-Eliminate-Exploit framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-batched-linear-bandits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring and Addressing Indexical Bias in Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-and-addressing-indexical-bias-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Information Retrieval (IR) systems are designed to deliver relevant content, but traditional systems may not optimize rankings for fairness, neutrality, or the balance of ideas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-and-addressing-indexical-bias-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offline Multi-Objective Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-multi-objective-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Offline optimization aims to maximize a black-box objective function with a static dataset and has wide applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-multi-objective-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vectorized Conditional Neural Fields: A Framework for Solving Time-dependent Parametric Partial Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vectorized-conditional-neural-fields-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer models are increasingly used for solving Partial Differential Equations (PDEs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vectorized-conditional-neural-fields-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M3LEO: A Multi-Modal, Multi-Label Earth Observation Dataset Integrating Interferometric SAR and RGB Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3leo-a-multi-modal-multi-label-earth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Satellite-based remote sensing has revolutionised the way we address global challenges in a rapidly evolving world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3leo-a-multi-modal-multi-label-earth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C^2RV: Cross-Regional and Cross-View Learning for Sparse-View CBCT Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c-2rv-cross-regional-and-cross-view-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cone beam computed tomography (CBCT) is an important imaging technology widely used in medical scenarios, such as diagnosis and preoperative planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c-2rv-cross-regional-and-cross-view-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Multi-Scale Decomposition Framework for Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-multi-scale-decomposition-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based and MLP-based methods have emerged as leading approaches in time series forecasting (TSF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-multi-scale-decomposition-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the World Model Implicit in a Generative Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-world-model-implicit-in-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building generative models that meaningfully capture the underlying logic of the domains they model would be immensely valuable; our results suggest new ways to assess how close a given model is to that goal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-world-model-implicit-in-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-Rank Similarity Mining for Multimodal Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-rank-similarity-mining-for-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though dataset distillation has witnessed rapid development in recent years, the distillation of multimodal data, e. g., image-text pairs, poses unique and under-explored challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-rank-similarity-mining-for-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spherinator and HiPSter: Representation Learning for Unbiased Knowledge Discovery from Simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spherinator-and-hipster-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a prototype using a rotational invariant hyperspherical variational convolutional autoencoder, utilizing a power distribution in the latent space, and trained on galaxies from IllustrisTNG simulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spherinator-and-hipster-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PaCE: Parsimonious Concept Engineering for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pace-parsimonious-concept-engineering-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Alignment methods are designed to reduce such undesirable output, via techniques such as fine-tuning, prompt engineering, and representation engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pace-parsimonious-concept-engineering-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReNO: Enhancing One-step Text-to-Image Models through Reward-based Noise Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reno-enhancing-one-step-text-to-image-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, given the same computational resources, a ReNO-optimized one-step model outperforms widely-used open-source models such as SDXL and PixArt-$\alpha$, highlighting the efficiency and effectiveness of ReNO in enhancing T2I model performance at inference time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reno-enhancing-one-step-text-to-image-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLSP-Emo: Towards Empathetic Large Speech-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blsp-emo-towards-empathetic-large-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present BLSP-Emo (Bootstrapped Language-Speech Pretraining with Emotion support), a novel approach to developing an end-to-end speech-language model capable of understanding both semantics and emotions in speech and generate empathetic responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blsp-emo-towards-empathetic-large-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HackAtari: Atari Learning Environments for Robust and Continual Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hackatari-atari-learning-environments-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, HackAtari can be used to improve the robustness of current and future RL algorithms, allowing Neuro-Symbolic RL, curriculum RL, causal RL, as well as LLM-driven RL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hackatari-atari-learning-environments-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lean Workbook: A large-scale Lean problem set formalized from natural language math problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lean-workbook-a-large-scale-lean-problem-set</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results indicate that the synthetic data pipeline can provide useful training data and improve the performance of LLMs in translating and understanding complex mathematical problems and proofs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lean-workbook-a-large-scale-lean-problem-set</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LNQ Challenge 2023: Learning Mediastinal Lymph Node Segmentation with a Probabilistic Lymph Node Atlas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lnq-challenge-2023-learning-mediastinal-lymph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The evaluation of lymph node metastases plays a crucial role in achieving precise cancer staging, influencing subsequent decisions regarding treatment options.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lnq-challenge-2023-learning-mediastinal-lymph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HeSum: a Novel Dataset for Abstractive Text Summarization in Hebrew</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hesum-a-novel-dataset-for-abstractive-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While large language models (LLMs) excel in various natural language tasks in English, their performance in lower-resourced languages like Hebrew, especially for generative tasks such as abstractive summarization, remains unclear.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hesum-a-novel-dataset-for-abstractive-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stereo-Depth Fusion through Virtual Pattern Projection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stereo-depth-fusion-through-virtual-pattern</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel general-purpose stereo and depth data fusion paradigm that mimics the active stereo principle by replacing the unreliable physical pattern projector with a depth sensor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stereo-depth-fusion-through-virtual-pattern</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Tissue Plane to Organ World: A Benchmark Dataset for Multimodal Biomedical Image Registration using Deep Co-Attention Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-tissue-plane-to-organ-world-a-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To gain the most information from this multimodal, multiscale approach, it is desirable to identify precisely where a histologic tissue section was taken from within the organ in order to correlate with the tissue features in exactly the same organ region.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-tissue-plane-to-organ-world-a-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bench2Drive: Towards Multi-Ability Benchmarking of Closed-Loop End-To-End Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bench2drive-towards-multi-ability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an era marked by the rapid scaling of foundation models, autonomous driving technologies are approaching a transformative threshold where end-to-end autonomous driving (E2E-AD) emerges due to its potential of scaling up in the data-driven manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bench2drive-towards-multi-ability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 3D-PC: a benchmark for visual perspective taking in humans and machines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-3d-pc-a-benchmark-for-visual-perspective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is an essential feature of human intelligence, which develops over the first decade of life and requires an ability to process the 3D structure of visual scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-3d-pc-a-benchmark-for-visual-perspective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Expressive Power of Spectral Invariant Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-expressive-power-of-spectral-invariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, we prove that EPNN itself is bounded by a recently proposed class of Subgraph GNNs, implying that all these spectral invariant architectures are strictly less expressive than 3-WL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-expressive-power-of-spectral-invariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging automatic strategy discovery to teach people how to select better projects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-automatic-strategy-discovery-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a computational method (MGPS) that automatically discovers project selection strategies that are optimized for real people and develop an intelligent tutor that teaches the discovered strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-automatic-strategy-discovery-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The CLRS-Text Algorithmic Reasoning Language Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-clrs-text-algorithmic-reasoning-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Three years ago, a similar issue was identified and rectified in the field of neural algorithmic reasoning, with the advent of the CLRS benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-clrs-text-algorithmic-reasoning-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pointer-Guided Pre-Training: Infusing Large Language Models with Paragraph-Level Contextual Awareness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointer-guided-pre-training-infusing-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce "pointer-guided segment ordering" (SO), a novel pre-training technique aimed at enhancing the contextual understanding of paragraph-level text representations in large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointer-guided-pre-training-infusing-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABEX: Data Augmentation for Low-Resource NLU via Expanding Abstract Descriptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abex-data-augmentation-for-low-resource-nlu</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present ABEX, a novel and effective generative data augmentation methodology for low-resource Natural Language Understanding (NLU) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abex-data-augmentation-for-low-resource-nlu</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class-Aware Cartilage Segmentation for Autonomous US-CT Registration in Robotic Intercostal Ultrasound Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-aware-cartilage-segmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, a dense skeleton graph-based non-rigid registration is presented to map the intercostal scanning path from a generic template to individual patients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-aware-cartilage-segmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLACE: Global Local Accelerated Coordinate Encoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glace-global-local-accelerated-coordinate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose GLACE, which integrates pre-trained global and local encodings and enables SCR to scale to large scenes with only a single small-sized network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glace-global-local-accelerated-coordinate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coarse-To-Fine Tensor Trains for Compact Visual Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse-to-fine-tensor-trains-for-compact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This has prevented practitioners from deploying the full potential of tensor networks for visual data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse-to-fine-tensor-trains-for-compact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency-based Matcher for Long-tailed Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-based-matcher-for-long-tailed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The successful application of semantic segmentation technology in the real world has been among the most exciting achievements in the computer vision community over the past decade.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-based-matcher-for-long-tailed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amortized Equation Discovery in Hybrid Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amortized-equation-discovery-in-hybrid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hybrid dynamical systems are prevalent in science and engineering to express complex systems with continuous and discrete states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amortized-equation-discovery-in-hybrid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Far Can We Compress Instant-NGP-Based NeRF?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-can-we-compress-instant-ngp-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce the Context-based NeRF Compression (CNC) framework, which leverages highly efficient context models to provide a storage-friendly NeRF representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-can-we-compress-instant-ngp-based</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
