<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 21:08:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Parametric Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-parametric-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on theoretical analysis, we observe that supervised contrastive loss tends to bias high-frequency classes and thus increases the difficulty of imbalanced learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-parametric-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device-friendly Guava fruit and leaf disease detection using deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/device-friendly-guava-fruit-and-leaf-disease</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents a deep learning-based plant disease diagnostic system using images of fruits and leaves.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/device-friendly-guava-fruit-and-leaf-disease</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Motion Deblurring Training: A Segmentation-Based Method for Simulating Non-Uniform Motion Blurred Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-motion-deblurring-training-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Successful training of end-to-end deep networks for real motion deblurring requires datasets of sharp/blurred image pairs that are realistic and diverse enough to achieve generalization to real blurred images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-motion-deblurring-training-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Attention GAN for Vehicle Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-attention-gan-for-vehicle-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The design of a safe and reliable Autonomous Driving stack (ADS) is one of the most challenging tasks of our era.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-attention-gan-for-vehicle-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Resolution in the Context of Efficient Video Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-resolution-in-the-context-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our key finding is that the major cause of degradation is not information loss in the down-sampling process, but rather the mismatch between network architecture and input scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-resolution-in-the-context-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-stage image denoising with the wavelet transform</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stage-image-denoising-with-the-wavelet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep convolutional neural networks (CNNs) are used for image denoising via automatically mining accurate structure information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stage-image-denoising-with-the-wavelet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAD: A Large-Scale Benchmark for Traffic Accidents Detection from Video Surveillance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tad-a-large-scale-benchmark-for-traffic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After integration and annotation by various dimensions, a large-scale traffic accidents dataset named TAD is proposed in this work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tad-a-large-scale-benchmark-for-traffic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAPA: Similarity-Aware Point Affiliation for Feature Upsampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sapa-similarity-aware-point-affiliation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce point affiliation into feature upsampling, a notion that describes the affiliation of each upsampled point to a semantic cluster formed by local decoder feature points with semantic similarity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sapa-similarity-aware-point-affiliation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Predictive Monitoring of Dynamic Systems for Signal Temporal Logic Specifications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-predictive-monitoring-of-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, effective approaches for the computation of feasible sets of STL formulae are provided.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-predictive-monitoring-of-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EasyRec: An easy-to-use, extendable and efficient framework for building industrial recommendation systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyrec-an-easy-to-use-extendable-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present EasyRec, an easy-to-use, extendable and efficient recommendation framework for building industrial recommendation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyrec-an-easy-to-use-extendable-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Material Prediction for Design Automation Using Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/material-prediction-for-design-automation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Successful material selection is critical in designing and manufacturing products for design automation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/material-prediction-for-design-automation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Large Language Models Truly Understand Prompts? A Case Study with Negated Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-truly-understand</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous work has shown that there exists a scaling law between the size of Language Models (LMs) and their zero-shot performance on different downstream NLP tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-truly-understand</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Image Clustering through Sample Ranking and Its Application to remote--sensing images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-image-clustering-through-sample</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Performing our method on a variety of datasets from remote sensing, we show that our method can be effectively applied to remote--sensing images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-image-clustering-through-sample</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News Summarization and Evaluation in the Era of GPT-3</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/news-summarization-and-evaluation-in-the-era</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study its impact on text summarization, focusing on the classic benchmark domain of news summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/news-summarization-and-evaluation-in-the-era</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOViS: Learning Orientation and Visual Signals for Vision and Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lovis-learning-orientation-and-visual-signals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding spatial and visual information is essential for a navigation agent who follows natural language instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lovis-learning-orientation-and-visual-signals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FONDUE: an algorithm to find the optimal dimensionality of the latent representations of variational autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fondue-an-algorithm-to-find-the-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the discrepancies between the IDE of the mean and sampled representations of a VAE after only a few steps of training reveal the presence of passive variables in the latent space, which, in well-behaved VAEs, indicates a superfluous number of dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fondue-an-algorithm-to-find-the-optimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where2comm: Communication-Efficient Collaborative Perception via Spatial Confidence Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/where2comm-communication-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Where2comm has two distinct advantages: i) it considers pragmatic compression and uses less communication to achieve higher perception performance by focusing on perceptually critical areas; and ii) it can handle varying communication bandwidth by dynamically adjusting spatial areas involved in communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/where2comm-communication-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Projections to Linear Subspaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-projections-to-linear-subspaces</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The merit of projecting data onto linear subspaces is well known from, e. g., dimension reduction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-projections-to-linear-subspaces</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Content-Emotion Duality via Disentanglement for Empathetic Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-content-emotion-duality-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve the task, it is essential to model the content-emotion duality of a dialogue, which is composed of the content view (i. e., what personal experiences are described) and the emotion view (i. e., the feelings of the speaker on these experiences).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-content-emotion-duality-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Explainable Machine Learning Approach to Visual-Interactive Labeling: A Case Study on Non-communicable Disease Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-explainable-machine-learning-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that EBM is an excellent choice of predictive model by comparing it against a rule-based and four other machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-explainable-machine-learning-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text Summarization with Oracle Expectation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-summarization-with-oracle-expectation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extractive summarization produces summaries by identifying and concatenating the most important sentences in a document.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-summarization-with-oracle-expectation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal Case Document Similarity: You Need Both Network and Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/legal-case-document-similarity-you-need-both</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments establish that our proposed network-based methods significantly improve the correlation with domain experts' opinion when compared to the existing methods for network-based legal document similarity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/legal-case-document-similarity-you-need-both</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-dataset Training of Transformers for Robust Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dataset-training-of-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the task of robust feature representations, aiming to generalize well on multiple datasets for action recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dataset-training-of-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-Distribution Detection with Hilbert-Schmidt Independence Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-hilbert</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing works attempt to solve the problem by explicitly imposing uncertainty on classifiers when OOD inputs are exposed to the classifier during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-hilbert</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A heterogeneous group CNN for image super-resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-heterogeneous-group-cnn-for-image-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To prevent loss of original information, a multi-level enhancement mechanism guides a CNN to achieve a symmetric architecture for promoting expressive ability of HGSRCNN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-heterogeneous-group-cnn-for-image-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural State-Space Modeling with Latent Causal-Effect Disentanglement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-state-space-modeling-with-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a novel neural formulation of state-space models (SSMs), we first introduce causal-effect modeling of the latent dynamics via a system of interacting neural ODEs that separately describes 1) the continuous-time dynamics of the internal intervention, and 2) its effect on the trajectory of the system's native state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-state-space-modeling-with-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prayatul Matrix: A Direct Comparison Approach to Evaluate Performance of Supervised Machine Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prayatul-matrix-a-direct-comparison-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, an alternative approach is proposed for direct comparison of supervised ML models in terms of individual instances within the dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prayatul-matrix-a-direct-comparison-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-RawVSR: Real-World Raw Video Super-Resolution with a Benchmark Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-rawvsr-real-world-raw-video-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our code and dataset are available at https://github. com/zmzhang1998/Real-RawVSR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-rawvsr-real-world-raw-video-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Learn with Generative Models of Neural Network Checkpoints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-learn-with-generative-models-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore a data-driven approach for learning to optimize neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-learn-with-generative-models-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carbon-Aware EV Charging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/carbon-aware-ev-charging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper examines the problem of optimizing the charging pattern of electric vehicles (EV) by taking real-time electricity grid carbon intensity into consideration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/carbon-aware-ev-charging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shrinking unit: a Graph Convolution-Based Unit for CNN-like 3D Point Cloud Feature Extractors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shrinking-unit-a-graph-convolution-based-unit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While part of this failure stems from the irregularity, unstructuredness, and disorder of point clouds, which makes the task of point cloud feature detection significantly more challenging than the image one, we argue that a lack of inspiration from the image domain might be the primary cause of such a gap.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shrinking-unit-a-graph-convolution-based-unit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORESEE: Model-based Reinforcement Learning using Unscented Transform with application to Tuning of Control Barrier Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foresee-model-based-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method, depending on the number of sigma points employed, can propagate either mean and covariance with minimal points, or higher-order moments with more points similarly to Monte Carlo.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foresee-model-based-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STD: Stable Triangle Descriptor for 3D place recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/std-stable-triangle-descriptor-for-3d-place</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For a triangle, its shape is uniquely determined by the length of the sides or included angles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/std-stable-triangle-descriptor-for-3d-place</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating self-supervised learning for lyrics recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-self-supervised-learning-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lyrics recognition is an important task in music processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-self-supervised-learning-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic Gradient Descent Captures How Children Learn About Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-gradient-descent-captures-how</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the model's learning trajectory captures the developmental trajectories of children, thereby providing support to the idea of development as stochastic optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-gradient-descent-captures-how</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application of Deep Learning in Generating Structured Radiology Reports: A Transformer-Based Technique</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-deep-learning-in-generating-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our transformer-based model in this study outperformed previously applied approaches such as ANN and CNN models based on ROUGE-1, ROUGE-2, ROUGE-L, and BLEU scores of 0. 816, 0. 668, 0. 528, and 0. 743, respectively, while providing an interpretable structured report.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-deep-learning-in-generating-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dive into Self-Supervised Learning for Medical Image Analysis: Data, Models and Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dive-into-self-supervised-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning (SSL) has achieved remarkable performance on various medical imaging tasks by dint of priors from massive unlabeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dive-into-self-supervised-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D$^{\bf{3}}$: Duplicate Detection Decontaminator for Multi-Athlete Tracking in Sports Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-bf-3-duplicate-detection-decontaminator-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, the duplicate detection is newly and precisely defined as occlusion misreporting on the same athlete by multiple detection boxes in one frame.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-bf-3-duplicate-detection-decontaminator-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Reward Shaping for a Robotic Sequential Picking Task from Visual Observations in a Logistics Scenario</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-reward-shaping-for-a-robotic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We focus on an unloading problem, typical of the logistics sector, modeled as a sequential pick-and-place task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-reward-shaping-for-a-robotic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Example Influence in Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-example-influence-in-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual Learning (CL) sequentially learns new tasks like human beings, with the goal to achieve better Stability (S, remembering past tasks) and Plasticity (P, adapting to new tasks).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-example-influence-in-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Transport-based Identity Matching for Identity-invariant Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-based-identity-matching-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, to find pairs of similar expressions from different identities, we define the inter-feature similarity as a transportation cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-based-identity-matching-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAESim: A probabilistic approach for self-supervised prototype discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vaesim-a-probabilistic-approach-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we reconstruct the sample based on a similarity measure between the sample embedding and the prototypical vectors of the clusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vaesim-a-probabilistic-approach-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-modal Segment Assemblage Network for Ad Video Editing with Importance-Coherence Reward</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-segment-assemblage-network-for-ad</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The existing method performs well at video segmentation stages but suffers from the problems of dependencies on extra cumbersome models and poor performance at the segment assemblage stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-segment-assemblage-network-for-ad</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Exponentially Modified Gaussian Oscillators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-exponentially-modified-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Acoustic modeling serves de-noising, data reconstruction, model-based testing and classification in audio processing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-exponentially-modified-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face Super-Resolution Using Stochastic Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-super-resolution-using-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this is the first time SDEs have been used for such an application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-super-resolution-using-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Semantic Descriptors for Zero-Shot Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-semantic-descriptors-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces a new ZSAR method based on the relationships of actions-objects and actions-descriptive sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-semantic-descriptors-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead or Murdered? Predicting Responsibility Perception in Femicide News Reports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dead-or-murdered-predicting-responsibility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then train regression models that predict the salience of GBV participants with respect to different dimensions of perceived responsibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dead-or-murdered-predicting-responsibility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-monotonic Resource Utilization in the Bandits with Knapsacks Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-monotonic-resource-utilization-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bandits with knapsacks (BwK) is an influential model of sequential decision-making under uncertainty that incorporates resource consumption constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-monotonic-resource-utilization-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developing a Knowledge Graph Framework for Pharmacokinetic Natural Product-Drug Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/developing-a-knowledge-graph-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NP-KG is a heterogeneous KG with biomedical ontologies, linked data, and full texts of the scientific literature, constructed with the Phenotype Knowledge Translator framework and the semantic relation extraction systems, SemRep and Integrated Network and Dynamic Reasoning Assembler.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/developing-a-knowledge-graph-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooperative Tuning of Multi-Agent Optimal Control Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-tuning-of-multi-agent-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from classical techniques for tuning parameters in a controller, we allow tunable parameters appearing in both the system dynamics and the objective functions of each agent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-tuning-of-multi-agent-optimal</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
