<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:10:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Theoretical Framework for Explaining Reinforcement Learning with Shapley Values</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-theoretical-framework-for-explaining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop a theoretical framework for explaining reinforcement learning through the influence of state features, which represent what the agent observes in its environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-theoretical-framework-for-explaining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Latent-Space Constraints in Personalized FL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-latent-space-constraints-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the Ditto algorithm is specifically considered, such measures are directly applicable to a number of other pFL settings, and the results motivate the use of constraints tailored to the various kinds of heterogeneity expected in FL systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-latent-space-constraints-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concept-Level Explainability for Auditing &amp; Steering LLM Responses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-level-explainability-for-auditing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As large language models (LLMs) become widely deployed, concerns about their safety and alignment grow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-level-explainability-for-auditing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIS Data-Driven Maritime Monitoring Based on Transformer: A Comprehensive Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ais-data-driven-maritime-monitoring-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, this paper reviews the research on Transformer-based AIS data-driven maritime monitoring, providing a comprehensive overview of the current applications of Transformer models in the marine field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ais-data-driven-maritime-monitoring-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifying Causal Direction via Variational Bayesian Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-causal-direction-via-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Telling apart the cause and effect between two random variables with purely observational data is a challenging problem that finds applications in various scientific disciplines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-causal-direction-via-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DynamicRAG: Leveraging Outputs of Large Language Model as Feedback for Dynamic Reranking in Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamicrag-leveraging-outputs-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) systems combine large language models (LLMs) with external knowledge retrieval, making them highly effective for knowledge-intensive tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamicrag-leveraging-outputs-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certified Data Removal Under High-dimensional Settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certified-data-removal-under-high-dimensional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine unlearning focuses on the computationally efficient removal of specific training data from trained models, ensuring that the influence of forgotten data is effectively eliminated without the need for full retraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certified-data-removal-under-high-dimensional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEAD: Iterative Data Selection for Efficient LLM Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lead-iterative-data-selection-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instruction tuning has emerged as a critical paradigm for improving the capabilities and alignment of large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lead-iterative-data-selection-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HALO: Half Life-Based Outdated Fact Filtering in Temporal Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/halo-half-life-based-outdated-fact-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[HALO consists of three modules: the temporal fact attention module, the dynamic relation-aware encoder module, and the outdated fact filtering module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/halo-half-life-based-outdated-fact-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReCDAP: Relation-Based Conditional Diffusion with Attention Pooling for Few-Shot Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recdap-relation-based-conditional-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Graphs (KGs), composed of triples in the form of (head, relation, tail) and consisting of entities and relations, play a key role in information retrieval systems such as question answering, entity search, and recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recdap-relation-based-conditional-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Survival Modeling in the Age of Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-survival-modeling-in-the-age-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior studies have trained bespoke cancer survival prediction models from unimodal or multimodal TCGA data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-survival-modeling-in-the-age-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring General Intelligence with Generated Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-general-intelligence-with-generated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, gg-bench is synthetically generated by (1) using a large language model (LLM) to generate natural language descriptions of novel games, (2) using the LLM to implement each game in code as a Gym environment, and (3) training reinforcement learning (RL) agents via self-play on the generated games.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-general-intelligence-with-generated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chronocept: Instilling a Sense of Time in Machines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chronocept-instilling-a-sense-of-time-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human cognition is deeply intertwined with a sense of time, known as Chronoception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chronocept-instilling-a-sense-of-time-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YuLan-OneSim: Towards the Next Generation of Social Simulator with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yulan-onesim-towards-the-next-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demonstrate the advantages of YuLan-OneSim, we conduct experiments to evaluate the quality of the automatically generated scenarios, the reliability, efficiency, and scalability of the simulation process, as well as the performance of the AI social researcher.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yulan-onesim-towards-the-next-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kalman Filter Enhanced GRPO for Reinforcement Learning-Based Language Model Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kalman-filter-enhanced-grpo-for-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, for language modeling, Group Relative Policy Optimization (GRPO) is proposed to compute the advantage for each output by subtracting the mean reward, as the baseline, for all outputs in the group.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kalman-filter-enhanced-grpo-for-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-training vs. Fine-tuning: A Reproducibility Study on Dense Retrieval Knowledge Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-vs-fine-tuning-a-reproducibility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research has questioned the role of fine-tuning vs. that of pre-training within dense retrievers, specifically arguing that retrieval knowledge is primarily gained during pre-training, meaning knowledge not acquired during pre-training cannot be sub-sequentially acquired via fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-vs-fine-tuning-a-reproducibility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Continuous Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-continuous-generative-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a unified framework for training, sampling, and analyzing these models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-continuous-generative-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Kernel Configurations at Scale: A Dataset for Performance and Evolution Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linux-kernel-configurations-at-scale-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Configuring the Linux kernel to meet specific requirements, such as binary size, is highly challenging due to its immense complexity-with over 15, 000 interdependent options evolving rapidly across different versions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linux-kernel-configurations-at-scale-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cache-Efficient Posterior Sampling for Reinforcement Learning with LLM-Derived Priors Across Discrete and Continuous Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cache-efficient-posterior-sampling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Integrating large language models (LLMs) as priors in reinforcement learning (RL) offers significant advantages but comes with substantial computational costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cache-efficient-posterior-sampling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALPCAH: Subspace Learning for Sample-wise Heteroscedastic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpcah-subspace-learning-for-sample-wise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper develops a subspace learning method, named ALPCAH, that can estimate the sample-wise noise variances and use this information to improve the estimate of the subspace basis associated with the low-rank structure of the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpcah-subspace-learning-for-sample-wise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Codifying Character Logic in Role-Playing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codifying-character-logic-in-role-playing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces Codified Profiles for role-playing, a novel approach that represents character logic as structured, executable functions for behavioral decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codifying-character-logic-in-role-playing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Actionable Pedagogical Feedback: A Multi-Perspective Analysis of Mathematics Teaching and Tutoring Dialogue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-actionable-pedagogical-feedback-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Effective feedback is essential for refining instructional practices in mathematics education, and researchers often turn to advanced natural language processing (NLP) models to analyze classroom dialogues from multiple perspectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-actionable-pedagogical-feedback-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCPCA: Fuzzy clustering of high-dimensional time series based on common principal component analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fcpca-fuzzy-clustering-of-high-dimensional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clustering multivariate time series data is a crucial task in many domains, as it enables the identification of meaningful patterns and groups in time-evolving data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fcpca-fuzzy-clustering-of-high-dimensional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABS-Mamba: SAM2-Driven Bidirectional Spiral Mamba Network for Medical Image Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abs-mamba-sam2-driven-bidirectional-spiral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate multi-modal medical image translation requires ha-rmonizing global anatomical semantics and local structural fidelity, a challenge complicated by intermodality information loss and structural distortion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abs-mamba-sam2-driven-bidirectional-spiral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anatomical Attention Alignment representation for Radiology Report Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomical-attention-alignment-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated Radiology report generation (RRG) aims at producing detailed descriptions of medical images, reducing radiologists' workload and improving access to high-quality diagnostic services.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomical-attention-alignment-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Visual Autoregressive Generation via Score Maximization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-visual-autoregressive-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When applied to continuous modalities such as visual data, Visual AutoRegressive modeling (VAR) typically resorts to quantization-based approaches to cast the data into a discrete space, which can introduce significant information loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-visual-autoregressive-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web-Bench: A LLM Code Benchmark Based on Web Standards and Frameworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/web-bench-a-llm-code-benchmark-based-on-web</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Among various attempts to address benchmark saturation, approaches based on software engineering have stood out, but the saturation of existing software engineering benchmarks is rapidly increasing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/web-bench-a-llm-code-benchmark-based-on-web</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skull stripping with purely synthetic data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skull-stripping-with-purely-synthetic-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While many skull stripping algorithms have been developed for multi-modal and multi-species cases, there is still a lack of a fundamentally generalizable approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skull-stripping-with-purely-synthetic-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-Driven Dual Style Mixing for Single-Domain Generalized Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-driven-dual-style-mixing-for-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we propose image-level style mixing between the diversified images and source domain images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-driven-dual-style-mixing-for-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metrics that matter: Evaluating image quality metrics for medical image generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metrics-that-matter-evaluating-image-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating generative models for synthetic medical imaging is crucial yet challenging, especially given the high standards of fidelity, anatomical accuracy, and safety required for clinical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metrics-that-matter-evaluating-image-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From raw affiliations to organization identifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-raw-affiliations-to-organization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate affiliation matching, which links affiliation strings to standardized organization identifiers, is critical for improving research metadata quality, facilitating comprehensive bibliometric analyses, and supporting data interoperability across scholarly knowledge bases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-raw-affiliations-to-organization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent RL Scaling Law: Agent RL with Spontaneous Code Execution for Mathematical Problem Solving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-rl-scaling-law-agent-rl-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) often struggle with mathematical reasoning tasks requiring precise, verifiable computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-rl-scaling-law-agent-rl-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Global-Local Feature Matching via Anomaly Synthesis for Multi-Class Point Cloud Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-global-local-feature-matching-via-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, GLFM is structured into three stages: Stage-I proposes an anomaly synthesis pipeline that stretches point clouds to create abundant anomaly data that are utilized to adapt the point cloud feature extractor for better feature representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-global-local-feature-matching-via-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ophora: A Large-Scale Data-Driven Text-Guided Ophthalmic Surgical Video Generation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ophora-a-large-scale-data-driven-text-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In ophthalmic surgery, developing an AI system capable of interpreting surgical videos and predicting subsequent operations requires numerous ophthalmic surgical videos with high-quality annotations, which are difficult to collect due to privacy concerns and labor consumption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ophora-a-large-scale-data-driven-text-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiMo: Unlocking the Reasoning Potential of Language Model -- From Pretraining to Posttraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimo-unlocking-the-reasoning-potential-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present MiMo-7B, a large language model born for reasoning tasks, with optimization across both pre-training and post-training stages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimo-unlocking-the-reasoning-potential-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Search To Sampling: Generative Models For Robust Algorithmic Recourse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-search-to-sampling-generative-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that existing methods train for these objectives separately and then search for recourse through a joint optimization over the recourse goals during inference, leading to poor recourse recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-search-to-sampling-generative-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Only Look One Step: Accelerating Backpropagation in Diffusion Sampling with Gradient Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-look-one-step-accelerating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, many downstream tasks require guiding the generated content based on specific differentiable metrics, typically necessitating backpropagation during the generation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-look-one-step-accelerating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Learning for Class Distribution Mismatch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-for-class-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, with a 60% mismatch proportion on Tiny-ImageNet dataset, our approach, without relying on labeled data, surpasses OpenMatch (with 40 labels per class) by 35. 1%, 63. 7%, and 72. 5% in classifying known, unknown, and new classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-for-class-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whitened CLIP as a Likelihood Surrogate of Images and Captions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whitened-clip-as-a-likelihood-surrogate-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We examine the use of Contrastive Language-Image Pre-training (CLIP) to assess the likelihood of images and captions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whitened-clip-as-a-likelihood-surrogate-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer-Based Dual-Optical Attention Fusion Crowd Head Point Counting and Localization Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-dual-optical-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, the dual-optical attention fusion crowd head point counting model (TAPNet) is proposed to address the problem of the difficulty of accurate counting in complex scenes such as crowd dense occlusion and low light in crowd counting tasks under UAV view.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-dual-optical-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Surgical Safety Margins in Osteosarcoma Knee Resections: An Unsupervised Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-surgical-safety-margins-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[According to the Pan American Health Organization, the number of cancer cases in Latin America was estimated at 4. 2 million in 2022 and is projected to rise to 6. 7 million by 2045.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-surgical-safety-margins-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Fake News Detection: MFND Dataset and Shallow-Deep Multitask Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-fake-news-detection-mfnd-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose a Shallow-Deep Multitask Learning (SDML) model for fake news, which fully uses unimodal and mutual modal features to mine the intrinsic semantics of news.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-fake-news-detection-mfnd-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Frequency Prior-Driven Adaptive Masking for Accelerating Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-frequency-prior-driven-adaptive-masking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The primary challenge in accelerating image super-resolution lies in reducing computation while maintaining performance and adaptability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-frequency-prior-driven-adaptive-masking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MELLM: Exploring LLM-Powered Micro-Expression Understanding Enhanced by Subtle Motion Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mellm-exploring-llm-powered-micro-expression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel Micro-Expression Large Language Model (MELLM), which incorporates a subtle facial motion perception strategy with the strong inference capabilities of MLLMs, representing the first exploration of MLLMs in the domain of ME analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mellm-exploring-llm-powered-micro-expression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Guided Diffusion Model for Single-Step Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-guided-diffusion-model-for-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose SAMSR, a semantic-guided diffusion framework that incorporates semantic segmentation masks into the sampling process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-guided-diffusion-model-for-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Split-then-Join Approach to Abstractive Summarization for Very Long Documents in a Low Resource Setting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-split-then-join-approach-to-abstractive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We'll use the pretrained $\texttt{BIGBIRD-PEGASUS}$ model by fine tuned the model on other domain dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-split-then-join-approach-to-abstractive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning (RL) Meets Urban Climate Modeling: Investigating the Efficacy and Impacts of RL-Based HVAC Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-rl-meets-urban-climate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study proposes an integrated framework combining RL with an urban climate model that incorporates a building energy model, aiming to evaluate the efficacy of RL-based HVAC control across different background climates, impacts of RL strategies on indoor climate and local urban climate, and the transferability of RL strategies across cities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-rl-meets-urban-climate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The power of fine-grained experts: Granularity boosts expressivity in Mixture of Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-power-of-fine-grained-experts-granularity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) layers are increasingly central to frontier model architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-power-of-fine-grained-experts-granularity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Page Classification using LLMs for Crawling Support</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/web-page-classification-using-llms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A web crawler is a system designed to collect web pages, and efficient crawling of new pages requires appropriate algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/web-page-classification-using-llms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Knowledge to Reasoning: Evaluating LLMs for Ionic Liquids Research in Chemical and Biological Engineering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-knowledge-to-reasoning-evaluating-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although Large Language Models (LLMs) have achieved remarkable performance in diverse general knowledge and reasoning tasks, their utility in the scientific domain of Chemical and Biological Engineering (CBE) is unclear.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-knowledge-to-reasoning-evaluating-llms</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
