<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:07:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Subject-Diffusion:Open Domain Personalized Text-to-Image Generation without Test-time Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subject-diffusion-open-domain-personalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Subject-Diffusion, a novel open-domain personalized image generation model that, in addition to not requiring test-time fine-tuning, also only requires a single reference image to support personalized generation of single- or multi-subject in any domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subject-diffusion-open-domain-personalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Character Time-series Matching For Robust License Plate Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/character-time-series-matching-for-robust-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic License Plate Recognition (ALPR) is becoming a popular study area and is applied in many fields such as transportation or smart city.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/character-time-series-matching-for-robust-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UWAT-GAN: Fundus Fluorescein Angiography Synthesis via Ultra-wide-angle Transformation Multi-scale GAN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uwat-gan-fundus-fluorescein-angiography</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on an in-house UWF image dataset demonstrate the superiority of the UWAT-GAN over the state-of-the-art methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uwat-gan-fundus-fluorescein-angiography</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BandRe: Rethinking Band-Pass Filters for Scale-Wise Object Detection Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bandre-rethinking-band-pass-filters-for-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scale-wise evaluation of object detectors is important for real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bandre-rethinking-band-pass-filters-for-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Visual Grounding with Scene Knowledge: Benchmark and Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-visual-grounding-with-scene-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, in this paper, we propose a novel benchmark of \underline{S}cene \underline{K}nowledge-guided \underline{V}isual \underline{G}rounding (SK-VG), where the image content and referring expressions are not sufficient to ground the target objects, forcing the models to have a reasoning ability on the long-form scene knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-visual-grounding-with-scene-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transferability of Convolutional Neural Networks in Stationary Learning Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferability-of-convolutional-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To accomplish this we investigate the properties of CNNs for tasks where the underlying signals are stationary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferability-of-convolutional-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tuning Pre-trained Model via Moment Probing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tuning-pre-trained-model-via-moment-probing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Distinguished from LP which builds a linear classification head based on the mean of final features (e. g., word tokens for ViT) or classification tokens, our MP performs a linear classifier on feature distribution, which provides the stronger representation ability by exploiting richer statistical information inherent in features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tuning-pre-trained-model-via-moment-probing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning minimal representations of stochastic processes with variational autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-minimal-representations-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stochastic processes have found numerous applications in science, as they are broadly used to model a variety of natural phenomena.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-minimal-representations-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Of Models and Tin Men -- a behavioural economics study of principal-agent problems in AI alignment using large-language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/of-models-and-tin-men-a-behavioural-economics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AI Alignment is often presented as an interaction between a single designer and an artificial agent in which the designer attempts to ensure the agent's behavior is consistent with its purpose, and risks arise solely because of conflicts caused by inadvertent misalignment between the utility function intended by the designer and the resulting internal utility function of the agent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/of-models-and-tin-men-a-behavioural-economics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedSoup: Improving Generalization and Personalization in Federated Learning via Selective Model Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedsoup-improving-generalization-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel federated model soup method (i. e., selective interpolation of model parameters) to optimize the trade-off between local and global performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedsoup-improving-generalization-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASK: Fine-grained Language Model Evaluation based on Alignment Skill Sets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flask-fine-grained-language-model-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce FLASK (Fine-grained Language Model Evaluation based on Alignment SKill Sets), a fine-grained evaluation protocol that can be used for both model-based and human-based evaluation which decomposes coarse-level scoring to an instance-wise skill set-level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flask-fine-grained-language-model-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vesper: A Compact and Effective Pretrained Model for Speech Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vesper-a-compact-and-effective-pretrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although PTMs shed new light on artificial general intelligence, they are constructed with general tasks in mind, and thus, their efficacy for specific tasks can be further improved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vesper-a-compact-and-effective-pretrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Flat Learning-based Model Predictive Control Using a Stability, State, and Input Constraining Safety Filter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-flat-learning-based-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This safety filter is then used to refine inputs from a flat model predictive controller to perform constrained nonlinear learning-based optimal control through two successive convex optimizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-flat-learning-based-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuron Sensitivity Guided Test Case Selection for Deep Learning Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuron-sensitivity-guided-test-case-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above-mentioned problem, we propose NSS, Neuron Sensitivity guided test case Selection, which can reduce the labeling time by selecting valuable test cases from unlabeled datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuron-sensitivity-guided-test-case-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PE-YOLO: Pyramid Enhancement Network for Dark Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pe-yolo-pyramid-enhancement-network-for-dark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current object detection models have achieved good results on many benchmark datasets, detecting objects in dark conditions remains a large challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pe-yolo-pyramid-enhancement-network-for-dark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breadcrumbs to the Goal: Goal-Conditioned Exploration from Human-in-the-Loop Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breadcrumbs-to-the-goal-goal-conditioned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This procedure can leverage noisy, asynchronous human feedback to learn policies with no hand-crafted reward design or exploration bonuses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breadcrumbs-to-the-goal-goal-conditioned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoding the Enigma: Benchmarking Humans and AIs on the Many Facets of Working Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-the-enigma-benchmarking-humans-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we introduce a comprehensive Working Memory (WorM) benchmark dataset for this purpose.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-the-enigma-benchmarking-humans-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amortized Variational Inference: When and Why?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amortized-variational-inference-when-and-why</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study A-VI as a general alternative to F-VI for approximate posterior inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amortized-variational-inference-when-and-why</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSQNet: Actor-agnostic Action Recognition with Multi-modal Query</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msqnet-actor-agnostic-action-recognition-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing action recognition methods are typically actor-specific due to the intrinsic topological and apparent differences among the actors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msqnet-actor-agnostic-action-recognition-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Traffic Controller Workload Level Prediction using Conformalized Dynamical Graph Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/air-traffic-controller-workload-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Air traffic control (ATC) is a safety-critical service system that demands constant attention from ground air traffic controllers (ATCos) to maintain daily aviation operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/air-traffic-controller-workload-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing PatchCore for Few/many-shot Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-patchcore-for-few-many-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Exhaustive experiments on the public VisA and MVTec AD datasets reveal that (I) significant performance improvements can be realized by optimizing hyperparameters such as the underlying feature extractor, and that (II) image-level augmentations can, but are not guaranteed, to improve performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-patchcore-for-few-many-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dataset and Strong Baselines for Classification of Czech News Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dataset-and-strong-baselines-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained models for Czech Natural Language Processing are often evaluated on purely linguistic tasks (POS tagging, parsing, NER) and relatively simple classification tasks such as sentiment classification or article classification from a single news source.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dataset-and-strong-baselines-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TREA: Tree-Structure Reasoning Schema for Conversational Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trea-tree-structure-reasoning-schema-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TREA constructs a multi-hierarchical scalable tree as the reasoning structure to clarify the causal relationships between mentioned entities, and fully utilizes historical conversations to generate more reasonable and suitable responses for recommended results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trea-tree-structure-reasoning-schema-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cascade-DETR: Delving into High-Quality Universal Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascade-detr-delving-into-high-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While dominating on the COCO benchmark, recent Transformer-based detection methods are not competitive in diverse domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascade-detr-delving-into-high-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMQ: Evolving Training-free Proxies for Automated Mixed Precision Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emq-evolving-training-free-proxies-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we devise an elaborate search space involving the existing proxies and perform an evolution search to discover the best correlated MQ proxy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emq-evolving-training-free-proxies-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self2Self+: Single-Image Denoising with Self-Supervised Learning and Image Quality Assessment Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self2self-single-image-denoising-with-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the feasibility of denoising procedures, in this study, we proposed a single-image self-supervised learning method in which only the noisy input image is used for network training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self2self-single-image-denoising-with-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperReenact: One-Shot Reenactment via Jointly Learning to Refine and Retarget Faces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperreenact-one-shot-reenactment-via-jointly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present our method for neural face reenactment, called HyperReenact, that aims to generate realistic talking head images of a source identity, driven by a target facial pose.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperreenact-one-shot-reenactment-via-jointly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Knowledge Distillation: Training a Large Model using a Small One for Retinal Image Matching on Limited Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reverse-knowledge-distillation-training-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel approach based on reverse knowledge distillation to train large models with limited data while preventing overfitting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reverse-knowledge-distillation-training-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kick Back &amp; Relax: Learning to Reconstruct the World by Watching SlowTV</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kick-back-relax-learning-to-reconstruct-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, existing approaches limit themselves to the automotive domain, resulting in models incapable of generalizing to complex environments such as natural or indoor settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kick-back-relax-learning-to-reconstruct-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the Factual Knowledge Boundary of Large Language Models with Retrieval Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-factual-knowledge-boundary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we present an initial analysis of the factual knowledge boundaries of LLMs and how retrieval augmentation affects LLMs on open-domain QA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-factual-knowledge-boundary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Spiking-UNet for Image Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-spiking-unet-for-image-processing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we adopt a flow-based training method to fine-tune the converted models, reducing time steps while preserving performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-spiking-unet-for-image-processing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spinal nerve segmentation method and dataset construction in endoscopic surgical scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spinal-nerve-segmentation-method-and-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Endoscopic surgery is currently an important treatment method in the field of spinal surgery and avoiding damage to the spinal nerves through video guidance is a key challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spinal-nerve-segmentation-method-and-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TwinLiteNet: An Efficient and Lightweight Model for Driveable Area and Lane Segmentation in Self-Driving Cars</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/twinlitenet-an-efficient-and-lightweight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driveable Area Segmentation and Lane Detection are particularly important for safe and efficient navigation on the road.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/twinlitenet-an-efficient-and-lightweight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlignDet: Aligning Pre-training and Fine-tuning in Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligndet-aligning-pre-training-and-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose AlignDet, a unified pre-training framework that can be adapted to various existing detectors to alleviate the discrepancies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligndet-aligning-pre-training-and-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Precipitation Nowcasting of Integrated Multi-satellitE Retrievals for GPM: A U-Net Convolutional LSTM Architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-precipitation-nowcasting-of-integrated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a deep learning architecture for nowcasting of precipitation almost globally every 30 min with a 4-hour lead time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-precipitation-nowcasting-of-integrated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Landscape of Natural Language Processing Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-landscape-of-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As an efficient approach to understand, generate, and process natural language texts, research in natural language processing (NLP) has exhibited a rapid spread and wide adoption in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-landscape-of-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLSFormer : Gated - Long, Short Sequence Transformer for Step Recognition in Surgical Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glsformer-gated-long-short-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These results validate the suitability of our proposed approach for automated surgical step recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glsformer-gated-long-short-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FigCaps-HF: A Figure-to-Caption Generative Framework and Benchmark with Human Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/figcaps-hf-a-figure-to-caption-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Captions are crucial for understanding scientific visualizations and documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/figcaps-hf-a-figure-to-caption-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Learning and Bias Correction with Pre-trained Audio Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-and-bias-correction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach allows representations derived for one task to be applied to another, and can result in high accuracy with less stringent training data requirements for the downstream task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-and-bias-correction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event Blob Tracking: An Asynchronous Real-Time Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-blob-tracking-an-asynchronous-real-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event-based cameras have become increasingly popular for tracking fast-moving objects due to their high temporal resolution, low latency, and high dynamic range.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-blob-tracking-an-asynchronous-real-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoxDiff: Text-to-Image Synthesis with Training-Free Box-Constrained Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boxdiff-text-to-image-synthesis-with-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As such paired data is time-consuming and labor-intensive to acquire and restricted to a closed set, this potentially becomes the bottleneck for applications in an open world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boxdiff-text-to-image-synthesis-with-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Sampling with Momentum for Mitigating Divergence Artifacts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-sampling-with-momentum-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first technique involves the incorporation of Heavy Ball (HB) momentum, a well-known technique for improving optimization, into existing diffusion numerical methods to expand their stability regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-sampling-with-momentum-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Language Models on Nucleotide Sequences of Human Genes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-language-models-on-nucleotide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This decision did not change the problem structure a lot due to the fact that both DNA and genes can be seen as 1D sequences consisting of four different nucleotides without losing much information and making too much simplification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-language-models-on-nucleotide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differences Between Hard and Noisy-labeled Samples: An Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differences-between-hard-and-noisy-labeled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study various data partitioning methods in the presence of label noise and observe that filtering out noisy samples from hard samples with this proposed metric results in the best datasets as evidenced by the high test accuracy achieved after models are trained on the filtered datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differences-between-hard-and-noisy-labeled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance Issue Identification in Cloud Systems with Relational-Temporal Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-issue-identification-in-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Performance issues permeate large-scale cloud service systems, which can lead to huge revenue losses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-issue-identification-in-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EdgeAL: An Edge Estimation Based Active Learning Approach for OCT Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edgeal-an-edge-estimation-based-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, selecting data for annotation remains a challenging problem due to the limited information available on unseen data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edgeal-an-edge-estimation-based-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNOS: A Strong Baseline for CAD-based Novel Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cnos-a-strong-baseline-for-cad-based-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a simple three-stage approach to segment unseen objects in RGB images using their CAD models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cnos-a-strong-baseline-for-cad-based-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learned Thresholds Token Merging and Pruning for Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learned-thresholds-token-merging-and-pruning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision transformers have demonstrated remarkable success in a wide range of computer vision tasks over the last years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learned-thresholds-token-merging-and-pruning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlendFace: Re-designing Identity Encoders for Face-Swapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blendface-re-designing-identity-encoders-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The great advancements of generative adversarial networks and face recognition models in computer vision have made it possible to swap identities on images from single sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blendface-re-designing-identity-encoders-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Federated Learning: State-of-the-art and Research Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-federated-learning-state-of-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, a systematic survey on this topic about the research challenges and state-of-the-art is essential.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-federated-learning-state-of-the</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
