<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:18:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Uniform Convergence of Lipschitz Functions with Dependent Gaussian Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniform-convergence-of-lipschitz-functions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many practical learning problems, training samples are not i. i. d., and there is an intrinsic dependency among samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniform-convergence-of-lipschitz-functions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CG-TGAN: Conditional Generative Adversarial Networks with Graph Neural Networks for Tabular Data Synthesizing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cg-tgan-conditional-generative-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The synthesized tabular data should reflect the relational meaning between columns of tabular data, so modeling the probability distribution of tabular data is a non-trivial task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cg-tgan-conditional-generative-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cluster-Driven Expert Pruning for Mixture-of-Experts Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-driven-expert-pruning-for-mixture-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) architectures have emerged as a promising paradigm for scaling large language models (LLMs) with sparse activation of task-specific experts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-driven-expert-pruning-for-mixture-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Tuning of Large Language Models for Knowledge-Grounded Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-tuning-of-large-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) demonstrate remarkable text comprehension and generation capabilities but often lack the ability to utilize up-to-date or domain-specific knowledge not included in their training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-tuning-of-large-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoTA with Less: MCTS-Guided Sample Selection for Data-Efficient Visual Reasoning Self-Improvement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sota-with-less-mcts-guided-sample-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an effective method to enhance visual reasoning with significantly fewer training samples, relying purely on self-improvement with no knowledge distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sota-with-less-mcts-guided-sample-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan-and-Refine: Diverse and Comprehensive Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plan-and-refine-diverse-and-comprehensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the global exploration phase, P&R generates a diverse set of plans for the given input, where each plan consists of a list of diverse query aspects with corresponding additional descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plan-and-refine-diverse-and-comprehensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM4Ranking: An Easy-to-use Framework of Utilizing Large Language Models for Document Reranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm4ranking-an-easy-to-use-framework-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Utilizing large language models (LLMs) for document reranking has been a popular and promising research direction in recent years, many studies are dedicated to improving the performance and efficiency of using LLMs for reranking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm4ranking-an-easy-to-use-framework-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimi-VL Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kimi-vl-technical-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Kimi-VL, an efficient open-source Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) vision-language model (VLM) that offers advanced multimodal reasoning, long-context understanding, and strong agent capabilities - all while activating only 2. 8B parameters in its language decoder (Kimi-VL-A3B).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kimi-vl-technical-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why We Feel: Breaking Boundaries in Emotional Reasoning with Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-we-feel-breaking-boundaries-in-emotional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing emotion analysis emphasizes which emotion arises (e. g., happy, sad, angry) but neglects the deeper why.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-we-feel-breaking-boundaries-in-emotional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Universal Features for Generalizable Image Forgery Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-universal-features-for-generalizable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, advanced image editing and generation methods have rapidly evolved, making detecting and locating forged image content increasingly challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-universal-features-for-generalizable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPIS: A novel dataset for personalized image aesthetic assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lapis-a-novel-dataset-for-personalized-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We assess the contribution of personal attributes and image attributes through ablation studies and find that performance deteriorates when certain personal and image attributes are removed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lapis-a-novel-dataset-for-personalized-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Likelihood-Based Out-of-Distribution Detection by Modeling Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-likelihood-based-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-distribution (OOD) detection is critical for ensuring the reliability of deep learning systems, particularly in safety-critical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-likelihood-based-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PixelFlow: Pixel-Space Generative Models with Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixelflow-pixel-space-generative-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present PixelFlow, a family of image generation models that operate directly in the raw pixel space, in contrast to the predominant latent-space models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixelflow-pixel-space-generative-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C3PO: Critical-Layer, Core-Expert, Collaborative Pathway Optimization for Test-Time Expert Re-Mixing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c3po-critical-layer-core-expert-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this observation, we develop a novel class of test-time optimization methods to re-weight or "re-mixing" the experts in different layers jointly for each test sample.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c3po-critical-layer-core-expert-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Impact of Multimodal Features on Chinese Spelling Correction: From Analysis to Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-impact-of-multimodal-features</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, LLMs face limitations in CSC, particularly over-correction, making them suboptimal for this task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-impact-of-multimodal-features</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novel Diffusion Models for Multimodal 3D Hand Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-diffusion-models-for-multimodal-3d-hand</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, these models overlook the synergy between hand movements and headset camera egomotion, either predicting hand trajectories in isolation or encoding egomotion only from past frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-diffusion-models-for-multimodal-3d-hand</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convergence-divergence models: Generalizations of phylogenetic trees modeling gene flow over time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convergence-divergence-models-generalizations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Phylogenetic trees commonly do not have enough flexibility to adequately model all evolutionary processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convergence-divergence-models-generalizations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLUS: Global-Local Reasoning Unified into A Single Large Language Model for Video Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glus-global-local-reasoning-unified-into-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel framework utilizing multi-modal large language models (MLLMs) for referring video object segmentation (RefVOS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glus-global-local-reasoning-unified-into-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Subspace Generation for Outlier Detection in High-Dimensional Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-subspace-generation-for-outlier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on 42 real-world datasets show that using V-GAN subspaces to build ensemble methods leads to a significant increase in one-class classification performance -- compared to existing subspace selection, feature selection, and embedding methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-subspace-generation-for-outlier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Discrepancy Learning: Synthetic Faces Detection Based on Multi-Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-discrepancy-learning-synthetic-faces</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous research focuses on the general differences between generated images and real images, often overlooking the discrepancies among various generative techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-discrepancy-learning-synthetic-faces</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ID-Booth: Identity-consistent Face Generation with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/id-booth-identity-consistent-face-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In turn, the produced data allows for effective augmentation of small-scale datasets and training of better-performing recognition models in a privacy-preserving manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/id-booth-identity-consistent-face-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A System for Comprehensive Assessment of RAG Frameworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-system-for-comprehensive-assessment-of-rag</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing evaluation frameworks fail to provide a holistic black-box approach to assessing RAG systems, especially in real-world deployment scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-system-for-comprehensive-assessment-of-rag</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Large Language Models through Neuro-Symbolic Integration and Ontological Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-large-language-models-through-neuro</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a neuro-symbolic approach integrating symbolic ontological reasoning and machine learning methods to enhance the consistency and reliability of LLM outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-large-language-models-through-neuro</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the HellaSwag? On the Validity of Common-Sense Reasoning Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-the-hellaswag-on-the-validity-of-common</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Measuring common-sense reasoning, therefore, is crucial for language models of different sizes and applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-the-hellaswag-on-the-validity-of-common</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echo Chamber: RL Post-training Amplifies Behaviors Learned in Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/echo-chamber-rl-post-training-amplifies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also find that models of different scales trained on the same data mixture will converge to distinct output distributions, suggesting that there are scale-dependent biases in model generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/echo-chamber-rl-post-training-amplifies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantically Encoding Activity Labels for Context-Aware Human Activity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantically-encoding-activity-labels-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During training, SEAL aligns the sensor data representations with their corresponding activity/context label embeddings in a shared embedding space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantically-encoding-activity-labels-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpecReason: Fast and Accurate Inference-Time Compute via Speculative Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/specreason-fast-and-accurate-inference-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our key insight in tackling these overheads is that LRM inference, and the reasoning that it embeds, is highly tolerant of approximations: complex tasks are typically broken down into simpler steps, each of which brings utility based on the semantic insight it provides for downstream steps rather than the exact tokens it generates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/specreason-fast-and-accurate-inference-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apt-Serve: Adaptive Request Scheduling on Hybrid Cache for Scalable LLM Inference Serving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apt-serve-adaptive-request-scheduling-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Apt-Serve, a scalable framework designed to enhance effective throughput in LLM inference serving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apt-serve-adaptive-request-scheduling-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Cheatsheet: Test-Time Learning with Adaptive Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-cheatsheet-test-time-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, our findings present DC as a promising approach for augmenting LMs with persistent memory, bridging the divide between isolated inference events and the cumulative, experience-driven learning characteristic of human cognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-cheatsheet-test-time-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClimateBench-M: A Multi-Modal Climate Data Benchmark with a Simple Generative Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/climatebench-m-a-multi-modal-climate-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Climate science studies the structure and dynamics of Earth's climate system and seeks to understand how climate changes over time, where the data is usually stored in the format of time series, recording the climate features, geolocation, time attributes, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/climatebench-m-a-multi-modal-climate-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Cross-Domain Code Search without Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-cross-domain-code-search-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose to break the query-code matching process of code search into two simpler tasks: query-comment matching and code-code matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-cross-domain-code-search-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLM-R1: A Stable and Generalizable R1-style Large Vision-Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlm-r1-a-stable-and-generalizable-r1-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this observation, we investigate the extension of R1-style reinforcement learning to Vision-Language Models (VLMs), aiming to enhance their visual reasoning capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlm-r1-a-stable-and-generalizable-r1-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task-Circuit Quantization: Leveraging Knowledge Localization and Interpretability for Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-circuit-quantization-leveraging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare TaCQ-based quantization to existing mixed-precision quantization methods when conditioning both on general-purpose and task-specific data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-circuit-quantization-leveraging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MRD-RAG: Enhancing Medical Diagnosis with Multi-Round Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mrd-rag-enhancing-medical-diagnosis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results indicate that our RAG framework can significantly enhance the diagnostic performance of LLMs, highlighting the potential of our approach in medical diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mrd-rag-enhancing-medical-diagnosis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-IFEngine: Towards Multimodal Instruction Following</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-ifengine-towards-multimodal-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Instruction Following (IF) ability measures how well Multi-modal Large Language Models (MLLMs) understand exactly what users are telling them and whether they are doing it right.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-ifengine-towards-multimodal-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perception-R1: Pioneering Perception Policy with Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perception-r1-pioneering-perception-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we return to the fundamentals and explore the effects of RL on different perception tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perception-r1-pioneering-perception-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Adversarial Robustness to Bias Elicitation in Large Language Models: Scalable Automated Assessment with LLM-as-a-Judge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-adversarial-robustness-to-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings reveal critical trade-offs between model size and safety, aiding the development of fairer and more robust future language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-adversarial-robustness-to-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhaseGen: A Diffusion-Based Approach for Complex-Valued MRI Data Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phasegen-a-diffusion-based-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce $\textit{PhaseGen}$, a novel complex-valued diffusion model for generating synthetic MRI raw data conditioned on magnitude images, commonly used in clinical practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phasegen-a-diffusion-based-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Time Series Forecasting via Multi-Level Text Alignment with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-time-series-forecasting-via-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The adaptation of large language models (LLMs) to time series forecasting poses unique challenges, as time series data is continuous in nature, while LLMs operate on discrete tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-time-series-forecasting-via-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probability Estimation and Scheduling Optimization for Battery Swap Stations via LRU-Enhanced Genetic Algorithm and Dual-Factor Decision System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probability-estimation-and-scheduling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the challenges of limited Battery Swap Stations datasets, high operational costs, and fluctuating user charging demand, this research proposes a probability estimation model based on charging pile data and constructs nine scenario-specific battery swap demand datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probability-estimation-and-scheduling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modular Control of Discrete Event System for Modeling and Mitigating Power System Cascading Failures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modular-control-of-discrete-event-system-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In prior work, we developed a new approach for identifying and preventing cascading failures in power systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modular-control-of-discrete-event-system-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoRI: Reducing Cross-Task Interference in Multi-Task Low-Rank Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lori-reducing-cross-task-interference-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose LoRA with Reduced Interference (LoRI), a simple yet effective approach that freezes the projection matrices $A$ as random projections and sparsifies the matrices $B$ using task-specific masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lori-reducing-cross-task-interference-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating quantum feature map design via large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-quantum-feature-map-design-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantum feature maps are a key component of quantum machine learning, encoding classical data into quantum states to exploit the expressive power of high-dimensional Hilbert spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-quantum-feature-map-design-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P2Object: Single Point Supervised Object Detection and Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p2object-single-point-supervised-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Point-to-Box Network (P2BNet), which constructs balanced \textbf{\textit{instance-level proposal bags}} by generating proposals in an anchor-like way and refining the proposals in a coarse-to-fine paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p2object-single-point-supervised-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraspClutter6D: A Large-scale Real-world Dataset for Robust Perception and Grasping in Cluttered Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graspclutter6d-a-large-scale-real-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust grasping in cluttered environments remains an open challenge in robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graspclutter6d-a-large-scale-real-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Diffusion U-Net Representations Contain Positional Embeddings and Anomalies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-diffusion-u-net-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have demonstrated remarkable capabilities in synthesizing realistic images, spurring interest in using their representations for various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-diffusion-u-net-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting GT2-FLS for Uncertainty Quantification: A Blueprint Calibration Strategy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-gt2-fls-for-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Uncertainty Quantification (UQ) is crucial for deploying reliable Deep Learning (DL) models in high-stakes applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-gt2-fls-for-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ColorizeDiffusion v2: Enhancing Reference-based Sketch Colorization Through Separating Utilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colorizediffusion-v2-enhancing-reference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we conduct an in-depth analysis of the \textbf{carrier}, defined as the latent representation facilitating information transfer from reference to sketch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colorizediffusion-v2-enhancing-reference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoEDiff-SR: Mixture of Experts-Guided Diffusion Model for Region-Adaptive MRI Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moediff-sr-mixture-of-experts-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI) at lower field strengths (e. g., 3T) suffers from limited spatial resolution, making it challenging to capture fine anatomical details essential for clinical diagnosis and neuroimaging research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moediff-sr-mixture-of-experts-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAFE-AD: Cross-Scenario Adaptive Feature Enhancement for Trajectory Planning in Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cafe-ad-cross-scenario-adaptive-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, open-loop training on the nuPlan dataset tends to cause causal confusion during closed-loop testing, and the dataset also presents a long-tail distribution of scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cafe-ad-cross-scenario-adaptive-feature</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
