<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 21:08:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Consistent Estimation of a Class of Distances Between Covariance Matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistent-estimation-of-a-class-of-distances</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This family of distances is particularly useful as it takes into consideration the fact that covariance matrices lie in the Riemannian manifold of positive definite matrices, thereby including a variety of commonly used metrics, such as the Euclidean distance, Jeffreys' divergence, and the log-Euclidean distance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistent-estimation-of-a-class-of-distances</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handling Long-Term Safety and Uncertainty in Safe Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handling-long-term-safety-and-uncertainty-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safety is one of the key issues preventing the deployment of reinforcement learning techniques in real-world robots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handling-long-term-safety-and-uncertainty-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>multiPI-TransBTS: A Multi-Path Learning Framework for Brain Tumor Image Segmentation Based on Multi-Physical Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multipi-transbts-a-multi-path-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Brain Tumor Segmentation (BraTS) plays a critical role in clinical diagnosis, treatment planning, and monitoring the progression of brain tumors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multipi-transbts-a-multi-path-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Grid Graph Neural Networks with Self-Attention for Computational Mechanics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-grid-graph-neural-networks-with-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel model merging Self-Attention with Message Passing in GNNs, achieving a 15\% reduction in RMSE on the well known flow past a cylinder benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-grid-graph-neural-networks-with-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient-Driven 3D Segmentation and Affordance Transfer in Gaussian Splatting Using 2D Masks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-driven-3d-segmentation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a byproduct, we discovered that inference-time gradients can also be used to prune Gaussians, resulting in up to 21% compression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-driven-3d-segmentation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing the Challenge of Detecting Character Knowledge Errors in LLM Role-Playing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-the-challenge-of-detecting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language model (LLM) role-playing has gained widespread attention, where the authentic character knowledge is crucial for constructing realistic LLM role-playing agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-the-challenge-of-detecting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhysMamba: Efficient Remote Physiological Measurement with SlowFast Temporal Difference Mamba</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physmamba-efficient-remote-physiological</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial-video based Remote photoplethysmography (rPPG) aims at measuring physiological signals and monitoring heart activity without any contact, showing significant potential in various applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physmamba-efficient-remote-physiological</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Controlled Study on Long Context Extension and Generalization in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-controlled-study-on-long-context-extension</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Broad textual understanding and in-context learning require language models that utilize full document contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-controlled-study-on-long-context-extension</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-in-one foundational models learning across quantum chemical levels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-in-one-foundational-models-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we introduce the all-in-one (AIO) ANI model architecture based on multimodal learning which can learn an arbitrary number of QC levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-in-one-foundational-models-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vista3D: Unravel the 3D Darkside of a Single Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vista3d-unravel-the-3d-darkside-of-a-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We embark on the age-old quest: unveiling the hidden dimensions of objects from mere glimpses of their visible parts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vista3d-unravel-the-3d-darkside-of-a-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedLF: Adaptive Logit Adjustment and Feature Optimization in Federated Long-Tailed Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedlf-adaptive-logit-adjustment-and-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on benchmark datasets CIFAR-10-LT and CIFAR-100-LT demonstrate that our approach effectively mitigates the problem of model performance degradation due to data heterogeneity and long-tailed distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedlf-adaptive-logit-adjustment-and-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAgICoRe: Multi-Agent, Iterative, Coarse-to-Fine Refinement for Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magicore-multi-agent-iterative-coarse-to-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, to ensure effective refinement, we employ a multi-agent loop with three agents: Solver, Reviewer (which generates targeted feedback based on step-wise RM scores), and the Refiner (which incorporates feedback).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magicore-multi-agent-iterative-coarse-to-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symmetry-Based Structured Matrices for Efficient Approximately Equivariant Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetry-based-structured-matrices-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a general framework -- based on a novel construction of symmetry-based structured matrices -- to build approximately equivariant NNs with significantly reduced parameter counts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetry-based-structured-matrices-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthesizing Evolving Symbolic Representations for Autonomous Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesizing-evolving-symbolic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Reinforcement Learning(DRL) is an effective tool for agents to learn policies in low-level state spaces to solve highly complex tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesizing-evolving-symbolic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAF-Net: A Dual-Branch Feature Decomposition Fusion Network with Domain Adaptive for Infrared and Visible Image Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/daf-net-a-dual-branch-feature-decomposition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Infrared and visible image fusion aims to combine complementary information from both modalities to provide a more comprehensive scene understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/daf-net-a-dual-branch-feature-decomposition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEOW: MEMOry Supervised LLM Unlearning Via Inverted Facts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meow-memory-supervised-llm-unlearning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLM Unlearning, a post-hoc approach to remove this information from trained LLMs, offers a promising solution to mitigate these risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meow-memory-supervised-llm-unlearning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unraveling the Hessian: A Key to Smooth Convergence in Loss Function Landscapes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-the-hessian-a-key-to-smooth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The loss landscape of neural networks is a critical aspect of their training, and understanding its properties is essential for improving their performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-the-hessian-a-key-to-smooth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitting Multilevel Factor Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fitting-multilevel-factor-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the inverse of an invertible PSD MLR matrix is also an MLR matrix with the same sparsity in factors, and we use the recursive Sherman-Morrison-Woodbury matrix identity to obtain the factors of the inverse.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fitting-multilevel-factor-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TART: An Open-Source Tool-Augmented Framework for Explainable Table-based Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tart-an-open-source-tool-augmented-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current Large Language Models (LLMs) exhibit limited ability to understand table structures and to apply precise numerical reasoning, which is crucial for tasks such as table question answering (TQA) and table-based fact verification (TFV).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tart-an-open-source-tool-augmented-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChefFusion: Multimodal Foundation Model Integrating Recipe and Food Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cheffusion-multimodal-foundation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Significant work has been conducted in the domain of food computing, yet these studies typically focus on single tasks such as t2t (instruction generation from food titles and ingredients), i2t (recipe generation from food images), or t2i (food image generation from recipes).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cheffusion-multimodal-foundation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qwen2-VL: Enhancing Vision-Language Model's Perception of the World at Any Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen2-vl-enhancing-vision-language-model-s</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Qwen2-VL Series, an advanced upgrade of the previous Qwen-VL models that redefines the conventional predetermined-resolution approach in visual processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen2-vl-enhancing-vision-language-model-s</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Human and AI Values based on Generative Psychometrics with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-human-and-ai-values-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces Generative Psychometrics for Values (GPV), an LLM-based, data-driven value measurement paradigm, theoretically grounded in text-revealed selective perceptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-human-and-ai-values-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computational Imaging for Long-Term Prediction of Solar Irradiance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-imaging-for-long-term</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The occlusion of the sun by clouds is one of the primary sources of uncertainties in solar power generation, and is a factor that affects the wide-spread use of solar power as a primary energy source.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-imaging-for-long-term</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lite-FBCN: Lightweight Fast Bilinear Convolutional Network for Brain Disease Classification from MRI Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lite-fbcn-lightweight-fast-bilinear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Achieving high accuracy with computational efficiency in brain disease classification from Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI) scans is challenging, particularly when both coarse and fine-grained distinctions are crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lite-fbcn-lightweight-fast-bilinear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mamba Fusion: Learning Actions Through Questioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-fusion-learning-actions-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video Language Models (VLMs) are crucial for generalizing across diverse tasks and using language cues to enhance learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-fusion-learning-actions-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OmniGen: Unified Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnigen-unified-image-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce OmniGen, a new diffusion model for unified image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnigen-unified-image-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient-free Post-hoc Explainability Using Distillation Aided Learnable Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-free-post-hoc-explainability-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a framework, named distillation aided explainability (DAX), that attempts to generate a saliency-based explanation in a model agnostic gradient free application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-free-post-hoc-explainability-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STCMOT: Spatio-Temporal Cohesion Learning for UAV-Based Multiple Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stcmot-spatio-temporal-cohesion-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiple object tracking (MOT) in Unmanned Aerial Vehicle (UAV) videos is important for diverse applications in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stcmot-spatio-temporal-cohesion-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sample Complexity Bounds for Linear System Identification from a Finite Set</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-complexity-bounds-for-linear-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper considers a finite sample perspective on the problem of identifying an LTI system from a finite set of possible systems using trajectory data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-complexity-bounds-for-linear-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Propulsion: Steering LLM with Tiny Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/propulsion-steering-llm-with-tiny-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancements in Large Language Models (LLMs) have revolutionized natural language processing (NLP) and related fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/propulsion-steering-llm-with-tiny-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal As a Plugin: Unsupervised Video Denoising with Pre-Trained Image Denoisers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-as-a-plugin-unsupervised-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in deep learning have shown impressive results in image and video denoising, leveraging extensive pairs of noisy and noise-free data for supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-as-a-plugin-unsupervised-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SkinMamba: A Precision Skin Lesion Segmentation Architecture with Cross-Scale Global State Modeling and Frequency Boundary Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skinmamba-a-precision-skin-lesion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Skin lesion segmentation is a crucial method for identifying early skin cancer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skinmamba-a-precision-skin-lesion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAD: Bidirectional Auto-regressive Diffusion for Text-to-Motion Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bad-bidirectional-auto-regressive-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoregressive models excel in modeling sequential dependencies by enforcing causal constraints, yet they struggle to capture complex bidirectional patterns due to their unidirectional nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bad-bidirectional-auto-regressive-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promptriever: Instruction-Trained Retrievers Can Be Prompted Like Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptriever-instruction-trained-retrievers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instruction-tuned language models (LM) are able to respond to imperative commands, providing a more natural user interface compared to their base counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptriever-instruction-trained-retrievers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynthSOD: Developing an Heterogeneous Dataset for Orchestra Music Source Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthsod-developing-an-heterogeneous-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in music source separation have significantly progressed, particularly in isolating vocals, drums, and bass elements from mixed tracks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthsod-developing-an-heterogeneous-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time-Series Forecasting, Knowledge Distillation, and Refinement within a Multimodal PDE Foundation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-forecasting-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new token library based on SymPy to encode differential equations as an additional modality for time-series models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-forecasting-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Analysis of the OpenAI O1-Preview Model in Solving Random K-SAT Problem: Does the LLM Solve the Problem Itself or Call an External SAT Solver?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-analysis-of-the-openai-o1-preview-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this manuscript I present an analysis on the performance of OpenAI O1-preview model in solving random K-SAT instances for K$\in {2, 3, 4}$ as a function of $\alpha=M/N$ where $M$ is the number of clauses and $N$ is the number of variables of the satisfiable problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-analysis-of-the-openai-o1-preview-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annealed Winner-Takes-All for Motion Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/annealed-winner-takes-all-for-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, to compensate for limited performance, some approaches rely on training with a large set of hypotheses, requiring a post-selection step during inference to significantly reduce the number of predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/annealed-winner-takes-all-for-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LC-Protonets: Multi-label Few-shot learning for world music audio tagging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lc-protonets-multi-label-few-shot-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Label-Combination Prototypical Networks (LC-Protonets) to address the problem of multi-label few-shot classification, where a model must generalize to new classes based on only a few available examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lc-protonets-multi-label-few-shot-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring and Enhancing Trustworthiness of LLMs in RAG through Grounded Attributions and Learning to Refuse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-and-enhancing-trustworthiness-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While many studies focus on evaluating the quality of end-to-end RAG systems, there is a lack of research on understanding the appropriateness of an LLM for the RAG task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-and-enhancing-trustworthiness-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Fields for Adaptive Photoacoustic Computed Tomography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-fields-for-adaptive-photoacoustic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Photoacoustic computed tomography (PACT) is a non-invasive imaging modality with wide medical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-fields-for-adaptive-photoacoustic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Physics Informed Neural Network (PINN) Methodology for Coupled Moving Boundary PDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-physics-informed-neural-network-pinn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Physics-Informed Neural Network (PINN) is a novel multi-task learning framework useful for solving physical problems modeled using differential equations (DEs) by integrating the knowledge of physics and known constraints into the components of deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-physics-informed-neural-network-pinn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Storytelling: Multi-Agent Generative AI for Dynamic Multimodal Narratives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-art-of-storytelling-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the concept of an education tool that utilizes Generative Artificial Intelligence (GenAI) to enhance storytelling for children.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-art-of-storytelling-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VALO: A Versatile Anytime Framework for LiDAR-based Object Detection Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valo-a-versatile-anytime-framework-for-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work addresses the challenge of adapting dynamic deadline requirements for LiDAR object detection deep neural networks (DNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valo-a-versatile-anytime-framework-for-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning Graph Enhanced Exemplars Retrieval for In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-graph-enhanced-exemplars-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models(LLMs) have exhibited remarkable few-shot learning capabilities and unified the paradigm of NLP tasks through the in-context learning(ICL) technique.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-graph-enhanced-exemplars-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advances in APPFL: A Comprehensive and Extensible Federated Learning Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-appfl-a-comprehensive-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) is a distributed machine learning paradigm enabling collaborative model training while preserving data privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-appfl-a-comprehensive-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORE-Bench: Fostering the Credibility of Published Research Through a Computational Reproducibility Agent Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/core-bench-fostering-the-credibility-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces such a benchmark, designed to measure the accuracy of AI agents in tackling a crucial yet surprisingly challenging aspect of scientific research: computational reproducibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/core-bench-fostering-the-credibility-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control-flow Reconstruction Attacks on Business Process Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/control-flow-reconstruction-attacks-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Process models may be automatically generated from event logs that contain as-is data of a business process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/control-flow-reconstruction-attacks-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chess Rating Estimation from Moves and Clock Times Using a CNN-LSTM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chess-rating-estimation-from-moves-and-clock</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this, we explore a method to estimate player ratings directly from game moves and clock times.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chess-rating-estimation-from-moves-and-clock</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSDNet: Multi-Scale Decoder for Few-Shot Semantic Segmentation via Transformer-Guided Prototyping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msdnet-multi-scale-decoder-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach introduces the spatial transformer decoder and the contextual mask generation module to improve the relational understanding between support and query images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msdnet-multi-scale-decoder-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
