<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 09:14:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>PiEEG-16 to Measure 16 EEG Channels with Raspberry Pi for Brain-Computer Interfaces and EEG devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pieeg-16-to-measure-16-eeg-channels-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article introduces a cost-effective gateway into the fascinating world of neuroscience: the PIEEG-16, a versatile shield for RaspberryPi designed to measure 16 channels of various biosignals, including EEG (electroencephalography), EMG (electromyography), and ECG (electrocardiography) without any data transfer over the network (Wi-Fi, Bluetooth) and processing and feature ectraction directly on the Raspberry in real-time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pieeg-16-to-measure-16-eeg-channels-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ODAQ: Open Dataset of Audio Quality - Benchmark on GitHub</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odaq-open-dataset-of-audio-quality-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ODAQ is a dataset addressing the scarcity of openly available collections of audio signals accompanied by corresponding subjective scores of perceived quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odaq-open-dataset-of-audio-quality-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>https://arxiv.org/pdf/2409.07491</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/https-arxiv-org-pdf-2409-07491</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article introduces a cost-effective gateway into the fascinating world of neuroscience: the PIEEG-16, a versatile shield for RaspberryPi designed to measure 16 channels of various biosignals, including EEG (electroencephalography), EMG (electromyography), and ECG (electrocardiography) without any data transfer over the network (Wi-Fi, Bluetooth) and processing and feature ectraction directly on the Raspberry in real-time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/https-arxiv-org-pdf-2409-07491</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCTAMamba: A State-Space Model Approach for Precision OCTA Vasculature Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/octamamba-a-state-space-model-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optical Coherence Tomography Angiography (OCTA) is a crucial imaging technique for visualizing retinal vasculature and diagnosing eye diseases such as diabetic retinopathy and glaucoma.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/octamamba-a-state-space-model-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSELM: Target Speaker Extraction using Discrete Tokens and Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tselm-target-speaker-extraction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose TSELM, a novel target speaker extraction network that leverages discrete tokens and language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tselm-target-speaker-extraction-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Agent Arena: Evaluating Multi-Modal OS Agents at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/windows-agent-arena-evaluating-multi-modal-os</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demonstrate Windows Agent Arena's capabilities, we also introduce a new multi-modal agent, Navi.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/windows-agent-arena-evaluating-multi-modal-os</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Role of Context in Reading Time Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-role-of-context-in-reading-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Another one is the pointwise mutual information (PMI) between a unit and its context, which turns out to yield the same predictive power as surprisal when controlling for unigram frequency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-role-of-context-in-reading-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDformer: Efficient End-to-End Transformer for Depth Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdformer-efficient-end-to-end-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The network consists of an input module for the depth map and RGB image features extraction and concatenation, a U-shaped encoder-decoder Transformer for extracting deep features, and a refinement module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdformer-efficient-end-to-end-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning for Two-Sample Testing under Right-Censored Data: A Simulation Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-for-two-sample-testing-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The focus of this study is to evaluate the effectiveness of Machine Learning (ML) methods for two-sample testing with right-censored observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-for-two-sample-testing-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating atmospheric variables from Digital Typhoon Satellite Images via Conditional Denoising Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-atmospheric-variables-from-digital</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study explores the application of diffusion models in the field of typhoons, predicting multiple ERA5 meteorological variables simultaneously from Digital Typhoon satellite images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-atmospheric-variables-from-digital</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProbTalk3D: Non-Deterministic Emotion Controllable Speech-Driven 3D Facial Animation Synthesis Using VQ-VAE</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probtalk3d-non-deterministic-emotion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our knowledge, that is the first non-deterministic 3D facial animation synthesis method incorporating a rich emotion dataset and emotion control with emotion labels and intensity levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probtalk3d-non-deterministic-emotion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microscopic-Mamba: Revealing the Secrets of Microscopic Images with Just 4M Parameters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/microscopic-mamba-revealing-the-secrets-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of medical microscopic image classification (MIC), CNN-based and Transformer-based models have been extensively studied.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/microscopic-mamba-revealing-the-secrets-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Pooling Method of Multi-layer Features from Pretrained Models for Speaker Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-pooling-method-of-multi-layer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in automatic speaker verification (ASV) studies have been achieved by leveraging large-scale pretrained networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-pooling-method-of-multi-layer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control+Shift: Generating Controllable Distribution Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/control-shift-generating-controllable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new method for generating realistic datasets with distribution shifts using any decoder-based generative model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/control-shift-generating-controllable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSBench: How Far Are Data Science Agents to Becoming Data Science Experts?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsbench-how-far-are-data-science-agents-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce DSBench, a comprehensive benchmark designed to evaluate data science agents with realistic tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsbench-how-far-are-data-science-agents-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASSNet: Adaptive Semantic Segmentation Network for Microtumors and Multi-Organ Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assnet-adaptive-semantic-segmentation-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose the Adaptive Semantic Segmentation Network (ASSNet), a transformer architecture that effectively integrates local and global features for precise medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assnet-adaptive-semantic-segmentation-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM Honeypot: Leveraging Large Language Models as Advanced Interactive Honeypot Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-honeypot-leveraging-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid evolution of cyber threats necessitates innovative solutions for detecting and analyzing malicious activity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-honeypot-leveraging-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Games for AI Control: Models of Safety Evaluations of AI Deployment Protocols</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/games-for-ai-control-models-of-safety</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the safety and usefulness of deployment protocols for untrusted AIs, AI Control uses a red-teaming exercise played between a protocol designer and an adversary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/games-for-ai-control-models-of-safety</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LED: Light Enhanced Depth Estimation at Night</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/led-light-enhanced-depth-estimation-at-night</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nighttime camera-based depth estimation is a highly challenging task, especially for autonomous driving applications, where accurate depth perception is essential for ensuring safe navigation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/led-light-enhanced-depth-estimation-at-night</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Evaluation Framework for Attributed Information Retrieval using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-evaluation-framework-for-attributed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the growing success of Large Language models (LLMs) in information-seeking scenarios, search engines are now adopting generative approaches to provide answers along with in-line citations as attribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-evaluation-framework-for-attributed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Monotonic Alignment Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-monotonic-alignment-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monotonic alignment search (MAS), introduced by Glow-TTS, is one of the most popular algorithm in TTS to estimate unknown alignments between text and speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-monotonic-alignment-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Few-Shot Image Classification through Learnable Multi-Scale Embedding and Attention Mechanisms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-few-shot-image-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conducted comprehensive evaluations on the MiniImageNet and FC100 datasets, specifically in the 5-way 1-shot and 5-way 5-shot scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-few-shot-image-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Text-guided Object Inpainting with Semantic Pre-inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-text-guided-object-inpainting-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to decompose the typical single-stage object inpainting into two cascaded processes: 1) semantic pre-inpainting that infers the semantic features of desired objects in a multi-modal feature space; 2) high-fieldity object generation in diffusion latent space that pivots on such inpainted semantic features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-text-guided-object-inpainting-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models are Pattern Matchers: Editing Semi-Structured and Structured Documents with ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-pattern-matchers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) offer numerous applications, the full extent of which is not yet understood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-pattern-matchers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Brain Tumor Representation in 3D High-Resolution MR Images via Interpretable State Space Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-brain-tumor-representation-in-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning meaningful and interpretable representations from high-dimensional volumetric magnetic resonance (MR) images is essential for advancing personalized medicine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-brain-tumor-representation-in-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From COCO to COCO-FP: A Deep Dive into Background False Positives for COCO Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-coco-to-coco-fp-a-deep-dive-into</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce COCO-FP, a new evaluation dataset derived from the ImageNet-1K dataset, designed to address this issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-coco-to-coco-fp-a-deep-dive-into</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WirelessAgent: Large Language Model Agents for Intelligent Wireless Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wirelessagent-large-language-model-agents-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wireless networks are increasingly facing challenges due to their expanding scale and complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wirelessagent-large-language-model-agents-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning incomplete factorization preconditioners for GMRES</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-incomplete-factorization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Incomplete factorization methods are one of the most commonly applied algebraic preconditioners for sparse linear equation systems and are able to speed up the convergence of Krylov subspace methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-incomplete-factorization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextBoost: Towards One-Shot Personalization of Text-to-Image Models via Fine-tuning Text Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textboost-towards-one-shot-personalization-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent breakthroughs in text-to-image models have opened up promising research avenues in personalized image generation, enabling users to create diverse images of a specific subject using natural language prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textboost-towards-one-shot-personalization-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Vision Foundation Models Enhance Domain Generalization in Medical Image Segmentation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-vision-foundation-models-enhance-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our extensive experiments on multiple datasets, encompassing various anatomies and modalities, reveal that FMs, particularly with the HQHSAM decode head, improve domain generalization for medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-vision-foundation-models-enhance-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiplex Graph Contrastive Learning with Soft Negatives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiplex-graph-contrastive-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Contrastive Learning (GCL) seeks to learn nodal or graph representations that contain maximal consistent information from graph-structured data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiplex-graph-contrastive-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AudioBERT: Audio Knowledge Augmented Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audiobert-audio-knowledge-augmented-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies have identified that language models, pretrained on text-only datasets, often lack elementary visual knowledge, \textit{e. g.,} colors of everyday objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audiobert-audio-knowledge-augmented-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Rules from KGs Guided by Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-rules-from-kgs-guided-by-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, our goal is to verify to which extent the exploitation of LMs is helpful for improving the quality of rule learning systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-rules-from-kgs-guided-by-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-Cost Tree Crown Dieback Estimation Using Deep Learning-Based Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-cost-tree-crown-dieback-estimation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we use an approach based on deep learning and vegetation indices to assess crown dieback from RGB aerial data without the need for expensive instrumentation such as LiDAR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-cost-tree-crown-dieback-estimation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Falsification for Learning-Based Control Systems: A Multi-Fidelity Bayesian Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-falsification-for-learning-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using full-fidelity simulator data in this optimization problem can be computationally expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-falsification-for-learning-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlashSplat: 2D to 3D Gaussian Splatting Segmentation Solved Optimally</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashsplat-2d-to-3d-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate the efficiency and robustness of our method in segmenting various scenes, and its superior performance in downstream tasks such as object removal and inpainting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashsplat-2d-to-3d-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lagrange Duality and Compound Multi-Attention Transformer for Semi-Supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lagrange-duality-and-compound-multi-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, our results indicate that CMAformer, combined with the feature fusion framework and the new consistency loss, demonstrates strong complementarity in semi-supervised learning ensembles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lagrange-duality-and-compound-multi-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-tuning Large Language Models for Entity Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-large-language-models-for-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments show that fine-tuning significantly improves the performance of the smaller models while the results for the larger models are mixed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-large-language-models-for-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Human Responses by Ordinal Archetypal Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-human-responses-by-ordinal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel framework for Archetypal Analysis (AA) tailored to ordinal data, particularly from questionnaires.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-human-responses-by-ordinal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thermal3D-GS: Physics-induced 3D Gaussians for Thermal Infrared Novel-view Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermal3d-gs-physics-induced-3d-gaussians-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, thermal infrared imaging is influenced by physical characteristics such as atmospheric transmission effects and thermal conduction, hindering the precise reconstruction of intricate details in thermal infrared scenes, manifesting as issues of floaters and indistinct edge features in synthesized images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermal3d-gs-physics-induced-3d-gaussians-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVENet: Evidence-based Ensemble Learning for Uncertainty-aware Brain Parcellation Using Diffusion MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evenet-evidence-based-ensemble-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key innovation of EVENet is the design of an evidential deep learning framework to quantify predictive uncertainty at each voxel during a single inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evenet-evidence-based-ensemble-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear Time Complexity Conformers with SummaryMixing for Streaming Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-time-complexity-conformers-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic speech recognition (ASR) with an encoder equipped with self-attention, whether streaming or non-streaming, takes quadratic time in the length of the speech utterance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-time-complexity-conformers-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabMixer: Noninvasive Estimation of the Mean Pulmonary Artery Pressure via Imaging and Tabular Data Mixing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabmixer-noninvasive-estimation-of-the-mean</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We test TabMixer for mPAP estimation and show that it enhances the performance of Convolutional Neural Networks, 3D-MLP and Vision Transformers while being competitive with previous modules for imaging and tabular data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabmixer-noninvasive-estimation-of-the-mean</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Realistic and Efficient Face Swapping: A Unified Approach with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realistic-and-efficient-face-swapping-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike prior works reliant on multiple off-the-shelf models, ours is a relatively unified approach and so it is resilient to errors in other off-the-shelf models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realistic-and-efficient-face-swapping-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asymptotics of Stochastic Gradient Descent with Dropout Regularization in Linear Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymptotics-of-stochastic-gradient-descent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes an asymptotic theory for online inference of the stochastic gradient descent (SGD) iterates with dropout regularization in linear regression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymptotics-of-stochastic-gradient-descent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaCAD: Adaptively Decoding to Balance Conflicts between Contextual and Parametric Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adacad-adaptively-decoding-to-balance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge conflict arises from discrepancies between information in the context of a large language model (LLM) and the knowledge stored in its parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adacad-adaptively-decoding-to-balance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent Workflow Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-workflow-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the potential of language model-based agents to solve real-world tasks such as web navigation, current methods still struggle with long-horizon tasks with complex action trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-workflow-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ontology-Free General-Domain Knowledge Graph-to-Text Generation Dataset Synthesis using Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontology-free-general-domain-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method proves to be a scalable and effective solution for generating high-quality G2T data, significantly advancing the field of G2T generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontology-free-general-domain-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gated Slot Attention for Efficient Linear-Time Sequence Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gated-slot-attention-for-efficient-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Linear attention Transformers and their gated variants, celebrated for enabling parallel training and efficient recurrent inference, still fall short in recall-intensive tasks compared to traditional Transformers and demand significant resources for training from scratch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gated-slot-attention-for-efficient-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diff-VPS: Video Polyp Segmentation via a Multi-task Diffusion Network with Adversarial Temporal Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diff-vps-video-polyp-segmentation-via-a-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We incorporate multi-task supervision into diffusion models to promote the discrimination of diffusion models on pixel-by-pixel segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diff-vps-video-polyp-segmentation-via-a-multi</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
