<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:11:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>PromptAttack: Probing Dialogue State Trackers with Adversarial Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptattack-probing-dialogue-state-trackers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key component of modern conversational systems is the Dialogue State Tracker (or DST), which models a user's goals and needs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptattack-probing-dialogue-state-trackers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GP-UNIT: Generative Prior for Versatile Unsupervised Image-to-Image Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gp-unit-generative-prior-for-versatile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel versatile framework, Generative Prior-guided UNsupervised Image-to-image Translation (GP-UNIT), that improves the quality, applicability and controllability of the existing translation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gp-unit-generative-prior-for-versatile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing a Better Asymmetric VQGAN for StableDiffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designing-a-better-asymmetric-vqgan-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The training cost of our asymmetric VQGAN is cheap, and we only need to retrain a new asymmetric decoder while keeping the vanilla VQGAN encoder and StableDiffusion unchanged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designing-a-better-asymmetric-vqgan-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GCT-TTE: Graph Convolutional Transformer for Travel Time Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gct-tte-graph-convolutional-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a new transformer-based model for the problem of travel time estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gct-tte-graph-convolutional-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Learning for Stochastic Optimization: A Bayesian Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-learning-for-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a principled approach to end-to-end learning in stochastic optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-learning-for-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch-level Routing in Mixture-of-Experts is Provably Sample-efficient for Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-level-routing-in-mixture-of-experts-is</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In deep learning, mixture-of-experts (MoE) activates one or few experts (sub-networks) on a per-sample or per-token basis, resulting in significant computation reduction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-level-routing-in-mixture-of-experts-is</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proximity-Informed Calibration for Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proximity-informed-calibration-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Confidence calibration is central to providing accurate and interpretable uncertainty estimates, especially under safety-critical scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proximity-informed-calibration-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A novel deeponet model for learning moving-solution operators with applications to earthquake hypocenter localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-deeponet-model-for-learning-moving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Seismicity induced by human activities poses a significant threat to public safety, emphasizing the need for accurate and timely earthquake hypocenter localization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-deeponet-model-for-learning-moving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rewarded soups: towards Pareto-optimal alignment by interpolating weights fine-tuned on diverse rewards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rewarded-soups-towards-pareto-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foundation models are first pre-trained on vast unsupervised datasets and then fine-tuned on labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rewarded-soups-towards-pareto-optimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Model for Crystalline Material Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-model-for-crystalline-material</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the greatest challenges facing our society is the discovery of new innovative crystal materials with specific properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-model-for-crystalline-material</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training-Free Neural Active Learning with Initialization-Robustness Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-free-neural-active-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce our expected variance with Gaussian processes (EV-GP) criterion for neural active learning, which is theoretically guaranteed to select data points which lead to trained NNs with both (a) good predictive performances and (b) initialization robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-free-neural-active-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XSemPLR: Cross-Lingual Semantic Parsing in Multiple Natural Languages and Meaning Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xsemplr-cross-lingual-semantic-parsing-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing CLSP models are separately proposed and evaluated on datasets of limited tasks and applications, impeding a comprehensive and unified evaluation of CLSP on a diverse range of NLs and MRs. To this end, we present XSemPLR, a unified benchmark for cross-lingual semantic parsing featured with 22 natural languages and 8 meaning representations by examining and selecting 9 existing datasets to cover 5 tasks and 164 domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xsemplr-cross-lingual-semantic-parsing-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Diffusion-based Image Translation using Asymmetric Gradient Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-diffusion-based-image-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have shown significant progress in image translation tasks recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-diffusion-based-image-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic Collapse: How Gradient Noise Attracts SGD Dynamics Towards Simpler Subnetworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-collapse-how-gradient-noise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we reveal a strong implicit bias of stochastic gradient descent (SGD) that drives overly expressive networks to much simpler subnetworks, thereby dramatically reducing the number of independent parameters, and improving generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-collapse-how-gradient-noise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SANGEET: A XML based Open Dataset for Research in Hindustani Sangeet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sangeet-a-xml-based-open-dataset-for-research</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dataset is intended to provide the ground truth information for music information research tasks, thereby supporting several data-driven analysis from a machine learning perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sangeet-a-xml-based-open-dataset-for-research</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptBench: Towards Evaluating the Robustness of Large Language Models on Adversarial Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptbench-towards-evaluating-the-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing reliance on Large Language Models (LLMs) across academia and industry necessitates a comprehensive understanding of their robustness to prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptbench-towards-evaluating-the-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youku-mPLUG: A 10 Million Large-scale Chinese Video-Language Dataset for Pre-training and Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/youku-mplug-a-10-million-large-scale-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, to facilitate a comprehensive evaluation of video-language models, we carefully build the largest human-annotated Chinese benchmarks covering three popular video-language tasks of cross-modal retrieval, video captioning, and video category classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/youku-mplug-a-10-million-large-scale-chinese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthesising Recursive Functions for First-Order Model Counting: Challenges, Progress, and Conjectures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesising-recursive-functions-for-first</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First-order model counting (FOMC) is a computational problem that asks to count the models of a sentence in finite-domain first-order logic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesising-recursive-functions-for-first</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IUTEAM1 at MEDIQA-Chat 2023: Is simple fine tuning effective for multilayer summarization of clinical conversations?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iuteam1-at-mediqa-chat-2023-is-simple-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clinical conversation summarization has become an important application of Natural language Processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iuteam1-at-mediqa-chat-2023-is-simple-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UCTB: An Urban Computing Tool Box for Spatiotemporal Crowd Flow Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uctb-an-urban-computing-tool-box-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we design and implement a spatiotemporal crowd flow prediction toolbox called UCTB (Urban Computing Tool Box), which integrates multiple spatiotemporal domain knowledge and state-of-the-art models simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uctb-an-urban-computing-tool-box-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Adjusting Weighted Expected Improvement for Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-adjusting-weighted-expected-improvement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian Optimization (BO) is a class of surrogate-based, sample-efficient algorithms for optimizing black-box problems with small evaluation budgets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-adjusting-weighted-expected-improvement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFDP: Common Frequency Domain Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfdp-common-frequency-domain-pruning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel end-to-end pipeline for model pruning via the frequency domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfdp-common-frequency-domain-pruning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1st Place Solution for PVUW Challenge 2023: Video Panoptic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1st-place-solution-for-pvuw-challenge-2023</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we successfully validated the effectiveness of the decoupling strategy in video panoptic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1st-place-solution-for-pvuw-challenge-2023</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git-Theta: A Git Extension for Collaborative Development of Machine Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/git-theta-a-git-extension-for-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Currently, most machine learning models are trained by centralized teams and are rarely updated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/git-theta-a-git-extension-for-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEC-Net: Vision Transformer Embrace Convolutional Neural Networks for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tec-net-vision-transformer-embrace</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The hybrid architecture of convolution neural networks (CNN) and Transformer has been the most popular method for medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tec-net-vision-transformer-embrace</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CorrMatch: Label Propagation via Correlation Matching for Semi-Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/corrmatch-label-propagation-via-correlation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a simple but performant semi-supervised semantic segmentation approach, termed CorrMatch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/corrmatch-label-propagation-via-correlation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dataset for Deep Learning-based Bone Structure Analyses in Total Hip Arthroplasty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dataset-for-deep-learning-based-bone</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For THA, it is of clinical significance to analyze the bone structure from the CT images, especially to observe the structure of the acetabulum and femoral head, before the surgical procedure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dataset-for-deep-learning-based-bone</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revising deep learning methods in parking lot occupancy detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revising-deep-learning-methods-in-parking-lot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parking guidance systems have recently become a popular trend as a part of the smart cities' paradigm of development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revising-deep-learning-methods-in-parking-lot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy-Based Self-Competition for Planning Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-based-self-competition-for-planning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AlphaZero-type algorithms may stop improving on single-player tasks in case the value network guiding the tree search is unable to approximate the outcome of an episode sufficiently well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-based-self-competition-for-planning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Normalization Layers Are All That Sharpness-Aware Minimization Needs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normalization-layers-are-all-that-sharpness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sharpness-aware minimization (SAM) was proposed to reduce sharpness of minima and has been shown to enhance generalization performance in various settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normalization-layers-are-all-that-sharpness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arabic Dysarthric Speech Recognition Using Adversarial and Signal-Based Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arabic-dysarthric-speech-recognition-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We perform further validation on real English dysarthric speech showing a WER improvement of 124% compared to the baseline trained only on healthy English LJSpeech dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arabic-dysarthric-speech-recognition-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Two Word Test: A Semantic Benchmark for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-two-word-test-a-semantic-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide versions of the task that probe meaningfulness ratings on a 0-4 scale as well as binary judgments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-two-word-test-a-semantic-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Models for Math Story Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/world-models-for-math-story-problems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we consolidate previous work on categorizing and representing math story problems and develop MathWorld, which is a graph-based semantic formalism specific for the domain of math story problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/world-models-for-math-story-problems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Learning Without Labeled Multimodal Data: Guarantees and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-learning-without-labeled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose two lower bounds based on the amount of shared information between modalities and the disagreement between separately trained unimodal classifiers, and derive an upper bound through connections to approximate algorithms for min-entropy couplings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-learning-without-labeled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can current NLI systems handle German word order? Investigating language model performance on a new German challenge set of minimal pairs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-current-nli-systems-handle-german-word</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We create WOGLI (Word Order in German Language Inference), the first adversarial NLI dataset for German word order that has the following properties: (i) each premise has an entailed and a non-entailed hypothesis; (ii) premise and hypotheses differ only in word order and necessary morphological changes to mark case and number.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-current-nli-systems-handle-german-word</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MobileNMT: Enabling Translation in 15MB and 30ms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobilenmt-enabling-translation-in-15mb-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the co-design of model and engine, compared with the existing system, we speed up 47. 0x and save 99. 5% of memory with only 11. 6% loss of BLEU.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobilenmt-enabling-translation-in-15mb-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT is fun, but it is not funny! Humor is still challenging Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-is-fun-but-it-is-not-funny-humor-is</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a series of exploratory experiments around jokes, i. e., generation, explanation, and detection, we seek to understand ChatGPT's capability to grasp and reproduce human humor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-is-fun-but-it-is-not-funny-humor-is</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Mask Free Neural Network for Monaural Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mask-free-neural-network-for-monaural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In speech enhancement, the lack of clear structural characteristics in the target speech phase requires the use of conservative and cumbersome network frameworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mask-free-neural-network-for-monaural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Semantic Communication: Diffusion Models Beyond Bit Recovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-semantic-communication-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove, through an in-depth assessment of multiple scenarios, that our method outperforms existing solutions in generating high-quality images with preserved semantic information even in cases where the received content is significantly degraded.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-semantic-communication-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Dataset and Empirical Study for Sentence Simplification in Chinese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-dataset-and-empirical-study-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sentence Simplification is a valuable technique that can benefit language learners and children a lot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-dataset-and-empirical-study-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gotta: Generative Few-shot Question Answering by Prompt-based Cloze Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gotta-generative-few-shot-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few-shot question answering (QA) aims at precisely discovering answers to a set of questions from context passages while only a few training samples are available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gotta-generative-few-shot-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unbalanced Optimal Transport for Unbalanced Word Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbalanced-optimal-transport-for-unbalanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monolingual word alignment is crucial to model semantic interactions between sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbalanced-optimal-transport-for-unbalanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zambezi Voice: A Multilingual Speech Corpus for Zambian Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zambezi-voice-a-multilingual-speech-corpus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dataset is created for speech recognition but can be extended to multilingual speech processing research for both supervised and unsupervised learning approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zambezi-voice-a-multilingual-speech-corpus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From the One, Judge of the Whole: Typed Entailment Graph Construction with Predicate Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-the-one-judge-of-the-whole-typed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entailment Graphs (EGs) have been constructed based on extracted corpora as a strong and explainable form to indicate context-independent entailment relations in natural languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-the-one-judge-of-the-whole-typed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allophant: Cross-lingual Phoneme Recognition with Articulatory Attributes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/allophant-cross-lingual-phoneme-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes Allophant, a multilingual phoneme recognizer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/allophant-cross-lingual-phoneme-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Reliability of Watermarks for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-reliability-of-watermarks-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are now deployed to everyday use and positioned to produce large quantities of text in the coming decade.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-reliability-of-watermarks-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyTrial: A Comprehensive Platform for Artificial Intelligence for Drug Development</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytrial-a-comprehensive-platform-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate the research and development of artificial intelligence (AI) for drug development, we developed a Python package, namely PyTrial, that implements various clinical trial tasks supported by AI algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytrial-a-comprehensive-platform-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional Diffusion Models for Weakly Supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-diffusion-models-for-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in denoising diffusion probabilistic models have shown great success in image synthesis tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-diffusion-models-for-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Dimensional Deep Image Prior for Curve Fitting of S-Parameters from Electromagnetic Solvers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-dimensional-deep-image-prior-for-curve</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DIP is a technique that optimizes the weights of a randomly-initialized convolutional neural network to fit a signal from noisy or under-determined measurements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-dimensional-deep-image-prior-for-curve</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the effects of robotic design on learning and neural control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-effects-of-robotic-design-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, this dissertation intimates the ability to automatically design robots that are more general purpose than current robots and that can perform various tasks while requiring less computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-effects-of-robotic-design-on</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
