<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 21:07:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Bag of Regions for Open-Vocabulary Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-bag-of-regions-for-open-vocabulary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The embeddings of regions in a bag are treated as embeddings of words in a sentence, and they are sent to the text encoder of a VLM to obtain the bag-of-regions embedding, which is learned to be aligned to the corresponding features extracted by a frozen VLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-bag-of-regions-for-open-vocabulary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Topology-Specific Experts for Molecular Property Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-topology-specific-experts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, motivated by this observation, we propose \proposed to leverage topology-specific prediction models (referred to as experts), each of which is responsible for each molecular group sharing similar topological semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-topology-specific-experts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Feature Integration for Perception-Dependent Examination-Bias Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-feature-integration-for-perception</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Eliminating examination bias accurately is pivotal to apply click-through data to train an unbiased ranking model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-feature-integration-for-perception</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying Valence and Arousal in Text with Multilingual Pre-trained Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-valence-and-arousal-in-text-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The analysis of emotions expressed in text has numerous applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-valence-and-arousal-in-text-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet Explorer: Targeted Representation Learning on the Open Web</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internet-explorer-targeted-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern vision models typically rely on fine-tuning general-purpose models pre-trained on large, static datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internet-explorer-targeted-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Role of Pre-training Data in Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-role-of-pre-training-data-in-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the impact of pre-training data distribution on the few-shot and full fine-tuning performance using 3 pre-training methods (supervised, contrastive language-image and image-image), 7 pre-training datasets, and 9 downstream datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-role-of-pre-training-data-in-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedCLIP: Fast Generalization and Personalization for CLIP in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedclip-fast-generalization-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, we design an attention-based adapter for the large model, CLIP, and the rest operations merely depend on adapters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedclip-fast-generalization-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal isotonic calibration for heterogeneous treatment effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-isotonic-calibration-for-heterogeneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose causal isotonic calibration, a novel nonparametric method for calibrating predictors of heterogeneous treatment effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-isotonic-calibration-for-heterogeneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The (Ab)use of Open Source Code to Train Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ab-use-of-open-source-code-to-train-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, Large Language Models (LLMs) have gained significant popularity due to their ability to generate human-like text and their potential applications in various fields, such as Software Engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ab-use-of-open-source-code-to-train-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orca: A Few-shot Benchmark for Chinese Conversational Machine Reading Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orca-a-few-shot-benchmark-for-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, model's comprehension ability towards real scenarios are hard to evaluate reasonably.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orca-a-few-shot-benchmark-for-chinese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Graph Revealers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-graph-revealers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse graph recovery methods works well where the data follows their assumptions but often they are not designed for doing downstream probabilistic queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-graph-revealers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extrapolated cross-validation for randomized ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extrapolated-cross-validation-for-randomized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method builds on two main ingredients: two initial estimators for small ensemble sizes using out-of-bag errors and a novel risk extrapolation technique leveraging the structure of the prediction risk decomposition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extrapolated-cross-validation-for-randomized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Systematic Rectification of Language Models via Dead-end Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/systematic-rectification-of-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Other methods rely on rule-based or prompt-based token elimination, which are limited as they dismiss future tokens and the overall meaning of the complete discourse.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/systematic-rectification-of-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inseq: An Interpretability Toolkit for Sequence Generation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inseq-an-interpretability-toolkit-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Past work in natural language processing interpretability focused mainly on popular classification tasks while largely overlooking generation settings, partly due to a lack of dedicated tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inseq-an-interpretability-toolkit-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Robustness and Uncertainty of Graph Models Under Structural Distributional Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-robustness-and-uncertainty-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the performance of graph models, it is important to test them on diverse and meaningful distributional shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-robustness-and-uncertainty-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatially-Adaptive Feature Modulation for Efficient Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatially-adaptive-feature-modulation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although numerous solutions have been proposed for image super-resolution, they are usually incompatible with low-power devices with many computational and memory constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatially-adaptive-feature-modulation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OccDepth: A Depth-Aware Method for 3D Semantic Scene Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occdepth-a-depth-aware-method-for-3d-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D Semantic Scene Completion (SSC) can provide dense geometric and semantic scene representations, which can be applied in the field of autonomous driving and robotic systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occdepth-a-depth-aware-method-for-3d-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IGB: Addressing The Gaps In Labeling, Features, Heterogeneity, and Size of Public Graph Datasets for Deep Learning Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/igb-addressing-the-gaps-in-labeling-features</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing public datasets for GNNs are relatively small, which limits the ability of GNNs to generalize to unseen data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/igb-addressing-the-gaps-in-labeling-features</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image to Sphere: Learning Equivariant Features for Efficient Pose Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-to-sphere-learning-equivariant-features</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting the pose of objects from a single image is an important but difficult computer vision problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-to-sphere-learning-equivariant-features</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Generalize towards Unseen Domains via a Content-Aware Style Invariant Framework for Disease Detection from Chest X-rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generalize-towards-unseen-domains</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several methods have been proposed to address this domain shift, such as utilizing adversarial learning or multi-domain mixups to extract domain-invariant high-level features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generalize-towards-unseen-domains</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaMA: Open and Efficient Foundation Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-open-and-efficient-foundation-language-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce LLaMA, a collection of foundation language models ranging from 7B to 65B parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-open-and-efficient-foundation-language-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>kNN-BOX: A Unified Framework for Nearest Neighbor Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knn-box-a-unified-framework-for-nearest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Augmenting the base neural model with a token-level symbolic datastore is a novel generation paradigm and has achieved promising results in machine translation (MT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knn-box-a-unified-framework-for-nearest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LODE: Locally Conditioned Eikonal Implicit Scene Completion from Sparse LiDAR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lode-locally-conditioned-eikonal-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel Eikonal formulation that conditions the implicit representation on localized shape priors which function as dense boundary value constraints, and demonstrate it works on SemanticKITTI and SemanticPOSS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lode-locally-conditioned-eikonal-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Informed Proposals for Discrete Distributions via Newton's Series Approximation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-informed-proposals-for-discrete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gradients have been exploited in proposal distributions to accelerate the convergence of Markov chain Monte Carlo algorithms on discrete distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-informed-proposals-for-discrete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpikeGPT: Generative Pre-trained Language Model with Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spikegpt-generative-pre-trained-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spiking neural networks (SNNs) have emerged as an energy-efficient approach to deep learning that leverage sparse and event-driven activations to reduce the computational overhead associated with model inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spikegpt-generative-pre-trained-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Super-Resolve Blurry Images with Events</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-super-resolve-blurry-images-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Super-Resolution from a single motion Blurred image (SRB) is a severely ill-posed problem due to the joint degradation of motion blurs and low spatial resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-super-resolve-blurry-images-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self Correspondence Distillation for End-to-End Weakly-Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-correspondence-distillation-for-end-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, to further improve the segmentation accuracy, we design a Variation-aware Refine Module to enhance the local consistency of pseudo-labels by computing pixel-level variation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-correspondence-distillation-for-end-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Is Not All You Need: Aligning Perception with Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-is-not-all-you-need-aligning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A big convergence of language, multimodal perception, action, and world modeling is a key step toward artificial general intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-is-not-all-you-need-aligning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Target-Aware Tracking with Long-term Context Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-aware-tracking-with-long-term-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most deep trackers still follow the guidance of the siamese paradigms and use a template that contains only the target without any contextual information, which makes it difficult for the tracker to cope with large appearance changes, rapid target movement, and attraction from similar objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-aware-tracking-with-long-term-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNNDelete: A General Strategy for Unlearning in Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnndelete-a-general-strategy-for-unlearning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deleted Edge Consistency ensures that the influence of deleted elements is removed from both model weights and neighboring representations, while Neighborhood Influence guarantees that the remaining model knowledge is preserved after deletion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnndelete-a-general-strategy-for-unlearning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient fair PCA for fair representation learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-fair-pca-for-fair-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We revisit the problem of fair principal component analysis (PCA), where the goal is to learn the best low-rank linear approximation of the data that obfuscates demographic information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-fair-pca-for-fair-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tailoring Language Generation Models under Total Variation Distance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-language-generation-models-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The standard paradigm of neural language generation adopts maximum likelihood estimation (MLE) as the optimizing method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-language-generation-models-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDF-Net: Multimodal Dual-Fusion Network for Abnormality Detection using CXR Images and Clinical Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdf-net-multimodal-dual-fusion-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel architecture consisting of two fusion methods that enable the model to simultaneously process patients' clinical data (structured data) and chest X-rays (image data).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdf-net-multimodal-dual-fusion-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Input-agnostic Manipulation Directions in StyleGAN with Text Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-input-agnostic-manipulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advantages of fast inference and human-friendly flexible manipulation, image-agnostic style manipulation via text guidance enables new applications that were not previously available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-input-agnostic-manipulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance is not enough: a story of the Rashomon's quartet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-is-not-enough-a-story-of-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[But what if the second best model describes the data equally well but in a completely different way?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-is-not-enough-a-story-of-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Pairwise Interaction for Generalizable DeepFake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-pairwise-interaction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We obtain 98. 48% BOSC accuracy on the FF++ dataset and 90. 87% BOSC accuracy on the CelebDF dataset suggesting a promising direction for generalization of DeepFake detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-pairwise-interaction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDIWS: Thermal Imaging Dataset for Person Detection in Intrusion Warning Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdiws-thermal-imaging-dataset-for-person</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a synthetic thermal imaging dataset for Person Detection in Intrusion Warning Systems (PDIWS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdiws-thermal-imaging-dataset-for-person</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closed-loop Error Correction Learning Accelerates Experimental Discovery of Thermoelectric Materials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closed-loop-error-correction-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The exploration of thermoelectric materials is challenging considering the large materials space, combined with added exponential degrees of freedom coming from doping and the diversity of synthetic pathways.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closed-loop-error-correction-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kernel Conditional Moment Constraints for Confounding Robust Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernel-conditional-moment-constraints-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It can be shown that our estimator contains the recently proposed sharp estimator by Dorn and Guo (2022) as a special case, and our method enables a novel extension of the classical marginal sensitivity model using f-divergence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernel-conditional-moment-constraints-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Lingual Question Answering over Knowledge Base as Reading Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-question-answering-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We convert KB subgraphs into passages to narrow the gap between KB schemas and questions, which enables our model to benefit from recent advances in multilingual pre-trained language models (MPLMs) and cross-lingual machine reading comprehension (xMRC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-question-answering-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-infused Contrastive Learning for Urban Imagery-based Socioeconomic Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-infused-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address such issues, in this paper, we propose a Knowledge-infused Contrastive Learning (KnowCL) model for urban imagery-based socioeconomic prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-infused-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partial Label Learning for Emotion Recognition from EEG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-label-learning-for-emotion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, PLL methods have not yet been adopted for EEG representation learning or implemented for emotion recognition tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-label-learning-for-emotion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TBFormer: Two-Branch Transformer for Image Forgery Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tbformer-two-branch-transformer-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Transformer-style network with two feature extraction branches for image forgery localization, and it is named as Two-Branch Transformer (TBFormer).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tbformer-two-branch-transformer-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HADES: Homologous Automated Document Exploration and Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hades-homologous-automated-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces HADES, a novel tool for automatic comparative documents with similar structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hades-homologous-automated-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jointly Optimizing Translations and Speech Timing to Improve Isochrony in Automatic Dubbing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jointly-optimizing-translations-and-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic dubbing (AD) is the task of translating the original speech in a video into target language speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jointly-optimizing-translations-and-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation of robot swarms for learning communication-aware coordination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-of-robot-swarms-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These methods learn a controller by observing demonstrations of an expert, such as the behaviour of a centralised omniscient controller, which can perceive the entire environment, including the state and observations of all agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-of-robot-swarms-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A parameter-free graph reduction for spectral clustering and SpectralNet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-parameter-free-graph-reduction-for-spectral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a graph reduction method that does not require any parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-parameter-free-graph-reduction-for-spectral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Effect of Points Dispersion on the $k$-nn Search in Random Projection Forests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-points-dispersion-on-the-k-nn-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[$k$-nn search in an rpForest is influenced by two factors: 1) the dispersion of points along the random direction and 2) the number of rpTrees in the rpForest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-points-dispersion-on-the-k-nn-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Framework for Soft Threshold Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-framework-for-soft-threshold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we reformulate soft threshold pruning as an implicit optimization problem solved using the Iterative Shrinkage-Thresholding Algorithm (ISTA), a classic method from the fields of sparse recovery and compressed sensing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-framework-for-soft-threshold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair Attribute Completion on Graph with Missing Attributes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-attribute-completion-on-graph-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tackling unfairness in graph learning models is a challenging task, as the unfairness issues on graphs involve both attributes and topological structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-attribute-completion-on-graph-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
