<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 21:06:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Source-free Subject Adaptation for EEG-based Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/source-free-subject-adaptation-for-eeg-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel and practical problem setup, namely source-free subject adaptation, where the source subject data are unavailable and only the pre-trained model parameters are provided for subject adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/source-free-subject-adaptation-for-eeg-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan To Predict: Learning an Uncertainty-Foreseeing Model for Model-Based Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plan-to-predict-learning-an-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Model-based Reinforcement Learning (MBRL), model learning is critical since an inaccurate model can bias policy learning via generating misleading samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plan-to-predict-learning-an-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massively Parallel Genetic Optimization through Asynchronous Propagation of Populations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/massively-parallel-genetic-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Propulate, an evolutionary optimization algorithm and software package for global optimization and in particular hyperparameter search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/massively-parallel-genetic-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Should I Engage with At What Time? A Missing Event Aware Temporal Graph Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/who-should-i-engage-with-at-what-time-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In real-world applications, events are not always observable, and estimating event time is as important as predicting future events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/who-should-i-engage-with-at-what-time-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Sketch Colorization using Adversarial Segmentation Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-sketch-colorization-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We leverage semantic image segmentation from a general-purpose panoptic segmentation network to generate an additional adversarial loss function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-sketch-colorization-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooperative Distributed MPC via Decentralized Real-Time Optimization: Implementation Results for Robot Formations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-distributed-mpc-via-decentralized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discuss the implementation via decentralized optimization algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-distributed-mpc-via-decentralized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEnt: An Entropy-based Model-agnostic Explainability Framework to Contrast Classifiers' Decisions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cent-an-entropy-based-model-agnostic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our Contrastive Entropy-based explanation method, CEnt, approximates a model locally by a decision tree to compute entropy information of different feature splits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cent-an-entropy-based-model-agnostic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Private Online Bayesian Estimation With Adaptive Truncation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-online-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel online and adaptive truncation method for differentially private Bayesian online estimation of a static parameter regarding a population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-online-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Quantum Processes with Memory -- Quantum Recurrent Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-quantum-processes-with-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recurrent neural networks play an important role in both research and industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-quantum-processes-with-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emerging Labour Flow Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emerging-labour-flow-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The study of labour dynamics has led to the introduction of labour flow networks (LFNs) as a way to conceptualise job-to-job flows, and to the development of mathematical models to explore the dynamics of these networked flows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emerging-labour-flow-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolutionary dynamics of glucose-deprived cancer cells: insights from experimentally-informed mathematical modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-dynamics-of-glucose-deprived</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Glucose is a primary energy source for cancer cells.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-dynamics-of-glucose-deprived</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-based assessment of sampling protocols for infectious disease genomic surveillance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-based-assessment-of-sampling-protocols</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consequently, it is convenient for countries with comparatively few resources to operate at lower sequencing rates, thereby profiting the most from adaptive sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-based-assessment-of-sampling-protocols</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JCSE: Contrastive Learning of Japanese Sentence Embeddings and Its Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jcse-contrastive-learning-of-japanese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this, we propose a novel Japanese sentence representation framework, JCSE (derived from ``Contrastive learning of Sentence Embeddings for Japanese''), that creates training data by generating sentences and synthesizing them with sentences available in a target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jcse-contrastive-learning-of-japanese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FECANet: Boosting Few-Shot Semantic Segmentation with Feature-Enhanced Context-Aware Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fecanet-boosting-few-shot-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few-shot semantic segmentation is the task of learning to locate each pixel of the novel class in the query image with only a few annotated support images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fecanet-boosting-few-shot-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Inference in Denoising Diffusion Models via MMD Finetuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-inference-in-denoising-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings show that the proposed method is able to produce high-quality samples in a fraction of the time required by widely-used diffusion models, and outperforms state-of-the-art techniques for accelerated sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-inference-in-denoising-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiview Compressive Coding for 3D Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiview-compressive-coding-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a simple framework that operates on 3D points of single objects or whole scenes coupled with category-agnostic large-scale training from diverse RGB-D videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiview-compressive-coding-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Deep Learning with Scenario-Based Override Rules: a Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-deep-learning-with-scenario-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNNs) have become a crucial instrument in the software development toolkit, due to their ability to efficiently solve complex problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-deep-learning-with-scenario-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RGB-D-Based Categorical Object Pose and Shape Estimation: Methods, Datasets, and Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgb-d-based-categorical-object-pose-and-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, various methods for 6D pose and shape estimation of objects at a per-category level have been proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgb-d-based-categorical-object-pose-and-shape</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDFormer: Propagation Delay-aware Dynamic Long-range Transformer for Traffic Flow Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdformer-propagation-delay-aware-dynamic-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, GNN-based models have three major limitations for traffic prediction: i) Most methods model spatial dependencies in a static manner, which limits the ability to learn dynamic urban traffic patterns; ii) Most methods only consider short-range spatial information and are unable to capture long-range spatial dependencies; iii) These methods ignore the fact that the propagation of traffic conditions between locations has a time delay in traffic systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdformer-propagation-delay-aware-dynamic-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpreting CNN Predictions using Conditional Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-cnn-predictions-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Supplying that information has two main challenges: how to represent this information in a form that is feedable to the GANs and how to effectively feed the representation to the GAN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-cnn-predictions-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interval Reachability of Nonlinear Dynamical Systems with Neural Network Controllers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interval-reachability-of-nonlinear-dynamical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This embedding provides a scalable approach for safety analysis of the neural control loop while preserving the nonlinear structure of the system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interval-reachability-of-nonlinear-dynamical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal conditional hidden Markov model for multimodal traffic prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-conditional-hidden-markov-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works overemphasize spatio-temporal correlations of traffic flow, ignoring the physical concepts that lead to the generation of observations and their causal relationship.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-conditional-hidden-markov-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum HyperNetworks: Training Binary Neural Networks in Quantum Superposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-hypernetworks-training-binary-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Binary neural networks, i. e., neural networks whose parameters and activations are constrained to only two possible values, offer a compelling avenue for the deployment of deep learning models on energy- and memory-limited devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-hypernetworks-training-binary-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmenting a Physics-Informed Neural Network for the 2D Burgers Equation by Addition of Solution Data Points</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-a-physics-informed-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we argue that the addition of the governing equations during training may provide a way to improve the overall performance of the model without relying on additional data, which is especially important for situations where the number of known solution points is limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-a-physics-informed-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Representing Noisy Image Without Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representing-noisy-image-without-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore a non-learning paradigm that aims to derive robust representation directly from noisy images, without the denoising as pre-processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representing-noisy-image-without-denoising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADAv2: Advanced Multi-Anchor Based Active Domain Adaptation Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/madav2-advanced-multi-anchor-based-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised domain adaption has been widely adopted in tasks with scarce annotated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/madav2-advanced-multi-anchor-based-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development, Optimization, and Deployment of Thermal Forward Vision Systems for Advance Vehicular Applications on Edge Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/development-optimization-and-deployment-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this research work, we have proposed a thermal tiny-YOLO multi-class object detection (TTYMOD) system as a smart forward sensing system that should remain effective in all weather and harsh environmental conditions using an end-to-end YOLO deep learning framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/development-optimization-and-deployment-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Supervised Semantic Segmentation via Gentle Teaching Assistant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-semantic-segmentation-via-4</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-Supervised Semantic Segmentation aims at training the segmentation model with limited labeled data and a large amount of unlabeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-semantic-segmentation-via-4</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Learning with Neuron Groups</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-learning-with-neuron-groups</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Local learning is an approach to model-parallelism that removes the standard end-to-end learning setup and utilizes local objective functions to permit parallel learning amongst model components in a deep network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-learning-with-neuron-groups</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SensorX2car: Sensors-to-car calibration for autonomous driving in road scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensorx2car-sensors-to-car-calibration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we present SensorX2car, a calibration toolbox for the online calibration of sensor-to-car coordinate systems in road scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensorx2car-sensors-to-car-calibration-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Advanced Computer Vision Techniques for Sports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-advanced-computer-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide a use case for such data: building a model for shot speed estimation with pose data obtained using only Computer Vision models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-advanced-computer-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAME: Attention Mechanism Based Feature Fusion for Generating Explanation Maps of Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tame-attention-mechanism-based-feature-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TAME can easily be applied to any convolutional neural network (CNN) by streamlining the optimization of the attention mechanism's training method and the selection of target model's feature maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tame-attention-mechanism-based-feature-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gated-ViGAT: Efficient Bottom-Up Event Recognition and Explanation Using a New Frame Selection Policy and Gating Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gated-vigat-efficient-bottom-up-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, Gated-ViGAT, an efficient approach for video event recognition, utilizing bottom-up (object) information, a new frame sampling policy and a gating mechanism is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gated-vigat-efficient-bottom-up-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention2Minority: A salient instance inference-based multiple instance learning for classifying small lesions in whole slide images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention2minority-a-salient-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method initially learns representations of normal WSIs, and it then compares the normal WSIs representations with all the input patches to infer the salient instances of the input WSI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention2minority-a-salient-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using CycleGANs to Generate Realistic STEM Images for Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-cyclegans-to-generate-realistic-stem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise of automation and machine learning (ML) in electron microscopy has the potential to revolutionize materials research by enabling the autonomous collection and processing of vast amounts of atomic resolution data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-cyclegans-to-generate-realistic-stem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergence of the SVD as an interpretable factorization in deep learning for inverse problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-the-svd-as-an-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the emergence of weight matrix singular value decomposition (SVD) in interpreting neural networks (NNs) for parameter estimation from noisy signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-the-svd-as-an-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Holistic Understanding of Mathematical Questions with Contrastive Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-holistic-understanding-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, in this paper, we propose a novel contrastive pre-training approach for mathematical question representations, namely QuesCo, which attempts to bring questions with more similar purposes closer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-holistic-understanding-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthcity: facilitating innovative use cases of synthetic data in different data modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthcity-facilitating-innovative-use-cases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthcity is an open-source software package for innovative use cases of synthetic data in ML fairness, privacy and augmentation across diverse tabular data modalities, including static data, regular and irregular time series, data with censoring, multi-source data, composite data, and more.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthcity-facilitating-innovative-use-cases</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Synthetic Hyperspectral Array Video Database with Applications to Cross-Spectral Reconstruction and Hyperspectral Video Coding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-synthetic-hyperspectral-array-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two novel algorithms for two different applications are proposed to prove the diversity of applications that can be addressed by this novel database.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-synthetic-hyperspectral-array-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEN2DWATER: A Novel Multispectral and Multitemporal Dataset and Deep Learning Benchmark for Water Resources Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sen2dwater-a-novel-multispectral-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Climate change has caused disruption in certain weather patterns, leading to extreme weather events like flooding and drought in different parts of the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sen2dwater-a-novel-multispectral-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact of the Euro 2020 championship on the spread of COVID-19</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-the-euro-2020-championship-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale events like the UEFA Euro~2020 football (soccer) championship offer a unique opportunity to quantify the impact of gatherings on the spread of COVID-19, as the number and dates of matches played by participating countries resembles a randomized study.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-the-euro-2020-championship-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Neural-Cracking-Machines: Self-Configurable Password Models from Auxiliary Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-neural-cracking-machines-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead, it exploits users' auxiliary information, such as email addresses, as a proxy signal to predict the underlying target password distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-neural-cracking-machines-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Close is ChatGPT to Human Experts? Comparison Corpus, Evaluation, and Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-close-is-chatgpt-to-human-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We call the collected dataset the Human ChatGPT Comparison Corpus (HC3).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-close-is-chatgpt-to-human-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-informed Information Field Theory for Modeling Physical Systems with Uncertainty Quantification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-information-field-theory-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As an addendum, the method is equipped with a metric which allows the posterior to automatically quantify model-form uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-information-field-theory-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strong inductive biases provably prevent harmless interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strong-inductive-biases-provably-prevent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Classical wisdom suggests that estimators should avoid fitting noise to achieve good generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strong-inductive-biases-provably-prevent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharp Eyes: A Salient Object Detector Working The Same Way as Human Visual Characteristics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharp-eyes-a-salient-object-detector-working</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the OS branch, we first aggregate multi-level features to adaptively select complementary components, and then feed the saliency features with expanded boundary into aggregated features to guide the network obtain complete prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharp-eyes-a-salient-object-detector-working</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Transport for Counterfactual Estimation: A Method for Causal Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-for-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we will have the dual view: doing an intervention, or changing the treatment (even just hypothetically, in a thought experiment, for example by asking what would have happened if a person had been Black) can have an impact on the values of x.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-for-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaRE: Finding Root Causes of Configuration Issues in Highly-Configurable Robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/care-finding-root-causes-of-configuration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robotic systems have several subsystems that possess a huge combinatorial configuration space and hundreds or even thousands of possible software and hardware configuration options interacting non-trivially.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/care-finding-root-causes-of-configuration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-based inexact graph matching on top of CNNs for semantic scene understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-based-inexact-graph-matching-on-top-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On FASSEG data, results show that our module improves accuracy of the CNN by about 6. 3% (the Hausdorff distance decreases from 22. 11 to 20. 71).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-based-inexact-graph-matching-on-top-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Synthetic Data Generation with Effective Nonlinear Causal Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-synthetic-data-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, typically, the variables of a dataset depend on one another, and these dependencies are not considered in data generation leading to the creation of implausible records.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-synthetic-data-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
