<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:08:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>xJailbreak: Representation Space Guided Reinforcement Learning for Interpretable LLM Jailbreaking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xjailbreak-representation-space-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safety alignment mechanism are essential for preventing large language models (LLMs) from generating harmful information or unethical content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xjailbreak-representation-space-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exponential Family Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exponential-family-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The self-attention mechanism is the backbone of the transformer neural network underlying most large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exponential-family-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Rollouts in Model-Based Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-rollouts-in-model-based-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model-based reinforcement learning (MBRL) seeks to enhance data efficiency by learning a model of the environment and generating synthetic rollouts from it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-rollouts-in-model-based-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Transformers Learn Full Bayesian Inference in Context?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-transformers-learn-full-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have emerged as the dominant architecture in the field of deep learning, with a broad range of applications and remarkable in-context learning (ICL) capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-transformers-learn-full-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DBSCAN in domains with periodic boundary conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dbscan-in-domains-with-periodic-boundary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many scientific problems involve data that is embedded in a space with periodic boundary conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dbscan-in-domains-with-periodic-boundary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outlier Synthesis via Hamiltonian Monte Carlo for Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-synthesis-via-hamiltonian-monte-carlo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Hamiltonian Monte Carlo with sampling acceptance rate almost close to 1 also makes our framework enjoy great efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-synthesis-via-hamiltonian-monte-carlo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HateBench: Benchmarking Hate Speech Detectors on LLM-Generated Content and Hate Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hatebench-benchmarking-hate-speech-detectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose HateBench, a framework for benchmarking hate speech detectors on LLM-generated hate speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hatebench-benchmarking-hate-speech-detectors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Phenology Modeling for Predicting Temperature Effects on Tree Dormancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-phenology-modeling-for-predicting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Biophysical models offer valuable insights into climate-phenology relationships in both natural and agricultural settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-phenology-modeling-for-predicting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model Critics for Execution-Free Evaluation of Code Changes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-critics-for-execution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Importantly, we assume access to the gold test patch for the problem (i. e., reference-aware) to assess both semantics and executability of generated patches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-critics-for-execution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polyp-Gen: Realistic and Diverse Polyp Image Generation for Endoscopic Dataset Expansion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyp-gen-realistic-and-diverse-polyp-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advancements in generating synthetic images for dataset expansion, existing endoscopic image generation algorithms failed to accurately generate the details of polyp boundary regions and typically required medical priors to specify plausible locations and shapes of polyps, which limited the realism and diversity of the generated images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyp-gen-realistic-and-diverse-polyp-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-high resolution multimodal MRI dense labelled holistic brain atlas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-high-resolution-multimodal-mri-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These labels were grouped at different scales to provide a holistic view of the brain at different levels in a coherent and consistent manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-high-resolution-multimodal-mri-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>B-RIGHT: Benchmark Re-evaluation for Integrity in Generalized Human-Object Interaction Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/b-right-benchmark-re-evaluation-for-integrity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human-object interaction (HOI) is an essential problem in artificial intelligence (AI) which aims to understand the visual world that involves complex relationships between humans and objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/b-right-benchmark-re-evaluation-for-integrity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream to Drive with Predictive Individual World Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dream-to-drive-with-predictive-individual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is still a challenging topic to make reactive driving behaviors in complex urban environments as road users' intentions are unknown.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dream-to-drive-with-predictive-individual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RODEO: Robust Outlier Detection via Exposing Adaptive Out-of-Distribution Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rodeo-robust-outlier-detection-via-exposing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce RODEO, a data-centric approach that generates effective outliers for robust outlier detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rodeo-robust-outlier-detection-via-exposing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CascadeV: An Implementation of Wurstchen Architecture for Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascadev-an-implementation-of-wurstchen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, with the tremendous success of diffusion models in the field of text-to-image (T2I) generation, increasing attention has been directed toward their potential in text-to-video (T2V) applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascadev-an-implementation-of-wurstchen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JRE-L: Journalist, Reader, and Editor LLMs in the Loop for Science Journalism for the General Audience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jre-l-journalist-reader-and-editor-llms-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Science journalism reports current scientific discoveries to non-specialists, aiming to enable public comprehension of the state of the art.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jre-l-journalist-reader-and-editor-llms-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A General Bayesian Framework for Informative Input Design in System Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-bayesian-framework-for-informative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We tackle the problem of informative input design for system identification, where we select inputs, observe the corresponding outputs from the true system, and optimize the parameters of our model to best fit the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-bayesian-framework-for-informative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SliceOcc: Indoor 3D Semantic Occupancy Prediction with Vertical Slice Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliceocc-indoor-3d-semantic-occupancy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To utilize these slice features, we propose SliceOcc, an RGB camera-based model specifically tailored for indoor 3D semantic occupancy prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliceocc-indoor-3d-semantic-occupancy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHiP: Cross-modal Hierarchical Direct Preference Optimization for Multimodal LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chip-cross-modal-hierarchical-direct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, in this work, we propose a Cross-modal Hierarchical Direct Preference Optimization (CHiP) to address these limitations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chip-cross-modal-hierarchical-direct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scanning Trojaned Models Using Out-of-Distribution Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scanning-trojaned-models-using-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TRODO leverages the concept of "blind spots"--regions where trojaned classifiers erroneously identify out-of-distribution (OOD) samples as in-distribution (ID).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scanning-trojaned-models-using-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting harassment and defamation in cyberbullying with emotion-adaptive training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-harassment-and-defamation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[EAT consistently improves the average macro F1, precision and recall by 20% in cyberbullying detection tasks across nine transformer-based models under low-resource settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-harassment-and-defamation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FactCG: Enhancing Fact Checkers with Graph-Based Multi-Hop Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factcg-enhancing-fact-checkers-with-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior research on training grounded factuality classification models to detect hallucinations in large language models (LLMs) has relied on public natural language inference (NLI) data and synthetic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factcg-enhancing-fact-checkers-with-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-Differentiating Any LLM Workflow: A Farewell to Manual Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-differentiating-any-llm-workflow-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have reshaped natural language processing, powering applications from multi-hop retrieval and question answering to autonomous agent workflows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-differentiating-any-llm-workflow-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Code Runtime Performance through Context-Aware Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-code-runtime-performance-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimizing software performance through automated code refinement offers a promising avenue for enhancing execution speed and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-code-runtime-performance-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Histoires Morales: A French Dataset for Assessing Moral Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histoires-morales-a-french-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While models are often adapted to user preferences, it is equally important to ensure they align with moral norms and behaviours in real-world social situations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histoires-morales-a-french-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VeriFact: Verifying Facts in LLM-Generated Clinical Text with Electronic Health Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifact-verifying-facts-in-llm-generated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods to ensure factual accuracy of text generated by large language models (LLM) in clinical medicine are lacking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifact-verifying-facts-in-llm-generated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Roughly Forced Nonlinear PDEs via Misspecified Kernel Methods and Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-roughly-forced-nonlinear-pdes-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the use of Gaussian Processes (GPs) or Neural Networks (NNs) to numerically approximate the solutions to nonlinear partial differential equations (PDEs) with rough forcing or source terms, which commonly arise as pathwise solutions to stochastic PDEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-roughly-forced-nonlinear-pdes-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mamba-Shedder: Post-Transformer Compression for Efficient Selective Structured State Space Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-shedder-post-transformer-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large pre-trained models have achieved outstanding results in sequence modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-shedder-post-transformer-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RDMM: Fine-Tuned LLM Models for On-Device Robotic Decision Making with Enhanced Contextual Awareness in Specific Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdmm-fine-tuned-llm-models-for-on-device</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research introduces a framework that utilizes RDMM (Robotics Decision-Making Models), which possess the capacity for decision-making within domain-specific contexts, as well as an awareness of their personal knowledge and capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdmm-fine-tuned-llm-models-for-on-device</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extending Information Bottleneck Attribution to Video Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-information-bottleneck-attribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce VIBA, a novel approach for explainable video classification by adapting Information Bottlenecks for Attribution (IBA) to video sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-information-bottleneck-attribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Models in Dialogue for Active Perception and Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-models-in-dialogue-for-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose an LLM based model dialogue approach, in which two deep learning models engage in a dialogue to actively control a drone to increase perception and anomaly detection accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-models-in-dialogue-for-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Visual Inspection Capability of Multi-Modal Large Language Models on Medical Time Series with Supportive Conformalized and Interpretable Small Specialized Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-visual-inspection-capability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) exhibit remarkable capabilities in visual inspection of medical time-series data, achieving proficiency comparable to human clinicians.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-visual-inspection-capability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeqSeg: Learning Local Segments for Automatic Vascular Model Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seqseg-learning-local-segments-for-automatic-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computational modeling of cardiovascular function has become a critical part of diagnosing, treating and understanding cardiovascular disease.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seqseg-learning-local-segments-for-automatic-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pfungst and Clever Hans: Identifying the unintended cues in a widely used Alzheimer's disease MRI dataset using explainable deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pfungst-and-clever-hans-identifying-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study aims to enlighten the underlying black-box nature and reveal individual contributions of T1-weighted (T1w) gray-white matter texture, volumetric information and preprocessing on classification performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pfungst-and-clever-hans-identifying-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CausalSR: Structural Causal Model-Driven Super-Resolution with Counterfactual Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalsr-structural-causal-model-driven-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel counterfactual learning strategy that leverages semantic guidance to reason about hypothetical degradation scenarios, leading to theoretically-grounded representations that capture invariant features across different degradation conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalsr-structural-causal-model-driven-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CILP-FGDI: Exploiting Vision-Language Model for Generalizable Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cilp-fgdi-exploiting-vision-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, domain-invariant and domain-relevant prompts are generated, and both positive (pulling together image features and domain-invariant prompts) and negative (pushing apart image features and domain-relevant prompts) views are used to train the image encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cilp-fgdi-exploiting-vision-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWIFT: Mapping Sub-series with Wavelet Decomposition Improves Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swift-mapping-sub-series-with-wavelet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose $\textit{SWIFT}$, a lightweight model that is not only powerful, but also efficient in deployment and inference for Long-term Time Series Forecasting (LTSF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swift-mapping-sub-series-with-wavelet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Tropical Cyclone Forecasting With Video Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-tropical-cyclone-forecasting-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tropical cyclone (TC) forecasting is crucial for disaster preparedness and mitigation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-tropical-cyclone-forecasting-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Attention-Sharing Information Distillation Transformer for Lightweight Single Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-attention-sharing-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose the Attention-Sharing Information Distillation (ASID) network, a lightweight SR network that integrates attention-sharing and an information distillation structure specifically designed for Transformer-based SR methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-attention-sharing-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing Out-of-Label Hazard Detection in Dashcam Videos: Insights from the COOOL Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-out-of-label-hazard-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel approach for hazard analysis in dashcam footage, addressing the detection of driver reactions to hazards, the identification of hazardous objects, and the generation of descriptive captions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-out-of-label-hazard-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Structural Convolution Network for Domain-Invariant Point Cloud Recognition of Autonomous Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-structural-convolution-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present the Multi-View Structural Convolution Network (MSCN) designed for domain-invariant point cloud recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-structural-convolution-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Retinal V2: Transfer an Elite Knowledge Spark into Fundus Vision-Language Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-retinal-v2-transfer-an-elite-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language pretraining (VLP) has been investigated to generalize across diverse downstream tasks for fundus image analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-retinal-v2-transfer-an-elite-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TopoNets: High Performing Vision and Language Models with Brain-Like Topography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toponets-high-performing-vision-and-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neurons in the brain are organized such that nearby cells tend to share similar functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toponets-high-performing-vision-and-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUCY: Linguistic Understanding and Control Yielding Early Stage of Her</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lucy-linguistic-understanding-and-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The film Her features Samantha, a sophisticated AI audio agent who is capable of understanding both linguistic and paralinguistic information in human speech and delivering real-time responses that are natural, informative and sensitive to emotional subtleties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lucy-linguistic-understanding-and-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parametric Retrieval Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parametric-retrieval-augmented-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce Parametric retrieval-augmented generation (Parametric RAG), a new RAG paradigm that integrates external knowledge directly into the parameters of feed-forward networks (FFN) of an LLM through document parameterization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parametric-retrieval-augmented-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Quantum Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-quantum-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Benchmarking and establishing proper statistical validation metrics for reinforcement learning (RL) remain ongoing challenges, where no consensus has been established yet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-quantum-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emilia: A Large-Scale, Extensive, Multilingual, and Diverse Dataset for Speech Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emilia-a-large-scale-extensive-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By leveraging Emilia-Pipe, we construct Emilia, the first multilingual speech generation dataset derived from in-the-wild speech data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emilia-a-large-scale-extensive-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CENSOR: Defense Against Gradient Inversion via Orthogonal Subspace Bayesian Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/censor-defense-against-gradient-inversion-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing gradient inversion attacks can exploit this vulnerability to recover private training instances from a client's gradient vectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/censor-defense-against-gradient-inversion-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is It Navajo? Accurate Language Detection in Endangered Athabaskan Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-it-navajo-accurate-language-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Endangered languages, such as Navajo - the most widely spoken Native American language - are significantly underrepresented in contemporary language technologies, exacerbating the challenges of their preservation and revitalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-it-navajo-accurate-language-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Formal Verification of Markov Processes with Learned Parameters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/formal-verification-of-markov-processes-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the problem of formally verifying properties of Markov processes where the parameters are the output of machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/formal-verification-of-markov-processes-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
