<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 09:15:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Flexible Recursive Network for Video Stereo Matching Based on Residual Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-flexible-recursive-network-for-video-stereo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The RecSM network accelerates stereo matching using a Multi-scale Residual Estimation Module (MREM), which employs the temporal context as a reference and rapidly calculates the disparity for the current frame by computing only the residual values between the current and previous frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-flexible-recursive-network-for-video-stereo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing Order Recovery in Complex and Long Static Handwriting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/writing-order-recovery-in-complex-and-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a new system to estimate the order recovery of thinned static trajectories, which allows to effectively resolve the clusters and select the order of the executed pen-downs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/writing-order-recovery-in-complex-and-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L-PR: Exploiting LiDAR Fiducial Marker for Unordered Low Overlap Multiview Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l-pr-exploiting-lidar-fiducial-marker-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we formulate the unordered multiview point cloud registration problem as a maximum a-posteriori (MAP) problem and develop a framework consisting of two levels of graphs to address it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l-pr-exploiting-lidar-fiducial-marker-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient User Sequence Learning for Online Services via Compressed Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-user-sequence-learning-for-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning representations of user behavior sequences is crucial for various online services, such as online fraudulent transaction detection mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-user-sequence-learning-for-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HASS: Hardware-Aware Sparsity Search for Dataflow DNN Accelerator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hass-hardware-aware-sparsity-search-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a Hardware-Aware Sparsity Search (HASS) to systematically determine an efficient sparsity solution for dataflow accelerators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hass-hardware-aware-sparsity-search-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PosterLLaVa: Constructing a Unified Multi-modal Layout Generator with LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posterllava-constructing-a-unified-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Layout generation is the keystone in achieving automated graphic design, requiring arranging the position and size of various multi-modal design elements in a visually pleasing and constraint-following manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posterllava-constructing-a-unified-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny models from tiny data: Textual and null-text inversion for few-shot distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiny-models-from-tiny-data-textual-and-null</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using knowledge distillation, the capabilities of high-performing but slow models can be transferred to tiny, efficient models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiny-models-from-tiny-data-textual-and-null</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CommonPower: Supercharging Machine Learning for Smart Grids</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/commonpower-supercharging-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore equipped with a generic forecasting interface, CommonPower constitutes a versatile tool significantly augmenting the exploration of safe RL controllers in smart grids on several dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/commonpower-supercharging-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second-order differential operators, stochastic differential equations and Brownian motions on embedded manifolds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/second-order-differential-operators</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose the retractive Euler-Maruyama method to solve a SDE, taking into account the second-order term of a tangent retraction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/second-order-differential-operators</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual-Text Cross Alignment: Refining the Similarity Score in Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-text-cross-alignment-refining-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The local visual areas are then cross-aligned with the finer descriptions by creating a similarity matrix using the pre-trained VLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-text-cross-alignment-refining-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PrE-Text: Training Language Models on Private Federated Data in the Age of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-text-training-language-models-on-private</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Altogether, these results suggest that training on DP synthetic data can be a better option than training a model on-device on private distributed data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-text-training-language-models-on-private</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MESS: Modern Electronic Structure Simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mess-modern-electronic-structure-simulations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce MESS: a modern electronic structure simulation package implemented in JAX; porting the ESS code to the ML world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mess-modern-electronic-structure-simulations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMCL: Boosting Deformable DETR-Based Detectors with Multi-Class Min-Margin Contrastive Learning for Superior Prohibited Item Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmcl-boosting-deformable-detr-based-detectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prohibited Item detection in X-ray images is one of the most effective security inspection methods. However, differing from natural light images, the unique overlapping phenomena in X-ray images lead to the coupling of foreground and background features, thereby lowering the accuracy of general object detectors. Therefore, we propose a Multi-Class Min-Margin Contrastive Learning (MMCL) method that, by clarifying the category semantic information of content queries under the deformable DETR architecture, aids the model in extracting specific category foreground information from coupled features. Specifically, after grouping content queries by the number of categories, we employ the Multi-Class Inter-Class Exclusion (MIE) loss to push apart content queries from different groups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmcl-boosting-deformable-detr-based-detectors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EngineBench: Flow Reconstruction in the Transparent Combustion Chamber III Optical Engine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enginebench-flow-reconstruction-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we propose a novel inpainting task using random edge gaps, a technique that emphasises realism by introducing occlusions at random sizes and orientations at the edges of the PIV images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enginebench-flow-reconstruction-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reproducibility study of FairAC</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducibility-study-of-fairac</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work aims to reproduce the findings of the paper "Fair Attribute Completion on Graph with Missing Attributes" written by Guo, Chu, and Li arXiv:2302. 12977 by investigating the claims made in the paper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducibility-study-of-fairac</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Guidance Information to Utilize Unlabeled Samples:A Label Encoding Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-guidance-information-to-utilize</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By analyzing the learning objective of ERM, we find that the guidance information for labeled samples in a specific category is the corresponding label encoding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-guidance-information-to-utilize</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained Causal Dynamics Learning with Quantization for Improving Robustness in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-causal-dynamics-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal dynamics learning has recently emerged as a promising approach to enhancing robustness in reinforcement learning (RL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-causal-dynamics-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BadAgent: Inserting and Activating Backdoor Attacks in LLM Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badagent-inserting-and-activating-backdoor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we show that such methods are vulnerable to our proposed backdoor attacks named BadAgent on various agent tasks, where a backdoor can be embedded by fine-tuning on the backdoor data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badagent-inserting-and-activating-backdoor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QJL: 1-Bit Quantized JL Transform for KV Cache Quantization with Zero Overhead</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qjl-1-bit-quantized-jl-transform-for-kv-cache</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, traditional quantization methods face significant memory overhead due to the need to store quantization constants (at least a zero point and a scale) in full precision per data block.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qjl-1-bit-quantized-jl-transform-for-kv-cache</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floating Anchor Diffusion Model for Multi-motif Scaffolding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/floating-anchor-diffusion-model-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motif scaffolding seeks to design scaffold structures for constructing proteins with functions derived from the desired motif, which is crucial for the design of vaccines and enzymes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/floating-anchor-diffusion-model-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Error-preserving Automatic Speech Recognition of Young English Learners' Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/error-preserving-automatic-speech-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we build an ASR system that satisfies these requirements: it works on spontaneous speech by young language learners and preserves their errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/error-preserving-automatic-speech-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models as Evaluators for Recommendation Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-as-evaluators-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also provide further insights into combining human labels with the LLM evaluation process and utilizing ensembles of multiple heterogeneous LLM evaluators to enhance the accuracy and stability of evaluations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-as-evaluators-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperFormer: Volumetric Transformer Architectures for MRI Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superformer-volumetric-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel framework for processing volumetric medical information using Visual Transformers (ViTs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superformer-volumetric-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DenoDet: Attention as Deformable Multi-Subspace Feature Denoising for Target Detection in SAR Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denodet-attention-as-deformable-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by traditional SAR image denoising, we propose DenoDet, a network aided by explicit frequency domain transform to calibrate convolutional biases and pay more attention to high-frequencies, forming a natural multi-scale subspace representation to detect targets from the perspective of multi-subspace denoising.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denodet-attention-as-deformable-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Contamination: Neural Networks Learn Uncorrelated Features and Fail to Generalize</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-contamination-neural-networks-learn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, by a theoretical study of two-layer ReLU networks optimized by stochastic gradient descent (SGD) under a structured feature model, we identify a fundamental yet unexplored feature learning proclivity of neural networks, feature contamination: neural networks can learn uncorrelated features together with predictive features, resulting in generalization failure under distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-contamination-neural-networks-learn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-to-Image Rectified Flow as Plug-and-Play Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-to-image-rectified-flow-as-plug-and-play</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides the generative capabilities of diffusion priors, motivated by the unique time-symmetry properties of rectified flow models, a variant of our method can additionally perform image inversion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-to-image-rectified-flow-as-plug-and-play</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A-Bench: Are LMMs Masters at Evaluating AI-generated Images?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bench-are-lmms-masters-at-evaluating-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How to accurately and efficiently assess AI-generated images (AIGIs) remains a critical challenge for generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bench-are-lmms-masters-at-evaluating-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Genetic Mutation from Whole Slide Images via Biomedical-Linguistic Knowledge Enhanced Multi-label Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-genetic-mutation-from-whole-slide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(b) A knowledge association module that fuses linguistic and biomedical knowledge into gene priors by transformer-based graph representation learning, capturing the intrinsic relationships between different genes' mutations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-genetic-mutation-from-whole-slide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSS: Contrastive Semantic Similarity for Uncertainty Quantification of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/css-contrastive-semantic-similarity-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These studies employ logits of NLI classifier for semantic clustering to estimate uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/css-contrastive-semantic-similarity-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional Idempotent Generative Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-idempotent-generative-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Conditional Idempotent Generative Networks (CIGN), a novel approach that expands upon Idempotent Generative Networks (IGN) to enable conditional generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-idempotent-generative-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Convolutional Branch and Bound</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-convolutional-branch-and-bound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article demonstrates the effectiveness of employing a deep learning model in an optimization pipeline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-convolutional-branch-and-bound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DREW : Towards Robust Data Provenance by Leveraging Error-Controlled Watermarking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drew-towards-robust-data-provenance-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identifying the origin of data is crucial for data provenance, with applications including data ownership protection, media forensics, and detecting AI-generated content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drew-towards-robust-data-provenance-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StreamSpeech: Simultaneous Speech-to-Speech Translation with Multi-task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streamspeech-simultaneous-speech-to-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Simultaneous speech-to-speech translation (Simul-S2ST, a. k. a streaming speech translation) outputs target speech while receiving streaming speech inputs, which is critical for real-time communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streamspeech-simultaneous-speech-to-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puzzle Pieces Picker: Deciphering Ancient Chinese Characters with Radical Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puzzle-pieces-picker-deciphering-ancient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Oracle Bone Inscriptions is one of the oldest existing forms of writing in the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puzzle-pieces-picker-deciphering-ancient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identification of Stone Deterioration Patterns with Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identification-of-stone-deterioration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we systematically evaluate the abilities of the main foundational multimodal models to recognise and classify anomalies and deterioration patterns of the stone elements that are useful in the practice of conservation and restoration of world heritage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identification-of-stone-deterioration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DifAttack++: Query-Efficient Black-Box Adversarial Attack via Hierarchical Disentangled Feature Space in Cross Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difattack-query-efficient-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work investigates efficient score-based black-box adversarial attacks with a high Attack Success Rate (ASR) and good generalizability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difattack-query-efficient-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xmodel-LM Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xmodel-lm-technical-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Xmodel-LM, a compact and efficient 1. 1B language model pre-trained on over 2 trillion tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xmodel-lm-technical-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Decomposition for Sentence Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/space-decomposition-for-sentence-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results demonstrate that MixSP decreased the overlap representation between upper-range and lower-range classes significantly while outperforming competitors on STS and zero-shot benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/space-decomposition-for-sentence-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Text-to-Image Retrieval with Large Language Models: A Plug-and-Play Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-text-to-image-retrieval-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we primarily address the issue of dialogue-form context query within the interactive text-to-image retrieval task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-text-to-image-retrieval-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Spiking neural networks meet temporal attention image decoding and adaptive spiking neuron</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-spiking-neural-networks-meet-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, our ALIF neuron model achieves remarkable classification accuracy on MNIST (99. 78\%) and CIFAR-10 (93. 89\%) datasets, demonstrating the effectiveness of learning adaptive thresholds for spiking neurons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-spiking-neural-networks-meet-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Copy-Move Forgery Detection and Localization Scheme: How to Avoid Missed Detection and False Alarm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-copy-move-forgery-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image copy-move is an operation that replaces one part of the image with another part of the same image, which can be used for illegal purposes due to the potential semantic changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-copy-move-forgery-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combinatorial Optimization with Automated Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combinatorial-optimization-with-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The idea of AutoGNP is to use graph neural architecture search algorithms to automatically find the best GNNs for a given NP-hard combinatorial optimization problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combinatorial-optimization-with-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linking Named Entities in Diderot's \textit{Encyclopédie} to Wikidata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linking-named-entities-in-diderot-s-textit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we describe the annotation of more than 10, 300 of the \textit{Encyclop\'edie} entries with Wikidata identifiers enabling us to connect these entries to the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linking-named-entities-in-diderot-s-textit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LW-DETR: A Transformer Replacement to YOLO for Real-Time Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lw-detr-a-transformer-replacement-to-yolo-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a light-weight detection transformer, LW-DETR, which outperforms YOLOs for real-time object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lw-detr-a-transformer-replacement-to-yolo-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Transformers with Weisfeiler-Leman</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-transformers-with-weisfeiler-leman</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While recent works aligning graph transformer architectures with the $k$-WL hierarchy have shown promising empirical results, employing transformers for higher orders of $k$ remains challenging due to a prohibitive runtime and memory complexity of self-attention as well as impractical architectural assumptions, such as an infeasible number of attention heads.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-transformers-with-weisfeiler-leman</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpikeLM: Towards General Spike-Driven Language Modeling via Elastic Bi-Spiking Mechanisms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spikelm-towards-general-spike-driven-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We plug this elastic bi-spiking mechanism in language modeling, named SpikeLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spikelm-towards-general-spike-driven-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADer: A Comprehensive Benchmark for Multi-class Visual Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ader-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses this issue by proposing a comprehensive visual anomaly detection benchmark, \textbf{\textit{ADer}}, which is a modular framework that is highly extensible for new methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ader-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computation-Efficient Era: A Comprehensive Survey of State Space Models in Medical Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computation-efficient-era-a-comprehensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State Space Models (SSMs), specifically the \textit{\textbf{Mamba}} model with selection mechanisms and hardware-aware architecture, have garnered immense interest lately in sequential modeling and visual representation learning, challenging the dominance of transformers by providing infinite context lengths and offering substantial efficiency maintaining linear complexity in the input sequence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computation-efficient-era-a-comprehensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultifacetEval: Multifaceted Evaluation to Probe LLMs in Mastering Medical Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multifaceteval-multifaceted-evaluation-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to explore the causes of this gap by employing a multifaceted examination schema to systematically probe the actual mastery of medical knowledge by current LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multifaceteval-multifaceted-evaluation-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-Encoding or Auto-Regression? A Reality Check on Causality of Self-Attention-Based Sequential Recommenders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-encoding-or-auto-regression-a-reality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We start by tracing the AE/AR debate back to its origin through a systematic re-evaluation of SASRec and BERT4Rec, discovering that AR models generally surpass AE models in sequential recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-encoding-or-auto-regression-a-reality</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
