<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 21:09:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting to Non-Stationary Environments: Multi-Armed Bandit Enhanced Retrieval-Augmented Generation on Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-to-non-stationary-environments-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The system utilizes real-time user feedback to adapt to dynamic environments, by selecting the appropriate retrieval method based on input queries and the historical multi-objective performance of each arm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-to-non-stationary-environments-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning Policy as Macro Regulator Rather than Macro Placer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-policy-as-macro</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In modern chip design, placement aims at placing millions of circuit modules, which is an essential step that significantly influences power, performance, and area (PPA) metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-policy-as-macro</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Motion Transfer with Diffusion Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-motion-transfer-with-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose DiTFlow, a method for transferring the motion of a reference video to a newly synthesized one, designed specifically for Diffusion Transformers (DiT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-motion-transfer-with-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granite Guardian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/granite-guardian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Granite Guardian models, a suite of safeguards designed to provide risk detection for prompts and responses, enabling safe and responsible use in combination with any large language model (LLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/granite-guardian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StoryWeaver: A Unified World Model for Knowledge-Enhanced Story Character Customization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/storyweaver-a-unified-world-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Story visualization has gained increasing attention in artificial intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/storyweaver-a-unified-world-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QAPyramid: Fine-grained Evaluation of Content Selection for Text Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qapyramid-fine-grained-evaluation-of-content</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Pyramid human evaluation protocol, which assesses content selection by breaking the reference summary into sub-units and verifying their presence in the system summary, has been widely adopted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qapyramid-fine-grained-evaluation-of-content</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Training Statistical Calibration for Higher Activation Sparsity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-training-statistical-calibration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Statistical Calibrated Activation Pruning (SCAP), a post-training activation pruning framework that (1) generalizes sparsification by input activations of Fully-Connected layers for generic and flexible application across Transformers, and (2) features a simple Mode-Centering technique to pre-calibrate activation distributions for maximizing post-training sparsity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-training-statistical-calibration-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Potential of Reverse Distillation for Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-potential-of-reverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Distillation (KD) is a promising approach for unsupervised Anomaly Detection (AD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-potential-of-reverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Linear Item-Item Model for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-linear-item-item-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, they solely deal with the sequential order of items (i. e., sequential information) and overlook the actual timestamp (i. e., temporal information).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-linear-item-item-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion Artifact Removal in Pixel-Frequency Domain via Alternate Masks and Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-artifact-removal-in-pixel-frequency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motion artifacts present in magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) can seriously interfere with clinical diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-artifact-removal-in-pixel-frequency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Optimization of Antibodies Informed by a Generative Model of Evolving Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-optimization-of-antibodies-informed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To build effective therapeutics, biologists iteratively mutate antibody sequences to improve binding and stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-optimization-of-antibodies-informed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconstructing Deep Neural Networks: Unleashing the Optimization Potential of Natural Gradient Descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructing-deep-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Natural gradient descent (NGD) is a powerful optimization technique for machine learning, but the computational complexity of the inverse Fisher information matrix limits its application in training deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructing-deep-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Parametric Approach to Adversarial Augmentation for Cross-Domain Iris Presentation Attack Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-parametric-approach-to-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Iris-based biometric systems are vulnerable to presentation attacks (PAs), where adversaries present physical artifacts (e. g., printed iris images, textured contact lenses) to defeat the system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-parametric-approach-to-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OmniDocBench: Benchmarking Diverse PDF Document Parsing with Comprehensive Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnidocbench-benchmarking-diverse-pdf</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Document content extraction is crucial in computer vision, especially for meeting the high-quality data needs of large language models (LLMs) and retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) technologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnidocbench-benchmarking-diverse-pdf</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartAgent: Chain-of-User-Thought for Embodied Personalized Agent in Cyber World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartagent-chain-of-user-thought-for-embodied</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose Chain-of-User-Thought (COUT), a novel embodied reasoning paradigm that takes a chain of thought from basic action thinking to explicit and implicit personalized preference thought to incorporate personalized factors into autonomous agent learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartagent-chain-of-user-thought-for-embodied</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DriveMM: All-in-One Large Multimodal Model for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivemm-all-in-one-large-multimodal-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Multimodal Models (LMMs) have demonstrated exceptional comprehension and interpretation capabilities in Autonomous Driving (AD) by incorporating large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivemm-all-in-one-large-multimodal-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Relation Extraction via Supervised Rationale Verification and Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-relation-extraction-via-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the rapid progress that existing automated feedback methods have made in correcting the output of large language models (LLMs), these methods cannot be well applied to the relation extraction (RE) task due to their designated feedback objectives and correction manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-relation-extraction-via-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBraMod: A Criss-Cross Brain Foundation Model for EEG Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbramod-a-criss-cross-brain-foundation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, existing EEG foundation models have limited generalizability on a wide range of downstream BCI tasks due to varying formats of EEG data, making it challenging to adapt to.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbramod-a-criss-cross-brain-foundation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks Are More Than Filters: Revisiting and Benchmarking from A Spectral Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-are-more-than-filters</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demystify such a conflict, this paper introduces a comprehensive benchmark to measure and evaluate GNNs' capability in capturing and leveraging the information encoded in different frequency components of the input graph data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-are-more-than-filters</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Dual-Exposure Quad-Bayer Patterns for Joint Denoising and Deblurring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-dual-exposure-quad-bayer-patterns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long exposures reduce noise but introduce blur.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-dual-exposure-quad-bayer-patterns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Automated Cross-domain Exploratory Data Analysis through Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-automated-cross-domain-exploratory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Exploratory data analysis (EDA), coupled with SQL, is essential for data analysts involved in data exploration and analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-automated-cross-domain-exploratory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Gap for Test-Time Multimodal Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-for-test-time-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in real-world dynamic scenarios, the distribution of target data is always changing and different from the source data used to train the model, which leads to performance degradation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-for-test-time-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FireFlow: Fast Inversion of Rectified Flow for Image Semantic Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fireflow-fast-inversion-of-rectified-flow-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though Rectified Flows (ReFlows) with distillation offers a promising way for fast sampling, its fast inversion transforms images back to structured noise for recovery and following editing remains unsolved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fireflow-fast-inversion-of-rectified-flow-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffCLIP: Few-shot Language-driven Multimodal Classifier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffclip-few-shot-language-driven-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this issue, we introduce DiffCLIP, a novel framework that extends CLIP to effectively convey comprehensive language-driven semantic information for accurate classification of high-dimensional multimodal remote sensing images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffclip-few-shot-language-driven-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACDiT: Interpolating Autoregressive Conditional Modeling and Diffusion Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acdit-interpolating-autoregressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The analysis of the trade-off between autoregressive modeling and diffusion demonstrates the potential of ACDiT to be used in long-horizon visual generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acdit-interpolating-autoregressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Outlier Exposure</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taylor-outlier-exposure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, constructing clean auxiliary OOD datasets, uncontaminated by in-distribution (ID) samples, is essential for OE; generally, a noisy OOD dataset contaminated with ID samples negatively impacts OE training dynamics and final detection performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taylor-outlier-exposure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Data Augmentation and Training for Perception DNN in Autonomous Aerial Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-data-augmentation-and-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, synthetic data generation solutions for aerial vehicles are still lacking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-data-augmentation-and-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Federated Learning Framework Against Gradient Inversion Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-federated-learning-framework-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By revisiting the key to privacy exposure in FL under GIA, which lies in the frequent sharing of model gradients that contain private data, we take a new perspective by designing a novel privacy preserve FL framework that effectively ``breaks the direct connection'' between the shared parameters and the local private data to defend against GIA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-federated-learning-framework-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maya: An Instruction Finetuned Multilingual Multimodal Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maya-an-instruction-finetuned-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of large Vision-Language Models (VLMs) has led to impressive results on academic benchmarks, primarily in widely spoken languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maya-an-instruction-finetuned-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frame Representation Hypothesis: Multi-Token LLM Interpretability and Concept-Guided Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frame-representation-hypothesis-multi-token</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interpretability is a key challenge in fostering trust for Large Language Models (LLMs), which stems from the complexity of extracting reasoning from model's parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frame-representation-hypothesis-multi-token</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntellectSeeker: A Personalized Literature Management System with the Probabilistic Model and Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intellectseeker-a-personalized-literature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce IntellectSeeker, an innovative and personalized intelligent academic literature management platform to address these challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intellectseeker-a-personalized-literature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ArtFormer: Controllable Generation of Diverse 3D Articulated Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artformer-controllable-generation-of-diverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel framework for modeling and conditional generation of 3D articulated objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artformer-controllable-generation-of-diverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARP: Hesitation-Aware Reframing in Transformer Inference Pass</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harp-hesitation-aware-reframing-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper aims to improve the performance of large language models by addressing the variable computational demands in inference steps, where some tokens require more computational resources than others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harp-hesitation-aware-reframing-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFL: Simplifying Chemical Structure Recognition with Ring-Free Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rfl-simplifying-chemical-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The primary objective of Optical Chemical Structure Recognition is to identify chemical structure images into corresponding markup sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rfl-simplifying-chemical-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hallucination Elimination and Semantic Enhancement Framework for Vision-Language Models in Traffic Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallucination-elimination-and-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large vision-language models (LVLMs) have demonstrated remarkable capabilities in multimodal understanding and generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallucination-elimination-and-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A data-driven learned discretization approach in finite volume schemes for hyperbolic conservation laws and varying boundary conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-driven-learned-discretization-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extend this approach to flux-limited finite volume schemes for hyperbolic scalar and systems of conservation laws.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-driven-learned-discretization-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Sequential Recommendation Models with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-sequential-recommendation-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The nature of the problem, as well as the good performance observed across various domains, has motivated the use of the transformer architecture, which has proven effective in leveraging increasingly larger amounts of training data when accompanied by an increase in the number of model parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-sequential-recommendation-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Method for Evaluating Hyperparameter Sensitivity in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-method-for-evaluating-hyperparameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of modern reinforcement learning algorithms critically relies on tuning ever-increasing numbers of hyperparameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-method-for-evaluating-hyperparameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EvRepSL: Event-Stream Representation via Self-Supervised Learning for Event-Based Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evrepsl-event-stream-representation-via-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most of the state-of-the-art event-stream representations are manually designed and the quality of these representations cannot be guaranteed due to the noisy nature of event-streams.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evrepsl-event-stream-representation-via-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PTSBench: A Comprehensive Post-Training Sparsity Benchmark Towards Algorithms and Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptsbench-a-comprehensive-post-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our PTSBench can provide (1) new observations for a better understanding of the PTS algorithms, (2) in-depth and comprehensive evaluations for the sparsification ability of models, and (3) a well-structured and easy-integrate open-source framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptsbench-a-comprehensive-post-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynCamMaster: Synchronizing Multi-Camera Video Generation from Diverse Viewpoints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syncammaster-synchronizing-multi-camera-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in video diffusion models have shown exceptional abilities in simulating real-world dynamics and maintaining 3D consistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syncammaster-synchronizing-multi-camera-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monte Carlo Tree Search based Space Transfer for Black-box Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-tree-search-based-space-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MCTS-transfer can not only provide a well-performing search space for warm-start but also adaptively identify and leverage the information of similar source tasks to reconstruct the search space during the optimization process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-tree-search-based-space-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-PoE: Multiple Choice Reasoning via. Process of Elimination using Multi-Modal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-poe-multiple-choice-reasoning-via-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Critically, this approach not only broadens the application of the elimination process to multi-modal contexts but also allows few-shot experiments, thereby addressing two principal limitations concerning usage of PoE only in zero-shot settings and only with a language-only framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-poe-multiple-choice-reasoning-via-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphNeuralNetworks.jl: Deep Learning on Graphs with Julia</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphneuralnetworks-jl-deep-learning-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GraphNeuralNetworks. jl is an open-source framework for deep learning on graphs, written in the Julia programming language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphneuralnetworks-jl-deep-learning-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoReason: Automatic Few-Shot Reasoning Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoreason-automatic-few-shot-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chain of Thought (CoT) was introduced in recent research as a method for improving step-by-step reasoning in Large Language Models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoreason-automatic-few-shot-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnable Evolutionary Multi-Objective Combinatorial Optimization via Sequence-to-Sequence Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-evolutionary-multi-objective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in learnable evolutionary algorithms have demonstrated the importance of leveraging population distribution information and historical evolutionary trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-evolutionary-multi-objective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimuDICE: Offline Policy Optimization Through World Model Updates and DICE Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simudice-offline-policy-optimization-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In offline reinforcement learning, deriving an effective policy from a pre-collected set of experiences is challenging due to the distribution mismatch between the target policy and the behavioral policy used to collect the data, as well as the limited sample size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simudice-offline-policy-optimization-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CURE: Clinical Understanding &amp; Retrieval Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cure-clinical-understanding-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the dominance of dense retrievers that do not generalize well beyond their training dataset distributions, domain-specific test sets are essential in evaluating retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cure-clinical-understanding-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOPy: A Framework for Black-box Vector Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vopy-a-framework-for-black-box-vector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce VOPy, an open-source Python library designed to address black-box vector optimization, where multiple objectives must be optimized simultaneously with respect to a partial order induced by a convex cone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vopy-a-framework-for-black-box-vector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Splatter-360: Generalizable 360$^{\circ}$ Gaussian Splatting for Wide-baseline Panoramic Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/splatter-360-generalizable-360-circ-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wide-baseline panoramic images are frequently used in applications like VR and simulations to minimize capturing labor costs and storage needs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/splatter-360-generalizable-360-circ-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
