<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 09:12:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Diagnosis and Prognosis of Faults in High-Speed Aeronautical Bearings with a Collaborative Selection Incremental Deep Transfer Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnosis-and-prognosis-of-faults-in-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The diagnosis and prognosis of aeronautical-bearing health conditions are essential to proactively ensuring efficient power transmission, safety, and reduced downtime.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnosis-and-prognosis-of-faults-in-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-task View Synthesis with Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-view-synthesis-with-neural-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle the MTVS problem, we propose MuvieNeRF, a framework that incorporates both multi-task and cross-view knowledge to simultaneously synthesize multiple scene properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-view-synthesis-with-neural-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EGVD: Event-Guided Video Deraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egvd-event-guided-video-deraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we approach video deraining by employing an event camera.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egvd-event-guided-video-deraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ComSD: Balancing Behavioral Quality and Diversity in Unsupervised Skill Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comsd-balancing-behavioral-quality-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ideal unsupervised skill discovery methods are able to produce diverse and qualified skills in the absence of extrinsic reward, while the discovered skill set can efficiently adapt to downstream tasks in various ways.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comsd-balancing-behavioral-quality-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Cephalometric Landmark Detection from the view of Human Pose Estimation with Lightweight Super-Resolution Head</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-cephalometric-landmark-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate localization of cephalometric landmarks holds great importance in the fields of orthodontics and orthognathics due to its potential for automating key point labeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-cephalometric-landmark-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segment Anything Model is a Good Teacher for Local Feature Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything-model-is-a-good-teacher-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To do so, first, we construct an auxiliary task of Pixel Semantic Relational Distillation (PSRD), which distillates feature relations with category-agnostic semantic information learned by the SAM encoder into a local feature learning network, to improve local feature description using semantic discrimination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything-model-is-a-good-teacher-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networked Inequality: Preferential Attachment Bias in Graph Neural Network Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/networked-inequality-preferential-attachment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further bridge GCN's preferential attachment bias with unfairness in link prediction and propose a new within-group fairness metric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/networked-inequality-preferential-attachment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoAgents: A Framework for Automatic Agent Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoagents-a-framework-for-automatic-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we introduce AutoAgents, an innovative framework that adaptively generates and coordinates multiple specialized agents to build an AI team according to different tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoagents-a-framework-for-automatic-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Unified Framework for Adaptable Problematic Content Detection via Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-unified-framework-for-adaptable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting problematic content, such as hate speech, is a multifaceted and ever-changing task, influenced by social dynamics, user populations, diversity of sources, and evolving language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-unified-framework-for-adaptable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Co-occurrence: Multi-modal Session-based Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-co-occurrence-multi-modal-session</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(2) How to fuse these heterogeneous descriptive information to comprehensively infer user interests?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-co-occurrence-multi-modal-session</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Long-Form Legal Question Answering with Retrieval-Augmented Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-long-form-legal-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To support this approach, we introduce and release the Long-form Legal Question Answering (LLeQA) dataset, comprising 1, 868 expert-annotated legal questions in the French language, complete with detailed answers rooted in pertinent legal provisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-long-form-legal-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guiding Instruction-based Image Editing via Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-instruction-based-image-editing-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experimental results demonstrate that expressive instructions are crucial to instruction-based image editing, and our MGIE can lead to a notable improvement in automatic metrics and human evaluation while maintaining competitive inference efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-instruction-based-image-editing-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wish to Have an Argument: Argumentative Reasoning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-wish-to-have-an-argument-argumentative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We frame our experiments in terms of the argument mining (AM) and argument pair extraction (APE) tasks, and evaluate their ability to perform reasoning at increasing levels of abstraction in the input and output representations (e. g., arbitrary label sets, semantic graphs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-wish-to-have-an-argument-argumentative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SegRCDB: Semantic Segmentation via Formula-Driven Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segrcdb-semantic-segmentation-via-formula-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SegRCDB has a high potential to contribute to semantic segmentation pre-training and investigation by enabling the creation of large datasets without manual annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segrcdb-semantic-segmentation-via-formula-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Incremental Transfer Learning: Combining Peer-to-Peer Federated Learning and Domain Incremental Learning for Multicenter Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-incremental-transfer-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Incremental transfer learning, which combines peer-to-peer federated learning and domain incremental learning, can overcome the data privacy issue and meanwhile preserve model performance by using continual learning techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-incremental-transfer-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Epipolar Constraint Meets Non-local Operators in Multi-View Stereo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-epipolar-constraint-meets-non-local-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This constraint reduces the 2D search space into the epipolar line in stereo matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-epipolar-constraint-meets-non-local-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information Flow in Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-flow-in-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide a comprehensive toolbox for understanding and enhancing self-supervised learning (SSL) methods through the lens of matrix information theory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-flow-in-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Depth Branches Network for Efficient Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-depth-branches-network-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based SR methods, while incorporating global structural details, frequently come with an abundance of parameters, leading to high computational overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-depth-branches-network-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCALE: Synergized Collaboration of Asymmetric Language Translation Engines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-synergized-collaboration-of-asymmetric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce SCALE, a collaborative framework that connects compact Specialized Translation Models (STMs) and general-purpose Large Language Models (LLMs) as one unified translation engine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-synergized-collaboration-of-asymmetric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promoting Generalized Cross-lingual Question Answering in Few-resource Scenarios via Self-knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promoting-generalized-cross-lingual-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach seeks to enhance cross-lingual QA transfer using a high-performing multilingual model trained on a large-scale dataset, complemented by a few thousand aligned QA examples across languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promoting-generalized-cross-lingual-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too Big, so Fail? -- Enabling Neural Construction Methods to Solve Large-Scale Routing Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/too-big-so-fail-enabling-neural-construction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years new deep learning approaches to solve combinatorial optimization problems, in particular NP-hard Vehicle Routing Problems (VRP), have been proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/too-big-so-fail-enabling-neural-construction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory Gym: Partially Observable Challenges to Memory-Based Agents in Endless Episodes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-gym-partially-observable-challenges-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It features partially observable 2D environments with discrete controls, namely Mortar Mayhem, Mystery Path, and Searing Spotlights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-gym-partially-observable-challenges-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspicion-Agent: Playing Imperfect Information Games with Theory of Mind Aware GPT4</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/suspicion-agent-playing-imperfect-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike perfect information games, where all elements are known to every player, imperfect information games emulate the real-world complexities of decision-making under uncertain or incomplete information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/suspicion-agent-playing-imperfect-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Sensitive Information Be Deleted From LLMs? Objectives for Defending Against Extraction Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-sensitive-information-be-deleted-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimentally, we show that even state-of-the-art model editing methods such as ROME struggle to truly delete factual information from models like GPT-J, as our whitebox and blackbox attacks can recover "deleted" information from an edited model 38% of the time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-sensitive-information-be-deleted-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redistributing the Precision and Content in 3D-LUT-based Inverse Tone-mapping for HDR/WCG Display</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redistributing-the-precision-and-content-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The latter requires more efficiency, thus the pre-calculated LUT (look-up table) has become a popular solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redistributing-the-precision-and-content-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRANDE: Gradient-Based Decision Tree Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grande-gradient-based-decision-tree-ensembles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the success of deep learning for text and image data, tree-based ensemble models are still state-of-the-art for machine learning with heterogeneous tabular data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grande-gradient-based-decision-tree-ensembles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Shift Equivalence of Convolutional Neural Networks in Industrial Defect Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-shift-equivalence-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In industrial defect segmentation tasks, while pixel accuracy and Intersection over Union (IoU) are commonly employed metrics to assess segmentation performance, the output consistency (also referred to equivalence) of the model is often overlooked.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-shift-equivalence-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Empirical Measurements to Augmented Data Rates: A Machine Learning Approach for MCS Adaptation in Sidelink Communication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-empirical-measurements-to-augmented-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a machine learning approach to predict suitable MCS levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-empirical-measurements-to-augmented-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Free Data Selection with General-Purpose Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-free-data-selection-with-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, current approaches, represented by active learning methods, typically follow a cumbersome pipeline that iterates the time-consuming model training and batch data selection repeatedly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-free-data-selection-with-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Streaming Language Models with Attention Sinks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-streaming-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we first demonstrate that the emergence of attention sink is due to the strong attention scores towards initial tokens as a ``sink'' even if they are not semantically important.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-streaming-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G4SATBench: Benchmarking and Advancing SAT Solving with Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g4satbench-benchmarking-and-advancing-sat</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) have recently emerged as a promising approach for solving the Boolean Satisfiability Problem (SAT), offering potential alternatives to traditional backtracking or local search SAT solvers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g4satbench-benchmarking-and-advancing-sat</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Representation Learning for Prediction of Temporal Event Sets in the Continuous Time Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-representation-learning-for-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this is the first work that solves the problem of predicting event set intensities in the continuous time domain by using TPPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-representation-learning-for-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nnSAM: Plug-and-play Segment Anything Model Improves nnUNet Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nnsam-plug-and-play-segment-anything-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent developments of foundation models in computer vision, especially the Segment Anything Model (SAM), allow scalable and domain-agnostic image segmentation to serve as a general-purpose segmentation tool.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nnsam-plug-and-play-segment-anything-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utility-based Adaptive Teaching Strategies using Bayesian Theory of Mind</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utility-based-adaptive-teaching-strategies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, human teachers seem to build mental models of the learner's internal state, a capacity known as Theory of Mind (ToM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utility-based-adaptive-teaching-strategies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ToRA: A Tool-Integrated Reasoning Agent for Mathematical Problem Solving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tora-a-tool-integrated-reasoning-agent-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models have made significant progress in various language tasks, yet they still struggle with complex mathematics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tora-a-tool-integrated-reasoning-agent-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-to-3D using Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-to-3d-using-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this stage, we increase the number of Gaussians by compactness-based densification to enhance continuity and improve fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-to-3d-using-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying CLIP Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-clip-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe that the main ingredient to the success of CLIP is its data and not the model architecture or pre-training objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-clip-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QonFusion -- Quantum Approaches to Gaussian Random Variables: Applications in Stable Diffusion and Brownian Motion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qonfusion-quantum-approaches-to-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The principal theme of our research is the incorporation of Quantum Random Number Generators (QRNGs) into classical models of diffusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qonfusion-quantum-approaches-to-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverse and Aligned Audio-to-Video Generation via Text-to-Video Model Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-and-aligned-audio-to-video-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method is based on a lightweight adaptor network, which learns to map the audio-based representation to the input representation expected by the text-to-video generation model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-and-aligned-audio-to-video-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qwen Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen-technical-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have revolutionized the field of artificial intelligence, enabling natural language processing tasks that were previously thought to be exclusive to humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen-technical-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Geometrized Cartoon Line Inbetweening</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-geometrized-cartoon-line-inbetweening-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To preserve the precision and detail of the line drawings, we propose a new approach, AnimeInbet, which geometrizes raster line drawings into graphs of endpoints and reframes the inbetweening task as a graph fusion problem with vertex repositioning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-geometrized-cartoon-line-inbetweening-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer-VQ: Linear-Time Transformers via Vector Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-vq-linear-time-transformers-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Transformer-VQ, a decoder-only transformer computing softmax-based dense self-attention in linear time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-vq-linear-time-transformers-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTC-DC Net: Monocular Height Estimation from Single Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/htc-dc-net-monocular-height-estimation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, we propose a method for monocular height estimation from optical imagery, which is currently one of the richest sources of remote sensing data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/htc-dc-net-monocular-height-estimation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Contractivity of Plug-and-Play Operators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-contractivity-of-plug-and-play</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The present work is motivated by the following questions: Can we relax the assumptions on the forward model?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-contractivity-of-plug-and-play</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Equivariance in State-of-the-Art Supervised Depth and Normal Predictors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-equivariance-in-state-of-the-art-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dense depth and surface normal predictors should possess the equivariant property to cropping-and-resizing -- cropping the input image should result in cropping the same output image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-equivariance-in-state-of-the-art-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Citations: Text-Based Metrics for Assessing Novelty and its Impact in Scientific Publications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-citations-text-based-metrics-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings support the use of text mining both to measure novel scientific ideas at the time of publication and to measure the impact of these new ideas on later scientific work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-citations-text-based-metrics-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Challenges of Fully Incremental Neural Dependency Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-challenges-of-fully-incremental-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the popularization of BiLSTMs and Transformer-based bidirectional encoders, state-of-the-art syntactic parsers have lacked incrementality, requiring access to the whole sentence and deviating from human language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-challenges-of-fully-incremental-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoding the Workplace &amp; EOR: An Employee Survey Analysis by Data Science Techniques and Visualization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-the-workplace-eor-an-employee-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research study explores the new dynamics of employee-organi-zation relationships (EOR) [6] using advanced data science methodologies and presents findings through accessible visualizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-the-workplace-eor-an-employee-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LagrangeBench: A Lagrangian Fluid Mechanics Benchmarking Suite</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lagrangebench-a-lagrangian-fluid-mechanics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning has been successfully applied to grid-based PDE modeling in various scientific applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lagrangebench-a-lagrangian-fluid-mechanics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hallucination Reduction in Long Input Text Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallucination-reduction-in-long-input-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We have used the following metrics to measure factual consistency at the entity level: precision-source, and F1-target.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallucination-reduction-in-long-input-text</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
