<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:06:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Effects of diversity incentives on sample diversity and downstream model performance in LLM-based text augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effects-of-diversity-incentives-on-sample</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The latest generative large language models (LLMs) have found their application in data augmentation tasks, where small numbers of text samples are LLM-paraphrased and then used to fine-tune the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effects-of-diversity-incentives-on-sample</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MuGI: Enhancing Information Retrieval through Multi-Text Generation Intergration with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mugi-enhancing-information-retrieval-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have emerged as a pivotal force in language technology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mugi-enhancing-information-retrieval-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Striking a Balance in Fairness for Dynamic Systems Through Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/striking-a-balance-in-fairness-for-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While significant advancements have been made in the field of fair machine learning, the majority of studies focus on scenarios where the decision model operates on a static population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/striking-a-balance-in-fairness-for-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prometheus-Vision: Vision-Language Model as a Judge for Fine-Grained Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prometheus-vision-vision-language-model-as-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assessing long-form responses generated by Vision-Language Models (VLMs) is challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prometheus-vision-vision-language-model-as-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Block Majorization Minimization with Extrapolation and Application to $β$-NMF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/block-majorization-minimization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a Block Majorization Minimization method with Extrapolation (BMMe) for solving a class of multi-convex optimization problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/block-majorization-minimization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proximal Causal Inference With Text Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proximal-causal-inference-with-text-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent text-based causal methods attempt to mitigate confounding bias by including unstructured text data as proxies of confounding variables that are partially or imperfectly measured.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proximal-causal-inference-with-text-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Machine Learning for Positive-Unlabelled Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-machine-learning-for-positive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Positive-Unlabelled (PU) learning is a growing field of machine learning that aims to learn classifiers from data consisting of labelled positive and unlabelled instances, which can be in reality positive or negative, but whose label is unknown.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-machine-learning-for-positive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Detection of Small Oriented Objects in Aerial Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-detection-of-small-oriented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Small oriented objects that represent tiny pixel-area in large-scale aerial images are difficult to detect due to their size and orientation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-detection-of-small-oriented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Every Node is Different: Dynamically Fusing Self-Supervised Tasks for Attributed Graph Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/every-node-is-different-dynamically-fusing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to dynamically learn the weights of SSL tasks for different nodes and fuse the embeddings learned from different SSL tasks to boost performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/every-node-is-different-dynamically-fusing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeing the roads through the trees: A benchmark for modeling spatial dependencies with aerial imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seeing-the-roads-through-the-trees-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we propose a road segmentation benchmark dataset, Chesapeake Roads Spatial Context (RSC), for evaluating the spatial long-range context understanding of geospatial machine learning models and show how commonly used semantic segmentation models can fail at this task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seeing-the-roads-through-the-trees-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Reinforcement Learning with a Budget of Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-reinforcement-learning-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an r-MDP, we cater to a diverse user population, each with unique preferences, through interaction with a small set of representative policies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-reinforcement-learning-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AboutMe: Using Self-Descriptions in Webpages to Document the Effects of English Pretraining Data Filters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aboutme-using-self-descriptions-in-webpages</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models' (LLMs) abilities are drawn from their pretraining data, and model development begins with data curation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aboutme-using-self-descriptions-in-webpages</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unreasonable Effectiveness of Easy Training Data for Hard Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-unreasonable-effectiveness-of-easy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present the surprising conclusion that current language models often generalize relatively well from easy to hard data, even performing as well as "oracle" models trained on hard data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-unreasonable-effectiveness-of-easy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERS: Unlocking the Power of Large Language Models in Search with Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inters-unlocking-the-power-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite this, their application to information retrieval (IR) tasks is still challenging due to the infrequent occurrence of many IR-specific concepts in natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inters-unlocking-the-power-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable 3D Panoptic Segmentation With Superpoint Graph Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-3d-panoptic-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a highly efficient method for panoptic segmentation of large 3D point clouds by redefining this task as a scalable graph clustering problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-3d-panoptic-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanity Checks Revisited: An Exploration to Repair the Model Parameter Randomisation Test</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sanity-checks-revisited-an-exploration-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Model Parameter Randomisation Test (MPRT) is widely acknowledged in the eXplainable Artificial Intelligence (XAI) community for its well-motivated evaluative principle: that the explanation function should be sensitive to changes in the parameters of the model function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sanity-checks-revisited-an-exploration-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Translation Models are Zero-Shot Detectors of Translation Direction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-translation-models-are-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting the translation direction of parallel text has applications for machine translation training and evaluation, but also has forensic applications such as resolving plagiarism or forgery allegations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-translation-models-are-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Candidate Speculative Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-candidate-speculative-decoding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One way to speed them up is speculative decoding, which generates candidate segments (a sequence of tokens) from a fast draft model that is then verified in parallel by the target model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-candidate-speculative-decoding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutual Distillation Learning For Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-distillation-learning-for-person-re</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid advancements in deep learning technologies, person re-identification (ReID) has witnessed remarkable performance improvements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-distillation-learning-for-person-re</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ada-Retrieval: An Adaptive Multi-Round Retrieval Paradigm for Sequential Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ada-retrieval-an-adaptive-multi-round</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most existing retrieval models employ a single-round inference paradigm, which may not adequately capture the dynamic nature of user preferences and stuck in one area in the item space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ada-retrieval-an-adaptive-multi-round</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kun: Answer Polishment for Chinese Self-Alignment with Instruction Back-Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kun-answer-polishment-for-chinese-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Kun, a novel approach for creating high-quality instruction-tuning datasets for large language models (LLMs) without relying on manual annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kun-answer-polishment-for-chinese-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Relation Distillation for Efficient Biomedical Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-relation-distillation-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[IGD constructs a graph representing instance features and relations, transferring these two types of knowledge by enforcing instance graph consistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-relation-distillation-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoupling Pixel Flipping and Occlusion Strategy for Consistent XAI Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupling-pixel-flipping-and-occlusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The R-OMS score enables a systematic comparison of occlusion strategies and resolves the disagreement problem by grouping consistent PF rankings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupling-pixel-flipping-and-occlusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RotationDrag: Point-based Image Editing with Rotated Diffusion Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rotationdrag-point-based-image-editing-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method tracks handle points more precisely by utilizing the feature map of the rotated images, thus ensuring precise optimization and high image fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rotationdrag-point-based-image-editing-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DQNC2S: DQN-based Cross-stream Crisis event Summarizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dqnc2s-dqn-based-cross-stream-crisis-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Summarizing multiple disaster-relevant data streams simultaneously is particularly challenging as existing Retrieve&Re-ranking strategies suffer from the inherent redundancy of multi-stream data and limited scalability in a multi-query setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dqnc2s-dqn-based-cross-stream-crisis-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency Masking for Universal Deepfake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-masking-for-universal-deepfake</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study spatial and frequency domain masking in training deepfake detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-masking-for-universal-deepfake</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Data Augmentation for Aspect Sentiment Quad Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-data-augmentation-for-aspect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aspect sentiment quad prediction (ASQP) aims to predict the quad sentiment elements for a given sentence, which is a critical task in the field of aspect-based sentiment analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-data-augmentation-for-aspect</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mapping Transformer Leveraged Embeddings for Cross-Lingual Document Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-transformer-leveraged-embeddings-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommendation systems, for documents, have become tools to find relevant content on the Web.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-transformer-leveraged-embeddings-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving the Discretised Multiphase Flow Equations with Interface Capturing on Structured Grids Using Machine Learning Libraries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-the-discretised-multiphase-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper solves the multiphase flow equations with interface capturing using the AI4PDEs approach (Artificial Intelligence for Partial Differential Equations).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-the-discretised-multiphase-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal and Between-Group Variability in College Dropout Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-and-between-group-variability-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale administrative data is a common input in early warning systems for college dropout in higher education.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-and-between-group-variability-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valid causal inference with unobserved confounding in high-dimensional settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valid-causal-inference-with-unobserved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose uncertainty intervals which allow for unobserved confounding, and show that the resulting inference is valid when the amount of unobserved confounding is small relative to the sample size; the latter is formalized in terms of convergence rates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valid-causal-inference-with-unobserved</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost in the Source Language: How Large Language Models Evaluate the Quality of Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lost-in-the-source-language-how-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have achieved remarkable results in the machine translation evaluation task, yet there remains a gap in knowledge regarding how they utilize the provided data to conduct evaluations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lost-in-the-source-language-how-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaHate: A Dataset for Unifying Efforts on Hate Speech Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metahate-a-dataset-for-unifying-efforts-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hate speech represents a pervasive and detrimental form of online discourse, often manifested through an array of slurs, from hateful tweets to defamatory posts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metahate-a-dataset-for-unifying-efforts-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Diverse Representations for Open Set Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-diverse-representations-for-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the differences in attention maps can lead to diverse representations so that the fused representations can well handle the open space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-diverse-representations-for-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty quantification for probabilistic machine learning in earth observation using conformal prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-for-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unreliable predictions can occur when using artificial intelligence (AI) systems with negative consequences for downstream applications, particularly when employed for decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-for-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Graph Convolutional Networks with Transformer Layer in social-based items recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-graph-convolutional-networks-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we have proposed an approach for improving the GCN for predicting ratings in social networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-graph-convolutional-networks-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Automation to Augmentation: Large Language Models Elevating Essay Scoring Landscape</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-automation-to-augmentation-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Receiving immediate and personalized feedback is crucial for second-language learners, and Automated Essay Scoring (AES) systems are a vital resource when human instructors are unavailable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-automation-to-augmentation-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Learning of Dense Hierarchical Representations for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-of-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper demonstrates a self-supervised framework for learning voxel-wise coarse-to-fine representations tailored for dense downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-of-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiCMAE: Hierarchical Contrastive Masked Autoencoder for Self-Supervised Audio-Visual Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hicmae-hierarchical-contrastive-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Audio-Visual Emotion Recognition (AVER) has garnered increasing attention in recent years for its critical role in creating emotion-ware intelligent machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hicmae-hierarchical-contrastive-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EASYTOOL: Enhancing LLM-based Agents with Concise Tool Instruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easytool-enhancing-llm-based-agents-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[EasyTool purifies essential information from extensive tool documentation of different sources, and elaborates a unified interface (i. e., tool instruction) to offer standardized tool descriptions and functionalities for LLM-based agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easytool-enhancing-llm-based-agents-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention to detail: inter-resolution knowledge distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-to-detail-inter-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of computer vision solutions for gigapixel images in digital pathology is hampered by significant computational limitations due to the large size of whole slide images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-to-detail-inter-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Image Deblurring Networks based on Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-image-deblurring-networks-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article introduces a sliding window model for defocus deblurring that achieves the best performance to date with extremely low memory usage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-image-deblurring-networks-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transforming Image Super-Resolution: A ConvFormer-based Efficient Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transforming-image-super-resolution-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in single-image super-resolution (SISR) has achieved remarkable performance, yet the computational costs of these methods remain a challenge for deployment on resource-constrained devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transforming-image-super-resolution-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the representation and methodology for wide and short range head pose estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-representation-and-methodology-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose a generalization of the geodesic angular distance metric that enables the construction of a loss that controls the contribution of each training sample to the optimization of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-representation-and-methodology-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Vulnerabilities in Large Language Models: In-context Learning Backdoor Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-vulnerabilities-in-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experimental results across several language models, ranging in size from 1. 3B to 40B parameters, demonstrate the effectiveness of our attack method, exemplified by a high average attack success rate of 95. 0% across the three datasets on OPT models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-vulnerabilities-in-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-end Learnable Clustering for Intent Learning in Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-learnable-clustering-for-intent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, the separation of representation learning and clustering optimization within a generalized expectation maximization (EM) framework often results in sub-optimal performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-learnable-clustering-for-intent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgical-DINO: Adapter Learning of Foundation Models for Depth Estimation in Endoscopic Surgery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgical-dino-adapter-learning-of-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is clear evidence in the results that zero-shot prediction on pre-trained weights in computer vision datasets or naive fine-tuning is not sufficient to use the foundation model in the surgical domain directly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgical-dino-adapter-learning-of-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prediction of Cellular Identities from Trajectory and Cell Fate Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-of-cellular-identities-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Determining cell identities in imaging sequences is an important yet challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-of-cellular-identities-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAT-LLM: Prompting Large Language Models with Text Style Definition for Chinese Article-style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-llm-prompting-large-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text style transfer is increasingly prominent in online entertainment and social media.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-llm-prompting-large-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weiss-Weinstein bound of frequency estimation error for very weak GNSS signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weiss-weinstein-bound-of-frequency-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tightness remains the center quest in all modern estimation bounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weiss-weinstein-bound-of-frequency-estimation</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
