<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 21:07:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>pyribs: A Bare-Bones Python Library for Quality Diversity Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyribs-a-bare-bones-python-library-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have seen a rise in the popularity of quality diversity (QD) optimization, a branch of optimization that seeks to find a collection of diverse, high-performing solutions to a given problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyribs-a-bare-bones-python-library-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAU: A Framework for Video-Based Traffic Analytics Leveraging Artificial Intelligence and Unmanned Aerial Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tau-a-framework-for-video-based-traffic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fifth, TAU has a fully independent algorithm for crossroad arbitration based on the data gathered from the different zones surrounding it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tau-a-framework-for-video-based-traffic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capturing the motion of every joint: 3D human pose and shape estimation with independent tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/capturing-the-motion-of-every-joint-3d-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present a novel method to estimate 3D human pose and shape from monocular videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/capturing-the-motion-of-every-joint-3d-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Knowledge Graph Embedding Models with Semantic-driven Loss Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-knowledge-graph-embedding-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In line with this commonly adopted assumption, we posit that semantically valid negative triples might be high-quality negative triples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-knowledge-graph-embedding-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Importance of Feature Representation for Flood Mapping using Classical Machine Learning Approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-importance-of-feature-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Climate change has increased the severity and frequency of weather disasters all around the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-importance-of-feature-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single Image Backdoor Inversion via Robust Smoothed Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-image-backdoor-inversion-via-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous works on backdoor inversion often recover the backdoor through an optimization process to flip a support set of clean images into the target class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-image-backdoor-inversion-via-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StrucTexTv2: Masked Visual-Textual Prediction for Document Image Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structextv2-masked-visual-textual-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to the masked multi-modal modeling methods for document image understanding that rely on both the image and text modalities, StrucTexTv2 models image-only input and potentially deals with more application scenarios free from OCR pre-processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structextv2-masked-visual-textual-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Markov Transformer for Simultaneous Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-markov-transformer-for-simultaneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Simultaneous machine translation (SiMT) outputs the target sequence while receiving the source sequence, and hence learning when to start translating each target token is the core challenge for SiMT task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-markov-transformer-for-simultaneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An end-to-end SE(3)-equivariant segmentation network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-end-to-end-se-3-equivariant-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convolutional neural networks (CNNs) allow for parameter sharing and translational equivariance by using convolutional kernels in their linear layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-end-to-end-se-3-equivariant-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pose Impact Estimation on Face Recognition using 3D-Aware Synthetic Data with Application to Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-impact-estimation-on-face-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating the quality of facial images is essential for operating face recognition systems with sufficient accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-impact-estimation-on-face-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlimited-Size Diffusion Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlimited-size-diffusion-restoration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our simple, parameter-free approaches can be used not only for image restoration but also for image generation of unlimited sizes, with the potential to be a general tool for diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlimited-size-diffusion-restoration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PS4: a Next-Generation Dataset for Protein Single Sequence Secondary Structure Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ps4-a-next-generation-dataset-for-protein</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Protein secondary structure prediction is a subproblem of protein folding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ps4-a-next-generation-dataset-for-protein</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Industrial Anomaly Detection via Hybrid Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-industrial-anomaly-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[2D-based Industrial Anomaly Detection has been widely discussed, however, multimodal industrial anomaly detection based on 3D point clouds and RGB images still has many untouched fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-industrial-anomaly-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coarse-to-Fine Covid-19 Segmentation via Vision-Language Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse-to-fine-covid-19-segmentation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segmentation of COVID-19 lesions can assist physicians in better diagnosis and treatment of COVID-19.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse-to-fine-covid-19-segmentation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Virtues of Laziness in Model-based RL: A Unified Objective and Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-virtues-of-laziness-in-model-based-rl-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel approach to addressing two fundamental challenges in Model-based Reinforcement Learning (MBRL): the computational expense of repeatedly finding a good policy in the learned model, and the objective mismatch between model fitting and policy computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-virtues-of-laziness-in-model-based-rl-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Gems: 4D Radar Scene Flow Learning Using Cross-Modal Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-gems-4d-radar-scene-flow-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes a novel approach to 4D radar-based scene flow estimation via cross-modal learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-gems-4d-radar-scene-flow-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Explorative Key-term Selection Strategies for Conversational Contextual Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-explorative-key-term-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these issues, we first propose ``ConLinUCB", a general framework for conversational bandits with better information incorporation, combining arm-level and key-term-level feedback to estimate user preference in one step at each time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-explorative-key-term-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIFT2: Speeding-up RIFT with A New Rotation-Invariance Technique</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rift2-speeding-up-rift-with-a-new-rotation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal image matching is an important prerequisite for multisource image information fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rift2-speeding-up-rift-with-a-new-rotation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Pathology Detection: A Deep Dive Into the State of the Art</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-pathology-detection-a-deep-dive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments demonstrate that newly developed feature-modeling methods from the industrial and medical literature achieve increased performance compared to previous work and set the new SOTA in a variety of modalities and datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-pathology-detection-a-deep-dive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Persian Benchmark for Joint Intent Detection and Slot Filling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-persian-benchmark-for-joint-intent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the effectiveness of our benchmark, we employ state-of-the-art methods for intent detection and slot filling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-persian-benchmark-for-joint-intent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORCHNet: A Robust Global Feature Aggregation approach for 3D LiDAR-based Place recognition in Orchards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orchnet-a-robust-global-feature-aggregation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address the place recognition problem in orchards resorting to 3D LiDAR data, which is considered a key modality for robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orchnet-a-robust-global-feature-aggregation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and Explicit Modelling of Image Hierarchies for Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-explicit-modelling-of-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The aim of this paper is to propose a mechanism to efficiently and explicitly model image hierarchies in the global, regional, and local range for image restoration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-explicit-modelling-of-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Generative Mixture Model for Robust Imbalance Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-generative-mixture-model-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, a deep generative classifier is proposed to mitigate this issue via both model perturbation and data perturbation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-generative-mixture-model-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralised construction of a global coordinate system in a large swarm of minimalistic robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralised-construction-of-a-global</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite being unable to measure the bearing of incoming messages, the robots running our algorithm can calculate their position within a swarm deployed in a regular formation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralised-construction-of-a-global</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProxyFormer: Proxy Alignment Assisted Point Cloud Completion with Missing Part Sensitive Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proxyformer-proxy-alignment-assisted-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we fuse information into point proxy via feature and position extractor, and generate features for missing point proxies from the features of existing point proxies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proxyformer-proxy-alignment-assisted-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Multiple Abstractions in Episodic RL via Reward Shaping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-multiple-abstractions-in-episodic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One major limitation to the applicability of Reinforcement Learning (RL) to many practical domains is the large number of samples required to learn an optimal policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-multiple-abstractions-in-episodic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look at the Intervention Procedure of Concept Bottleneck Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-the-intervention-procedure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concept bottleneck models (CBMs) are a class of interpretable neural network models that predict the target response of a given input based on its high-level concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-the-intervention-procedure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Learning to Bridge Vision and Language Models for Multimodal Few-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-to-bridge-vision-and-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods are trying to communicate visual concepts as prompts to frozen language models, but rely on hand-engineered task induction to reduce the hypothesis space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-to-bridge-vision-and-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trade-off between Universality and Label Efficiency of Representations from Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-trade-off-between-universality-and-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[foundation models) has recently become a prevalent learning paradigm, where one first pre-trains a representation using large-scale unlabeled data, and then learns simple predictors on top of the representation using small labeled data from the downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-trade-off-between-universality-and-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M-L2O: Towards Generalizable Learning-to-Optimize by Test-Time Fast Self-Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-l2o-towards-generalizable-learning-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This data-driven procedure yields L2O that can efficiently solve problems similar to those seen in training, that is, drawn from the same ``task distribution".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-l2o-towards-generalizable-learning-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instruction Clarification Requests in Multimodal Collaborative Dialogue Games: Tasks, and an Analysis of the CoDraw Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-clarification-requests-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In visual instruction-following dialogue games, players can engage in repair mechanisms in face of an ambiguous or underspecified instruction that cannot be fully mapped to actions in the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-clarification-requests-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text classification dataset and analysis for Uzbek language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-classification-dataset-and-analysis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also present a comprehensive evaluation of different models, ranging from traditional bag-of-words models to deep learning architectures, on this newly created dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-classification-dataset-and-analysis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information-Restricted Neural Language Models Reveal Different Brain Regions' Sensitivity to Semantics, Syntax and Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-restricted-neural-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A fundamental question in neurolinguistics concerns the brain regions involved in syntactic and semantic processing during speech comprehension, both at the lexical (word processing) and supra-lexical levels (sentence and discourse processing).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-restricted-neural-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonlinear Intensity, Scale and Rotation Invariant Matching for Multimodal Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonlinear-intensity-scale-and-rotation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an effective method for the matching of multimodal images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonlinear-intensity-scale-and-rotation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Context Instruction Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-instruction-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instruction learning of Large Language Models (LLMs) has enabled zero-shot task generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-instruction-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IQ-Flow: Mechanism Design for Inducing Cooperative Behavior to Self-Interested Agents in Sequential Social Dilemmas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iq-flow-mechanism-design-for-inducing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to resolve this issue, we propose the Incentive Q-Flow (IQ-Flow) algorithm, which modifies the system's reward setup with an incentive regulator agent such that the cooperative policy also corresponds to the self-interested policy for the agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iq-flow-mechanism-design-for-inducing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Surgical Context Inference and Translation to Gestures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-surgical-context-inference-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate the performance of each stage of our method by comparing the results with the ground truth segmentation masks, the consensus context labels, and the gesture labels in the JIGSAWS dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-surgical-context-inference-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learned Risk Metric Maps for Kinodynamic Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learned-risk-metric-maps-for-kinodynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Learned Risk Metric Maps (LRMM) for real-time estimation of coherent risk metrics of high dimensional dynamical systems operating in unstructured, partially observed environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learned-risk-metric-maps-for-kinodynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PA&amp;DA: Jointly Sampling PAth and DAta for Consistent NAS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pa-da-jointly-sampling-path-and-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method only requires negligible computation cost for optimizing the sampling distributions of path and data, but achieves lower gradient variance during supernet training and better generalization performance for the supernet, resulting in a more consistent NAS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pa-da-jointly-sampling-path-and-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-aided Contrastive Consensus Learning for Co-salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-aided-contrastive-consensus-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To learn better group consensus, we propose the Group Consensus Aggregation Module (GCAM) to abstract the common features of each image group; meanwhile, to make the consensus representation more discriminative, we introduce the Memory-based Contrastive Module (MCM), which saves and updates the consensus of images from different groups in a queue of memories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-aided-contrastive-consensus-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLM-Dialog: Noise-tolerant Pre-training for Knowledge-grounded Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glm-dialog-noise-tolerant-pre-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present GLM-Dialog, a large-scale language model (LLM) with 10B parameters capable of knowledge-grounded conversation in Chinese using a search engine to access the Internet knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glm-dialog-noise-tolerant-pre-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goal Driven Discovery of Distributional Differences via Language Descriptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goal-driven-discovery-of-distributional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mining large corpora can generate useful discoveries but is time-consuming for humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goal-driven-discovery-of-distributional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The In-Sample Softmax for Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-in-sample-softmax-for-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We highlight a simple fact: it is more straightforward to approximate an in-sample \emph{softmax} using only actions in the dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-in-sample-softmax-for-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable and Intervenable Ultrasonography-based Machine Learning Models for Pediatric Appendicitis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-and-intervenable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Appendicitis is among the most frequent reasons for pediatric abdominal surgeries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-and-intervenable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Segmentation as Gaussian Process Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-segmentation-as-gaussian-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Against this issue, in this paper, we propose to formulate the IS task as a Gaussian process (GP)-based pixel-wise binary classification model on each image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-segmentation-as-gaussian-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Im2Hands: Learning Attentive Implicit Representation of Interacting Two-Hand Shapes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/im2hands-learning-attentive-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To handle the shape complexity and interaction context between two hands, Im2Hands models the occupancy volume of two hands - conditioned on an RGB image and coarse 3D keypoints - by two novel attention-based modules responsible for (1) initial occupancy estimation and (2) context-aware occupancy refinement, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/im2hands-learning-attentive-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Control Autonomous Fleets from Observation via Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-control-autonomous-fleets-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous Mobility-on-Demand (AMoD) systems are a rapidly evolving mode of transportation in which a centrally coordinated fleet of self-driving vehicles dynamically serves travel requests.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-control-autonomous-fleets-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HugNLP: A Unified and Comprehensive Library for Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hugnlp-a-unified-and-comprehensive-library</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce HugNLP, a unified and comprehensive library for natural language processing (NLP) with the prevalent backend of HuggingFace Transformers, which is designed for NLP researchers to easily utilize off-the-shelf algorithms and develop novel methods with user-defined models and tasks in real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hugnlp-a-unified-and-comprehensive-library</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Particle-based Online Bayesian Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/particle-based-online-bayesian-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online optimization has gained increasing interest due to its capability of tracking real-world streaming data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/particle-based-online-bayesian-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DECOR-NET: A COVID-19 Lung Infection Segmentation Network Improved by Emphasizing Low-level Features and Decorrelating Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decor-net-a-covid-19-lung-infection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since 2019, coronavirus Disease 2019 (COVID-19) has been widely spread and posed a serious threat to public health.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decor-net-a-covid-19-lung-infection</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
