<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 21:07:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>PASTA-GAN++: A Versatile Framework for High-Resolution Unpaired Virtual Try-on</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pasta-gan-a-versatile-framework-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we take a step forwards to explore versatile virtual try-on solutions, which we argue should possess three main properties, namely, they should support unsupervised training, arbitrary garment categories, and controllable garment editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pasta-gan-a-versatile-framework-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards the Neuroevolution of Low-level Artificial General Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-neuroevolution-of-low-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate a method to evolve a biologically-inspired artificial neural network that learns from environment reactions named Neuroevolution of Artificial General Intelligence (NAGI), a framework for low-level AGI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-neuroevolution-of-low-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransNorm: Transformer Provides a Strong Spatial Normalization Mechanism for a Deep Segmentation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transnorm-transformer-provides-a-strong</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the past few years, convolutional neural networks (CNNs), particularly U-Net, have been the prevailing technique in the medical image processing era.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transnorm-transformer-provides-a-strong</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camouflaged Object Detection via Context-aware Cross-level Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camouflaged-object-detection-via-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose a novel Context-aware Cross-level Fusion Network (C2F-Net), which fuses context-aware cross-level features for accurately identifying camouflaged objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camouflaged-object-detection-via-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shift-tolerant Perceptual Similarity Metric</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shift-tolerant-perceptual-similarity-metric-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the effect of small misalignment, specifically a small shift between the input and reference image, on existing metrics, and accordingly develops a shift-tolerant similarity metric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shift-tolerant-perceptual-similarity-metric-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoTransition: Learning to Recommend Video Transition Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autotransition-learning-to-recommend-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First we learn the embedding of video transitions through a video transition classification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autotransition-learning-to-recommend-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Vizier: Distributed Infrastructure and API for Reliable and Flexible Blackbox Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-vizier-distributed-infrastructure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vizier is the de-facto blackbox and hyperparameter optimization service across Google, having optimized some of Google's largest products and research efforts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-vizier-distributed-infrastructure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marker and source-marker reprogramming of Most Permissive Boolean networks and ensembles with BoNesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marker-and-source-marker-reprogramming-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we demonstrate how the software BoNesis can be employed to exhaustively identify combinations of perturbations which enforce properties on their fixed points and attractors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marker-and-source-marker-reprogramming-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALBench: A Framework for Evaluating Active Learning in Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/albench-a-framework-for-evaluating-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate the research in this field, this paper contributes an active learning benchmark framework named as ALBench for evaluating active learning in object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/albench-a-framework-for-evaluating-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolutionary Multiparty Distance Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-multiparty-distance-minimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of evolutionary multiobjective optimization, the decision maker (DM) concerns conflicting objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-multiparty-distance-minimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mid-level Representation Enhancement and Graph Embedded Uncertainty Suppressing for Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mid-level-representation-enhancement-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, GUS is introduced to suppress the feature ambiguity in the representation space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mid-level-representation-enhancement-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe and Robust Experience Sharing for Deterministic Policy Gradient Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-and-robust-experience-sharing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning in high dimensional continuous tasks is challenging, mainly when the experience replay memory is very limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-and-robust-experience-sharing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factorial User Modeling with Hierarchical Graph Neural Network for Enhanced Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factorial-user-modeling-with-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most sequential recommendation (SR) systems employing graph neural networks (GNNs) only model a user's interaction sequence as a flat graph without hierarchy, overlooking diverse factors in the user's preference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factorial-user-modeling-with-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardly Perceptible Trojan Attack against Neural Networks with Bit Flips</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardly-perceptible-trojan-attack-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The security of deep neural networks (DNNs) has attracted increasing attention due to their widespread use in various applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardly-perceptible-trojan-attack-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifying Hard Noise in Long-Tailed Sample Distribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-hard-noise-in-long-tailed-sample</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such imbalanced training data makes a classifier less discriminative for the tail classes, whose previously "easy" noises are now turned into "hard" ones -- they are almost as outliers as the clean tail samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-hard-noise-in-long-tailed-sample</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging GAN Priors for Few-Shot Part Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-gan-priors-for-few-shot-part</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, this work is an attempt to explore the internal relevance between generation tasks and perception tasks by prompt designing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-gan-priors-for-few-shot-part</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SiRi: A Simple Selective Retraining Mechanism for Transformer-based Visual Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siri-a-simple-selective-retraining-mechanism</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, SiRi conveys a significant principle to the research of visual grounding, i. e., a better initialized vision-language encoder would help the model converge to a better local minimum, advancing the performance accordingly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siri-a-simple-selective-retraining-mechanism</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concurrent Subsidiary Supervision for Unsupervised Source-Free Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concurrent-subsidiary-supervision-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prime challenge in unsupervised domain adaptation (DA) is to mitigate the domain shift between the source and target domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concurrent-subsidiary-supervision-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Driven Sample Average Approximation with Covariate Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-sample-average-approximation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study optimization for data-driven decision-making when we have observations of the uncertain parameters within the optimization model together with concurrent observations of covariates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-sample-average-approximation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Video Deblurring Guided by Motion Magnitude</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-video-deblurring-guided-by-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video deblurring is a highly under-constrained problem due to the spatially and temporally varying blur.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-video-deblurring-guided-by-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Combinatorial Optimization Layers: a Probabilistic Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-combinatorial-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combinatorial optimization (CO) layers in machine learning (ML) pipelines are a powerful tool to tackle data-driven decision tasks, but they come with two main challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-combinatorial-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast expansion into harmonics on the disk: a steerable basis with fast radial convolutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-expansion-into-harmonics-on-the-disk-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a fast and numerically accurate method for expanding digitized $L \times L$ images representing functions on $[-1, 1]^2$ supported on the disk $\{x \in \mathbb{R}^2 : |x|<1\}$ in the harmonics (Dirichlet Laplacian eigenfunctions) on the disk.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-expansion-into-harmonics-on-the-disk-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AADG: Automatic Augmentation for Domain Generalization on Retinal Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aadg-automatic-augmentation-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a data manipulation based domain generalization method, called Automated Augmentation for Domain Generalization (AADG).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aadg-automatic-augmentation-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Pix2Vox++ for 3D Cardiac Reconstruction from 2D echo views</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-pix2vox-for-3d-cardiac</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate geometric quantification of the human heart is a key step in the diagnosis of numerous cardiac diseases, and in the management of cardiac patients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-pix2vox-for-3d-cardiac</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPS-GLASS: Learning Nighttime Semantic Segmentation Using Daytime Video and GPS data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gps-glass-learning-nighttime-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nighttime semantic segmentation is especially challenging due to a lack of annotated nighttime images and a large domain gap from daytime images with sufficient annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gps-glass-learning-nighttime-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstracting Sketches through Simple Primitives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstracting-sketches-through-simple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Toward equipping machines with such capabilities, we propose the Primitive-based Sketch Abstraction task where the goal is to represent sketches using a fixed set of drawing primitives under the influence of a budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstracting-sketches-through-simple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShAPO: Implicit Representations for Multi-Object Shape, Appearance, and Pose Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapo-implicit-representations-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A novel disentangled shape and appearance database of priors is first learned to embed objects in their respective shape and appearance space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapo-implicit-representations-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight and Progressively-Scalable Networks for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-and-progressively-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we thoroughly analyze the design of convolutional blocks (the type of convolutions and the number of channels in convolutions), and the ways of interactions across multiple scales, all from lightweight standpoint for semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-and-progressively-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atomic structure generation from reconstructing structural fingerprints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomic-structure-generation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These methods would help identify or, in the case of generative models, even create novel crystal structures of materials with a set of specified functional properties to then be synthesized or isolated in the laboratory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomic-structure-generation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Trimap Video Matting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-trimap-video-matting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key of OTVM is the joint modeling of trimap propagation and alpha prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-trimap-video-matting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generator Knows What Discriminator Should Learn in Unconditional GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generator-knows-what-discriminator-should</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we explore the efficacy of dense supervision in unconditional generation and find generator feature maps can be an alternative of cost-expensive semantic label maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generator-knows-what-discriminator-should</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGV: Boosting Adversarial Example Transferability from Large Geometric Vicinity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgv-boosting-adversarial-example</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose transferability from Large Geometric Vicinity (LGV), a new technique to increase the transferability of black-box adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgv-boosting-adversarial-example</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Visual Representation from Modality-Shared Contrastive Language-Image Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-visual-representation-from-modality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale multi-modal contrastive pre-training has demonstrated great utility to learn transferable features for a range of downstream tasks by mapping multiple modalities into a shared embedding space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-visual-representation-from-modality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CENet: Toward Concise and Efficient LiDAR Semantic Segmentation for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cenet-toward-concise-and-efficient-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate and fast scene understanding is one of the challenging task for autonomous driving, which requires to take full advantage of LiDAR point clouds for semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cenet-toward-concise-and-efficient-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaKo: Knowledge-driven Visual Question Answering via Late Knowledge-to-Text Injection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lako-knowledge-driven-visual-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual question answering (VQA) often requires an understanding of visual concepts and language semantics, which relies on external knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lako-knowledge-driven-visual-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using clarification questions to improve software developers' Web search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-clarification-questions-to-improve-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods: We describe a set of clarification questions derived from a corpus of software developer queries and a neural approach to recommending them for a newly issued query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-clarification-questions-to-improve-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Reliable Online Method for Joint Estimation of Focal Length and Camera Rotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reliable-online-method-for-joint-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Linear perspectivecues deriving from regularities of the built environment can be used to recalibrate both intrinsic and extrinsic camera parameters online, but these estimates can be unreliable due to irregularities in the scene, uncertainties in line segment estimation and background clutter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reliable-online-method-for-joint-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable User Dialogue Act Augmentation for Dialogue State Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-user-dialogue-act-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior work has demonstrated that data augmentation is useful for improving dialogue state tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-user-dialogue-act-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Smart City Security: Violence and Weaponized Violence Detection using DCNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-smart-city-security-violence-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this ever connected society, CCTVs have had a pivotal role in enforcing safety and security of the citizens by recording unlawful activities for the authorities to take actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-smart-city-security-violence-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconciling Security and Communication Efficiency in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconciling-security-and-communication</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-device Federated Learning is an increasingly popular machine learning setting to train a model by leveraging a large population of client devices with high privacy and security guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconciling-security-and-communication</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V$^2$L: Leveraging Vision and Vision-language Models into Large-scale Product Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v-2-l-leveraging-vision-and-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While model ensemble is common, we show that combining the vision models and vision-language models brings particular benefits from their complementarity and is a key factor to our superiority.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v-2-l-leveraging-vision-and-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hansel: A Chinese Few-Shot and Zero-Shot Entity Linking Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hansel-a-chinese-few-shot-and-zero-shot-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then establish a strong baseline that scores a R@1 of 46. 2% on Few-Shot and 76. 6% on Zero-Shot on our dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hansel-a-chinese-few-shot-and-zero-shot-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Bipedal Walking On Planned Footsteps For Humanoid Robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-bipedal-walking-on-planned-footsteps</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enable the application of RL policies for humanoid robots in real-world settings, it is crucial to build a system that can achieve robust walking in any direction, on 2D and 3D terrains, and be controllable by a user-command.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-bipedal-walking-on-planned-footsteps</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Guided Synthesis of Artistic Images with Retrieval-Augmented Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-synthesis-of-artistic-images-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In RDMs, a set of nearest neighbors is retrieved from an external database during training for each training instance, and the diffusion model is conditioned on these informative samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-synthesis-of-artistic-images-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifelong DP: Consistently Bounded Differential Privacy in Lifelong Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelong-dp-consistently-bounded-differential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show that the process of continually learning new tasks and memorizing previous tasks introduces unknown privacy risks and challenges to bound the privacy loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelong-dp-consistently-bounded-differential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NewsStories: Illustrating articles with visual summaries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/newsstories-illustrating-articles-with-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we explore a novel setting where the goal is to learn a self-supervised visual-language representation that is robust to varying text length and the number of images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/newsstories-illustrating-articles-with-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bundle MCR: Towards Conversational Bundle Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bundle-mcr-towards-conversational-bundle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MCR, which uses a conversational paradigm to elicit user interests by asking user preferences on tags (e. g., categories or attributes) and handling user feedback across multiple rounds, is an emerging recommendation setting to acquire user feedback and narrow down the output space, but has not been explored in the context of bundle recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bundle-mcr-towards-conversational-bundle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient One Pass Self-distillation with Zipf's Label Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-one-pass-self-distillation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes an efficient self-distillation method named Zipf's Label Smoothing (Zipf's LS), which uses the on-the-fly prediction of a network to generate soft supervision that conforms to Zipf distribution without using any contrastive samples or auxiliary parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-one-pass-self-distillation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monocular 3D Object Detection with Depth from Motion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-3d-object-detection-with-depth-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Perceiving 3D objects from monocular inputs is crucial for robotic systems, given its economy compared to multi-sensor settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-3d-object-detection-with-depth-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MV-FCOS3D++: Multi-View Camera-Only 4D Object Detection with Pretrained Monocular Backbones</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mv-fcos3d-multi-view-camera-only-4d-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this technical report, we present our solution, dubbed MV-FCOS3D++, for the Camera-Only 3D Detection track in Waymo Open Dataset Challenge 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mv-fcos3d-multi-view-camera-only-4d-object</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
