<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 21:08:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning With Individualized Privacy Through Client Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-with-individualized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on this idea, we propose an adapted method for enabling Individualized Differential Privacy (IDP) in Federated Learning (FL) by handling clients according to their personal privacy preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-with-individualized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Invariance Self-training for Reliable Semi-supervised Surgical Phase Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-invariance-self-training-for-reliable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate surgical phase recognition is crucial for advancing computer-assisted interventions, yet the scarcity of labeled data hinders training reliable deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-invariance-self-training-for-reliable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICoTA: Red-teaming of In-the-wild Conversation with Test Attempts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ricota-red-teaming-of-in-the-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With these prompts, we aim to evaluate LLMs' ability to identify the type of conversation and users' testing purposes to derive chatbot design implications for mitigating jailbreaking risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ricota-red-teaming-of-in-the-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Scene Adaptation for Vision-and-Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-scene-adaptation-for-vision-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the proposed task, one has to address two challenges in existing VLN datasets: the lack of OOD data, and the limited number and style diversity of instructions for each scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-scene-adaptation-for-vision-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiChallenge: A Realistic Multi-Turn Conversation Evaluation Benchmark Challenging to Frontier LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multichallenge-a-realistic-multi-turn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present MultiChallenge, a pioneering benchmark evaluating large language models (LLMs) on conducting multi-turn conversations with human users, a crucial yet underexamined capability for their applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multichallenge-a-realistic-multi-turn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reqo: A Robust and Explainable Query Optimization Cost Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reqo-a-robust-and-explainable-query</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating these innovations, we propose a cost model for a Robust and Explainable Query Optimizer, Reqo, that improves the accuracy, robustness, and explainability of cost estimation, outperforming state-of-the-art approaches in all three dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reqo-a-robust-and-explainable-query</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus: Harmful Fine-tuning Attack for Large Language Models Bypassing Guardrail Moderation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virus-harmful-fine-tuning-attack-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By designing a new red-teaming method, we in this paper show that purely relying on the moderation guardrail for data filtration is not reliable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virus-harmful-fine-tuning-attack-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Action Recognition Using Temporal Shift Module and Ensemble Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/action-recognition-using-temporal-shift</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The competition aimed to recognize human actions using a diverse dataset of 20 action classes, collected from multi-modal sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/action-recognition-using-temporal-shift</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Geometric Perspective for High-Dimensional Multiplex Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-geometric-perspective-for-high-dimensional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the node representations reside on highly curved manifolds, thus rendering their exploitation more challenging for downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-geometric-perspective-for-high-dimensional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>acoupi: An Open-Source Python Framework for Deploying Bioacoustic AI Models on Edge Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acoupi-an-open-source-python-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By modularising key elements of the bioacoustic monitoring workflow, acoupi allows users to easily customise, extend, or select specific components to fit their unique monitoring needs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acoupi-an-open-source-python-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Beyond the Surface: How Far Can Continual Pre-Training with LoRA Enhance LLMs' Domain-Specific Insight Learning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-beyond-the-surface-how-far-can</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable performance on various tasks, yet their ability to extract and internalize deeper insights from domain-specific datasets remains underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-beyond-the-surface-how-far-can</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the Gap Between Synthetic and Ground Truth Time Series Distributions via Neural Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-gap-between-synthetic-and-ground</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Neural Mapper for Vector Quantized Time Series Generator (NM-VQTSG), a novel method aimed at addressing fidelity challenges in vector quantized (VQ) time series generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-gap-between-synthetic-and-ground</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Conversational XAI All You Need? Human-AI Decision Making With a Conversational XAI Assistant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-conversational-xai-all-you-need-human-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In comparison to an XAI dashboard, we found that the conversational XAI interface can bring about a better understanding of the AI system among users and higher user trust.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-conversational-xai-all-you-need-human-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFPE: A Diverse Fingerprint Ensemble for Enhancing LLM Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfpe-a-diverse-fingerprint-ensemble-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have shown remarkable capabilities across various natural language processing tasks but often struggle to excel uniformly in diverse or complex domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfpe-a-diverse-fingerprint-ensemble-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Quantification and Decomposition for LLM-based Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-and-decomposition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the widespread adoption of large language models (LLMs) for recommendation, we demonstrate that LLMs often exhibit uncertainty in their recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-and-decomposition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMP in the Odyssey: Provably Robust Reinforcement Learning with Certified Radius Maximization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camp-in-the-odyssey-provably-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the results, \texttt{CAMP} can achieve up to twice the certified expected return compared to that of baselines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camp-in-the-odyssey-provably-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Making Flowchart Images Machine Interpretable</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-making-flowchart-images-machine-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computer programming textbooks and software documentations often contain flowcharts to illustrate the flow of an algorithm or procedure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-making-flowchart-images-machine-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PulmoFusion: Advancing Pulmonary Health with Efficient Multi-Modal Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pulmofusion-advancing-pulmonary-health-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel, non-invasive approach using multimodal predictive models that integrate RGB or thermal video data with patient metadata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pulmofusion-advancing-pulmonary-health-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Janus-Pro: Unified Multimodal Understanding and Generation with Data and Model Scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/janus-pro-unified-multimodal-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Janus-Pro, an advanced version of the previous work Janus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/janus-pro-unified-multimodal-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Your Model Ranking on Chatbot Arena by Vote Rigging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-your-model-ranking-on-chatbot-arena</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first introduce a straightforward target-only rigging strategy that focuses on new battles involving $m_{t}$, identifying it via watermarking or a binary classifier, and exclusively voting for $m_{t}$ wins.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-your-model-ranking-on-chatbot-arena</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yin-Yang: Developing Motifs With Long-Term Structure And Controllability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yin-yang-developing-motifs-with-long-term</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose Yin-Yang, a framework consisting of a phrase generator, phrase refiner, and phrase selector models for the development of motifs into melodies with long-term structure and controllability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yin-yang-developing-motifs-with-long-term</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Code Generation to Solve Open Instances of Combinatorial Design Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-code-generation-to-solve-open-instances</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Handbook of Combinatorial Designs catalogs many types of combinatorial designs, together with lists of open instances for which existence has not yet been determined.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-code-generation-to-solve-open-instances</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Multimodal LLM for Inspirational User Interface Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-multimodal-llm-for-inspirational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspirational search, the process of exploring designs to inform and inspire new creative work, is pivotal in mobile user interface (UI) design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-multimodal-llm-for-inspirational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DBSCAN in domains with periodic boundary conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dbscan-in-domains-with-periodic-boundary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many scientific problems involve data that is embedded in a space with periodic boundary conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dbscan-in-domains-with-periodic-boundary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HateBench: Benchmarking Hate Speech Detectors on LLM-Generated Content and Hate Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hatebench-benchmarking-hate-speech-detectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose HateBench, a framework for benchmarking hate speech detectors on LLM-generated hate speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hatebench-benchmarking-hate-speech-detectors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A General Bayesian Framework for Informative Input Design in System Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-bayesian-framework-for-informative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We tackle the problem of informative input design for system identification, where we select inputs, observe the corresponding outputs from the true system, and optimize the parameters of our model to best fit the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-bayesian-framework-for-informative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outlier Synthesis via Hamiltonian Monte Carlo for Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-synthesis-via-hamiltonian-monte-carlo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Hamiltonian Monte Carlo with sampling acceptance rate almost close to 1 also makes our framework enjoy great efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-synthesis-via-hamiltonian-monte-carlo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Rollouts in Model-Based Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-rollouts-in-model-based-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model-based reinforcement learning (MBRL) seeks to enhance data efficiency by learning a model of the environment and generating synthetic rollouts from it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-rollouts-in-model-based-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JRE-L: Journalist, Reader, and Editor LLMs in the Loop for Science Journalism for the General Audience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jre-l-journalist-reader-and-editor-llms-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Science journalism reports current scientific discoveries to non-specialists, aiming to enable public comprehension of the state of the art.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jre-l-journalist-reader-and-editor-llms-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Phenology Modeling for Predicting Temperature Effects on Tree Dormancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-phenology-modeling-for-predicting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Biophysical models offer valuable insights into climate-phenology relationships in both natural and agricultural settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-phenology-modeling-for-predicting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Transformers Learn Full Bayesian Inference in Context?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-transformers-learn-full-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have emerged as the dominant architecture in the field of deep learning, with a broad range of applications and remarkable in-context learning (ICL) capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-transformers-learn-full-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exponential Family Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exponential-family-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The self-attention mechanism is the backbone of the transformer neural network underlying most large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exponential-family-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model Critics for Execution-Free Evaluation of Code Changes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-critics-for-execution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Importantly, we assume access to the gold test patch for the problem (i. e., reference-aware) to assess both semantics and executability of generated patches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-critics-for-execution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xJailbreak: Representation Space Guided Reinforcement Learning for Interpretable LLM Jailbreaking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xjailbreak-representation-space-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safety alignment mechanism are essential for preventing large language models (LLMs) from generating harmful information or unethical content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xjailbreak-representation-space-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amplifier: Bringing Attention to Neglected Low-Energy Components in Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amplifier-bringing-attention-to-neglected-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an energy amplification technique to address the issue that existing models easily overlook low-energy components in time series forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amplifier-bringing-attention-to-neglected-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Increasing Information for Model Predictive Control with Semi-Markov Decision Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/increasing-information-for-model-predictive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works in Learning-Based Model Predictive Control of dynamical systems show impressive sample complexity performances using criteria from Information Theory to accelerate the learning procedure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/increasing-information-for-model-predictive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RLPP: A Residual Method for Zero-Shot Real-World Autonomous Racing on Scaled Platforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlpp-a-residual-method-for-zero-shot-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive testing on the F1TENTH platform demonstrates that RLPP improves lap times by up to 6. 37 %, closing the gap to the SotA methods by more than 52 % and providing reliable performance in zero-shot real-world deployment, overcoming key challenges associated with the Sim-to-Real transfer and reducing the performance gap from simulation to reality by more than 8-fold when compared to the baseline RL controller.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlpp-a-residual-method-for-zero-shot-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RDMM: Fine-Tuned LLM Models for On-Device Robotic Decision Making with Enhanced Contextual Awareness in Specific Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdmm-fine-tuned-llm-models-for-on-device</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research introduces a framework that utilizes RDMM (Robotics Decision-Making Models), which possess the capacity for decision-making within domain-specific contexts, as well as an awareness of their personal knowledge and capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdmm-fine-tuned-llm-models-for-on-device</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Histoires Morales: A French Dataset for Assessing Moral Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histoires-morales-a-french-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While models are often adapted to user preferences, it is equally important to ensure they align with moral norms and behaviours in real-world social situations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histoires-morales-a-french-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mamba-Shedder: Post-Transformer Compression for Efficient Selective Structured State Space Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-shedder-post-transformer-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large pre-trained models have achieved outstanding results in sequence modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-shedder-post-transformer-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Code Runtime Performance through Context-Aware Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-code-runtime-performance-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimizing software performance through automated code refinement offers a promising avenue for enhancing execution speed and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-code-runtime-performance-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Roughly Forced Nonlinear PDEs via Misspecified Kernel Methods and Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-roughly-forced-nonlinear-pdes-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the use of Gaussian Processes (GPs) or Neural Networks (NNs) to numerically approximate the solutions to nonlinear partial differential equations (PDEs) with rough forcing or source terms, which commonly arise as pathwise solutions to stochastic PDEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-roughly-forced-nonlinear-pdes-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VeriFact: Verifying Facts in LLM-Generated Clinical Text with Electronic Health Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifact-verifying-facts-in-llm-generated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods to ensure factual accuracy of text generated by large language models (LLM) in clinical medicine are lacking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifact-verifying-facts-in-llm-generated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-Differentiating Any LLM Workflow: A Farewell to Manual Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-differentiating-any-llm-workflow-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have reshaped natural language processing, powering applications from multi-hop retrieval and question answering to autonomous agent workflows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-differentiating-any-llm-workflow-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FactCG: Enhancing Fact Checkers with Graph-Based Multi-Hop Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factcg-enhancing-fact-checkers-with-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior research on training grounded factuality classification models to detect hallucinations in large language models (LLMs) has relied on public natural language inference (NLI) data and synthetic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factcg-enhancing-fact-checkers-with-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extending Information Bottleneck Attribution to Video Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-information-bottleneck-attribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce VIBA, a novel approach for explainable video classification by adapting Information Bottlenecks for Attribution (IBA) to video sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-information-bottleneck-attribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scanning Trojaned Models Using Out-of-Distribution Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scanning-trojaned-models-using-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TRODO leverages the concept of "blind spots"--regions where trojaned classifiers erroneously identify out-of-distribution (OOD) samples as in-distribution (ID).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scanning-trojaned-models-using-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHiP: Cross-modal Hierarchical Direct Preference Optimization for Multimodal LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chip-cross-modal-hierarchical-direct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, in this work, we propose a Cross-modal Hierarchical Direct Preference Optimization (CHiP) to address these limitations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chip-cross-modal-hierarchical-direct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Functional Brain Connectome Analysis: Do Graph Deep Learning Models Help?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-functional-brain-connectome</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Functional brain connectome is crucial for deciphering the neural mechanisms underlying cognitive functions and neurological disorders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-functional-brain-connectome</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting harassment and defamation in cyberbullying with emotion-adaptive training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-harassment-and-defamation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[EAT consistently improves the average macro F1, precision and recall by 20% in cyberbullying detection tasks across nine transformer-based models under low-resource settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-harassment-and-defamation-in</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
