<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 21:08:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Knowledge Graphs for Automating AI of Digital Twins</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-knowledge-graphs-for-automating-ai-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Digital Twins are digital representations of systems in the Internet of Things (IoT) that are often based on AI models that are trained on data from those systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-knowledge-graphs-for-automating-ai-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoupled Mixup for Generalized Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-mixup-for-generalized-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the observation is that noise-prone regions such as textural and clutter backgrounds are adverse to the generalization ability of CNN models during training, we enhance features from discriminative regions and suppress noise-prone ones when combining an image pair.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-mixup-for-generalized-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OTSeq2Set: An Optimal Transport Enhanced Sequence-to-Set Model for Extreme Multi-label Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/otseq2set-an-optimal-transport-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, such models can't predict a relatively complete and variable-length label subset for each document, because they select positive labels relevant to the document by a fixed threshold or take top k labels in descending order of scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/otseq2set-an-optimal-transport-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geographic Citation Gaps in NLP Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geographic-citation-gaps-in-nlp-research</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Similar disparities are also believed to exist for paper citation counts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geographic-citation-gaps-in-nlp-research</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Language Models for Code Syntax Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-language-models-for-code-syntax</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our key observation is that existing language models pretrained on code still lack the understanding of code syntax.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-language-models-for-code-syntax</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid and robust endoscopic content area estimation: A lean GPU-based pipeline and curated benchmark dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-and-robust-endoscopic-content-area</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The estimation of the content area is a common task in endoscopic image processing and computer vision pipelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-and-robust-endoscopic-content-area</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Affirmative Interpretations from Negation Improves Natural Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-affirmative-interpretations-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the fact that understanding a negated statement often requires humans to infer affirmative interpretations, in this paper we show that doing so benefits models for three natural language understanding tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-affirmative-interpretations-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Tumors Make AI Segment Tumors Better</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-tumors-make-ai-segment-tumors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a novel strategy to generate synthetic tumors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-tumors-make-ai-segment-tumors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemFormer: Semantic Guided Activation Transformer for Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semformer-semantic-guided-activation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent mainstream weakly supervised semantic segmentation (WSSS) approaches are mainly based on Class Activation Map (CAM) generated by a CNN (Convolutional Neural Network) based image classifier.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semformer-semantic-guided-activation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Data Perspectivism and Personalization: An Application to Social Norms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-data-perspectivism-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of using a single ground truth for language processing tasks, several recent studies have examined how to represent and predict the labels of the set of annotators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-data-perspectivism-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inducer-tuning: Connecting Prefix-tuning and Adapter-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inducer-tuning-connecting-prefix-tuning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prefix-tuning, or more generally continuous prompt tuning, has become an essential paradigm of parameter-efficient transfer learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inducer-tuning-connecting-prefix-tuning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Design Concepts for CAD Sketches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-design-concepts-for-cad-sketches</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sketch design concepts are recurring patterns found in parametric CAD sketches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-design-concepts-for-cad-sketches</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimpleDG: Simple Domain Generalization Baseline without Bells and Whistles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simpledg-simple-domain-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a simple domain generalization baseline, which wins second place in both the common context generalization track and the hybrid context generalization track respectively in NICO CHALLENGE 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simpledg-simple-domain-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eeny, meeny, miny, moe. How to choose data for morphological inflection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eeny-meeny-miny-moe-how-to-choose-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore four sampling strategies for the task of morphological inflection using a Transformer model: a pair of oracle experiments where data is chosen based on whether the model already can or cannot inflect the test forms correctly, as well as strategies based on high/low model confidence, entropy, as well as random selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eeny-meeny-miny-moe-how-to-choose-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAMFormer: Multi-Modal Transformer with Learned Attention Mask for Early Intent Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tamformer-multi-modal-transformer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human intention prediction is a growing area of research where an activity in a video has to be anticipated by a vision-based system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tamformer-multi-modal-transformer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of Synthetically Generated CT for use in Transcranial Focused Ultrasound Procedures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-synthetically-generated-ct-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Among 20 targets, differences in simulated peak pressure between rCT and sCT were largest without phase correction (12. 4$\pm$8. 1%) and smallest with Kranion phases (7. 3$\pm$6. 0%).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-synthetically-generated-ct-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unknown area exploration for robots with energy constraints using a modified Butterfly Optimization Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unknown-area-exploration-for-robots-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Butterfly Optimization Algorithm (BOA) is a recent metaheuristic that has been used in several optimization problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unknown-area-exploration-for-robots-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CU-Net: LiDAR Depth-Only Completion With Coupled U-Net</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cu-net-lidar-depth-only-completion-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that existing depth-only methods can obtain satisfactory results in the areas where the measurement points are almost accurate and evenly distributed (denoted as normal areas), while the performance is limited in the areas where the foreground and background points are overlapped due to occlusion (denoted as overlap areas) and the areas where there are no measurement points around (denoted as blank areas) since the methods have no reliable input information in these areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cu-net-lidar-depth-only-completion-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M$^3$ViT: Mixture-of-Experts Vision Transformer for Efficient Multi-task Learning with Model-Accelerator Co-design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-3-vit-mixture-of-experts-vision-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, when deploying MTL onto those real-world systems that are often resource-constrained or latency-sensitive, two prominent challenges arise: (i) during training, simultaneously optimizing all tasks is often difficult due to gradient conflicts across tasks; (ii) at inference, current MTL regimes have to activate nearly the entire model even to just execute a single task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-3-vit-mixture-of-experts-vision-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residual Learning of Neural Text Generation with $n$-gram Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/residual-learning-of-neural-text-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The combination of $n$-gram and neural LMs not only allows the neural part to focus on the deeper understanding of language but also provides a flexible way to customize an LM by switching the underlying $n$-gram model without changing the neural model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/residual-learning-of-neural-text-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How precise are performance estimates for typical medical image segmentation tasks?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-precise-are-performance-estimates-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to estimate what is the typical confidence that can be expected in such studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-precise-are-performance-estimates-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffusionDB: A Large-scale Prompt Gallery Dataset for Text-to-Image Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusiondb-a-large-scale-prompt-gallery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze prompts in the dataset and discuss key properties of these prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusiondb-a-large-scale-prompt-gallery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BioNLI: Generating a Biomedical NLI Dataset Using Lexico-semantic Constraints for Adversarial Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bionli-generating-a-biomedical-nli-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel semi-supervised procedure that bootstraps an NLI dataset from existing biomedical dataset that pairs mechanisms with experimental evidence in abstracts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bionli-generating-a-biomedical-nli-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multitask Detection of Speaker Changes, Overlapping Speech and Voice Activity Using wav2vec 2.0</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multitask-detection-of-speaker-changes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore the effectiveness of this model on three basic speech classification tasks: speaker change detection, overlapped speech detection, and voice activity detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multitask-detection-of-speaker-changes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSel: N-ary Relation Extraction from Scientific Text and Tables by Learning to Retrieve and Select</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resel-n-ary-relation-extraction-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of extracting N-ary relation tuples from scientific articles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resel-n-ary-relation-extraction-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Radiance Fields for 3D Video Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-radiance-fields-for-3d-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of training a single model that combines all the frames, we formulate the dynamic modeling problem with an incremental learning paradigm in which per-frame model difference is trained to complement the adaption of a base model on the current frame.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-radiance-fields-for-3d-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIMA -- Multifunctional IoT Integrated Menstrual Aid</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mima-multifunctional-iot-integrated-menstrual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Currently, the concept of period pants revolves around pad-free and hassle-free periods for women, whereas most women still prefer sanitary pads during their period cycle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mima-multifunctional-iot-integrated-menstrual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning on Large-scale Text-attributed Graphs via Variational Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-on-large-scale-text-attributed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an efficient and effective solution to learning on large text-attributed graphs by fusing graph structure and language learning with a variational Expectation-Maximization (EM) framework, called GLEM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-on-large-scale-text-attributed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coresets for Vertical Federated Learning: Regularized Linear Regression and $K$-Means Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coresets-for-vertical-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vertical federated learning (VFL), where data features are stored in multiple parties distributively, is an important area in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coresets-for-vertical-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Federated Learning via Heterogeneous Modular Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-federated-learning-via-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized Federated Learning (PFL) which collaboratively trains a federated model while considering local clients under privacy constraints has attracted much attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-federated-learning-via-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>History-Based, Bayesian, Closure for Stochastic Parameterization: Application to Lorenz '96</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/history-based-bayesian-closure-for-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we develop a new type of parameterization (closure) which is based on a Bayesian formalism for neural networks, to account for uncertainty quantification, and includes memory, to account for the non-instantaneous response of the closure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/history-based-bayesian-closure-for-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RGB-T Semantic Segmentation with Location, Activation, and Sharpening</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgb-t-semantic-segmentation-with-location</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The highlight of LASNet is that we fully consider the characteristics of cross-modal features at different levels, and accordingly propose three specific modules for better segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgb-t-semantic-segmentation-with-location</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pretrained audio neural networks for Speech emotion recognition in Portuguese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pretrained-audio-neural-networks-for-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This dataset contains about $50$ minutes of Brazilian Portuguese speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pretrained-audio-neural-networks-for-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Robust Bias Mitigation Procedure Based on the Stereotype Content Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-robust-bias-mitigation-procedure-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Stereotype Content model (SCM) states that we tend to perceive minority groups as cold, incompetent or both.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-robust-bias-mitigation-procedure-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Fuzzy Neural Network with Evolutionary Rule Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-fuzzy-neural-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ERL is inspired by the theory of biological evolution; it encourages rule variations while activating superior rules and deactivating inferior rules for local clients with non-IID data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-fuzzy-neural-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Task: Deriving Semantic Class Targets for the Physical Sciences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-task-deriving-semantic-class-targets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We define deriving semantic class targets as a novel multi-modal task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-task-deriving-semantic-class-targets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coordinate Descent for SLOPE</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coordinate-descent-for-slope</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The lasso is the most famous sparse regression and feature selection method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coordinate-descent-for-slope</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoregressive Structured Prediction with Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-structured-prediction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have seen a paradigm shift in NLP towards using pretrained language models ({PLM}) for a wide range of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-structured-prediction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparison of neural closure models for discretised PDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-of-neural-closure-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Of the two trajectory fitting procedures, the discretise-then-optimise approach produces more accurate models than the optimise-then-discretise approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-of-neural-closure-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causality Detection using Multiple Annotation Decision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-detection-using-multiple-annotation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper describes the work that has been submitted to the 5th workshop on Challenges and Applications of Automated Extraction of socio-political events from text (CASE 2022).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-detection-using-multiple-annotation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monotonic segmental attention for automatic speech recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monotonic-segmental-attention-for-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We restrict the decoder attention to segments to avoid quadratic runtime of global attention, better generalize to long sequences, and eventually enable streaming.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monotonic-segmental-attention-for-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CS1QA: A Dataset for Assisting Code-based Question Answering in an Introductory Programming Course</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cs1qa-a-dataset-for-assisting-code-based-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce CS1QA, a dataset for code-based question answering in the programming education domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cs1qa-a-dataset-for-assisting-code-based-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Automatically Extracting UML Class Diagrams from Natural Language Specifications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-automatically-extracting-uml-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To develop our approach, we create a dataset of UML class diagrams and their English specifications with the help of volunteers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-automatically-extracting-uml-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid HMM Decoder For Convolutional Codes By Joint Trellis-Like Structure and Channel Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-hmm-decoder-for-convolutional-codes-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the use of a Hidden Markov Model (HMM) for the reconstruction of convolutional codes and decoding by the Viterbi algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-hmm-decoder-for-convolutional-codes-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading Between the Lines: Modeling User Behavior and Costs in AI-Assisted Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reading-between-the-lines-modeling-user</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AI code-recommendation systems (CodeRec), such as Copilot, can assist programmers inside an IDE by suggesting and autocompleting arbitrary code; potentially improving their productivity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reading-between-the-lines-modeling-user</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highly Efficient Real-Time Streaming and Fully On-Device Speaker Diarization with Multi-Stage Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/highly-efficient-real-time-streaming-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This multi-stage clustering strategy is critical for streaming on-device speaker diarization systems, where the budgets of CPU, memory and battery are tight.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/highly-efficient-real-time-streaming-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Sentiment Analysis for Code-Switched Text Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-sentiment-analysis-for-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of training on the entire code-switched corpus at once, we create buckets based on the fraction of words in the resource-rich language and progressively train from resource-rich language dominated samples to low-resource language dominated samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-sentiment-analysis-for-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Search Is What You Need For Neural Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-search-is-what-you-need-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our findings, we further assess the contrastive search decoding method using off-the-shelf LMs on four generation tasks across 16 languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-search-is-what-you-need-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deconfounding Legal Judgment Prediction for European Court of Human Rights Cases Towards Better Alignment with Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deconfounding-legal-judgment-prediction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work demonstrates that Legal Judgement Prediction systems without expert-informed adjustments can be vulnerable to shallow, distracting surface signals that arise from corpus construction, case distribution, and confounding factors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deconfounding-legal-judgment-prediction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Spectral Method for Assessing and Combining Multiple Data Visualizations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-spectral-method-for-assessing-and-combining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then it leverages the eigenscores to obtain a consensus visualization, which has much improved { quality over the individual visualizations in capturing the underlying true data structure.}]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-spectral-method-for-assessing-and-combining</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
