<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 21:05:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual-Augmented Importance Sampling for Semi-Offline Policy Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-augmented-importance-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In applying reinforcement learning (RL) to high-stakes domains, quantitative and qualitative evaluation using observational data can help practitioners understand the generalization performance of new policies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-augmented-importance-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scale-Adaptive Feature Aggregation for Efficient Space-Time Video Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-adaptive-feature-aggregation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Space-Time Video Super-Resolution (STVSR) task aims to enhance the visual quality of videos, by simultaneously performing video frame interpolation (VFI) and video super-resolution (VSR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-adaptive-feature-aggregation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-modal Active Complementary Learning with Self-refining Correspondence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-active-complementary-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, image-text matching has attracted more and more attention from academia and industry, which is fundamental to understanding the latent correspondence across visual and textual modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-active-complementary-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Spatio-Temporal Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-spatio-temporal-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose a structure distillation approach based on the Graph Information Bottleneck (GIB) principle with an explainable objective, which is instantiated by the STG encoder and decoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-spatio-temporal-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuro-Inspired Fragmentation and Recall to Overcome Catastrophic Forgetting in Curiosity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-inspired-fragmentation-and-recall-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep reinforcement learning methods exhibit impressive performance on a range of tasks but still struggle on hard exploration tasks in large environments with sparse rewards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-inspired-fragmentation-and-recall-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Space-Time Hash Encoding for Efficient Dynamic Scene Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-space-time-hash-encoding-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the Masked Space-Time Hash encoding (MSTH), a novel method for efficiently reconstructing dynamic 3D scenes from multi-view or monocular videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-space-time-hash-encoding-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-Guided Complexity-Controlled Abstractions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-guided-complexity-controlled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks often learn task-specific latent representations that fail to generalize to novel settings or tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-guided-complexity-controlled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Deep Learning Approach to Teeth Segmentation and Orientation from Panoramic X-rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-approach-to-teeth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed model's accuracy and versatility offer promising prospects for improving dental diagnoses, treatment planning, and personalized healthcare in the oral domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-approach-to-teeth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LightLM: A Lightweight Deep and Narrow Language Model for Generative Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightlm-a-lightweight-deep-and-narrow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LightLM tackles the issue by introducing a light-weight deep and narrow Transformer architecture, which is specifically tailored for direct generation of recommendation items.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightlm-a-lightweight-deep-and-narrow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deja Vu: Contextual Sparsity for Efficient LLMs at Inference Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deja-vu-contextual-sparsity-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that contextual sparsity exists, that it can be accurately predicted, and that we can exploit it to speed up LLM inference in wall-clock time without compromising LLM's quality or in-context learning ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deja-vu-contextual-sparsity-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CROP: Conservative Reward for Model-based Offline Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crop-conservative-reward-for-model-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Offline reinforcement learning (RL) aims to optimize policy using collected data without online interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crop-conservative-reward-for-model-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lil-Bevo: Explorations of Strategies for Training Language Models in More Humanlike Ways</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lil-bevo-explorations-of-strategies-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We pretrained our masked language models with three ingredients: an initial pretraining with music data, training on shorter sequences before training on longer ones, and masking specific tokens to target some of the BLiMP subtasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lil-bevo-explorations-of-strategies-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Semi-Implicit Variational Inference with Application to Diffusion Model Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-semi-implicit-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-implicit variational inference (SIVI) has been introduced to expand the analytical variational families by defining expressive semi-implicit distributions in a hierarchical manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-semi-implicit-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Structure-Aware Diffusion Process for Low-Light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-structure-aware-diffusion-process-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To harness the capabilities of diffusion models, we delve into this intricate process and advocate for the regularization of its inherent ODE-trajectory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-structure-aware-diffusion-process-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDENAS: Internal Dependency Exploration for Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idenas-internal-dependency-exploration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research proposes IDENAS, an Internal Dependency-based Exploration for Neural Architecture Search, integrating NAS with feature selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idenas-internal-dependency-exploration-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBD: A Certified Backdoor Detector Based on Local Dominant Probability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbd-a-certified-backdoor-detector-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, for backdoor attacks with random perturbation triggers bounded by $\ell_2\leq0. 75$ which achieves more than 90\% attack success rate, CBD achieves 100\% (98\%), 100\% (84\%), 98\% (98\%), and 72\% (40\%) empirical (certified) detection true positive rates on the four benchmark datasets GTSRB, SVHN, CIFAR-10, and TinyImageNet, respectively, with low false positive rates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbd-a-certified-backdoor-detector-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Trie of Rules: a fast data structure for the representation of association rules</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-trie-of-rules-a-fast-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel data structure, called the Trie of rules, for storing a ruleset that is generated by association rule mining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-trie-of-rules-a-fast-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symbolic Planning and Code Generation for Grounded Dialogue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-planning-and-code-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) excel at processing and generating both text and code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-planning-and-code-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The IMS Toucan System for the Blizzard Challenge 2023</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ims-toucan-system-for-the-blizzard</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For our contribution to the Blizzard Challenge 2023, we improved on the system we submitted to the Blizzard Challenge 2021.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ims-toucan-system-for-the-blizzard</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorporating Probing Signals into Multimodal Machine Translation via Visual Question-Answering Pairs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-probing-signals-into-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an in-depth study of multimodal machine translation (MMT), examining the prevailing understanding that MMT systems exhibit decreased sensitivity to visual information when text inputs are complete.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-probing-signals-into-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bias in Evaluation Processes: An Optimization-Based Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bias-in-evaluation-processes-an-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We characterize the distributions that arise from our model and study the effect of the parameters on the observed distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bias-in-evaluation-processes-an-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Logical Forms improve fidelity in Table-to-Text generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-logical-forms-improve-fidelity-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Table-to-text systems generate natural language statements from structured data like tables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-logical-forms-improve-fidelity-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>miditok: A Python package for MIDI file tokenization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miditok-a-python-package-for-midi-file</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in natural language processing has been adapted to the symbolic music modality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miditok-a-python-package-for-midi-file</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing to Unseen Domains in Diabetic Retinopathy Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-to-unseen-domains-in-diabetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, automated diabetic retinopathy classification using deep learning techniques has gained interest in the medical imaging community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-to-unseen-domains-in-diabetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>torchdistill Meets Hugging Face Libraries for Reproducible, Coding-Free Deep Learning Studies: A Case Study on NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchdistill-meets-hugging-face-libraries-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reproducibility in scientific work has been becoming increasingly important in research communities such as machine learning, natural language processing, and computer vision communities due to the rapid development of the research domains supported by recent advances in deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchdistill-meets-hugging-face-libraries-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Voices, Local Biases: Socio-Cultural Prejudices across Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-voices-local-biases-socio-cultural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we highlight the significance of these social biases and the new dimensions through an extensive comparison of embedding methods, reinforcing the need to address them in pursuit of more equitable language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-voices-local-biases-socio-cultural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isometric Motion Manifold Primitives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isometric-motion-manifold-primitives</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Motion Manifold Primitive (MMP) produces, for a given task, a continuous manifold of trajectories each of which can successfully complete the task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isometric-motion-manifold-primitives</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combating Representation Learning Disparity with Geometric Harmonization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combating-representation-learning-disparity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning (SSL) as an effective paradigm of representation learning has achieved tremendous success on various curated datasets in diverse scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combating-representation-learning-disparity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Open Source Data Contamination Report for Llama Series Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-open-source-data-contamination-report-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data contamination in language model evaluation is increasingly prevalent as the popularity of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-open-source-data-contamination-report-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Temporal Sentence Grounding From Narrated EgoVideos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-temporal-sentence-grounding-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to traditional benchmarks on which this task is evaluated, these datasets offer finer-grained sentences to ground in notably longer videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-temporal-sentence-grounding-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoK: Pitfalls in Evaluating Black-Box Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sok-pitfalls-in-evaluating-black-box-attacks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these works make different assumptions on the adversary's knowledge and current literature lacks a cohesive organization centered around the threat model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sok-pitfalls-in-evaluating-black-box-attacks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Iterative Refinement with Diffusion Models for Video Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-iterative-refinement-with-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video grounding aims to localize the target moment in an untrimmed video corresponding to a given sentence query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-iterative-refinement-with-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond MLE: Convex Learning for Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-mle-convex-learning-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a novel class of training objectives based on convex functions, which enables text generation models to focus on highly probable outputs without having to estimate the entire data distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-mle-convex-learning-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-weighted Loss Functions for Improved Adversarial Attacks on Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-weighted-loss-functions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art deep neural networks have been shown to be extremely powerful in a variety of perceptual tasks like semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-weighted-loss-functions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JudgeLM: Fine-tuned Large Language Models are Scalable Judges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/judgelm-fine-tuned-large-language-models-are</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we propose to fine-tune LLMs as scalable judges (JudgeLM) to evaluate LLMs efficiently and effectively in open-ended benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/judgelm-fine-tuned-large-language-models-are</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Expressive Power of Low-Rank Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-expressive-power-of-low-rank-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-Rank Adaptation (LoRA), a parameter-efficient fine-tuning method that leverages low-rank adaptation of weight matrices, has emerged as a prevalent technique for fine-tuning pre-trained models such as large language models and diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-expressive-power-of-low-rank-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M2C: Towards Automatic Multimodal Manga Complement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m2c-towards-automatic-multimodal-manga</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In other words, the Multimodal Manga Complement (M2C) task has not been investigated, which aims to handle the aforementioned issues by providing a shared semantic space for vision and language understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m2c-towards-automatic-multimodal-manga</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETA: Evaluating the Impact of Protein Transfer Learning with Sub-word Tokenization on Downstream Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peta-evaluating-the-impact-of-protein</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, despite the wealth of benchmarks and studies in the natural language community, there remains a lack of a comprehensive benchmark for systematically evaluating protein language model quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peta-evaluating-the-impact-of-protein</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dialogue-based generation of self-driving simulation scenarios using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialogue-based-generation-of-self-driving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Simulation is an invaluable tool for developing and evaluating controllers for self-driving cars.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialogue-based-generation-of-self-driving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circuit as Set of Points</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circuit-as-set-of-points</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our work, we propose a novel perspective for circuit design by treating circuit components as point clouds and using Transformer-based point cloud perception methods to extract features from the circuit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circuit-as-set-of-points</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and Addressing the Pitfalls of Bisimulation-based Representations in Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-addressing-the-pitfalls-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also shed light on the critical role of reward scaling in bounding the scale of bisimulation measurements and of the value error they induce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-addressing-the-pitfalls-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Codebook Features: Sparse and Discrete Interpretability for Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codebook-features-sparse-and-discrete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this setting, our approach overcomes the superposition problem by assigning states to distinct codes, and we find that we can make the neural network behave as if it is in a different state by activating the code for that state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codebook-features-sparse-and-discrete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEVContrast: Self-Supervision in BEV Space for Automotive Lidar Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bevcontrast-self-supervision-in-bev-space-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a surprisingly simple and efficient method for self-supervision of 3D backbone on automotive Lidar point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bevcontrast-self-supervision-in-bev-space-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Bias and Fairness in Gender-Neutral Pretrained Vision-and-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-bias-and-fairness-in-gender</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We quantify bias amplification in pretraining and after fine-tuning on three families of vision-and-language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-bias-and-fairness-in-gender</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending Against Transfer Attacks From Public Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defending-against-transfer-attacks-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate the transfer attacks in this setting and propose a specialized defense method based on a game-theoretic perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defending-against-transfer-attacks-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IndustReal: A Dataset for Procedure Step Recognition Handling Execution Errors in Egocentric Videos in an Industrial-Like Setting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/industreal-a-dataset-for-procedure-step</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Annotations and benchmark performance are provided for action recognition and assembly state detection, as well as the new PSR task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/industreal-a-dataset-for-procedure-step</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HCT: Hybrid Convnet-Transformer for Parkinson's disease detection and severity prediction from gait</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hct-hybrid-convnet-transformer-for-parkinson</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our hybrid architecture exploits the strengths of both Convolutional Neural Networks (ConvNets) and Transformers to accurately detect PD and determine the severity stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hct-hybrid-convnet-transformer-for-parkinson</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lookup Table meets Local Laplacian Filter: Pyramid Reconstruction Network for Tone Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lookup-table-meets-local-laplacian-filter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we utilize local Laplacian filters to refine the edge details in the high-frequency components in an adaptive manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lookup-table-meets-local-laplacian-filter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Neural Controlled Differential Equations for Treatment Effect Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-neural-controlled-differential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Treatment effect estimation in continuous time is crucial for personalized medicine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-neural-controlled-differential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Effects of Projectors in Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-effects-of-projectors-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interestingly, we discovered that even if the student and the teacher have the same feature dimensions, adding a projector still helps to improve the distillation performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-effects-of-projectors-in</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
