<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 09:13:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>JCSE: Contrastive Learning of Japanese Sentence Embeddings and Its Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jcse-contrastive-learning-of-japanese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this, we propose a novel Japanese sentence representation framework, JCSE (derived from ``Contrastive learning of Sentence Embeddings for Japanese''), that creates training data by generating sentences and synthesizing them with sentences available in a target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jcse-contrastive-learning-of-japanese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RGB-D-Based Categorical Object Pose and Shape Estimation: Methods, Datasets, and Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgb-d-based-categorical-object-pose-and-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, various methods for 6D pose and shape estimation of objects at a per-category level have been proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgb-d-based-categorical-object-pose-and-shape</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Deep Learning with Scenario-Based Override Rules: a Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-deep-learning-with-scenario-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNNs) have become a crucial instrument in the software development toolkit, due to their ability to efficiently solve complex problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-deep-learning-with-scenario-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Inference in Denoising Diffusion Models via MMD Finetuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-inference-in-denoising-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings show that the proposed method is able to produce high-quality samples in a fraction of the time required by widely-used diffusion models, and outperforms state-of-the-art techniques for accelerated sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-inference-in-denoising-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiview Compressive Coding for 3D Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiview-compressive-coding-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a simple framework that operates on 3D points of single objects or whole scenes coupled with category-agnostic large-scale training from diverse RGB-D videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiview-compressive-coding-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Quantum Processes with Memory -- Quantum Recurrent Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-quantum-processes-with-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recurrent neural networks play an important role in both research and industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-quantum-processes-with-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpreting CNN Predictions using Conditional Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-cnn-predictions-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Supplying that information has two main challenges: how to represent this information in a form that is feedable to the GANs and how to effectively feed the representation to the GAN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-cnn-predictions-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interval Reachability of Nonlinear Dynamical Systems with Neural Network Controllers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interval-reachability-of-nonlinear-dynamical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This embedding provides a scalable approach for safety analysis of the neural control loop while preserving the nonlinear structure of the system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interval-reachability-of-nonlinear-dynamical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDFormer: Propagation Delay-aware Dynamic Long-range Transformer for Traffic Flow Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdformer-propagation-delay-aware-dynamic-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, GNN-based models have three major limitations for traffic prediction: i) Most methods model spatial dependencies in a static manner, which limits the ability to learn dynamic urban traffic patterns; ii) Most methods only consider short-range spatial information and are unable to capture long-range spatial dependencies; iii) These methods ignore the fact that the propagation of traffic conditions between locations has a time delay in traffic systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdformer-propagation-delay-aware-dynamic-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Private Online Bayesian Estimation With Adaptive Truncation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-online-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel online and adaptive truncation method for differentially private Bayesian online estimation of a static parameter regarding a population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-online-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaRE: Finding Root Causes of Configuration Issues in Highly-Configurable Robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/care-finding-root-causes-of-configuration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robotic systems have several subsystems that possess a huge combinatorial configuration space and hundreds or even thousands of possible software and hardware configuration options interacting non-trivially.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/care-finding-root-causes-of-configuration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning-Rate-Free Learning by D-Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-rate-free-learning-by-d-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we describe a single-loop method, with no back-tracking or line searches, which does not require knowledge of $D$ yet asymptotically achieves the optimal rate of convergence for the complexity class of convex Lipschitz functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-rate-free-learning-by-d-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Synthetic Data Generation with Effective Nonlinear Causal Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-synthetic-data-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, typically, the variables of a dataset depend on one another, and these dependencies are not considered in data generation leading to the creation of implausible records.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-synthetic-data-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-based inexact graph matching on top of CNNs for semantic scene understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-based-inexact-graph-matching-on-top-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On FASSEG data, results show that our module improves accuracy of the CNN by about 6. 3% (the Hausdorff distance decreases from 22. 11 to 20. 71).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-based-inexact-graph-matching-on-top-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergence of the SVD as an interpretable factorization in deep learning for inverse problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-the-svd-as-an-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the emergence of weight matrix singular value decomposition (SVD) in interpreting neural networks (NNs) for parameter estimation from noisy signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-the-svd-as-an-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmenting a Physics-Informed Neural Network for the 2D Burgers Equation by Addition of Solution Data Points</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-a-physics-informed-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we argue that the addition of the governing equations during training may provide a way to improve the overall performance of the model without relying on additional data, which is especially important for situations where the number of known solution points is limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-a-physics-informed-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SensorX2car: Sensors-to-car calibration for autonomous driving in road scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensorx2car-sensors-to-car-calibration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we present SensorX2car, a calibration toolbox for the online calibration of sensor-to-car coordinate systems in road scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensorx2car-sensors-to-car-calibration-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Learning with Neuron Groups</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-learning-with-neuron-groups</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Local learning is an approach to model-parallelism that removes the standard end-to-end learning setup and utilizes local objective functions to permit parallel learning amongst model components in a deep network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-learning-with-neuron-groups</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Supervised Semantic Segmentation via Gentle Teaching Assistant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-semantic-segmentation-via-4</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-Supervised Semantic Segmentation aims at training the segmentation model with limited labeled data and a large amount of unlabeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-semantic-segmentation-via-4</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADAv2: Advanced Multi-Anchor Based Active Domain Adaptation Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/madav2-advanced-multi-anchor-based-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised domain adaption has been widely adopted in tasks with scarce annotated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/madav2-advanced-multi-anchor-based-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Representing Noisy Image Without Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representing-noisy-image-without-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore a non-learning paradigm that aims to derive robust representation directly from noisy images, without the denoising as pre-processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representing-noisy-image-without-denoising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAME: Attention Mechanism Based Feature Fusion for Generating Explanation Maps of Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tame-attention-mechanism-based-feature-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TAME can easily be applied to any convolutional neural network (CNN) by streamlining the optimization of the attention mechanism's training method and the selection of target model's feature maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tame-attention-mechanism-based-feature-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gated-ViGAT: Efficient Bottom-Up Event Recognition and Explanation Using a New Frame Selection Policy and Gating Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gated-vigat-efficient-bottom-up-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, Gated-ViGAT, an efficient approach for video event recognition, utilizing bottom-up (object) information, a new frame sampling policy and a gating mechanism is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gated-vigat-efficient-bottom-up-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development, Optimization, and Deployment of Thermal Forward Vision Systems for Advance Vehicular Applications on Edge Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/development-optimization-and-deployment-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this research work, we have proposed a thermal tiny-YOLO multi-class object detection (TTYMOD) system as a smart forward sensing system that should remain effective in all weather and harsh environmental conditions using an end-to-end YOLO deep learning framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/development-optimization-and-deployment-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention2Minority: A salient instance inference-based multiple instance learning for classifying small lesions in whole slide images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention2minority-a-salient-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method initially learns representations of normal WSIs, and it then compares the normal WSIs representations with all the input patches to infer the salient instances of the input WSI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention2minority-a-salient-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Neural-Cracking-Machines: Self-Configurable Password Models from Auxiliary Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-neural-cracking-machines-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead, it exploits users' auxiliary information, such as email addresses, as a proxy signal to predict the underlying target password distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-neural-cracking-machines-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Close is ChatGPT to Human Experts? Comparison Corpus, Evaluation, and Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-close-is-chatgpt-to-human-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We call the collected dataset the Human ChatGPT Comparison Corpus (HC3).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-close-is-chatgpt-to-human-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthcity: facilitating innovative use cases of synthetic data in different data modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthcity-facilitating-innovative-use-cases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthcity is an open-source software package for innovative use cases of synthetic data in ML fairness, privacy and augmentation across diverse tabular data modalities, including static data, regular and irregular time series, data with censoring, multi-source data, composite data, and more.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthcity-facilitating-innovative-use-cases</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-informed Information Field Theory for Modeling Physical Systems with Uncertainty Quantification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-information-field-theory-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As an addendum, the method is equipped with a metric which allows the posterior to automatically quantify model-form uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-information-field-theory-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strong inductive biases provably prevent harmless interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strong-inductive-biases-provably-prevent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Classical wisdom suggests that estimators should avoid fitting noise to achieve good generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strong-inductive-biases-provably-prevent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharp Eyes: A Salient Object Detector Working The Same Way as Human Visual Characteristics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharp-eyes-a-salient-object-detector-working</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the OS branch, we first aggregate multi-level features to adaptively select complementary components, and then feed the saliency features with expanded boundary into aggregated features to guide the network obtain complete prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharp-eyes-a-salient-object-detector-working</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Holistic Understanding of Mathematical Questions with Contrastive Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-holistic-understanding-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, in this paper, we propose a novel contrastive pre-training approach for mathematical question representations, namely QuesCo, which attempts to bring questions with more similar purposes closer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-holistic-understanding-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Advanced Computer Vision Techniques for Sports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-advanced-computer-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide a use case for such data: building a model for shot speed estimation with pose data obtained using only Computer Vision models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-advanced-computer-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the State of German (Abstractive) Text Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-state-of-german-abstractive-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We attribute poor evaluation quality to a variety of different factors, which are investigated in more detail in this work: A lack of qualitative (and diverse) gold data considered for training, understudied (and untreated) positional biases in some of the existing datasets, and the lack of easily accessible and streamlined pre-processing strategies or analysis tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-state-of-german-abstractive-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expected Gradients of Maxout Networks and Consequences to Parameter Initialization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expected-gradients-of-maxout-networks-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the gradients of a maxout network with respect to inputs and parameters and obtain bounds for the moments depending on the architecture and the parameter distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expected-gradients-of-maxout-networks-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithms for Acyclic Weighted Finite-State Automata with Failure Arcs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/algorithms-for-acyclic-weighted-finite-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pathsum in ordinary acyclic WFSAs is efficiently computed by the backward algorithm in time $O(|E|)$, where $E$ is the set of transitions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/algorithms-for-acyclic-weighted-finite-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd Swiss German Speech to Standard German Text Shared Task at SwissText 2022</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2nd-swiss-german-speech-to-standard-german</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the results and findings of the 2nd Swiss German speech to Standard German text shared task at SwissText 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2nd-swiss-german-speech-to-standard-german</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Improving the Explainability of Text-based Information Retrieval with Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-improving-the-explainability-of-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a general architecture to incorporate knowledge graphs for XIR in various steps of the retrieval process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-improving-the-explainability-of-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calculation of Epidemic First Passage and Peak Time Probability Distributions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calculation-of-epidemic-first-passage-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the timing of the peak of a disease outbreak forms an important part of epidemic forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calculation-of-epidemic-first-passage-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Falsification of Digital Twins</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-falsification-of-digital-twins</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Digital twins hold substantial promise in many applications, but rigorous procedures for assessing their accuracy are essential for their widespread deployment in safety-critical settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-falsification-of-digital-twins</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mortality Prediction with Adaptive Feature Importance Recalibration for Peritoneal Dialysis Patients: a deep-learning-based study on a real-world longitudinal follow-up dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mortality-prediction-with-adaptive-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, our objective is to develop a deep learning model for a real-time, individualized, and interpretable mortality prediction model - AICare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mortality-prediction-with-adaptive-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Multi-Robot Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-multi-robot-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through simulations and real-world experiments, we show that: (i) when homogeneous methods fail due to strong heterogeneous requirements, HetGPPO succeeds, and, (ii) when homogeneous methods are able to learn apparently heterogeneous behaviors, HetGPPO achieves higher resilience to both training and deployment noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-multi-robot-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Domain Adaptation for Breaking the Limits of Low-quality Fundus Image Quality Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-domain-adaptation-for-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most of the existing image enhancement methods mainly focus on improving the image quality by leveraging the guidance of high-quality images, which is difficult to be collected in medical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-domain-adaptation-for-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SwaNNFlight System: On-the-Fly Sim-to-Real Adaptation via Anchored Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-swannflight-system-on-the-fly-sim-to-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[And (iii) anchor critics to help stabilize the fine-tuning of agents during sim-to-real transfer, online learning from real data while retaining behavior optimized in simulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-swannflight-system-on-the-fly-sim-to-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Visual Reconstruction in Language Semantic Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-visual-reconstruction-in-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Both masked image modeling (MIM) and natural language supervision have facilitated the progress of transferable visual pre-training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-visual-reconstruction-in-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face Inverse Rendering via Hierarchical Decoupling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-inverse-rendering-via-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous face inverse rendering methods often require synthetic data with ground truth and/or professional equipment like a lighting stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-inverse-rendering-via-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USER: Unified Semantic Enhancement with Momentum Contrast for Image-Text Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-unified-semantic-enhancement-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(2) It limits the scale of negative sample pairs by employing the mini-batch based end-to-end training mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-unified-semantic-enhancement-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CS-lol: a Dataset of Viewer Comment with Scene in E-sports Live-streaming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cs-lol-a-dataset-of-viewer-comment-with-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Billions of live-streaming viewers share their opinions on scenes they are watching in real-time and interact with the event, commentators as well as other viewers via text comments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cs-lol-a-dataset-of-viewer-comment-with-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising Diffusion Probabilistic Models as a Defense against Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-probabilistic-models-as-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Networks are infamously sensitive to small perturbations in their inputs, making them vulnerable to adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-probabilistic-models-as-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Language Models Worse than Humans at Following Prompts? It's Complicated</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-language-models-worse-than-humans-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we challenge a central assumption in such work: that humans would perform badly when given pathological instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-language-models-worse-than-humans-at</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
