<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 21:06:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mining Gaze for Contrastive Learning toward Computer-Assisted Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-gaze-for-contrastive-learning-toward</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accordingly, we introduce the Medical contrastive Gaze Image Pre-training (McGIP) as a plug-and-play module for contrastive learning frameworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-gaze-for-contrastive-learning-toward</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ControlNet-XS: Designing an Efficient and Effective Architecture for Controlling Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlnet-xs-designing-an-efficient-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this, a recent and highly popular approach is to use a controlling network, such as ControlNet, in combination with a pre-trained image generation model, such as Stable Diffusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlnet-xs-designing-an-efficient-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Naturally Aggregated Appearance for Efficient 3D Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-naturally-aggregated-appearance-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural radiance fields, which represent a 3D scene as a color field and a density field, have demonstrated great progress in novel view synthesis yet are unfavorable for editing due to the implicitness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-naturally-aggregated-appearance-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Open Set Scenarios for Skeleton-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-open-set-scenarios-for-skeleton</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In real-world scenarios, human actions often fall outside the distribution of training data, making it crucial for models to recognize known actions and reject unknown ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-open-set-scenarios-for-skeleton</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Text to Articulate Talk: Deep Text to Audiovisual Speech Synthesis achieving both Auditory and Photo-realism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-text-to-articulate-talk-deep-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method, which we call NEUral Text to ARticulate Talk (NEUTART), is a talking face generator that uses a joint audiovisual feature space, as well as speech-informed 3D facial reconstructions and a lip-reading loss for visual supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-text-to-articulate-talk-deep-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concrete Subspace Learning based Interference Elimination for Multi-task Model Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concrete-subspace-learning-based-interference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the upper level, we focus on learning a shared Concrete mask to identify the subspace, while at the inner level, model merging is performed to maximize the performance of the merged model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concrete-subspace-learning-based-interference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U-MixFormer: UNet-like Transformer with Mix-Attention for Efficient Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-mixformer-unet-like-transformer-with-mix</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation has witnessed remarkable advancements with the adaptation of the Transformer architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-mixformer-unet-like-transformer-with-mix</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STDiff: Spatio-temporal Diffusion for Continuous Stochastic Video Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stdiff-spatio-temporal-diffusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting future frames of a video is challenging because it is difficult to learn the uncertainty of the underlying factors influencing their contents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stdiff-spatio-temporal-diffusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sherpa3D: Boosting High-Fidelity Text-to-3D Generation via Coarse 3D Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sherpa3d-boosting-high-fidelity-text-to-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of retraining a costly viewpoint-aware model, we study how to fully exploit easily accessible coarse 3D knowledge to enhance the prompts and guide 2D lifting optimization for refinement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sherpa3d-boosting-high-fidelity-text-to-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IEKG: A Commonsense Knowledge Graph for Idiomatic Expressions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iekg-a-commonsense-knowledge-graph-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike prior works that enable IE comprehension through fine-tuning PTLMs with sentences containing IEs, in this work, we construct IEKG, a commonsense knowledge graph for figurative interpretations of IEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iekg-a-commonsense-knowledge-graph-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M3SOT: Multi-frame, Multi-field, Multi-space 3D Single Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3sot-multi-frame-multi-field-multi-space-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D Single Object Tracking (SOT) stands a forefront task of computer vision, proving essential for applications like autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3sot-multi-frame-multi-field-multi-space-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Meta-Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-meta-prompting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We call these approaches meta-prompting, or prompting to obtain prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-meta-prompting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compound Text-Guided Prompt Tuning via Image-Adaptive Cues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compound-text-guided-prompt-tuning-via-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce text supervision to the optimization of prompts, which enables two benefits: 1) releasing the model reliance on the pre-defined category names during inference, thereby enabling more flexible prompt generation; 2) reducing the number of inputs to the text encoder, which decreases GPU memory consumption significantly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compound-text-guided-prompt-tuning-via-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UIEDP:Underwater Image Enhancement with Diffusion Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uiedp-underwater-image-enhancement-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose UIE with Diffusion Prior (UIEDP), a novel framework treating UIE as a posterior distribution sampling process of clear images conditioned on degraded underwater inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uiedp-underwater-image-enhancement-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intraoperative 2D/3D Image Registration via Differentiable X-ray Rendering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intraoperative-2d-3d-image-registration-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Preoperatively, a CNN is trained to regress the pose of a randomly oriented synthetic X-ray rendered from the preoperative CT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intraoperative-2d-3d-image-registration-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Hierarchical Prompt with Structured Linguistic Knowledge for Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-hierarchical-prompt-with-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation and prioritize harnessing structured knowledge, this paper advocates for leveraging LLMs to build a graph for each description to model the entities and attributes describing the category, as well as their correlations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-hierarchical-prompt-with-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUST: An Effective and Scalable Framework for Multimodal Search of Target Modality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/must-an-effective-and-scalable-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the problem of multimodal search of target modality, where the task involves enhancing a query in a specific target modality by integrating information from auxiliary modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/must-an-effective-and-scalable-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoschAI @ Causal News Corpus 2023: Robust Cause-Effect Span Extraction using Multi-Layer Sequence Tagging and Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boschai-causal-news-corpus-2023-robust-cause</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding causality is a core aspect of intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boschai-causal-news-corpus-2023-robust-cause</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiAD: A Diffusion-based Framework for Multi-class Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diad-a-diffusion-based-framework-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstruction-based approaches have achieved remarkable outcomes in anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diad-a-diffusion-based-framework-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MATK: The Meme Analytical Tool Kit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matk-the-meme-analytical-tool-kit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise of social media platforms has brought about a new digital culture called memes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matk-the-meme-analytical-tool-kit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ternary Spike: Learning Ternary Spikes for Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ternary-spike-learning-ternary-spikes-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To handle the problem, we propose a ternary spike neuron to transmit information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ternary-spike-learning-ternary-spikes-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffAIL: Diffusion Adversarial Imitation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffail-diffusion-adversarial-imitation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a method named diffusion adversarial imitation learning (DiffAIL), which introduces the diffusion model into the AIL framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffail-diffusion-adversarial-imitation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GTA: Gated Toxicity Avoidance for LM Performance Preservation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gta-gated-toxicity-avoidance-for-lm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings reveal that gated toxicity avoidance efficiently achieves comparable levels of toxicity reduction to the original CTG methods while preserving the generation performance of the language model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gta-gated-toxicity-avoidance-for-lm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dense X Retrieval: What Retrieval Granularity Should We Use?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-x-retrieval-what-retrieval-granularity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discover that the retrieval unit choice significantly impacts the performance of both retrieval and downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-x-retrieval-what-retrieval-granularity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASF-YOLO: A Novel YOLO Model with Attentional Scale Sequence Fusion for Cell Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asf-yolo-a-novel-yolo-model-with-attentional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel Attentional Scale Sequence Fusion based You Only Look Once (YOLO) framework (ASF-YOLO) which combines spatial and scale features for accurate and fast cell instance segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asf-yolo-a-novel-yolo-model-with-attentional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMT-VIS: Taxonomy-aware Multi-dataset Joint Training for Video Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tmt-vis-taxonomy-aware-multi-dataset-joint-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[What we possess are numerous isolated filed-specific datasets, thus, it is appealing to jointly train models across the aggregation of datasets to enhance data volume and diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tmt-vis-taxonomy-aware-multi-dataset-joint-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attribute Annotation and Bias Evaluation in Visual Datasets for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attribute-annotation-and-bias-evaluation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the often overlooked issue of fairness in the autonomous driving domain, particularly in vision-based perception and prediction systems, which play a pivotal role in the overall functioning of Autonomous Vehicles (AVs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attribute-annotation-and-bias-evaluation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EQ-Bench: An Emotional Intelligence Benchmark for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eq-bench-an-emotional-intelligence-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce EQ-Bench, a novel benchmark designed to evaluate aspects of emotional intelligence in Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eq-bench-an-emotional-intelligence-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Connectivity-Driven Pseudo-labeling for Cross-domain Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-connectivity-driven-pseudo-labeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach formulates pseudo-labels at the connectivity level and thus can facilitate learning structured and low-noise semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-connectivity-driven-pseudo-labeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flexible visual prompts for in-context learning in computer vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-visual-prompts-for-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we propose a technique for support set selection, which involves choosing the most relevant images to include in this set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-visual-prompts-for-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proxy-based Item Representation for Attribute and Context-aware Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proxy-based-item-representation-for-attribute</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, that the proxy embeddings are shared across all items allows the infrequent items to borrow training signals of frequent items in a unified model structure and end-to-end manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proxy-based-item-representation-for-attribute</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Textual Prompt Guided Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textual-prompt-guided-image-restoration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, an effective textual prompt guided image restoration model has been proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textual-prompt-guided-image-restoration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MalPurifier: Enhancing Android Malware Detection with Adversarial Purification against Evasion Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/malpurifier-enhancing-android-malware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results on two Android malware datasets demonstrate that MalPurifier outperforms the state-of-the-art defenses, and it significantly strengthens the vulnerable malware detector against 37 evasion attacks, achieving accuracies over 90. 91%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/malpurifier-enhancing-android-malware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Prior Mask: Eliminate Redundant Action for Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-prior-mask-eliminate-redundant-action-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The large action space is one fundamental obstacle to deploying Reinforcement Learning methods in the real world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-prior-mask-eliminate-redundant-action-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSOT: Curriculum and Structure-Aware Optimal Transport for Learning with Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csot-curriculum-and-structure-aware-optimal-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the current approaches rely heavily on the model's predictions and evaluate each sample independently without considering either the global and local structure of the sample distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csot-curriculum-and-structure-aware-optimal-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurvBeNIM: The Beran-Based Neural Importance Model for Explaining the Survival Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survbenim-the-beran-based-neural-importance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A new method called the Survival Beran-based Neural Importance Model (SurvBeNIM) is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survbenim-the-beran-based-neural-importance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Label Skews in Federated Learning with Model Concatenation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-label-skews-in-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, non-IID data has been a key challenge in FL, which could significantly degrade the accuracy of the final model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-label-skews-in-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAT: Behavior-Aware Human-Like Trajectory Prediction for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bat-behavior-aware-human-like-trajectory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to accurately predict the trajectory of surrounding vehicles is a critical hurdle to overcome on the journey to fully autonomous vehicles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bat-behavior-aware-human-like-trajectory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-class Support Vector Machine with Maximizing Minimum Margin</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-class-support-vector-machine-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Support Vector Machine (SVM) stands out as a prominent machine learning technique widely applied in practical pattern recognition tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-class-support-vector-machine-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Decision Making with History-Average Dependent Costs (Extended)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-decision-making-with-history-average</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many online sequential decision-making scenarios, a learner's choices affect not just their current costs but also the future ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-decision-making-with-history-average</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Localization Is All You Evaluate: Data Leakage in Online Mapping Datasets and How to Fix It</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localization-is-all-you-evaluate-data-leakage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The state-of-the-art methods for online mapping are based on supervised learning and are trained predominantly using two datasets: nuScenes and Argoverse 2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localization-is-all-you-evaluate-data-leakage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyPE-GT: where Graph Transformers meet Hyperbolic Positional Encodings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hype-gt-where-graph-transformers-meet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Transformers (GTs) facilitate the comprehension of graph-structured data by calculating the self-attention of node pairs without considering node position information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hype-gt-where-graph-transformers-meet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EdgeSAM: Prompt-In-the-Loop Distillation for On-Device Deployment of SAM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edgesam-prompt-in-the-loop-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is also the first SAM variant that can run at over 30 FPS on an iPhone 14.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edgesam-prompt-in-the-loop-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Meta-Level Learning Algorithm for Sequential Hyper-Parameter Space Reduction in AutoML</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-meta-level-learning-algorithm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AutoML platforms have numerous options for the algorithms to try for each step of the analysis, i. e., different possible algorithms for imputation, transformations, feature selection, and modelling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-meta-level-learning-algorithm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CorresNeRF: Image Correspondence Priors for Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/corresnerf-image-correspondence-priors-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present CorresNeRF, a novel method that leverages image correspondence priors computed by off-the-shelf methods to supervise NeRF training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/corresnerf-image-correspondence-priors-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Ultra-Fine to Fine: Fine-tuning Ultra-Fine Entity Typing Models to Fine-grained</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-ultra-fine-to-fine-fine-tuning-ultra</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We can simply fine-tune the previously trained model with a small number of examples annotated under this schema.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-ultra-fine-to-fine-fine-tuning-ultra</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaCo: Targeted Concept Removal in Output Embeddings for NLP via Information Theory and Explainability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taco-targeted-concept-removal-in-output</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In evaluation, we show that the proposed post-hoc approach significantly reduces gender-related associations in NLP models while preserving the overall performance and functionality of the models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taco-targeted-concept-removal-in-output</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EasyVolcap: Accelerating Neural Volumetric Video Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyvolcap-accelerating-neural-volumetric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Volumetric video is a technology that digitally records dynamic events such as artistic performances, sporting events, and remote conversations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyvolcap-accelerating-neural-volumetric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSPNet: Scale and Spatial Priors Guided Generalizable and Interpretable Pedestrian Attribute Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sspnet-scale-and-spatial-priors-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The AFSS module learns to provide reasonable scale prior information for different attribute groups, allowing the model to focus on different levels of feature maps with varying semantic granularity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sspnet-scale-and-spatial-priors-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Subgraph-GNNs via Edge-Level Ego-Network Encodings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-subgraph-gnns-via-edge-level-ego</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel edge-level ego-network encoding for learning on graphs that can boost Message Passing Graph Neural Networks (MP-GNNs) by providing additional node and edge features or extending message-passing formats.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-subgraph-gnns-via-edge-level-ego</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
