<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:29:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Local Color Distributions Prior for Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-color-distributions-prior-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing image enhancement methods are typically designed to address either the over- or under-exposure problem in the input image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-color-distributions-prior-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlled Text Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlled-text-reduction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Producing a reduced version of a source text, as in generic or focused summarization, inherently involves two distinct subtasks: deciding on targeted content and generating a coherent text conveying it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlled-text-reduction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IQUAFLOW: A new framework to measure image quality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iquaflow-a-new-framework-to-measure-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[IQUAFLOW is a new image quality framework that provides a set of tools to assess image quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iquaflow-a-new-framework-to-measure-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-IQ: Characterizing subgroups with heterogeneous outcomes in tabular data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-iq-characterizing-subgroups-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High model performance, on average, can hide that models may systematically underperform on subgroups of the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-iq-characterizing-subgroups-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal and Independent: Multilingual Probing Framework for Exhaustive Model Interpretation and Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-and-independent-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus we propose a toolkit to systematize the multilingual flaws in multilingual models, providing a reproducible experimental setup for 104 languages and 80 morphosyntactic features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-and-independent-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAGformer: Directed Acyclic Graph Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dagformer-directed-acyclic-graph-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many fields, such as natural language processing and computer vision, the Transformer architecture has become the standard.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dagformer-directed-acyclic-graph-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precision Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precision-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore unique considerations involved in fitting ML models to data with very high precision, as is often required for science applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precision-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gallery Filter Network for Person Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gallery-filter-network-for-person-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In person search, we aim to localize a query person from one scene in other gallery scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gallery-filter-network-for-person-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual Multimodal Learning with Machine Translated Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-multimodal-learning-with-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We call this framework TD-MML: Translated Data for Multilingual Multimodal Learning, and it can be applied to any multimodal dataset and model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-multimodal-learning-with-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Object Detection in Remote Sensing Imagery with Noisy and Sparse Geo-Annotations (Full Version)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-object-detection-in-remote-sensing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to create the necessary training annotations for object detectors, imagery can be georeferenced and combined with data from other sources, such as points of interest localized by GPS sensors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-object-detection-in-remote-sensing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reliability-Aware Prediction via Uncertainty Learning for Person Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliability-aware-prediction-via-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(3) the data uncertainty and the model uncertainty are jointly learned in a unified network, and they serve as two fundamental criteria for the reliability assessment: if a probe is high-quality (low data uncertainty) and the model is confident in the prediction of the probe (low model uncertainty), the final ranking will be assessed as reliable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliability-aware-prediction-via-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiplicity-adjusted bootstrap tilting lower confidence bounds for conditional prediction performance measures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiplicity-adjusted-bootstrap-tilting-lower</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Typically, model selection and evaluation are strictly separated endeavors, splitting the sample at hand into a training, validation, and evaluation set, and only compute a single confidence interval for the prediction performance of the final selected model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiplicity-adjusted-bootstrap-tilting-lower</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focused Concatenation for Context-Aware Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focused-concatenation-for-context-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A straightforward approach to context-aware neural machine translation consists in feeding the standard encoder-decoder architecture with a window of consecutive sentences, formed by the current sentence and a number of sentences from its context concatenated to it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focused-concatenation-for-context-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cascading Biases: Investigating the Effect of Heuristic Annotation Strategies on Data and Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascading-biases-investigating-the-effect-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cognitive psychologists have documented that humans use cognitive heuristics, or mental shortcuts, to make quick decisions while expending less effort.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascading-biases-investigating-the-effect-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holistically-Attracted Wireframe Parsing: From Supervised to Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holistically-attracted-wireframe-parsing-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the core is a parsimonious representation that encodes a line segment using a closed-form 4D geometric vector, which enables lifting line segments in wireframe to an end-to-end trainable holistic attraction field that has built-in geometry-awareness, context-awareness and robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holistically-attracted-wireframe-parsing-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ares: A System-Oriented Wargame Framework for Adversarial ML</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ares-a-system-oriented-wargame-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the discovery of adversarial attacks against machine learning models nearly a decade ago, research on adversarial machine learning has rapidly evolved into an eternal war between defenders, who seek to increase the robustness of ML models against adversarial attacks, and adversaries, who seek to develop better attacks capable of weakening or defeating these defenses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ares-a-system-oriented-wargame-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaFormer Baselines for Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metaformer-baselines-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By simply applying depthwise separable convolutions as token mixer in the bottom stages and vanilla self-attention in the top stages, the resulting model CAFormer sets a new record on ImageNet-1K: it achieves an accuracy of 85. 5% at 224x224 resolution, under normal supervised training without external data or distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metaformer-baselines-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Representation Learning for Gaze Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-representation-learning-for-gaze</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, SSL exploits contrastive learning to encourage visual representations to be invariant under various image transformations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-representation-learning-for-gaze</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Different Tunes Played with Equal Skill: Exploring a Unified Optimization Subspace for Delta Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/different-tunes-played-with-equal-skill</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fathom the mystery, we hypothesize that the adaptations of different DETs could all be reparameterized as low-dimensional optimizations in a unified optimization subspace, which could be found by jointly decomposing independent solutions of different DETs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/different-tunes-played-with-equal-skill</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structural generalization is hard for sequence-to-sequence models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-generalization-is-hard-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sequence-to-sequence (seq2seq) models have been successful across many NLP tasks, including ones that require predicting linguistic structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-generalization-is-hard-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full-Text Argumentation Mining on Scientific Publications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/full-text-argumentation-mining-on-scientific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a sequential pipeline model combining ADUR and ARE for full-text SAM, and provide a first analysis of the performance of pretrained language models (PLMs) on both subtasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/full-text-argumentation-mining-on-scientific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergent world representations: Exploring a sequence model trained on a synthetic task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergent-world-representations-exploring-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models show a surprising range of capabilities, but the source of their apparent competence is unclear.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergent-world-representations-exploring-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Euphemism Detection in Few-Shot and Zero-Shot Settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-euphemism-detection-in-few-shot-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work builds upon the Euphemism Detection Shared Task proposed in the EMNLP 2022 FigLang Workshop, and extends it to few-shot and zero-shot settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-euphemism-detection-in-few-shot-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECG Artifact Removal from Single-Channel Surface EMG Using Fully Convolutional Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecg-artifact-removal-from-single-channel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Electrocardiogram (ECG) artifact contamination often occurs in surface electromyography (sEMG) applications when the measured muscles are in proximity to the heart.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecg-artifact-removal-from-single-channel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Removing Radio Frequency Interference from Auroral Kilometric Radiation with Stacked Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/removing-radio-frequency-interference-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we extended recent work in image processing to remove RFI from time-frequency spectrograms containing auroral kilometric radiation (AKR), a coherent radio emission originating from the Earth's auroral zones that is used to study astrophysical plasmas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/removing-radio-frequency-interference-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA FLARE: Federated Learning from Simulation to Real-World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nvidia-flare-federated-learning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) enables building robust and generalizable AI models by leveraging diverse datasets from multiple collaborators without centralizing the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nvidia-flare-federated-learning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Revisiting of Linguistic Knowledge Fusion in Language Understanding Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-revisiting-of-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though linguistic knowledge emerges during large-scale language model pretraining, recent work attempt to explicitly incorporate human-defined linguistic priors into task-specific fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-revisiting-of-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selecting and Composing Learning Rate Policies for Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-and-composing-learning-rate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we develop an LR tuning mechanism for auto-verification of a given LR policy with respect to the desired accuracy goal under the pre-defined training time constraint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-and-composing-learning-rate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing the Obvious: A Concreteness-based Ensemble Model for Noun Property Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualizing-the-obvious-a-concreteness-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose to extract these properties from images and use them in an ensemble model, in order to complement the information that is extracted from language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualizing-the-obvious-a-concreteness-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event-Centric Question Answering via Contrastive Learning and Invertible Event Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-centric-question-answering-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed model utilizes an invertible transformation matrix to project semantic vectors of events into a common event embedding space, trained with contrastive learning, and thus naturally inject event semantic knowledge into mainstream QA pipelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-centric-question-answering-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Discard Fixed-Window Audio Segmentation in Speech-to-Text Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-discard-fixed-window-audio-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For real-life applications, it is crucial that end-to-end spoken language translation models perform well on continuous audio, without relying on human-supplied segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-discard-fixed-window-audio-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Memo: Extractive Memorization in Constrained Sequence Generation Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-memo-extractive-memorization-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Memorization presents a challenge for several constrained Natural Language Generation (NLG) tasks such as Neural Machine Translation (NMT), wherein the proclivity of neural models to memorize noisy and atypical samples reacts adversely with the noisy (web crawled) datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-memo-extractive-memorization-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Long-Term Memory in 3D Mazes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-long-term-memory-in-3d-mazes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most benchmark tasks in reinforcement learning do not test long-term memory in agents, slowing down progress in this important research direction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-long-term-memory-in-3d-mazes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA: Neural Architecture Search and Acceleration for Hardware Inspired Hybrid Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nasa-neural-architecture-search-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiplication is arguably the most cost-dominant operation in modern deep neural networks (DNNs), limiting their achievable efficiency and thus more extensive deployment in resource-constrained applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nasa-neural-architecture-search-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subspace-based Set Operations on a Pre-trained Word Embedding Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subspace-based-set-operations-on-a-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Word embedding is a fundamental technology in natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subspace-based-set-operations-on-a-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monocular Dynamic View Synthesis: A Reality Check</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-dynamic-view-synthesis-a-reality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the recent progress on dynamic view synthesis (DVS) from monocular video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-dynamic-view-synthesis-a-reality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutual Information Alleviates Hallucinations in Abstractive Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-information-alleviates-hallucinations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant progress in the quality of language generated from abstractive summarization models, these models still exhibit the tendency to hallucinate, i. e., output content not supported by the source document.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-information-alleviates-hallucinations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anticipative Feature Fusion Transformer for Multi-Modal Action Anticipation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anticipative-feature-fusion-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although human action anticipation is a task which is inherently multi-modal, state-of-the-art methods on well known action anticipation datasets leverage this data by applying ensemble methods and averaging scores of unimodal anticipation networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anticipative-feature-fusion-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GANI: Global Attacks on Graph Neural Networks via Imperceptible Node Injections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gani-global-attacks-on-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, to make the node injections as imperceptible and effective as possible, we propose a sampling operation to determine the degree of the newly injected nodes, and then generate features and select neighbors for these injected nodes based on the statistical information of features and evolutionary perturbations obtained from a genetic algorithm, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gani-global-attacks-on-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Knowledge Graph Construction: A Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-knowledge-graph-construction-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our contributions are threefold: (1) We present a detailed, complete taxonomy for the generative KGC methods; (2) We provide a theoretical and empirical analysis of the generative KGC methods; (3) We propose several research directions that can be developed in the future.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-knowledge-graph-construction-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holistic Interaction Transformer Network for Action Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holistic-interaction-transformer-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Actions are about how we interact with the environment, including other people, objects, and ourselves.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holistic-interaction-transformer-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BotsTalk: Machine-sourced Framework for Automatic Curation of Large-scale Multi-skill Dialogue Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/botstalk-machine-sourced-framework-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To build open-domain chatbots that are able to use diverse communicative skills, we propose a novel framework BotsTalk, where multiple agents grounded to the specific target skills participate in a conversation to automatically annotate multi-skill dialogues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/botstalk-machine-sourced-framework-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Align: Learning Optimal Transport-based Alignment Dynamics for Fast and Accurate Inference on Missing Modality Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-align-learning-optimal-transport-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing multimodal tasks mostly target at the complete input modality setting, i. e., each modality is either complete or completely missing in both training and test sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-align-learning-optimal-transport-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coupling User Preference with External Rewards to Enable Driver-centered and Resource-aware EV Charging Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coupling-user-preference-with-external</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Electric Vehicle (EV) charging recommendation that both accommodates user preference and adapts to the ever-changing external environment arises as a cost-effective strategy to alleviate the range anxiety of private EV drivers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coupling-user-preference-with-external</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Non-transferable Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-non-transferable-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training a good deep learning model requires substantial data and computing resources, which makes the resulting neural model a valuable intellectual property.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-non-transferable-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Perform Complex Tasks through Compositional Fine-Tuning of Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-perform-complex-tasks-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present compositional fine-tuning (CFT): an approach based on explicitly decomposing a target task into component tasks, and then fine-tuning smaller LMs on a curriculum of such component tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-perform-complex-tasks-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Rotation in Self-Supervised Contrastive Learning: Adaptive Positive or Negative Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-rotation-in-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The semantics of an image can be rotation-invariant or rotation-variant, so whether the rotated image is treated as positive or negative should be determined based on the content of the image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-rotation-in-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model and Data Transfer for Cross-Lingual Sequence Labelling in Zero-Resource Settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-and-data-transfer-for-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zero-resource cross-lingual transfer approaches aim to apply supervised models from a source language to unlabelled target languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-and-data-transfer-for-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-document Event Coreference Search: Task, Dataset and Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-document-event-coreference-search-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of Cross-document Coreference Resolution has been traditionally formulated as requiring to identify all coreference links across a given set of documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-document-event-coreference-search-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McQueen: a Benchmark for Multimodal Conversational Query Rewrite</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcqueen-a-benchmark-for-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the task of multimodal conversational query rewrite (McQR), which performs query rewrite under the multimodal visual conversation setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcqueen-a-benchmark-for-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
