<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 21:07:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Traffic state data imputation: An efficient generating method based on the graph aggregator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-state-data-imputation-an-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Road traffic state estimation is an essential component of intelligent transportation systems (ITSs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-state-data-imputation-an-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature-Based Time-Series Analysis in R using the theft Package</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-based-time-series-analysis-in-r-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With an increasing volume and complexity of time-series datasets in the sciences and industry, theft provides a standardized framework for comprehensively quantifying and interpreting informative structure in time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-based-time-series-analysis-in-r-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Weighting Game: Evaluating Quality of Explainability Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-weighting-game-evaluating-quality-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The objective of this paper is to assess the quality of explanation heatmaps for image classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-weighting-game-evaluating-quality-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voxels Intersecting along Orthogonal Levels Attention U-Net (viola-Unet) to Segment Intracerebral Haemorrhage Using Computed Tomography Head Scans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voxels-intersecting-along-orthogonal-levels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model predictions were compared during 5-fold cross validation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voxels-intersecting-along-orthogonal-levels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Action Recommendation for Smart Home via Two-Level Encoders and Commonsense Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-action-recommendation-for-smart-home</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SmartSense then summarizes sequences of users considering queried contexts in a query-attentive manner to extract the query-related patterns from the sequential actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-action-recommendation-for-smart-home</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zeus: Understanding and Optimizing GPU Energy Consumption of DNN Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zeus-understanding-and-optimizing-gpu-energy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we observe that common practices to improve training performance can often lead to inefficient energy usage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zeus-understanding-and-optimizing-gpu-energy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Learning for OOD in Object detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-for-ood-in-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive learning is commonly applied to self-supervised learning, and has been shown to outperform traditional approaches such as the triplet loss and N-pair loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-for-ood-in-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring High-quality Target Domain Information for Unsupervised Domain Adaptive Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-high-quality-target-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such a strategy can generate the object boundaries in target domain (edge of target-domain object areas) with the correct labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-high-quality-target-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiplex Heterogeneous Graph Convolutional Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiplex-heterogeneous-graph-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Heterogeneous graph convolutional networks have gained great popularity in tackling various network analytical tasks on heterogeneous network data, ranging from link prediction to node classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiplex-heterogeneous-graph-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mining Legal Arguments in Court Decisions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-legal-arguments-in-court-decisions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identifying, classifying, and analyzing arguments in legal discourse has been a prominent area of research since the inception of the argument mining field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-legal-arguments-in-court-decisions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On deceiving malware classification with section injection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-deceiving-malware-classification-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that a mere increase of 7% in the malware size causes an accuracy drop between 25% and 40% for malware family classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-deceiving-malware-classification-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EEGNN: Edge Enhanced Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eegnn-edge-enhanced-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training deep graph neural networks (GNNs) poses a challenging task, as the performance of GNNs may suffer from the number of hidden message-passing layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eegnn-edge-enhanced-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dropout is NOT All You Need to Prevent Gradient Leakage</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dropout-is-not-all-you-need-to-prevent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that state of the art attacks are not able to reconstruct the client data due to the stochasticity induced by dropout during model training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dropout-is-not-all-you-need-to-prevent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Your Model Sensitive? SPeDaC: A New Benchmark for Detecting and Classifying Sensitive Personal Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-your-model-sensitive-spedac-a-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years we have seen the exponential growth of applications, including dialogue systems, that handle sensitive personal information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-your-model-sensitive-spedac-a-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoShard: Automated Embedding Table Sharding for Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoshard-automated-embedding-table-sharding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is a significant design challenge of distributed systems named embedding table sharding, i. e., how we should partition the embedding tables to balance the costs across devices, which is a non-trivial task because 1) it is hard to efficiently and precisely measure the cost, and 2) the partition problem is known to be NP-hard.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoshard-automated-embedding-table-sharding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety and Performance, Why not Both? Bi-Objective Optimized Model Compression toward AI Software Deployment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-and-performance-why-not-both-bi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By simulating the attack mechanism as the safety test, SafeCompress can automatically compress a big model to a small one following the dynamic sparse training paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-and-performance-why-not-both-bi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeing your sleep stage: cross-modal distillation from EEG to infrared video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seeing-your-sleep-stage-cross-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[$S^3VE$ is a large-scale dataset including synchronized infrared video and EEG signal for sleep stage classification, including 105 subjects and 154, 573 video clips that is more than 1100 hours long.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seeing-your-sleep-stage-cross-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PPMN: Pixel-Phrase Matching Network for One-Stage Panoptic Narrative Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppmn-pixel-phrase-matching-network-for-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate these drawbacks, we propose a one-stage end-to-end Pixel-Phrase Matching Network (PPMN), which directly matches each phrase to its corresponding pixels instead of region proposals and outputs panoptic segmentation by simple combination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppmn-pixel-phrase-matching-network-for-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable cytometry cell-type annotation with flow-based deep generative models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-cytometry-cell-type-annotation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cytometry enables precise single-cell phenotyping within heterogeneous populations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-cytometry-cell-type-annotation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep is a Luxury We Don't Have</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-is-a-luxury-we-don-t-have</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we tackle this complexity by leveraging a linear self-attention approximation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-is-a-luxury-we-don-t-have</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodness of Fit Metrics for Multi-class Predictor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goodness-of-fit-metrics-for-multi-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The multi-class prediction had gained popularity over recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goodness-of-fit-metrics-for-multi-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Probabilistic Framework for Mutation Testing in Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-framework-for-mutation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods: In this work, we propose a Probabilistic Mutation Testing (PMT) approach that alleviates the inconsistency problem and allows for a more consistent decision on whether a mutant is killed or not.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-framework-for-mutation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Modular Framework for Reinforcement Learning Optimal Execution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modular-framework-for-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, we develop a modular framework for the application of Reinforcement Learning to the problem of Optimal Trade Execution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modular-framework-for-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Transport Features for Morphometric Population Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-features-for-morphometric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the proposed optimal transport feature extraction step in the context of a volumetric morphometric analysis of the OASIS-1 study for Alzheimer's disease.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-features-for-morphometric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cine-AI: Generating Video Game Cutscenes in the Style of Human Directors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cine-ai-generating-video-game-cutscenes-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cutscenes form an integral part of many video games, but their creation is costly, time-consuming, and requires skills that many game developers lack.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cine-ai-generating-video-game-cutscenes-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PASS: De novo assembler for short peptide sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pass-de-novo-assembler-for-short-peptide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to characterize proteins at sequence-level resolution is vital to biological research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pass-de-novo-assembler-for-short-peptide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointTree: Transformation-Robust Point Cloud Encoder with Relaxed K-D Trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointtree-transformation-robust-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Being able to learn an effective semantic representation directly on raw point clouds has become a central topic in 3D understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointtree-transformation-robust-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family based HLA imputation and optimization of haplo-identical transplants</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/family-based-hla-imputation-and-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use GRAMM to detect recombination events and show that the rate of falsely detected recombination events (False Positive Rate) in simulations is very low.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/family-based-hla-imputation-and-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSUMNet: Unified Modality Part Streams are All You Need for Efficient Pose-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psumnet-unified-modality-part-streams-are-all</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the representation level, we propose a global frame based part stream approach as opposed to conventional modality based streams.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psumnet-unified-modality-part-streams-are-all</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heatmap Regression for Lesion Detection using Pointwise Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heatmap-regression-for-lesion-detection-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many clinical contexts, detecting all lesions is imperative for evaluating disease activity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heatmap-regression-for-lesion-detection-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled Modeling of Domain and Relevance for Adaptable Dense Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-modeling-of-domain-and-relevance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By making the REM and DAMs disentangled, DDR enables a flexible training paradigm in which REM is trained with supervision once and DAMs are trained with unsupervised data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-modeling-of-domain-and-relevance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive and Implicit Regularization for Matrix Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-and-implicit-regularization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Theoretically, we show that the adaptive regularization of \ReTwo{AIR} enhances the implicit regularization and vanishes at the end of training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-and-implicit-regularization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differencing based Self-supervised pretraining for Scene Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differencing-based-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SCD is challenging due to noisy changes in illumination, seasonal variations, and perspective differences across a pair of views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differencing-based-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>K-UNN: k-Space Interpolation With Untrained Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-unn-k-space-interpolation-with-untrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, untrained neural networks (UNNs) have shown satisfactory performances for MR image reconstruction on random sampling trajectories without using additional full-sampled training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-unn-k-space-interpolation-with-untrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Face Morphing Attack Detection via Self-paced Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-face-morphing-attack-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, given variations in the morphing attacks, the performance of supervised MAD solutions drops significantly due to the insufficient diversity and quantity of the existing MAD datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-face-morphing-attack-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TotalSegmentator: robust segmentation of 104 anatomical structures in CT images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/totalsegmentator-robust-segmentation-of-104</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we train a segmentation algorithm on this new dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/totalsegmentator-robust-segmentation-of-104</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixSKD: Self-Knowledge Distillation from Mixup for Image Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixskd-self-knowledge-distillation-from-mixup</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MixSKD mutually distills feature maps and probability distributions between the random pair of original images and their mixup images in a meaningful way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixskd-self-knowledge-distillation-from-mixup</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Re-creation of Creations: A New Paradigm for Lyric-to-Melody Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roc-a-new-paradigm-for-lyric-to-melody</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our paradigm has two stages: (1) creation stage, where a huge amount of music pieces are generated by a neural-based melody language model and indexed in a database through several key features (e. g., chords, tonality, rhythm, and structural information including chorus or verse); (2) re-creation stage, where melodies are recreated by retrieving music pieces from the database according to the key features from lyrics and concatenating best music pieces based on composition guidelines and melody language model scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roc-a-new-paradigm-for-lyric-to-melody</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Sequence-Level Training for Visual Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-sequence-level-training-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the extensive adoption of machine learning on the task of visual object tracking, recent learning-based approaches have largely overlooked the fact that visual tracking is a sequence-level task in its nature; they rely heavily on frame-level training, which inevitably induces inconsistency between training and testing in terms of both data distributions and task objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-sequence-level-training-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-Guided Face Animation by Recurrent StyleGAN-based Generator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-guided-face-animation-by-recurrent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a recurrent motion generator to extract a series of semantic and motion information from the language and feed it along with visual information to a pre-trained StyleGAN to generate high-quality frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-guided-face-animation-by-recurrent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Quantification of Sparse Travel Demand Prediction with Spatial-Temporal Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-of-sparse-travel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, spatial-temporal deep learning models demonstrate the tremendous potential to enhance prediction accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-of-sparse-travel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSAC: Bayesian Strategy Network Based Soft Actor-Critic in Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bsac-bayesian-strategy-network-based-soft</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adopting reasonable strategies is challenging but crucial for an intelligent agent with limited resources working in hazardous, unstructured, and dynamic environments to improve the system utility, decrease the overall cost, and increase mission success probability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bsac-bayesian-strategy-network-based-soft</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech Enhancement and Dereverberation with Diffusion-based Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-enhancement-and-dereverberation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we show that the proposed method achieves remarkable state-of-the-art performance in single-channel speech dereverberation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-enhancement-and-dereverberation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILAN: Masked Image Pretraining on Language Assisted Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/milan-masked-image-pretraining-on-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When the masked autoencoder is pretrained and finetuned on ImageNet-1K dataset with an input resolution of 224x224, MILAN achieves a top-1 accuracy of 85. 4% on ViTB/16, surpassing previous state-of-the-arts by 1%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/milan-masked-image-pretraining-on-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empirical investigations on WVA structural issues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-investigations-on-wva-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we want to present the results of empirical verification of some issues concerning the methods for overcoming catastrophic forgetting in neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-investigations-on-wva-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Specific Text Generation for Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-specific-text-generation-for-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Preservation of domain knowledge from the source to target is crucial in any translation workflow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-specific-text-generation-for-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularizing Deep Neural Networks with Stochastic Estimators of Hessian Trace</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-deep-neural-networks-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we develop a novel regularization method for deep neural networks by penalizing the trace of Hessian.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-deep-neural-networks-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Self-adaptation: Enhancing Generalization with a Single Sample</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-self-adaptation-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we challenge this premise with a self-adaptive approach for semantic segmentation that adjusts the inference process to each input sample.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-self-adaptation-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Inference of Temporal Logic Formulas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-inference-of-temporal-logic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is great interest in learning formal specifications that characterize the ideal behavior of such systems -- that is, formulas in temporal logic that are satisfied by the system's output signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-inference-of-temporal-logic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for a Needle in a Haystack: A Comprehensive Study of Hallucinations in Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-for-a-needle-in-a-haystack-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the problem of hallucinations in neural machine translation (NMT) has received some attention, research on this highly pathological phenomenon lacks solid ground.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-for-a-needle-in-a-haystack-a</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
