<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 03:56:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and Robust 2D-to-BEV Representation Learning via Geometry-guided Kernel Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-robust-2d-to-bev-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GKT leverages the geometric priors to guide the transformer to focus on discriminative regions and unfolds kernel features to generate BEV representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-robust-2d-to-bev-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VITA: Video Instance Segmentation via Object Token Association</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vita-video-instance-segmentation-via-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we use an image object detector as a means of distilling object-specific contexts into object tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vita-video-instance-segmentation-via-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicit Regularization in Overparametrized Models via Noise Injection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-regularization-in-overparametrized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Injecting noise within gradient descent has several desirable features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-regularization-in-overparametrized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiSparse: Disentangled Sparsification for Multitask Model Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disparse-disentangled-sparsification-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyzed the pruning masks generated with DiSparse and observed strikingly similar sparse network architecture identified by each task even before the training starts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disparse-disentangled-sparsification-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Prompt Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-prompt-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The size of vision models has grown exponentially over the last few years, especially after the emergence of Vision Transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-prompt-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BigVGAN: A Universal Neural Vocoder with Large-Scale Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bigvgan-a-universal-neural-vocoder-with-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent progress in generative adversarial network(GAN)-based vocoders, where the model generates raw waveform conditioned on mel spectrogram, it is still challenging to synthesize high-fidelity audio for numerous speakers across varied recording environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bigvgan-a-universal-neural-vocoder-with-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Layer-wise Image Vectorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-layer-wise-image-vectorization-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image rasterization is a mature technique in computer graphics, while image vectorization, the reverse path of rasterization, remains a major challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-layer-wise-image-vectorization-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distillation Decision Tree</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-decision-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With well-known advantages in interpretation, decision tree is a competitive candidate of the transparent model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-decision-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Relational Intervention Approach for Unsupervised Dynamics Generalization in Model-Based Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-relational-intervention-approach-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, because environments are not labelled, the extracted information inevitably contains redundant information unrelated to the dynamics in transition segments and thus fails to maintain a crucial property of $Z$: $Z$ should be similar in the same environment and dissimilar in different ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-relational-intervention-approach-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analytical Composition of Differential Privacy via the Edgeworth Accountant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analytical-composition-of-differential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many modern machine learning algorithms are composed of simple private algorithms; thus, an increasingly important problem is to efficiently compute the overall privacy loss under composition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analytical-composition-of-differential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointNeXt: Revisiting PointNet++ with Improved Training and Scaling Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointnext-revisiting-pointnet-with-improved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we revisit the classical PointNet++ through a systematic study of model training and scaling strategies, and offer two major contributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointnext-revisiting-pointnet-with-improved</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Spatiotemporal Representation Learning for Longitudinally-consistent Neuroimage Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-spatiotemporal-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent self-supervised advances in medical computer vision exploit global and local anatomical self-similarity for pretraining prior to downstream tasks such as segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-spatiotemporal-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Margins and Generalisation for Voting Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-margins-and-generalisation-for-voting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the generalisation properties of majority voting on finite ensembles of classifiers, proving margin-based generalisation bounds via the PAC-Bayes theory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-margins-and-generalisation-for-voting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neo-GNNs: Neighborhood Overlap-aware Graph Neural Networks for Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neo-gnns-neighborhood-overlap-aware-graph-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have been widely applied to various fields for learning over graph-structured data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neo-gnns-neighborhood-overlap-aware-graph-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAR Despeckling using a Denoising Diffusion Probabilistic Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sar-despeckling-using-a-denoising-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The despeckled image is recovered by a reverse process which iteratively predicts the added noise using a noise predictor which is conditioned on the speckled image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sar-despeckling-using-a-denoising-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STIP: A SpatioTemporal Information-Preserving and Perception-Augmented Model for High-Resolution Video Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stip-a-spatiotemporal-information-preserving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve the information loss problem, the proposed model aims to preserve the spatiotemporal information for videos during the feature extraction and the state transitions, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stip-a-spatiotemporal-information-preserving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Identification for Austronesian Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-identification-for-austronesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper provides language identification models for low- and under-resourced languages in the Pacific region with a focus on previously unavailable Austronesian languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-identification-for-austronesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Node Feature Estimation with Structured Variational Graph Autoencoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-node-feature-estimation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a graph with partial observations of node features, how can we estimate the missing features accurately?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-node-feature-estimation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Attention Multi-Layer Perceptron</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-attention-multi-layer-perceptron-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) have achieved great success in many graph-based applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-attention-multi-layer-perceptron-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the Imitation Game: Quantifying and extrapolating the capabilities of language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-the-imitation-game-quantifying-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BIG-bench focuses on tasks that are believed to be beyond the capabilities of current language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-the-imitation-game-quantifying-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xplique: A Deep Learning Explainability Toolbox</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xplique-a-deep-learning-explainability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today's most advanced machine-learning models are hardly scrutable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xplique-a-deep-learning-explainability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOAM: A Follower-aware Speaker Model For Vision-and-Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foam-a-follower-aware-speaker-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The speaker-follower models have proven to be effective in vision-and-language navigation, where a speaker model is used to synthesize new instructions to augment the training data for a follower navigation model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foam-a-follower-aware-speaker-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFA: Coupled-hypersphere-based Feature Adaptation for Target-Oriented Anomaly Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfa-coupled-hypersphere-based-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, this paper points out the negative effects of biased features of pre-trained CNNs and emphasizes the importance of the adaptation to the target dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfa-coupled-hypersphere-based-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crosslinguistic word order variation reflects evolutionary pressures of dependency and information locality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crosslinguistic-word-order-variation-reflects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using data from 80 languages in 17 language families and phylogenetic modeling, we demonstrate that languages evolve to balance these pressures, such that word order change is accompanied by change in the frequency distribution of the syntactic structures which speakers communicate to maintain overall efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crosslinguistic-word-order-variation-reflects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An FPGA-based Solution for Convolution Operation Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-fpga-based-solution-for-convolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hardware-based acceleration is an extensive attempt to facilitate many computationally-intensive mathematics operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-fpga-based-solution-for-convolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlearning Protected User Attributes in Recommendations with Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlearning-protected-user-attributes-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct experiments on the MovieLens-1M and LFM-2b-DemoBias datasets, and evaluate the effectiveness of the bias mitigation method based on the inability of external attackers in revealing the users' gender information from the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlearning-protected-user-attributes-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGConv: Adaptive Graph Convolution on 3D Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agconv-adaptive-graph-convolution-on-3d-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Adaptive Graph Convolution (AGConv) for wide applications of point cloud analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agconv-adaptive-graph-convolution-on-3d-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Loss Matters in Weakly Supervised Multi-Label Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-loss-matters-in-weakly-supervised-multi-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we first regard unobserved labels as negative labels, casting the WSML task into noisy multi-label classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-loss-matters-in-weakly-supervised-multi-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Diffusion Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-diffusion-processes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gaussian processes provide an elegant framework for specifying prior and posterior distributions over functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-diffusion-processes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Myocardial Motion Tracking via Latent Space Exploration with Biomechanics-informed Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-myocardial-motion-tracking-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to most existing approaches which impose explicit generic regularization such as smoothness, in this work we propose a novel method that can implicitly learn an application-specific biomechanics-informed prior and embed it into a neural network-parameterized transformation model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-myocardial-motion-tracking-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled Ontology Embedding for Zero-shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-ontology-embedding-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on ontologies for augmenting ZSL, and propose to learn disentangled ontology embeddings guided by ontology properties to capture and utilize more fine-grained class relationships in different aspects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-ontology-embedding-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Fusion Mixture-of-Experts are Domain Generalizable Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-fusion-mixture-of-experts-are-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose Sparse Fusion Mixture-of-Experts (SF-MoE), which incorporates sparsity and fusion mechanisms into the MoE framework to keep the model both sparse and predictive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-fusion-mixture-of-experts-are-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blind Face Restoration: Benchmark Datasets and a Baseline Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-face-restoration-benchmark-datasets-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we first synthesize two blind face restoration benchmark datasets called EDFace-Celeb-1M (BFR128) and EDFace-Celeb-150K (BFR512).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-face-restoration-benchmark-datasets-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SYNERgy between SYNaptic consolidation and Experience Replay for general continual learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synergy-between-synaptic-consolidation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual learning (CL) in the brain is facilitated by a complex set of mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synergy-between-synaptic-consolidation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mathematical model bridges disparate timescales of lifelong learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathematical-model-bridges-disparate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model connects previously disparate timescales -- and the subdisciplines that typically study each timescale in isolation -- to offer a unified account of the timecourse of skill acquisition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathematical-model-bridges-disparate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling strokes in fast neural style transfer using content transforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-strokes-in-fast-neural-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demonstrate the real-world applicability of our approach, we present StyleTune, a mobile app for interactive editing of neural style transfers at multiple levels of control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-strokes-in-fast-neural-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedHPO-B: A Benchmark Suite for Federated Hyperparameter Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedhpo-b-a-benchmark-suite-for-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to this uniqueness, existing HPO benchmarks no longer satisfy the need to compare HPO methods in the FL setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedhpo-b-a-benchmark-suite-for-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Self-supervised and Weight-preserving Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-self-supervised-and-weight-preserving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose the self-supervised and weight-preserving neural architecture search (SSWP-NAS) as an extension of the current NAS framework by allowing the self-supervision and retaining the concomitant weights discovered during the search stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-self-supervised-and-weight-preserving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCAMPS: Synthetics for Camera Measurement of Physiological Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scamps-synthetics-for-camera-measurement-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The use of cameras and computational algorithms for noninvasive, low-cost and scalable measurement of physiological (e. g., cardiac and pulmonary) vital signs is very attractive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scamps-synthetics-for-camera-measurement-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Distribution Discrepancy for Anomaly Detection in Chest X-Rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-distribution-discrepancy-for-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During training, module A takes both known normal and unlabeled images as inputs, capturing anomalous features from unlabeled images in some way, while module B models the distribution of only known normal images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-distribution-discrepancy-for-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Learning of 3D Scene Flow from Monocular Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-of-3d-scene-flow-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised learning of scene flow in this paper mainly consists of two parts: (i) depth estimation and camera pose estimation, and (ii) scene flow estimation based on four different loss functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-of-3d-scene-flow-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing Reinforcement Learning Algorithms for Digital Interventions: Pre-implementation Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designing-reinforcement-learning-algorithms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online reinforcement learning (RL) algorithms are increasingly used to personalize digital interventions in the fields of mobile health and online education.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designing-reinforcement-learning-algorithms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pFL-Bench: A Comprehensive Benchmark for Personalized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pfl-bench-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized Federated Learning (pFL) has gained increasing attention in recent years due to its success in handling the statistical heterogeneity of FL clients via utilizing and deploying distinct local models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pfl-bench-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoregressive Perturbations for Data Poisoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-perturbations-for-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, existing methods require knowledge of both the target architecture and the complete dataset so that a surrogate network can be trained, the parameters of which are used to generate the attack.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-perturbations-for-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sampling-based techniques for designing school boundaries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampling-based-techniques-for-designing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by these recent developments, we develop a set of similar sampling techniques for designing school boundaries based on the flip proposal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampling-based-techniques-for-designing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wavelet Regularization Benefits Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavelet-regularization-benefits-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since adversarial vulnerability can be regarded as a high-frequency phenomenon, it is essential to regulate the adversarially-trained neural network models in the frequency domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavelet-regularization-benefits-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metric Based Few-Shot Graph Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metric-based-few-shot-graph-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we tackle the problem of few-shot graph classification, showing that equipping a simple distance metric learning baseline with a state-of-the-art graph embedder allows to obtain competitive results on the task. While the simplicity of the architecture is enough to outperform more complex ones, it also allows straightforward additions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metric-based-few-shot-graph-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proactively Reducing the Hate Intensity of Online Posts via Hate Speech Normalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proactively-reducing-the-hate-intensity-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Curbing online hate speech has become the need of the hour; however, a blanket ban on such activities is infeasible for several geopolitical and cultural reasons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proactively-reducing-the-hate-intensity-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Deformable Image Registration with Absent Correspondences in Pre-operative and Post-Recurrence Brain Tumor MRI Scans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-deformable-image-registration-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Registration of pre-operative and post-recurrence brain images is often needed to evaluate the effectiveness of brain gliomas treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-deformable-image-registration-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Boundary-guided Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-boundary-guided-adversarial-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial training is proved to be the most effective strategy that injects adversarial examples into model training to improve the robustness of DNN models to adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-boundary-guided-adversarial-training</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
