<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 21:07:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Responsible Visual Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/responsible-visual-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the negative implications of harmful images on research, we create a transparent and public dataset, AltBear, which expresses harmful information using teddy bears instead of humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/responsible-visual-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpreting Themes from Educational Stories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-themes-from-educational-stories</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reading comprehension continues to be a crucial research focus in the NLP community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-themes-from-educational-stories</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptAD: Learning Prompts with only Normal Samples for Few-Shot Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptad-learning-prompts-with-only-normal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The vision-language model has brought great improvement to few-shot industrial anomaly detection, which usually needs to design of hundreds of prompts through prompt engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptad-learning-prompts-with-only-normal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoT: Enhancing Large Language Models with Reflection on Search Trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rot-enhancing-large-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It uses a strong LLM to summarize guidelines from previous tree search experiences to enhance the ability of a weak LLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rot-enhancing-large-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Normalizing Flows on the Product Space of SO(3) Manifolds for Probabilistic Human Pose Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normalizing-flows-on-the-product-space-of-so</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Normalizing flows have proven their efficacy for density estimation in Euclidean space, but their application to rotational representations, crucial in various domains such as robotics or human pose modeling, remains underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normalizing-flows-on-the-product-space-of-so</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-DEED: Temporal-Discriminability Enhancer Encoder-Decoder for Precise Event Spotting in Sports Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-deed-temporal-discriminability-enhancer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce T-DEED, a Temporal-Discriminability Enhancer Encoder-Decoder for Precise Event Spotting in sports videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-deed-temporal-discriminability-enhancer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cell-Free Multi-User MIMO Equalization via In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cell-free-multi-user-mimo-equalization-via-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we demonstrate that ICL can be also used to tackle the problem of multi-user equalization in cell-free MIMO systems with limited fronthaul capacity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cell-free-multi-user-mimo-equalization-via-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DepthMOT: Depth Cues Lead to a Strong Multi-Object Tracker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depthmot-depth-cues-lead-to-a-strong-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by this, even though the bounding boxes of objects are close on the camera plane, we can differentiate them in the depth dimension, thereby establishing a 3D perception of the objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depthmot-depth-cues-lead-to-a-strong-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have You Merged My Model? On The Robustness of Large Language Model IP Protection Methods Against Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/have-you-merged-my-model-on-the-robustness-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model merging is a promising lightweight model empowerment technique that does not rely on expensive computing devices (e. g., GPUs) or require the collection of specific training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/have-you-merged-my-model-on-the-robustness-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpeechAlign: Aligning Speech Generation to Human Preferences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechalign-aligning-speech-generation-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the integration of human feedback to align speech outputs to human preferences is often neglected.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechalign-aligning-speech-generation-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGSDF: Continual Global Learning of Signed Distance Fields Aided by Local Updating</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgsdf-continual-global-learning-of-signed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implicit reconstruction of ESDF (Euclidean Signed Distance Field) involves training a neural network to regress the signed distance from any point to the nearest obstacle, which has the advantages of lightweight storage and continuous querying.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgsdf-continual-global-learning-of-signed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HSViT: Horizontally Scalable Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hsvit-horizontally-scalable-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the Vision Transformer (ViT) architecture gains prominence in computer vision and attracts significant attention from multimedia communities, its deficiency in prior knowledge (inductive bias) regarding shift, scale, and rotational invariance necessitates pre-training on large-scale datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hsvit-horizontally-scalable-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoCodeRover: Autonomous Program Improvement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autocoderover-autonomous-program-improvement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in Large Language Models (LLMs) has significantly impacted the development process, where developers can use LLM-based programming assistants to achieve automated coding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autocoderover-autonomous-program-improvement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAF-DPM: A Nonlinear Activation-Free Diffusion Probabilistic Model for Document Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naf-dpm-a-nonlinear-activation-free-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-world documents may suffer various forms of degradation, often resulting in lower accuracy in optical character recognition (OCR) systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naf-dpm-a-nonlinear-activation-free-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Quantization and Mapping Synergy in Hardware-Aware Deep Neural Network Accelerators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-quantization-and-mapping-synergy-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Energy efficiency and memory footprint of a convolutional neural network (CNN) implemented on a CNN inference accelerator depend on many factors, including a weight quantization strategy (i. e., data types and bit-widths) and mapping (i. e., placement and scheduling of DNN elementary operations on hardware units of the accelerator).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-quantization-and-mapping-synergy-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-Augmented Open-Vocabulary Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-open-vocabulary-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, RALF consists of two modules: Retrieval Augmented Losses (RAL) and Retrieval-Augmented visual Features (RAF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-open-vocabulary-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Mathematical Reasoning Beyond Accuracy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-mathematical-reasoning-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To measure reasoning beyond final-answer accuracy, we introduce ReasonEval, a new methodology for evaluating the quality of reasoning steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-mathematical-reasoning-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Monocular 3D Detectors with LiDAR from the Past</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-monocular-3d-detectors-with-lidar-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate 3D object detection is crucial to autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-monocular-3d-detectors-with-lidar-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MealRec$^+$: A Meal Recommendation Dataset with Meal-Course Affiliation for Personalization and Healthiness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mealrec-a-meal-recommendation-dataset-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to constraints related to user health privacy and meal scenario characteristics, the collection of data that includes both meal-course affiliation and two levels of interactions is impeded.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mealrec-a-meal-recommendation-dataset-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATFNet: Adaptive Time-Frequency Ensembled Network for Long-term Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atfnet-adaptive-time-frequency-ensembled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To capitalize on both of these strengths, we propose ATFNet, an innovative framework that combines a time domain module and a frequency domain module to concurrently capture local and global dependencies in time series data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atfnet-adaptive-time-frequency-ensembled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SafetyPrompts: a Systematic Review of Open Datasets for Evaluating and Improving Large Language Model Safety</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safetyprompts-a-systematic-review-of-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers and practitioners have met these concerns by introducing an abundance of new datasets for evaluating and improving LLM safety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safetyprompts-a-systematic-review-of-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GloSoFarID: Global multispectral dataset for Solar Farm IDentification in satellite imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glosofarid-global-multispectral-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Solar Photovoltaic (PV) technology is increasingly recognized as a pivotal solution in the global pursuit of clean and renewable energy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glosofarid-global-multispectral-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Task Learning for Features Extraction in Financial Annual Reports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-features-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For assessing various performance indicators of companies, the focus is shifting from strictly financial (quantitative) publicly disclosed information to qualitative (textual) information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-features-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOEG: A New Approach for Object-Centric Predictive Process Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hoeg-a-new-approach-for-object-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To leverage this enriched data, we propose the Heterogeneous Object Event Graph encoding (HOEG), which integrates events and objects into a graph structure with diverse node types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hoeg-a-new-approach-for-object-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class Similarity Transition: Decoupling Class Similarities and Imbalance from Generalized Few-shot Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-similarity-transition-decoupling-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper focuses on the relevance between base and novel classes, and improves GFSS in two aspects: 1) mining the similarity between base and novel classes to promote the learning of novel classes, and 2) mitigating the class imbalance issue caused by the volume difference between the support set and the training set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-similarity-transition-decoupling-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flexible Fairness Learning via Inverse Conditional Permutation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-fairness-learning-via-inverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Equalized odds, as a popular notion of algorithmic fairness, aims to ensure that sensitive variables, such as race and gender, do not unfairly influence the algorithm prediction when conditioning on the true outcome.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-fairness-learning-via-inverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Spatial Inconsistency in Classifier-Free Diffusion Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-spatial-inconsistency-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Classifier-Free Guidance (CFG) has been widely used in text-to-image diffusion models, where the CFG scale is introduced to control the strength of text guidance on the whole image space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-spatial-inconsistency-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Sequence Labeling with Semi-Supervised Boundary-Aware Language Model Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chinese-sequence-labeling-with-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results on Chinese sequence labeling datasets demonstrate that the improved BABERT variant outperforms the vanilla version, not only on these tasks but also more broadly across a range of Chinese natural language understanding tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chinese-sequence-labeling-with-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-agent Long-term 3D Human Pose Forecasting via Interaction-aware Trajectory Conditioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-long-term-3d-human-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model effectively handles the multi-modality of human motion and the complexity of long-term multi-agent interactions, improving performance in complex environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-long-term-3d-human-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Refinement Strategy for Automated Data Labeling: Facial Landmark Diagnosis in Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-refinement-strategy-for-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated data labeling techniques are crucial for accelerating the development of deep learning models, particularly in complex medical imaging applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-refinement-strategy-for-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LayoutLLM: Layout Instruction Tuning with Large Language Models for Document Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layoutllm-layout-instruction-tuning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core of LayoutLLM is a layout instruction tuning strategy, which is specially designed to enhance the comprehension and utilization of document layouts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layoutllm-layout-instruction-tuning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tree Search-Based Policy Optimization under Stochastic Execution Delay</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-search-based-policy-optimization-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that given observed delay values, it is sufficient to perform a policy search in the class of Markov policies in order to reach optimal performance, thus extending the deterministic fixed delay case.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-search-based-policy-optimization-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming Transformers for Realistic Lidar Point Cloud Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-transformers-for-realistic-lidar-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion Models (DMs) have achieved State-Of-The-Art (SOTA) results in the Lidar point cloud generation task, benefiting from their stable training and iterative refinement during sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-transformers-for-realistic-lidar-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIM: A Time Interval Machine for Audio-Visual Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tim-a-time-interval-machine-for-audio-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the interplay between the two modalities in long videos by explicitly modelling the temporal extents of audio and visual events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tim-a-time-interval-machine-for-audio-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITA-ECBS: A Bounded-Suboptimal Algorithm for Combined Target-Assignment and Path-Finding Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ita-ecbs-a-bounded-suboptimal-algorithm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-Agent Path Finding (MAPF), i. e., finding collision-free paths for multiple robots, plays a critical role in many applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ita-ecbs-a-bounded-suboptimal-algorithm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Data Pruning: Uncovering and Overcoming Implicit Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-data-pruning-uncovering-and-overcoming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, little is known about its impact on classification bias of the trained models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-data-pruning-uncovering-and-overcoming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Optics for Video Snapshot Compressive Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-optics-for-video-snapshot-compressive-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe this is a milestone for real-world video SCI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-optics-for-video-snapshot-compressive-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David and Goliath: An Empirical Evaluation of Attacks and Defenses for QNNs at the Deep Edge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/david-and-goliath-an-empirical-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill this gap, we empirically evaluate the effectiveness of attacks and defenses from (full-precision) ANNs on (constrained) QNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/david-and-goliath-an-empirical-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fighting crime with Transformers: Empirical analysis of address parsing methods in payment data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fighting-crime-with-transformers-empirical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the emergence of Transformers and Generative Large Language Models (LLM), we explore the performance of state-of-the-art solutions given the constraint of processing a vast amount of daily data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fighting-crime-with-transformers-empirical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-Temporal Attention and Gaussian Processes for Personalized Video Gaze Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-attention-and-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, our approach integrates Gaussian processes to include individual-specific traits, facilitating the personalization of our model with just a few labeled samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-attention-and-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MindSet: Vision. A toolbox for testing DNNs on key psychological experiments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mindset-vision-a-toolbox-for-testing-dnns-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiple benchmarks have been developed to assess the alignment between deep neural networks (DNNs) and human vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mindset-vision-a-toolbox-for-testing-dnns-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Evaluate Entity Resolution Systems: An Entity-Centric Framework with Application to Inventor Name Disambiguation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-evaluate-entity-resolution-systems-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These benchmark data sets can then be used for model training and a variety of evaluation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-evaluate-entity-resolution-systems-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models on a Diet: Cost-Efficient Development of Encoders for Closely-Related Languages via Additional Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-on-a-diet-cost-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The world of language models is going through turbulent times, better and ever larger models are coming out at an unprecedented speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-on-a-diet-cost-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Every Object from Events</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-every-object-from-events</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object detection is critical in autonomous driving, and it is more practical yet challenging to localize objects of unknown categories: an endeavour known as Class-Agnostic Object Detection (CAOD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-every-object-from-events</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated discovery of symbolic laws governing skill acquisition from naturally occurring data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-discovery-of-symbolic-laws</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Skill acquisition is a key area of research in cognitive psychology as it encompasses multiple psychological processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-discovery-of-symbolic-laws</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technical Report: The Graph Spectral Token -- Enhancing Graph Transformers with Spectral Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/technical-report-the-graph-spectral-token</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Transformers have emerged as a powerful alternative to Message-Passing Graph Neural Networks (MP-GNNs) to address limitations such as over-squashing of information exchange.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/technical-report-the-graph-spectral-token</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Diffusion Model for Multi-Contrast MRI Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-diffusion-model-for-multi-contrast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, diffusion models (DM) have been applied in magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) super-resolution (SR) reconstruction, exhibiting impressive performance, especially with regard to detailed reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-diffusion-model-for-multi-contrast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Stream Sampling with Fuzzy Task Boundaries and Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-stream-sampling-with-fuzzy-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of continual learning, the presence of noisy labels within data streams represents a notable obstacle to model reliability and fairness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-stream-sampling-with-fuzzy-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camera-Based Remote Physiology Sensing for Hundreds of Subjects Across Skin Tones</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camera-based-remote-physiology-sensing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remote photoplethysmography (rPPG) emerges as a promising method for non-invasive, convenient measurement of vital signs, utilizing the widespread presence of cameras.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camera-based-remote-physiology-sensing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensorized Ant Colony Optimization for GPU Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensorized-ant-colony-optimization-for-gpu</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the tensorization of ant system, we propose a preprocessing method to reduce the computational overhead by calculating the probability transition matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensorized-ant-colony-optimization-for-gpu</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
