<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 09:17:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>VersaGen: Unleashing Versatile Visual Control for Text-to-Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/versagen-unleashing-versatile-visual-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the rapid advancements in text-to-image (T2I) synthesis, enabling precise visual control remains a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/versagen-unleashing-versatile-visual-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMI-Net: Adaptive Mask Inpainting Network for Industrial Anomaly Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ami-net-adaptive-mask-inpainting-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this manner, the model can leverage the visible normal global contextual information to restore the masked anomalous regions, thereby effectively suppressing the reconstruction of defects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ami-net-adaptive-mask-inpainting-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNN Applied to Ego-nets for Friend Suggestions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnn-applied-to-ego-nets-for-friend</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we develop the WalkGNN model which is capable of working effectively in the social network domain, where these graph-level link prediction tasks are heterogeneous, dynamic and featureless.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnn-applied-to-ego-nets-for-friend</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vertical Federated Unlearning via Backdoor Certification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vertical-federated-unlearning-via-backdoor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an innovative modification to traditional VFL by employing a mechanism that inverts the typical learning trajectory with the objective of extracting specific data contributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vertical-federated-unlearning-via-backdoor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RL-LLM-DT: An Automatic Decision Tree Generation Method Based on RL Evaluation and LLM Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-llm-dt-an-automatic-decision-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After iterative refinements, our curling AI based on the decision tree ranks first on the Jidi platform among 34 curling AIs in total, which demonstrates that LLMs can significantly enhance the robustness and adaptability of decision trees, representing a substantial advancement in the field of Game AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-llm-dt-an-automatic-decision-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Domain Adaptive Object Detection via Dual Probabilistic Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-domain-adaptive-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[IDSA utilizes instance-level sampling to mine domain-shared category samples and calculates alignment weight through Gaussian distribution to conduct the domain-shared category domain alignment to address the feature heterogeneity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-domain-adaptive-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just a Simple Transformation is Enough for Data Protection in Vertical Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/just-a-simple-transformation-is-enough-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vertical Federated Learning (VFL) aims to enable collaborative training of deep learning models while maintaining privacy protection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/just-a-simple-transformation-is-enough-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D$^2$-Actor: Learning Pose-Conditioned 3D-Aware Denoiser for Realistic Gaussian Avatar Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-2-actor-learning-pose-conditioned-3d-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advancements in neural implicit representations and differentiable rendering have markedly improved the ability to learn animatable 3D avatars from sparse multi-view RGB videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-2-actor-learning-pose-conditioned-3d-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biased or Flawed? Mitigating Stereotypes in Generative Language Models by Addressing Task-Specific Flaws</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biased-or-flawed-mitigating-stereotypes-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, when a model misinterprets a text and produces a response that reinforces a stereotype, it becomes difficult to determine whether the issue arises from inherent bias or from a misunderstanding of the given content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biased-or-flawed-mitigating-stereotypes-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedCAR: Cross-client Adaptive Re-weighting for Generative Models in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedcar-cross-client-adaptive-re-weighting-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative models trained on multi-institutional datasets can provide an enriched understanding through diverse data distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedcar-cross-client-adaptive-re-weighting-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPGL: Enhancing Session-based Recommendation with Single Positive Graph Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spgl-enhancing-session-based-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It also takes into account the reverse positional information of items when constructing session representations to incorporate temporal information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spgl-enhancing-session-based-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-View Geo-Localization with Street-View and VHR Satellite Imagery in Decentrality Settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-view-geo-localization-with-street-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BIM uses bird's-eye view images derived from street-view panoramas as an intermediary, simplifying the cross-view challenge with decentrality to a cross-view problem and a decentrality problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-view-geo-localization-with-street-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vocabulary Expansion of Chat Models with Unlabeled Target Language Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vocabulary-expansion-of-chat-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the impact of using unlabeled target language data for VE on chat models for the first time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vocabulary-expansion-of-chat-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPaR: Self-Play with Tree-Search Refinement to Improve Instruction-Following in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spar-self-play-with-tree-search-refinement-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such practice can introduce content variations irrelevant to whether the instruction is precisely followed (e. g., different expressions about the same semantic), interfering with the goal of teaching models to recognize the key differences that lead to improved instruction following.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spar-self-play-with-tree-search-refinement-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Diffusion Transformers for Generative Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-diffusion-transformers-for-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Causal Diffusion as the autoregressive (AR) counterpart of Diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-diffusion-transformers-for-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Method for Detecting Legal Article Competition for Korean Criminal Law Using a Case-augmented Mention Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-method-for-detecting-legal-article</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As social systems become increasingly complex, legal articles are also growing more intricate, making it progressively harder for humans to identify any potential competitions among them, particularly when drafting new laws or applying existing laws.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-method-for-detecting-legal-article</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoX: Geometric Problem Solving Through Unified Formalized Vision-Language Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geox-geometric-problem-solving-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the significant differences between geometric diagram-symbol and natural image-text, we introduce unimodal pre-training to develop a diagram encoder and symbol decoder, enhancing the understanding of geometric images and corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geox-geometric-problem-solving-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-modal and Multi-scale Spatial Environment Understanding for Immersive Visual Text-to-Speech</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-and-multi-scale-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The multi-modal aims to take both the RGB and Depth spaces of the spatial image to learn more comprehensive spatial information, and the multi-scale seeks to model the local and global spatial knowledge simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-and-multi-scale-spatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlphaZero Neural Scaling and Zipf's Law: a Tale of Board Games and Power Laws</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alphazero-neural-scaling-and-zipf-s-law-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent theories suggest that loss power laws arise from Zipf's law, a power law observed in domains like natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alphazero-neural-scaling-and-zipf-s-law-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring Functionality of Attention Heads from their Parameters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-functionality-of-attention-heads</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We showcase the utility of MAPS for answering two types of questions: (a) given a predefined operation, mapping how strongly heads across the model implement it, and (b) given an attention head, inferring its salient functionality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-functionality-of-attention-heads</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized LLM for Generating Customized Responses to the Same Query from Different Users</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-llm-for-generating-customized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing work on large language model (LLM) personalization assigned different responding roles to LLM, but overlooked the diversity of questioners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-llm-for-generating-customized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDEA-Bench: How Far are Generative Models from Professional Designing?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idea-bench-how-far-are-generative-models-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-world design tasks - such as picture book creation, film storyboard development using character sets, photo retouching, visual effects, and font transfer - are highly diverse and complex, requiring deep interpretation and extraction of various elements from instructions, descriptions, and reference images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idea-bench-how-far-are-generative-models-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wonderful Matrices: Combining for a More Efficient and Effective Foundation Model Architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wonderful-matrices-combining-for-a-more</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to make the foundation model more efficient and effective, our idea is combining sequence transformation and state transformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wonderful-matrices-combining-for-a-more</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SciFaultyQA: Benchmarking LLMs on Faulty Science Question Detection with a GAN-Inspired Approach to Synthetic Dataset Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scifaultyqa-benchmarking-llms-on-faulty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By analyzing such patterns, we developed a novel method for generating synthetic datasets to evaluate and benchmark the performance of various LLMs in identifying these flawed questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scifaultyqa-benchmarking-llms-on-faulty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BetaExplainer: A Probabilistic Method to Explain Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/betaexplainer-a-probabilistic-method-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) are powerful tools for conducting inference on graph data but are often seen as "black boxes" due to difficulty in extracting meaningful subnetworks driving predictive performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/betaexplainer-a-probabilistic-method-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does it Chug? Towards a Data-Driven Understanding of Guitar Tone Description</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-it-chug-towards-a-data-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we pursue a data-driven approach to further our understanding of such adjectives in the context of guitar tone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-it-chug-towards-a-data-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Region-Based Optimization in Continual Learning for Audio Deepfake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/region-based-optimization-in-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a continual learning method named Region-Based Optimization (RegO) for audio deepfake detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/region-based-optimization-in-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAIR: Manipulating Collaborative and Multimodal Information for E-Commerce Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stair-manipulating-collaborative-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to combine the two distinct types of information, some additional challenges are encountered: 1) Modality erasure: Vanilla graph convolution, which proves rather useful in collaborative filtering, however erases multimodal information; 2) Modality forgetting: Multimodal information tends to be gradually forgotten as the recommendation loss essentially facilitates the learning of collaborative information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stair-manipulating-collaborative-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Visual and Semantic Interpretability through Visually Grounded Concept Bottleneck Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-visual-and-semantic-interpretability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce visually Grounded Concept Bottleneck Models (GCBM), which derive concepts on the image level using segmentation and detection foundation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-visual-and-semantic-interpretability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual and Explainable Text Detoxification with Parallel Corpora</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-and-explainable-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even with various regulations in place across countries and social media platforms (Government of India, 2021; European Parliament and Council of the European Union, 2022, digital abusive speech remains a significant issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-and-explainable-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Semantic Consistency and Style Diversity for Domain Generalized Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-semantic-consistency-and-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we introduce a novel framework, named SCSD for Semantic Consistency prediction and Style Diversity generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-semantic-consistency-and-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NoteContrast: Contrastive Language-Diagnostic Pretraining for Medical Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/notecontrast-contrastive-language-diagnostic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further improve the automated adjudication of medical notes, we developed an approach based on i) models for ICD-10 diagnostic code sequences using a large real-world data set, ii) large language models for medical notes, and iii) contrastive pre-training to build an integrated model of both ICD-10 diagnostic codes and corresponding medical text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/notecontrast-contrastive-language-diagnostic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RetroLLM: Empowering Large Language Models to Retrieve Fine-grained Evidence within Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrollm-empowering-large-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, to mitigate false pruning in the process of constrained evidence generation, we introduce (1) hierarchical FM-Index constraints, which generate corpus-constrained clues to identify a subset of relevant documents before evidence generation, reducing irrelevant decoding space; and (2) a forward-looking constrained decoding strategy, which considers the relevance of future sequences to improve evidence accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrollm-empowering-large-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatTime: A Unified Multimodal Time Series Foundation Model Bridging Numerical and Textual Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chattime-a-unified-multimodal-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we innovatively model time series as a foreign language and construct ChatTime, a unified framework for time series and text processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chattime-a-unified-multimodal-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring More from Multiple Gait Modalities for Human Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-more-from-multiple-gait-modalities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The gait, as a kind of soft biometric characteristic, can reflect the distinct walking patterns of individuals at a distance, exhibiting a promising technique for unrestrained human identification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-more-from-multiple-gait-modalities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCoralDet: Efficient real-time underwater soft coral detection with YOLO</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scoraldet-efficient-real-time-underwater-soft</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose SCoralDet, a soft coral detection model based on the YOLO architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scoraldet-efficient-real-time-underwater-soft</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BioBridge: Unified Bio-Embedding with Bridging Modality in Code-Switched EMR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biobridge-unified-bio-embedding-with-bridging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pediatric Emergency Department (PED) overcrowding presents a significant global challenge, prompting the need for efficient solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biobridge-unified-bio-embedding-with-bridging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Mapper Algorithm with implicit intervals and its optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mapper-algorithm-with-implicit-intervals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Variants of the standard Mapper algorithms have been developed to address these limitations, yet most of them still require manual tuning of parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mapper-algorithm-with-implicit-intervals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmark and Robustness Study of In-Context-Learning with Large Language Models in Music Entity Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-and-robustness-study-of-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advent of large language models (LLMs), these outperform SLMs in a variety of downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-and-robustness-study-of-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skip Tuning: Pre-trained Vision-Language Models are Effective and Efficient Adapters Themselves</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skip-tuning-pre-trained-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompt tuning (PT) has long been recognized as an effective and efficient paradigm for transferring large pre-trained vision-language models (VLMs) to downstream tasks by learning a tiny set of context vectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skip-tuning-pre-trained-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future Sight and Tough Fights: Revolutionizing Sequential Recommendation with FENRec</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/future-sight-and-tough-fights-revolutionizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sequential recommendation (SR) systems predict user preferences by analyzing time-ordered interaction sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/future-sight-and-tough-fights-revolutionizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No More Adam: Learning Rate Scaling at Initialization is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-more-adam-learning-rate-scaling-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By adjusting learning rates without relying on adaptive second-order momentum, SGD-SaI helps prevent training imbalances from the very first iteration and cuts the optimizer's memory usage by half compared to AdamW.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-more-adam-learning-rate-scaling-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Random Features for Scalable Interpolation of Spatiotemporal Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-random-features-for-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While deep GPs can overcome this issue, training and making inference with them are difficult, again requiring crude approximations via inducing points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-random-features-for-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constructing Confidence Intervals for Average Treatment Effects from Multiple Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-confidence-intervals-for-average</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Constructing confidence intervals (CIs) for the average treatment effect (ATE) from patient records is crucial to assess the effectiveness and safety of drugs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-confidence-intervals-for-average</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Re-Attentional Controllable Video Diffusion Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-attentional-controllable-video-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, the controllability of video editing remains a formidable challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-attentional-controllable-video-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Slow Gradient Approximation for Binary Neural Network Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-slow-gradient-approximation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, hypernetwork based methods, which utilize neural networks to learn the gradients of non-differentiable quantization functions, have emerged as a promising approach due to their adaptive learning capabilities to reduce estimation errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-slow-gradient-approximation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making FETCH! Happen: Finding Emergent Dog Whistles Through Common Habitats</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-fetch-happen-finding-emergent-dog</link>
      <description><![CDATA[WARNING: This paper contains content that maybe upsetting or offensive to some readers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-fetch-happen-finding-emergent-dog</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asymmetric Learning for Spectral Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymmetric-learning-for-spectral-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on eighteen benchmark datasets show that asymmetric learning consistently improves the performance of spectral GNNs for both heterophilic and homophilic graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymmetric-learning-for-spectral-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Flow Is All You Need to Sample Out-of-Distribution Chemical Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-flow-is-all-you-need-to-sample-out</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating novel molecules with higher properties than the training space, namely the out-of-distribution generation, is important for ${de~novo}$ drug design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-flow-is-all-you-need-to-sample-out</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glimpse: Enabling White-Box Methods to Use Proprietary Models for Zero-Shot LLM-Generated Text Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glimpse-enabling-white-box-methods-to-use</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advanced large language models (LLMs) can generate text almost indistinguishable from human-written text, highlighting the importance of LLM-generated text detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glimpse-enabling-white-box-methods-to-use</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
