<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 09:13:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>EHRDiff: Exploring Realistic EHR Synthesis with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ehrdiff-exploring-realistic-ehr-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of diffusion models in realistic EHR synthesis is rarely explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ehrdiff-exploring-realistic-ehr-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marginalia and machine learning: Handwritten text recognition for Marginalia Collections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marginalia-and-machine-learning-handwritten</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pressing need for digitization of historical document collections has led to a strong interest in designing computerised image processing methods for automatic handwritten text recognition (HTR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marginalia-and-machine-learning-handwritten</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TrojDiff: Trojan Attacks on Diffusion Models with Diverse Targets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trojdiff-trojan-attacks-on-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To answer these questions, we propose an effective Trojan attack against diffusion models, TrojDiff, which optimizes the Trojan diffusion and generative processes during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trojdiff-trojan-attacks-on-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QVRF: A Quantization-error-aware Variable Rate Framework for Learned Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qvrf-a-quantization-error-aware-variable-rate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a Quantization-error-aware Variable Rate Framework (QVRF) that utilizes a univariate quantization regulator a to achieve wide-range variable rates within a single model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qvrf-a-quantization-error-aware-variable-rate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DACov: A Deeper Analysis of Data Augmentation on the Computed Tomography Segmentation Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dacov-a-deeper-analysis-of-data-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings show that GAN-based techniques and spatial-level transformations are the most promising for improving the learning of deep models on this problem, with the StarGANv2 + F with a probability of 0. 3 achieving the highest F-score value on the Ricord1a dataset in the unified training strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dacov-a-deeper-analysis-of-data-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creation and evaluation of timelines for longitudinal user posts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creation-and-evaluation-of-timelines-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is increasing interest to work with user generated content in social media, especially textual posts over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creation-and-evaluation-of-timelines-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuron Structure Modeling for Generalizable Remote Physiological Measurement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuron-structure-modeling-for-generalizable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that most domain generalization methods do not work well in this problem, as domain labels are ambiguous in complicated environmental changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuron-structure-modeling-for-generalizable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated crack propagation measurement on asphalt concrete specimens using an optical flow-based deep neural network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-crack-propagation-measurement-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article proposes a deep neural network, namely CrackPropNet, to measure crack propagation on asphalt concrete (AC) specimens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-crack-propagation-measurement-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lemmas: Generation, Selection, Application</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lemmas-generation-selection-application</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Noting that lemmas are a key feature of mathematics, we engage in an investigation of the role of lemmas in automated theorem proving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lemmas-generation-selection-application</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleGANEX: StyleGAN-Based Manipulation Beyond Cropped Aligned Faces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styleganex-stylegan-based-manipulation-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in face manipulation using StyleGAN have produced impressive results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styleganex-stylegan-based-manipulation-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single-branch Network for Multimodal Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-branch-network-for-multimodal-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid growth of social media platforms, users are sharing billions of multimedia posts containing audio, images, and text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-branch-network-for-multimodal-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Semi-Supervised Few-Shot Object Detection with SoftER Teacher</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-semi-supervised-few-shot-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing approaches to few-shot detection assume abundant base labels to adapt to novel objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-semi-supervised-few-shot-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sliced-Wasserstein on Symmetric Positive Definite Matrices for M/EEG Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliced-wasserstein-on-symmetric-positive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When dealing with electro or magnetoencephalography records, many supervised prediction tasks are solved by working with covariance matrices to summarize the signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliced-wasserstein-on-symmetric-positive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-Based Trit-Plane Coding for Progressive Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-based-trit-plane-coding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trit-plane coding enables deep progressive image compression, but it cannot use autoregressive context models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-based-trit-plane-coding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Few-shot Semantic Segmentation from Image Label Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-few-shot-semantic-segmentation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few-shot semantic segmentation aims to learn to segment unseen class objects with the guidance of only a few support images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-few-shot-semantic-segmentation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Importance of Aligning Training Strategy with Evaluation for Diffusion Models in 3D Multiclass Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/importance-of-aligning-training-strategy-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, denoising diffusion probabilistic models (DDPM) have been applied to image segmentation by generating segmentation masks conditioned on images, while the applications were mainly limited to 2D networks without exploiting potential benefits from the 3D formulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/importance-of-aligning-training-strategy-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-site, Multi-domain Airway Tree Modeling (ATM'22): A Public Benchmark for Pulmonary Airway Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-site-multi-domain-airway-tree-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, new methods have extended the reach of pulmonary airway segmentation that is closer to the limit of image resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-site-multi-domain-airway-tree-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACR: Attention Collaboration-based Regressor for Arbitrary Two-Hand Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acr-attention-collaboration-based-regressor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method significantly outperforms the best interacting-hand approaches on the InterHand2. 6M dataset while yielding comparable performance with the state-of-the-art single-hand methods on the FreiHand dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acr-attention-collaboration-based-regressor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Select Camera Views: Efficient Multiview Understanding at Few Glances</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-select-camera-views-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiview camera setups have proven useful in many computer vision applications for reducing ambiguities, mitigating occlusions, and increasing field-of-view coverage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-select-camera-views-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Diffusion MRI Denoising and Super-Resolution using Swin Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-diffusion-mri-denoising-and-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments on two other unrelated datasets, one of children with neurodevelopmental disorders and one of traumatic brain injury patients, show that our method demonstrates superior denoising despite wide data distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-diffusion-mri-denoising-and-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVOLIN Benchmark: Evaluation of Line Detection and Association</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolin-benchmark-evaluation-of-line-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is missing a complete benchmark where one can evaluate lines from a sequential stream of images in all its stages: Line detection, Line Association and Pose error.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolin-benchmark-evaluation-of-line-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decision-BADGE: Decision-based Adversarial Batch Attack with Directional Gradient Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decision-badge-decision-based-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The combination of Decision-BADGE and the accuracy loss function performs better than both score-based image-dependent attack and white-box universal attack methods in terms of attack time efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decision-badge-decision-based-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Recommendation Systems with User Personality Inferred from Product Reviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-recommendation-systems-with-user</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on our two newly contributed personality datasets -- Amazon-beauty and Amazon-music -- validate our hypothesis, showing performance boosts of 3--28%. Our analysis uncovers that varying personality types contribute differently to recommendation performance: open and extroverted personalities are most helpful in music recommendation, while a conscientious personality is most helpful in beauty product recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-recommendation-systems-with-user</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Stochastic Gradient Riemannian Langevin Dynamics in Non-Diagonal Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-stochastic-gradient-riemannian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For best performance the methods should use a Riemannian metric that improves posterior exploration by accounting for the local curvature, but the existing methods resort to simple diagonal metrics to remain computationally efficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-stochastic-gradient-riemannian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entropic Wasserstein Component Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropic-wasserstein-component-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dimension reduction (DR) methods provide systematic approaches for analyzing high-dimensional data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropic-wasserstein-component-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PC-JeDi: Diffusion for Particle Cloud Generation in High Energy Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pc-jedi-diffusion-for-particle-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new method to efficiently generate jets in High Energy Physics called PC-JeDi.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pc-jedi-diffusion-for-particle-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Spiking Neural Networks with High Representation Similarity Model Visual Pathways of Macaque and Mouse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-spiking-neural-networks-with-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, they highly simplify the computational properties of neurons compared to their biological counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-spiking-neural-networks-with-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Cross-View Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-cross-view-pose-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Localization Decoder produces a dense probability distribution in a coarse-to-fine manner with a novel Localization Matching Upsampling module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-cross-view-pose-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-distribution Detection with Implicit Outlier Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It leads to a min-max learning scheme -- searching to synthesize OOD data that leads to worst judgments and learning from such OOD data for uniform performance in OOD detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Regret Bounds for Online Kernel Selection under Bandit Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-regret-bounds-for-online-kernel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply the two algorithms to online kernel selection with time constraint and prove new regret bounds matching or improving the previous $O(\sqrt{T\ln{K}} +\Vert f\Vert^2_{\mathcal{H}_i}\max\{\sqrt{T},\frac{T}{\sqrt{\mathcal{R}}}\})$ expected bound where $\mathcal{R}$ is the time budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-regret-bounds-for-online-kernel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Federated Learning for Collaborative Intelligence in Massive IoT Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-federated-learning-for-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implementing existing federated learning in massive Internet of Things (IoT) networks faces critical challenges such as imbalanced and statistically heterogeneous data and device diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-federated-learning-for-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invertible Kernel PCA with Random Fourier Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invertible-kernel-pca-with-random-fourier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Kernel principal component analysis (kPCA) is a widely studied method to construct a low-dimensional data representation after a nonlinear transformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invertible-kernel-pca-with-random-fourier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Image-in-Audio Deep Steganography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-image-in-audio-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of steganography has experienced a surge of interest due to the recent advancements in AI-powered techniques, particularly in the context of multimodal setups that enable the concealment of signals within signals of a different nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-image-in-audio-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting the relevance of traditional genres: a network analysis of fiction readers' preferences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-relevance-of-traditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our analysis reveals that the network communities correspond to existing combinations of traditional genres, but that the exact communities differ depending on whether we consider books that people read or books that people enjoy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-relevance-of-traditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEAM: An Integrated Activation-Coupled Model of Sentence Processing and Eye Movements in Reading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seam-an-integrated-activation-coupled-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our knowledge, this is the first-ever integration of a complete process model of eye-movement control with linguistic dependency completion processes in sentence comprehension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seam-an-integrated-activation-coupled-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDS3D: Dense Pseudo-Labels with Dynamic Threshold for Semi-Supervised 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dds3d-dense-pseudo-labels-with-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a simple yet effective semi-supervised 3D object detector named DDS3D.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dds3d-dense-pseudo-labels-with-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GaitEditer: Attribute Editing for Gait Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaitediter-attribute-editing-for-gait</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gait pattern is a promising biometric for applications, as it can be captured from a distance without requiring individual cooperation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaitediter-attribute-editing-for-gait</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spawrious: A Benchmark for Fine Control of Spurious Correlation Biases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spawrious-a-benchmark-for-fine-control-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The problem of spurious correlations (SCs) arises when a classifier relies on non-predictive features that happen to be correlated with the labels in the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spawrious-a-benchmark-for-fine-control-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Rotation Averaging: Uncertainties and Robust Losses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-rotation-averaging-uncertainties</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we revisit the rotation averaging problem applied in global Structure-from-Motion pipelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-rotation-averaging-uncertainties</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Splines for Non-Linear Approximations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-splines-for-non-linear-approximations-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantum Computing offers a new paradigm for efficient computing and many AI applications could benefit from its potential boost in performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-splines-for-non-linear-approximations-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Legibility of Visual Text Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-legibility-of-visual-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address this gap by learning models that predict the legibility of a perturbed string, and rank candidate perturbations based on their legibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-legibility-of-visual-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perspective Projection-Based 3D CT Reconstruction from Biplanar X-rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perspective-projection-based-3d-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[X-ray computed tomography (CT) is one of the most common imaging techniques used to diagnose various diseases in the medical field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perspective-projection-based-3d-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mimic before Reconstruct: Enhancing Masked Autoencoders with Feature Mimicking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimic-before-reconstruct-enhancing-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate this, previous methods simply replace the pixel reconstruction targets of 75% masked tokens by encoded features from pre-trained image-image (DINO) or image-language (CLIP) contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimic-before-reconstruct-enhancing-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provable Data Subset Selection For Efficient Neural Network Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provable-data-subset-selection-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce the first algorithm to construct coresets for \emph{RBFNNs}, i. e., small weighted subsets that approximate the loss of the input data on any radial basis function network and thus approximate any function defined by an \emph{RBFNN} on the larger input data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provable-data-subset-selection-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Image Modeling with Local Multi-Scale Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-image-modeling-with-local-multi-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The lower layers are not explicitly guided and the interaction among their patches is only used for calculating new activations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-image-modeling-with-local-multi-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TANGOS: Regularizing Tabular Neural Networks through Gradient Orthogonalization and Specialization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tangos-regularizing-tabular-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Tabular Neural Gradient Orthogonalization and Specialization (TANGOS), a novel framework for regularization in the tabular setting built on latent unit attributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tangos-regularizing-tabular-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Certified Training and Robustness Verification of Neural ODEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-certified-training-and-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Ordinary Differential Equations (NODEs) are a novel neural architecture, built around initial value problems with learned dynamics which are solved during inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-certified-training-and-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic 3d regression with projected huber distribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-3d-regression-with-projected</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also show that the mode of the predicted distribution outperform our regression baselines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-3d-regression-with-projected</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RiDDLE: Reversible and Diversified De-identification with Latent Encryptor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/riddle-reversible-and-diversified-de</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents RiDDLE, short for Reversible and Diversified De-identification with Latent Encryptor, to protect the identity information of people from being misused.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/riddle-reversible-and-diversified-de</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BaDLAD: A Large Multi-Domain Bengali Document Layout Analysis Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badlad-a-large-multi-domain-bengali-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While strides have been made in deep learning based Bengali Optical Character Recognition (OCR) in the past decade, the absence of large Document Layout Analysis (DLA) datasets has hindered the application of OCR in document transcription, e. g., transcribing historical documents and newspapers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badlad-a-large-multi-domain-bengali-document</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
