<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 09:15:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Segmenting Medical Images with Limited Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmenting-medical-images-with-limited-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While computer vision has proven valuable for medical image segmentation, its application faces challenges such as limited dataset sizes and the complexity of effectively leveraging unlabeled images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmenting-medical-images-with-limited-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Adversarial Robustness of Semantic Segmentation: Trying Harder Pays Off</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-adversarial-robustness-of-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results indicate that most of the state-of-the-art models have a dramatically larger sensitivity to adversarial perturbations than previously reported.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-adversarial-robustness-of-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Yet Efficient Conformal Prediction Sets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-yet-efficient-conformal-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conformal prediction (CP) can convert any model's output into prediction sets guaranteed to include the true label with any user-specified probability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-yet-efficient-conformal-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FANet: Feature Amplification Network for Semantic Segmentation in Cluttered Background</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fanet-feature-amplification-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing deep learning approaches leave out the semantic cues that are crucial in semantic segmentation present in complex scenarios including cluttered backgrounds and translucent objects, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fanet-feature-amplification-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LightenDiffusion: Unsupervised Low-Light Image Enhancement with Latent-Retinex Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightendiffusion-unsupervised-low-light-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a diffusion-based unsupervised framework that incorporates physically explainable Retinex theory with diffusion models for low-light image enhancement, named LightenDiffusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightendiffusion-unsupervised-low-light-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Region Attention Transformer for Medical Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/region-attention-transformer-for-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the majority of existing Transformers conduct attention within fixed and coarsely partitioned regions (\text{e. g.} the entire image or fixed patches), resulting in interference from irrelevant regions and fragmentation of continuous image content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/region-attention-transformer-for-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Chatbot for Asylum-Seeking Migrants in Europe</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-chatbot-for-asylum-seeking-migrants-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present ACME: A Chatbot for asylum-seeking Migrants in Europe.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-chatbot-for-asylum-seeking-migrants-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soft Prompts Go Hard: Steering Visual Language Models with Hidden Meta-Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soft-prompts-go-hard-steering-visual-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new type of indirect injection vulnerabilities in language models that operate on images: hidden "meta-instructions" that influence how the model interprets the image and steer the model's outputs to express an adversary-chosen style, sentiment, or point of view.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soft-prompts-go-hard-steering-visual-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPT: Label-driven Automated Prompt Tuning for OOD Detection with Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lapt-label-driven-automated-prompt-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The LAPT framework operates autonomously, requiring only ID class names as input and eliminating the need for manual intervention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lapt-label-driven-automated-prompt-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are They the Same Picture? Adapting Concept Bottleneck Models for Human-AI Collaboration in Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-they-the-same-picture-adapting-concept</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image retrieval plays a pivotal role in applications from wildlife conservation to healthcare, for finding individual animals or relevant images to aid diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-they-the-same-picture-adapting-concept</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DART: An Automated End-to-End Object Detection Pipeline with Data Diversification, Open-Vocabulary Bounding Box Annotation, Pseudo-Label Review, and Model Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dart-an-automated-end-to-end-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Swift and accurate detection of specified objects is crucial for many industrial applications, such as safety monitoring on construction sites.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dart-an-automated-end-to-end-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symmetry Awareness Encoded Deep Learning Framework for Brain Imaging Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetry-awareness-encoded-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The heterogeneity of neurological conditions, ranging from structural anomalies to functional impairments, presents a significant challenge in medical imaging analysis tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetry-awareness-encoded-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Molecule Language Model with Augmented Pairs and Expertise Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecule-language-model-with-augmented-pairs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the molecules and their textual descriptions via molecule language models (MoLM) recently got a surge of interest among researchers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecule-language-model-with-augmented-pairs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KUNPENG: An Embodied Large Model for Intelligent Maritime</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kunpeng-an-embodied-large-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intelligent maritime, as an essential component of smart ocean construction, deeply integrates advanced artificial intelligence technology and data analysis methods, which covers multiple aspects such as smart vessels, route optimization, safe navigation, aiming to enhance the efficiency of ocean resource utilization and the intelligence of transportation networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kunpeng-an-embodied-large-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmark Environment for Offline Reinforcement Learning in Racing Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-environment-for-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The environment simulates a single-agent racing game in which the objective is to complete the track through optimal navigation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-environment-for-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PID: Physics-Informed Diffusion Model for Infrared Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pid-physics-informed-diffusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Infrared imaging technology has gained significant attention for its reliable sensing ability in low visibility conditions, prompting many studies to convert the abundant RGB images to infrared images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pid-physics-informed-diffusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let Me DeCode You: Decoder Conditioning with Tabular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-me-decode-you-decoder-conditioning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When labels are not available during inference, our model infers the necessary conditioning embedding directly from the input data, thanks to a feed-forward network learned during the training phase.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-me-decode-you-decoder-conditioning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stepwise Verification and Remediation of Student Reasoning Errors with Large Language Model Tutors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stepwise-verification-and-remediation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show empirically that finding the mistake in a student solution is challenging for current models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stepwise-verification-and-remediation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFaults: Model-Based Diagnosis for Fault Localization in C Programs with Multiple Test Cases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfaults-model-based-diagnosis-for-fault</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several formula-based fault localization (FBFL) methods have been proposed, but they fail to guarantee a set of diagnoses across all failing tests or may produce redundant diagnoses that are not subset-minimal, particularly for programs with multiple faults.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfaults-model-based-diagnosis-for-fault</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reshaping the Online Data Buffering and Organizing Mechanism for Continual Test-Time Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reshaping-the-online-data-buffering-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we systematically analyze the challenges of this task: online environment, unsupervised nature, and the risks of error accumulation and catastrophic forgetting under continual domain shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reshaping-the-online-data-buffering-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Anomaly Synthesis Strategy with Gradient Ascent for Industrial Anomaly Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-anomaly-synthesis-strategy-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Anomaly synthesis strategies can effectively enhance unsupervised anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-anomaly-synthesis-strategy-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProDepth: Boosting Self-Supervised Multi-Frame Monocular Depth with Probabilistic Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prodepth-boosting-self-supervised-multi-frame</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised multi-frame monocular depth estimation relies on the geometric consistency between successive frames under the assumption of a static scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prodepth-boosting-self-supervised-multi-frame</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Few-Shot Relation Extraction with The Integration of Traditional RE Methods and Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-few-shot-relation-extraction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, DSARE innovatively injects the prior knowledge of LLMs into traditional RE models, and conversely enhances LLMs' task-specific aptitude for RE through relation extraction augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-few-shot-relation-extraction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refuse Whenever You Feel Unsafe: Improving Safety in LLMs via Decoupled Refusal Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refuse-whenever-you-feel-unsafe-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DeRTa incorporates two novel components: (1) Maximum Likelihood Estimation (MLE) with Harmful Response Prefix, which trains models to recognize and avoid unsafe content by appending a segment of harmful response to the beginning of a safe response, and (2) Reinforced Transition Optimization (RTO), which equips models with the ability to transition from potential harm to safety refusal consistently throughout the harmful response sequence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refuse-whenever-you-feel-unsafe-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPIQA: A Dataset for Multimodal Question Answering on Scientific Papers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiqa-a-dataset-for-multimodal-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging the breadth of expertise and ability of multimodal large language models (MLLMs) to understand figures, we employ automatic and manual curation to create the dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiqa-a-dataset-for-multimodal-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flow-Based Generative Emulation of Grids of Stellar Evolutionary Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-based-generative-emulation-of-grids-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a flow-based generative approach to emulate grids of stellar evolutionary models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-based-generative-emulation-of-grids-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transductive Active Learning with Application to Safe Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transductive-active-learning-with-application</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze Safe BO under the lens of a generalization of active learning with concrete prediction targets where sampling is restricted to an accessible region of the domain, while prediction targets may lie outside this region.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transductive-active-learning-with-application</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global-Local Collaborative Inference with LLM for Lidar-Based Open-Vocabulary Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-local-collaborative-inference-with-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Global-Local Collaborative Scheme (GLIS) for the lidar-based OVD task, which contains a local branch to generate object-level detection result and a global branch to obtain scene-level global feature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-local-collaborative-inference-with-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Image Prior: Embedding Noise Prior into Conditional Denoising Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-image-prior-embedding-noise-prior-into</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce a Locally Noise Prior Estimation (LoNPE) algorithm, which accurately estimates the noise prior directly from a single raw noisy image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-image-prior-embedding-noise-prior-into</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastImpute: A Baseline for Open-source, Reference-Free Genotype Imputation Methods -- A Case Study in PRS313</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastimpute-a-baseline-for-open-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Genotype imputation enhances genetic data by predicting missing SNPs using reference haplotype information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastimpute-a-baseline-for-open-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Canopy: A Country-Scale Benchmark for Canopy Height Estimation at Very High Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-canopy-a-country-scale-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimating canopy height and canopy height change at meter resolution from satellite imagery has numerous applications, such as monitoring forest health, logging activities, wood resources, and carbon stocks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-canopy-a-country-scale-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music Proofreading with RefinPaint: Where and How to Modify Compositions given Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/music-proofreading-with-refinpaint-where-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoregressive generative transformers are key in music generation, producing coherent compositions but facing challenges in human-machine collaboration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/music-proofreading-with-refinpaint-where-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing the Dark Secrets of Extremely Large Kernel ConvNets on Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-the-dark-secrets-of-extremely-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robustness is a vital aspect to consider when deploying deep learning models into the wild.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-the-dark-secrets-of-extremely-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Network Causal Explanation via Neural Causal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-network-causal-explanation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our explainer is based on the observation that a graph often consists of a causal underlying subgraph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-network-causal-explanation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Entity-Level Hallucination in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-entity-level-hallucination-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this challenge, this paper proposes Dynamic Retrieval Augmentation based on hallucination Detection (DRAD) as a novel method to detect and mitigate hallucinations in LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-entity-level-hallucination-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANIEL: A fast Document Attention Network for Information Extraction and Labelling of handwritten documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/daniel-a-fast-document-attention-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite this, these integrated approaches have not yet matched the performance of language models, when applied to information extraction in plain text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/daniel-a-fast-document-attention-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guidelines for Augmentation Selection in Contrastive Learning for Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guidelines-for-augmentation-selection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised contrastive learning has become a key technique in deep learning, particularly in time series analysis, due to its ability to learn meaningful representations without explicit supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guidelines-for-augmentation-selection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards stable training of parallel continual learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-stable-training-of-parallel-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parallel Continual Learning (PCL) tasks investigate the training methods for continual learning with multi-source input, where data from different tasks are learned as they arrive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-stable-training-of-parallel-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DenseFusion-1M: Merging Vision Experts for Comprehensive Multimodal Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/densefusion-1m-merging-vision-experts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate the cutting-edge research of MLLMs on comprehensive vision perception, we thereby propose Perceptual Fusion, using a low-budget but highly effective caption engine for complete and accurate image descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/densefusion-1m-merging-vision-experts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Visual Place Recognition Based Robot Navigation Through Verification of Localization Estimates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-visual-place-recognition-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiment 2 showed a decrease in aggregate mean along-track localization error from ~2. 0m to ~0. 5m, and an increase in the aggregate precision of localization attempts from ~97% to ~99%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-visual-place-recognition-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prediction Exposes Your Face: Black-box Model Inversion via Prediction Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-exposes-your-face-black-box-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model inversion (MI) attack reconstructs the private training data of a target model given its output, posing a significant threat to deep learning models and data privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-exposes-your-face-black-box-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Load and Capacity Scheduling for Flexible Radio Resource Management of High-Throughput Satellites</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-load-and-capacity-scheduling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work first explores using flexible beam-user mapping to optimize the beam service range and beam position, in order to adapt the non-uniform traffic demand to offer in high-throughput satellite (HTS) systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-load-and-capacity-scheduling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eyeballvul: a future-proof benchmark for vulnerability detection in the wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eyeballvul-a-future-proof-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The benchmark consists of a list of revisions in different repositories, each associated with the list of known vulnerabilities present at that revision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eyeballvul-a-future-proof-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedMedICL: Towards Holistic Evaluation of Distribution Shifts in Federated Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedmedicl-towards-holistic-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response, we introduce FedMedICL, a unified framework and benchmark to holistically evaluate federated medical imaging challenges, simultaneously capturing label, demographic, and temporal distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedmedicl-towards-holistic-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FairDomain: Achieving Fairness in Cross-Domain Medical Image Segmentation and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairdomain-achieving-fairness-in-cross-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the fairness issue under the setting of domain transfer is almost unexplored, while it is common that clinics rely on different imaging technologies (e. g., different retinal imaging modalities) for patient diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairdomain-achieving-fairness-in-cross-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Surgery: Modulating LLM's Behavior Via Simple Parameter Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-surgery-modulating-llm-s-behavior-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, models modified through SFT and RLHF may deviate from the pretrained models, potentially leading to a degradation in foundational LLM capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-surgery-modulating-llm-s-behavior-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient Boosting Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-boosting-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GBRL expands the toolkit for RL practitioners, demonstrating the viability and promise of GBT within the RL paradigm, particularly in domains characterized by structured or categorical features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-boosting-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSCENet: Dynamic Screening and Clinical-Enhanced Multimodal Fusion for MPNs Subtype Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dscenet-dynamic-screening-and-clinical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(1) A dynamic screening module is proposed to flexibly adapt the feature learning of local patches, reducing the interference of irrelevant features and enhancing their diagnostic representativeness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dscenet-dynamic-screening-and-clinical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RTMW: Real-Time Multi-Person 2D and 3D Whole-body Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rtmw-real-time-multi-person-2d-and-3d-whole</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present RTMW (Real-Time Multi-person Whole-body pose estimation models), a series of high-performance models for 2D/3D whole-body pose estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rtmw-real-time-multi-person-2d-and-3d-whole</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoBencher: Creating Salient, Novel, Difficult Datasets for Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autobencher-creating-salient-novel-difficult</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present three desiderata for a good benchmark for language models: (i) salience (e. g., knowledge about World War II is more salient than a random day in history), (ii) novelty (i. e., the benchmark reveals new trends in model rankings not shown by previous benchmarks), and (iii) difficulty (i. e., the benchmark should be difficult for existing models, leaving headroom for future improvement).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autobencher-creating-salient-novel-difficult</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
