<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 21:07:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Grouped Pointwise Convolutions Reduce Parameters in Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grouped-pointwise-convolutions-reduce</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Deep Convolutional Neural Networks (DCNNs), the parameter count in pointwise convolutions quickly grows due to the multiplication of the filters and input channels from the preceding layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grouped-pointwise-convolutions-reduce</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color-aware two-branch DCNN for efficient plant disease classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-aware-two-branch-dcnn-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep convolutional neural networks (DCNNs) have been successfully applied to plant disease detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-aware-two-branch-dcnn-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Robustness of Dialogue History Representation in Conversational Question Answering: A Comprehensive Study and a New Prompt-based Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-robustness-of-dialogue-history</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that high benchmark scores do not necessarily translate to strong robustness, and that various methods can perform extremely differently under different settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-robustness-of-dialogue-history</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERNERMED++: Transfer Learning in German Medical NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gernermed-transfer-learning-in-german-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a statistical model for German medical natural language processing trained for named entity recognition (NER) as an open, publicly available model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gernermed-transfer-learning-in-german-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technical Report for CVPR 2022 LOVEU AQTC Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/technical-report-for-cvpr-2022-loveu-aqtc</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This technical report presents the 2nd winning model for AQTC, a task newly introduced in CVPR 2022 LOng-form VidEo Understanding (LOVEU) challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/technical-report-for-cvpr-2022-loveu-aqtc</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lighter The Better: Rethinking Transformers in Medical Image Segmentation Through Adaptive Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-lighter-the-better-rethinking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our best knowledge, this is the first work on transformer pruning for medical image analysis tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-lighter-the-better-rethinking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summarizing Videos using Concentrated Attention and Considering the Uniqueness and Diversity of the Video Frames</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/summarizing-videos-using-concentrated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of simply modeling the frames' dependencies based on global attention, our method integrates a concentrated attention mechanism that is able to focus on non-overlapping blocks in the main diagonal of the attention matrix, and to enrich the existing information by extracting and exploiting knowledge about the uniqueness and diversity of the associated frames of the video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/summarizing-videos-using-concentrated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LViT: Language meets Vision Transformer in Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lvit-language-meets-vision-transformer-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our model, medical text annotation is introduced to compensate for the quality deficiency in image data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lvit-language-meets-vision-transformer-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SRCN3D: Sparse R-CNN 3D Surround-View Camera Object Detection and Tracking for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srcn3d-sparse-r-cnn-3d-surround-view-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes Sparse R-CNN 3D (SRCN3D), a novel two-stage fully-convolutional mapping pipeline for surround-view camera detection and tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srcn3d-sparse-r-cnn-3d-surround-view-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Foresight With a Local Dynamics Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-foresight-with-a-local-dynamics-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By combining the LDM with model-free policy learning, we can learn policies which can solve complex manipulation tasks using one-step lookahead planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-foresight-with-a-local-dynamics-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Procrustes Analysis with Deformations: A Closed-Form Solution by Eigenvalue Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procrustes-analysis-with-deformations-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that this property fortunately holds true for most common transformation models, including the affine and TPS models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procrustes-analysis-with-deformations-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An extensible Benchmarking Graph-Mesh dataset for studying Steady-State Incompressible Navier-Stokes Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-extensible-benchmarking-graph-mesh-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in \emph{Geometric Deep Learning} (GDL) has shown its potential to provide powerful data-driven models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-extensible-benchmarking-graph-mesh-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling Model Failures as Directions in Latent Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-model-failures-as-directions-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods for isolating hard subpopulations and spurious correlations in datasets often require human intervention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-model-failures-as-directions-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>vMFNet: Compositionality Meets Domain-generalised Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vmfnet-compositionality-meets-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, with a reconstruction module, unlabeled data can also be used to learn the vMF kernels and likelihoods by recombining them to reconstruct the input image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vmfnet-compositionality-meets-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-scale Physical Representations for Approximating PDE Solutions with Graph Neural Operators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-physical-representations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study three multi-resolution schema with integral kernel operators that can be approximated with \emph{Message Passing Graph Neural Networks} (MPGNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-physical-representations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Placenta Segmentation in Ultrasound Imaging: Addressing Sources of Uncertainty and Limited Field-of-View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/placenta-segmentation-in-ultrasound-imaging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic segmentation of the placenta in fetal ultrasound (US) is challenging due to the (i) high diversity of placenta appearance, (ii) the restricted quality in US resulting in highly variable reference annotations, and (iii) the limited field-of-view of US prohibiting whole placenta assessment at late gestation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/placenta-segmentation-in-ultrasound-imaging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditionally Elicitable Dynamic Risk Measures for Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditionally-elicitable-dynamic-risk</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel framework to solve risk-sensitive reinforcement learning (RL) problems where the agent optimises time-consistent dynamic spectral risk measures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditionally-elicitable-dynamic-risk</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Data-Driven Requirements Engineering Approach: Automatic Analysis of User Reviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-data-driven-requirements</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We are concerned by Data Driven Requirements Engineering, and in particular the consideration of user's reviews.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-data-driven-requirements</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Score Matching for Truncated Density Estimation on a Manifold</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-matching-for-truncated-density</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When observations are truncated, we are limited to an incomplete picture of our dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-matching-for-truncated-density</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finstreder: Simple and fast Spoken Language Understanding with Finite State Transducers using modern Speech-to-Text models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finstreder-simple-and-fast-spoken-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Spoken Language Understanding (SLU) the task is to extract important information from audio commands, like the intent of what a user wants the system to do and special entities like locations or numbers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finstreder-simple-and-fast-spoken-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TE2Rules: Extracting Rule Lists from Tree Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/te2rules-extracting-rule-lists-from-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tree Ensemble (TE) models (e. g. Gradient Boosted Trees and Random Forests) often provide higher prediction performance compared to single decision trees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/te2rules-extracting-rule-lists-from-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONVIQT: Contrastive Video Quality Estimator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conviqt-contrastive-video-quality-estimator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Perceptual video quality assessment (VQA) is an integral component of many streaming and video sharing platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conviqt-contrastive-video-quality-estimator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C2FTrans: Coarse-to-Fine Transformers for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c2ftrans-coarse-to-fine-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most recent transformer-based methods for medical image segmentation directly apply vanilla transformers as an auxiliary module in CNN-based methods, resulting in severe detail loss due to the rigid patch partitioning scheme in transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c2ftrans-coarse-to-fine-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDKtor: Automatic Diadochokinetic Speech Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddktor-automatic-diadochokinetic-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These segmentations predicted by the models are used to obtain measures of speech rate and sound duration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddktor-automatic-diadochokinetic-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Twitter Data to Understand Public Perceptions of Approved versus Off-label Use for COVID-19-related Medications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-twitter-data-to-understand-public</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time-trend analysis revealed that Hydroxychloroquine and Ivermectin received much more discussion than Molnupiravir and Remdesivir, particularly during COVID-19 surges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-twitter-data-to-understand-public</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correctly Modeling TX and RX Chain in (Distributed) Massive MIMO -- New Fundamental Insights on Coherency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correctly-modeling-tx-and-rx-chain-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, the Local Oscillator (LO) effect should be modeled as $+\phi$ in the transmitter chain and $-\phi$ in the receiver chain, i. e., different signs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correctly-modeling-tx-and-rx-chain-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Online Voltage Control with an Unknown Grid Topology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-online-voltage-control-with-an-unknown</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Voltage control generally requires accurate information about the grid's topology in order to guarantee network stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-online-voltage-control-with-an-unknown</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimization-Induced Graph Implicit Nonlinear Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-induced-graph-implicit-nonlinear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we show that the optimization-induced variants of our models can boost the performance and improve training stability and efficiency as well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-induced-graph-implicit-nonlinear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Ensemble Training by Jointly Learning Label Dependencies and Member Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-ensemble-training-by-jointly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training an ensemble of different sub-models has empirically proven to be an effective strategy to improve deep neural networks' adversarial robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-ensemble-training-by-jointly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Data Collection System for Brownfield CNC Milling Machines: A New Benchmark Dataset for Data-Driven Machine Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-data-collection-system-for-brownfield</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enhance the scalability of machine learning in real-world applications, this paper presents a benchmark dataset for process monitoring of brownfield milling machines based on acceleration data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-data-collection-system-for-brownfield</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CC-Riddle: A Question Answering Dataset of Chinese Character Riddles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cc-riddle-a-question-answering-dataset-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chinese character riddle is a challenging riddle game which takes a single character as the solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cc-riddle-a-question-answering-dataset-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NERDA-Con: Extending NER models for Continual Learning -- Integrating Distinct Tasks and Updating Distribution Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerda-con-extending-ner-models-for-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With increasing applications in areas such as biomedical information extraction pipelines and social media analytics, Named Entity Recognition (NER) has become an indispensable tool for knowledge extraction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerda-con-extending-ner-models-for-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Steer Your Adversary: Targeted and Efficient Model Stealing Defenses with Gradient Redirection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-steer-your-adversary-targeted-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To meet these challenges, we present a new approach to model stealing defenses called gradient redirection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-steer-your-adversary-targeted-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Prior Learning via Neural Architecture Search for Blind Face Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-prior-learning-via-neural-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a Face Restoration Searching Network (FRSNet) to adaptively search the suitable feature extraction architecture within our specified search space, which can directly contribute to the restoration quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-prior-learning-via-neural-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Anomaly Detection Based On Reservoir Sampling and LOF for IoT devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-anomaly-detection-based-on-reservoir</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The growing number of IoT devices and their use to monitor the operation of machines and equipment increases interest in anomaly detection algorithms running on devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-anomaly-detection-based-on-reservoir</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHELS: Exclusive Feature Sets for Novelty Detection and Continual Learning Without Class Boundaries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shels-exclusive-feature-sets-for-novelty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by natural learners, we introduce a Sparse High-level-Exclusive, Low-level-Shared feature representation (SHELS) that simultaneously encourages learning exclusive sets of high-level features and essential, shared low-level features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shels-exclusive-feature-sets-for-novelty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory Safe Computations with XLA Compiler</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-safe-computations-with-xla-compiler</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe that further focus on removing memory constraints at a compiler level will widen the range of machine learning methods that can be developed in the future.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-safe-computations-with-xla-compiler</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TTS-CGAN: A Transformer Time-Series Conditional GAN for Biosignal Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tts-cgan-a-transformer-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For time-series data, the suite of data augmentation strategies we can use to expand the size of the dataset is limited by the need to maintain the basic properties of the signal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tts-cgan-a-transformer-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyEPO: A PyTorch-based End-to-End Predict-then-Optimize Library for Linear and Integer Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyepo-a-pytorch-based-end-to-end-predict-then</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It provides two base algorithms: the first is based on the convex surrogate loss function from the seminal work of Elmachtoub & Grigas (2021), and the second is based on the differentiable black-box solver approach of Vlastelica et al. (2019).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyepo-a-pytorch-based-end-to-end-predict-then</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Symmetric Rules with SATNet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-symmetric-rules-with-satnet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SATNet is a differentiable constraint solver with a custom backpropagation algorithm, which can be used as a layer in a deep-learning system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-symmetric-rules-with-satnet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pedestrian 3D Bounding Box Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pedestrian-3d-bounding-box-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safety is still the main issue of autonomous driving, and in order to be globally deployed, they need to predict pedestrians' motions sufficiently in advance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pedestrian-3d-bounding-box-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study of Challenges in Converting Deep Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-challenges-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Usually DL models are developed and trained using DL frameworks that have their own internal mechanisms/formats to represent and train DL models, and usually those formats cannot be recognized by other frameworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-challenges-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMT-based Weighted Model Integration with Structure Awareness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smt-based-weighted-model-integration-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weighted Model Integration (WMI) is a popular formalism aimed at unifying approaches for probabilistic inference in hybrid domains, involving logical and algebraic constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smt-based-weighted-model-integration-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Evolutionary and Multi-scale Graph Structure for Multivariate Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-evolutionary-and-multi-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To equip the graph neural network with a flexible and practical graph structure, in this paper, we investigate how to model the evolutionary and multi-scale interactions of time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-evolutionary-and-multi-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Gait Representation from Massive Unlabelled Walking Videos: A Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-gait-representation-from-massive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As far as we know, GaitLU-1M is the first large-scale unlabelled gait dataset, and GaitSSB is the first method that achieves remarkable unsupervised results on the aforementioned benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-gait-representation-from-massive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithms for audio inpainting based on probabilistic nonnegative matrix factorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/algorithms-for-audio-inpainting-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we treat the missing samples as latent variables, and derive two expectation-maximization algorithms for estimating the parameters of the model, depending on whether we formulate the problem in the time- or time-frequency domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/algorithms-for-audio-inpainting-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Dataflow Dialogue Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-dataflow-dialogue-design-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper argues that this perception is wrong: 1) Suggestions for a simplified format for the annotation of the dataset are presented, 2) An implementation of the DF execution engine is released\footnote{https://github. com/telepathylabsai/OpenDF}, which can serve as a sandbox allowing researchers to easily implement, and experiment with, new DF dialogue designs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-dataflow-dialogue-design-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BertNet: Harvesting Knowledge Graphs from Pretrained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bertnet-harvesting-knowledge-graphs-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, we derive from diverse LMs a family of new KGs (e. g., BertNet and RoBERTaNet) that contain a richer set of commonsense relations, including complex ones (e. g., "A is capable of but not good at B"), than the human-annotated KGs (e. g., ConceptNet).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bertnet-harvesting-knowledge-graphs-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sublinear-Time Clustering Oracle for Signed Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sublinear-time-clustering-oracle-for-signed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide a local clustering oracle for signed graphs with such a clear community structure, that can answer membership queries, i. e., "Given a vertex $v$, which community does $v$ belong to?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sublinear-time-clustering-oracle-for-signed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robustifying Vision Transformer without Retraining from Scratch by Test-Time Class-Conditional Feature Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustifying-vision-transformer-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision Transformer (ViT) is becoming more popular in image processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustifying-vision-transformer-without</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
