<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 09:16:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Distribution-based Emotion Recognition in Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-based-emotion-recognition-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic emotion recognition in conversation (ERC) is crucial for emotion-aware conversational artificial intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-based-emotion-recognition-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Named Entity Linking: A New Dataset and A Baseline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-named-entity-linking-a-new-dataset-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since each entity often contains rich visual and textual information in KBs, we thus propose three different sub-tasks, i. e., visual to visual entity linking (V2VEL), visual to textual entity linking (V2TEL), and visual to visual-textual entity linking (V2VTEL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-named-entity-linking-a-new-dataset-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Shot Character Understanding in Movies as an Assessment to Meta-Learning of Theory-of-Mind</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-character-understanding-in-movies-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When reading a story, humans can rapidly understand new fictional characters with a few observations, mainly by drawing analogy to fictional and real people they met before in their lives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-character-understanding-in-movies-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimalist Data Wrangling with Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimalist-data-wrangling-with-python</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Minimalist Data Wrangling with Python is envisaged as a student's first introduction to data science, providing a high-level overview as well as discussing key concepts in detail.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimalist-data-wrangling-with-python</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Point Cloud Registration Framework Based on Deep Graph Matching(TPAMI Version)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-point-cloud-registration-framework-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel deep graph matching-based framework for point cloud registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-point-cloud-registration-framework-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe Latent Diffusion: Mitigating Inappropriate Degeneration in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-latent-diffusion-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-conditioned image generation models have recently achieved astonishing results in image quality and text alignment and are consequently employed in a fast-growing number of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-latent-diffusion-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask More and Mask Later: Efficient Pre-training of Masked Language Models by Disentangling the [MASK] Token</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-more-and-mask-later-efficient-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show: (1) [MASK]s can indeed be appended at a later layer, being disentangled from the word embedding; (2) The gathering of contextualized information from unmasked tokens can be conducted with a few layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-more-and-mask-later-efficient-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks with Adaptive Readouts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-with-adaptive-readouts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that in some problems such as binding affinity prediction where molecules are typically presented in a canonical form it might be possible to relax the constraints on permutation invariance of the hypothesis space and learn a more effective model of the affinity by employing an adaptive readout function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-with-adaptive-readouts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributional Shift Adaptation using Domain-Specific Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-shift-adaptation-using-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning algorithms typically assume that the training and test samples come from the same distributions, i. e., in-distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-shift-adaptation-using-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoSA : A System to Accelerate Annotations on Business Documents with Human-in-the-Loop</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dosa-a-system-to-accelerate-annotations-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An initial document-specific model can be trained and its inference can be used as feedback for generating more automated annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dosa-a-system-to-accelerate-annotations-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Aesthetic and Technical Effects for Video Quality Assessment of User Generated Content</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-aesthetic-and-technical-effects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better explain the quality perception mechanisms and learn more robust representations, we aim to disentangle the effects of aesthetic quality issues and technical quality issues risen by the complicated video generation processes in the UGC-VQA problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-aesthetic-and-technical-effects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trackerless freehand ultrasound with sequence modelling and auxiliary transformation over past and future frames</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trackerless-freehand-ultrasound-with-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Little benefit was observed by adding frames more than one second away from the predicted transformation, with or without LSTM-based RNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trackerless-freehand-ultrasound-with-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord Questions: A Computational Approach To Diversity Analysis in News Coverage</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discord-questions-a-computational-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are many potential benefits to news readers accessing diverse sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discord-questions-a-computational-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcome-Oriented Prescriptive Process Monitoring Based on Temporal Logic Patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outcome-oriented-prescriptive-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such encoded log is used to train a Machine Learning classifier to learn a mapping between the temporal patterns and the outcome of a process execution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outcome-oriented-prescriptive-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACSum: Controllable Summarization with Mixed Attributes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/macsum-controllable-summarization-with-mixed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose two simple and effective parameter-efficient approaches for the new task of mixed controllable summarization based on hard prompt tuning and soft prefix tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/macsum-controllable-summarization-with-mixed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best of Both Worlds: a Framework for Combining Degradation Prediction with High Performance Super-Resolution Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-best-of-both-worlds-a-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To date, the best-performing blind super-resolution (SR) techniques follow one of two paradigms: A) generate and train a standard SR network on synthetic low-resolution - high-resolution (LR - HR) pairs or B) attempt to predict the degradations an LR image has suffered and use these to inform a customised SR network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-best-of-both-worlds-a-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep W-Networks: Solving Multi-Objective Optimisation Problems With Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-w-networks-solving-multi-objective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we build on advances introduced by the Deep Q-Networks (DQN) approach to extend the multi-objective tabular Reinforcement Learning (RL) algorithm W-learning to large state spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-w-networks-solving-multi-objective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third-Party Aligner for Neural Word Alignments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/third-party-aligner-for-neural-word</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Word alignment is to find translationally equivalent words between source and target sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/third-party-aligner-for-neural-word</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crises Do Not Cause Lower Short-Term Growth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crises-do-not-cause-lower-short-term-growth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is commonly believed that financial crises "lead to" lower growth of a country during the two-year recession period, which can be reflected by their post-crisis GDP growth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crises-do-not-cause-lower-short-term-growth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Data Depth via Multi-Armed Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-data-depth-via-multi-armed-bandits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, we may want to find the most central point in a data set (a generalized median), or to identify and remove all outliers (points on the fringe of the data set with low depth).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-data-depth-via-multi-armed-bandits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPEN: Probing Conceptual Knowledge in Pre-trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copen-probing-conceptual-knowledge-in-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe this is a critical bottleneck for realizing human-like cognition in PLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copen-probing-conceptual-knowledge-in-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Significance-Based Categorical Data Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/significance-based-categorical-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a by-product, we can further calculate an empirical $p$-value to assess the statistical significance of a set of clusters and develop an improved gap statistic for estimating the cluster number.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/significance-based-categorical-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When &amp; How to Transfer with Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-how-to-transfer-with-transfer-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In deep learning, transfer learning (TL) has become the de facto approach when dealing with image related tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-how-to-transfer-with-transfer-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleviating Sparsity of Open Knowledge Graphs with Ternary Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alleviating-sparsity-of-open-knowledge-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparsity of formal knowledge and roughness of non-ontological construction make sparsity problem particularly prominent in Open Knowledge Graphs (OpenKGs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alleviating-sparsity-of-open-knowledge-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLATE: A Sequence Labeling Approach for Task Extraction from Free-form Inked Content</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slate-a-sequence-labeling-approach-for-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SLATE, a sequence labeling approach for extracting tasks from free-form content such as digitally handwritten (or "inked") notes on a virtual whiteboard.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slate-a-sequence-labeling-approach-for-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dynamic Graph Interactive Framework with Label-Semantic Injection for Spoken Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamic-graph-interactive-framework-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-intent detection and slot filling joint models are gaining increasing traction since they are closer to complicated real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamic-graph-interactive-framework-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Discovery in Linear Latent Variable Models Subject to Measurement Error</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-in-linear-latent-variable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate a somewhat surprising connection between this problem and causal discovery in the presence of unobserved parentless causes, in the sense that there is a mapping, given by the mixing matrix, between the underlying models to be inferred in these problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-in-linear-latent-variable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going for GOAL: A Resource for Grounded Football Commentaries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/going-for-goal-a-resource-for-grounded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the course of a game is unpredictable, so are commentaries, which makes them a unique resource to investigate dynamic language grounding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/going-for-goal-a-resource-for-grounded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Follow Instructions in Text-Based Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-follow-instructions-in-text-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-based games present a unique class of sequential decision making problem in which agents interact with a partially observable, simulated environment via actions and observations conveyed through natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-follow-instructions-in-text-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reduced Order Probabilistic Emulation for Physics-Based Thermosphere Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduced-order-probabilistic-emulation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The geospace environment is volatile and highly driven.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduced-order-probabilistic-emulation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OutlierDetection.jl: A modular outlier detection ecosystem for the Julia programming language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlierdetection-jl-a-modular-outlier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, it provides a standardized, yet flexible, interface for future outlier detection algorithms and allows for model composition unseen in previous packages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlierdetection-jl-a-modular-outlier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperparameter optimization in deep multi-target prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameter-optimization-in-deep-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result of the ever increasing complexity of configuring and fine-tuning machine learning models, the field of automated machine learning (AutoML) has emerged over the past decade.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameter-optimization-in-deep-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COV19IR : COVID-19 Domain Literature Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cov19ir-covid-19-domain-literature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Increasing number of COVID-19 research literatures cause new challenges in effective literature screening and COVID-19 domain knowledge aware Information Retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cov19ir-covid-19-domain-literature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Unstructured Knowledge Access in Conversational Dialogue with ASR Errors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-unstructured-knowledge-access-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge cluster classification is boosted from 0. 7924 to 0. 9333 in Recall@1.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-unstructured-knowledge-access-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spoofing Attack Detection in the Physical Layer with Commutative Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spoofing-attack-detection-in-the-physical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a spoofing attack, an attacker impersonates a legitimate user to access or tamper with data intended for or produced by the legitimate user.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spoofing-attack-detection-in-the-physical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preserving Semantics in Textual Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-semantics-in-textual-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of this kind of adversarial attack is to modify the input text to fool a classifier while maintaining the original meaning of the text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-semantics-in-textual-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhaseAug: A Differentiable Augmentation for Speech Synthesis to Simulate One-to-Many Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phaseaug-a-differentiable-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous generative adversarial network (GAN)-based neural vocoders are trained to reconstruct the exact ground truth waveform from the paired mel-spectrogram and do not consider the one-to-many relationship of speech synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phaseaug-a-differentiable-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Quantum Programming with Unbounded Loops</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-quantum-programming-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emergence of variational quantum applications has led to the development of automatic differentiation techniques in quantum computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-quantum-programming-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Graph Neural Networks at Scale: Combining Approximate PageRank and CoreRank</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-graph-neural-networks-at-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have achieved great successes in many learning tasks performed on graph structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-graph-neural-networks-at-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Shortcuts in Medical Images -- A Case Study in Chest X-rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-shortcuts-in-medical-images-a-case</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The availability of large public datasets and the increased amount of computing power have shifted the interest of the medical community to high-performance algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-shortcuts-in-medical-images-a-case</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing Down(stream)time: Pretraining Molecular GNNs using Heterogeneous AI Accelerators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-down-stream-time-pretraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The demonstrated success of transfer learning has popularized approaches that involve pretraining models from massive data sources and subsequent finetuning towards a specific task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-down-stream-time-pretraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimOn: A Simple Framework for Online Temporal Action Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simon-a-simple-framework-for-online-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, the evaluation for Online Detection of Action Start (ODAS) demonstrates the effectiveness and robustness of our method in the online setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simon-a-simple-framework-for-online-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Summarization via Node Grouping: A Spectral Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-summarization-via-node-grouping-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By initially allowing relaxed (fractional) solutions for integer maximization, we analytically expose the underlying connections to the spectral properties of the adjacency matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-summarization-via-node-grouping-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning advisor networks for noisy image classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-advisor-networks-for-noisy-image-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduced the novel concept of advisor network to address the problem of noisy labels in image classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-advisor-networks-for-noisy-image-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Determining Accessible Sidewalk Width by Extracting Obstacle Information from Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/determining-accessible-sidewalk-width-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Obstacles on the sidewalk often block the path, limiting passage and resulting in frustration and wasted time, especially for citizens and visitors who use assistive devices (wheelchairs, walkers, strollers, canes, etc).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/determining-accessible-sidewalk-width-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective compression learning of latent representations for variable-rate image compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-compression-learning-of-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this, we first generate a 3D importance map as the nature of input content to represent the underlying importance of the representation elements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-compression-learning-of-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BER: Balanced Error Rate For Speaker Diarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ber-balanced-error-rate-for-speaker</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DER is the primary metric to evaluate diarization performance while facing a dilemma: the errors in short utterances or segments tend to be overwhelmed by longer ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ber-balanced-error-rate-for-speaker</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new BART prior for flexible modeling with categorical predictors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-bart-prior-for-flexible-modeling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Regression trees built with these indicators partition the levels using a ``remove one a time strategy.'']]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-bart-prior-for-flexible-modeling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubly Inhomogeneous Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doubly-inhomogeneous-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, by borrowing information over time and population, it allows us to detect weaker signals and has better convergence properties when compared to applying the clustering algorithm per time or the change point detection algorithm per subject.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doubly-inhomogeneous-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Individualized and Global Feature Attributions for Gradient Boosted Trees in the Presence of $\ell_2$ Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individualized-and-global-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Prediction Decomposition Attribution (PreDecomp), a novel individualized feature attribution for gradient boosted trees when they are trained with $\ell_2$ regularization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individualized-and-global-feature</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
