<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 21:09:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of the performance of U-Net neural networks for the segmentation of living cells</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-the-performance-of-u-net-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The automated analysis of microscopy images is a challenge in the context of single-cell tracking and quantification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-the-performance-of-u-net-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Transformer Can Understand Both 2D &amp; 3D Molecular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-transformer-can-understand-both-2d-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this goal, in this work, we develop a novel Transformer-based Molecular model called Transformer-M, which can take molecular data of 2D or 3D formats as input and generate meaningful semantic representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-transformer-can-understand-both-2d-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Monitoring of User Stress, Heart Rate and Heart Rate Variability on Mobile Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-monitoring-of-user-stress-heart</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The user's pulse wave is then used to determine stress (according to the Baevsky Stress Index), heart rate, and heart rate variability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-monitoring-of-user-stress-heart</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffDock: Diffusion Steps, Twists, and Turns for Molecular Docking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffdock-diffusion-steps-twists-and-turns-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting the binding structure of a small molecule ligand to a protein -- a task known as molecular docking -- is critical to drug design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffdock-diffusion-steps-twists-and-turns-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpBoost: A Vertical Federated Tree Boosting Framework Based on Order-Preserving Desensitization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opboost-a-vertical-federated-tree-boosting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the solution based on Local Differential Privacy (LDP) addresses the above problems, it leads to the low accuracy of the trained model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opboost-a-vertical-federated-tree-boosting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Models and Learning Algorithms for Core-Periphery Structured Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-models-and-learning-algorithms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on learning the core scores of a graph from its node attributes and connectivity structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-models-and-learning-algorithms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concise and interpretable multi-label rule sets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concise-and-interpretable-multi-label-rule</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-label classification is becoming increasingly ubiquitous, but not much attention has been paid to interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concise-and-interpretable-multi-label-rule</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Models for Graphs Benefit From Discrete State Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-for-graphs-benefit-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Denoising diffusion probabilistic models and score matching models have proven to be very powerful for generative tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-for-graphs-benefit-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Log-Linear-Time Gaussian Processes Using Binary Tree Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/log-linear-time-gaussian-processes-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new kernel that allows for Gaussian process regression in $O((n+m)\log(n+m))$ time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/log-linear-time-gaussian-processes-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centroid Distance Keypoint Detector for Colored Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centroid-distance-keypoint-detector-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results demonstrate that our proposed CED keypoint detector requires minimal computational time while attaining high repeatability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centroid-distance-keypoint-detector-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When to Make Exceptions: Exploring Language Models as Accounts of Human Moral Judgment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-make-exceptions-exploring-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using a state-of-the-art large language model (LLM) as a basis, we propose a novel moral chain of thought (MORALCOT) prompting strategy that combines the strengths of LLMs with theories of moral reasoning developed in cognitive science to predict human moral judgments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-make-exceptions-exploring-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HYPRO: A Hybridly Normalized Probabilistic Model for Long-Horizon Prediction of Event Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypro-a-hybridly-normalized-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we tackle the important yet under-investigated problem of making long-horizon prediction of event sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypro-a-hybridly-normalized-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDFAIR: Benchmarking Fairness for Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medfair-benchmarking-fairness-for-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce MEDFAIR, a framework to benchmark the fairness of machine learning models for medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medfair-benchmarking-fairness-for-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dense Prediction Transformer for Scale Estimation in Monocular Visual Odometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-prediction-transformer-for-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monocular visual odometry consists of the estimation of the position of an agent through images of a single camera, and it is applied in autonomous vehicles, medical robots, and augmented reality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-prediction-transformer-for-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complementary consistency semi-supervised learning for 3D left atrial image segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complementary-consistency-semi-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A complementary consistency training is formed by the inter-model perturbation between the primary model and the auxiliary models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complementary-consistency-semi-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICRegL: Self-Supervised Learning of Local Visual Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vicregl-self-supervised-learning-of-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most recent self-supervised methods for learning image representations focus on either producing a global feature with invariance properties, or producing a set of local features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vicregl-self-supervised-learning-of-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Background Bias in Deep Metric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-background-bias-in-deep-metric-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Metric Learning trains a neural network to map input images to a lower-dimensional embedding space such that similar images are closer together than dissimilar images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-background-bias-in-deep-metric-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Target Training for Multi-Source Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-target-training-for-multi-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given any existing fully-trained one-step MSDA model, BORT$^2$ turns it to a labeling function to generate pseudo-labels for the target data and trains a target model using pseudo-labeled target data only.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-target-training-for-multi-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COARSE3D: Class-Prototypes for Contrastive Learning in Weakly-Supervised 3D Point Cloud Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse3d-class-prototypes-for-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Annotation of large-scale 3D data is notoriously cumbersome and costly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse3d-class-prototypes-for-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Lipschitz Neural Networks for Certified L-infinity Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-lipschitz-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing neural networks with bounded Lipschitz constant is a promising way to obtain certifiably robust classifiers against adversarial examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-lipschitz-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Image Restoration with Attention Retractable Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-image-restoration-with-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is considered as a dense attention strategy since the interactions of tokens are restrained in dense regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-image-restoration-with-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APAUNet: Axis Projection Attention UNet for Small Target in 3D Medical Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apaunet-axis-projection-attention-unet-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In 3D medical image segmentation, small targets segmentation is crucial for diagnosis but still faces challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apaunet-axis-projection-attention-unet-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooperative Self-Training for Multi-Target Adaptive Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-self-training-for-multi-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we address multi-target domain adaptation (MTDA) in semantic segmentation, which consists in adapting a single model from an annotated source dataset to multiple unannotated target datasets that differ in their underlying data distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-self-training-for-multi-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Positive Pair Distillation Considered Harmful: Continual Meta Metric Learning for Lifelong Object Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/positive-pair-distillation-considered-harmful</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lifelong object re-identification incrementally learns from a stream of re-identification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/positive-pair-distillation-considered-harmful</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MBW: Multi-view Bootstrapping in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbw-multi-view-bootstrapping-in-the-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our Multi-view Bootstrapping in the Wild (MBW) approach demonstrates impressive results on standard human datasets, as well as tigers, cheetahs, fish, colobus monkeys, chimpanzees, and flamingos from videos captured casually in a zoo.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbw-multi-view-bootstrapping-in-the-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreDSNet: Joint Monocular Depth and Semantic Segmentation with Fast Fourier Convolutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fredsnet-joint-monocular-depth-and-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments show that FreDSNet has similar performance as specific state of the art methods for semantic segmentation and depth estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fredsnet-joint-monocular-depth-and-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How deep convolutional neural networks lose spatial information with training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-deep-convolutional-neural-networks-lose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we (i) show empirically for various architectures that stability to image diffeomorphisms is achieved by spatial pooling in the first half of the net, and by channel pooling in the second half, (ii) introduce a scale-detection task for a simple model of data where pooling is learned during training, which captures all empirical observations above and (iii) compute in this model how stability to diffeomorphisms and noise scale with depth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-deep-convolutional-neural-networks-lose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monte Carlo Tree Search based Variable Selection for High Dimensional Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-tree-search-based-variable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian optimization (BO) is a class of popular methods for expensive black-box optimization, and has been widely applied to many scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-tree-search-based-variable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explanation-by-Example Based on Item Response Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanation-by-example-based-on-item-response</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intelligent systems that use Machine Learning classification algorithms are increasingly common in everyday society.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanation-by-example-based-on-item-response</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Spectrogram Temporal Resolution for Audio Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-spectrogram-temporal-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Starting from a high-temporal-resolution spectrogram such as one-millisecond hop size, we show that DiffRes can improve classification accuracy with the same computational complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-spectrogram-temporal-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhythmic Gesticulator: Rhythm-Aware Co-Speech Gesture Synthesis with Hierarchical Neural Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rhythmic-gesticulator-rhythm-aware-co-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel co-speech gesture synthesis method that achieves convincing results both on the rhythm and semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rhythmic-gesticulator-rhythm-aware-co-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Unlearning for Mitigating Privacy Risks in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-unlearning-for-mitigating-privacy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pretrained Language Models (LMs) memorize a vast amount of knowledge during initial pretraining, including information that may violate the privacy of personal lives and identities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-unlearning-for-mitigating-privacy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Collocate Visual-Linguistic Neural Modules for Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-collocate-visual-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is because the language is only partially observable, for which we need to dynamically collocate the modules during the process of image captioning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-collocate-visual-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mintaka: A Complex, Natural, and Multilingual Dataset for End-to-End Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mintaka-a-complex-natural-and-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Mintaka, a complex, natural, and multilingual dataset designed for experimenting with end-to-end question-answering models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mintaka-a-complex-natural-and-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Label-Deficient Keyword Spotting Using Self-Supervised Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-label-deficient-keyword-spotting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the use of self-supervised pretraining for the smaller KWS models in a label-deficient scenario.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-label-deficient-keyword-spotting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fill in Fabrics: Body-Aware Self-Supervised Inpainting for Image-Based Virtual Try-On</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fill-in-fabrics-body-aware-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous virtual try-on methods usually focus on aligning a clothing item with a person, limiting their ability to exploit the complex pose, shape and skin color of the person, as well as the overall structure of the clothing, which is vital to photo-realistic virtual try-on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fill-in-fabrics-body-aware-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Synthetic Data with The Nearest Neighbors Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-synthetic-data-with-the-nearest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The $k$ nearest neighbor algorithm ($k$NN) is one of the most popular nonparametric methods used for various purposes, such as treatment effect estimation, missing value imputation, classification, and clustering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-synthetic-data-with-the-nearest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The current state of single-cell proteomics data analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-current-state-of-single-cell-proteomics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sound data analysis is essential to retrieve meaningful biological information from single-cell proteomics experiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-current-state-of-single-cell-proteomics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention Distillation: self-supervised vision transformer students need more guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-distillation-self-supervised-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In experiments on ImageNet-Subset and ImageNet-1K, we show that our method AttnDistill outperforms existing self-supervised knowledge distillation (SSKD) methods and achieves state-of-the-art k-NN accuracy compared with self-supervised learning (SSL) methods learning from scratch (with the ViT-S model).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-distillation-self-supervised-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under the Cover Infant Pose Estimation using Multimodal Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/under-the-cover-infant-pose-estimation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we present a novel dataset, Simultaneously-collected multimodal Mannequin Lying pose (SMaL) dataset, for under the cover infant pose estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/under-the-cover-infant-pose-estimation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Paradigms for Exploiting Parallel Experiments in Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-paradigms-for-exploiting-parallel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, a key limitation of BO is that it is an inherently sequential algorithm (one experiment is proposed per round) and thus cannot directly exploit high-throughput (parallel) experiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-paradigms-for-exploiting-parallel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Driven Active Vision for Implicit Scene Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-driven-active-vision-for-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our proposed approach on the ABC dataset and the in the wild CO3D dataset, and show that: (1) we are able to obtain high quality state-of-the-art occupancy reconstructions; (2) our perspective conditioned uncertainty definition is effective to drive improvements in next best view selection and outperforms strong baseline approaches; and (3) we can further improve shape understanding by performing a gradient-based search on the view selection candidates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-driven-active-vision-for-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Effectiveness of Masked Language Modeling and Adapters for Factual Knowledge Injection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effectiveness-of-masked-language-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the problem of injecting factual knowledge into large pre-trained language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effectiveness-of-masked-language-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Equivariant Segmentation with Instance-Unique Querying</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-equivariant-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prevalent state-of-the-art instance segmentation methods fall into a query-based scheme, in which instance masks are derived by querying the image feature using a set of instance-aware embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-equivariant-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpeechCLIP: Integrating Speech with Pre-Trained Vision and Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechclip-integrating-speech-with-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data-driven speech processing models usually perform well with a large amount of text supervision, but collecting transcribed speech data is costly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechclip-integrating-speech-with-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BVI-VFI: A Video Quality Database for Video Frame Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bvi-vfi-a-video-quality-database-for-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to narrow this research gap, we have developed a new video quality database named BVI-VFI, which contains 540 distorted sequences generated by applying five commonly used VFI algorithms to 36 diverse source videos with various spatial resolutions and frame rates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bvi-vfi-a-video-quality-database-for-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenDexGrasp: Generalizable Dexterous Grasping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gendexgrasp-generalizable-dexterous-grasping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By leveraging the contact map as a hand-agnostic intermediate representation, GenDexGrasp efficiently generates diverse and plausible grasping poses with a high success rate and can transfer among diverse multi-fingered robotic hands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gendexgrasp-generalizable-dexterous-grasping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hypothesis Engineering for Zero-Shot Hate Speech Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypothesis-engineering-for-zero-shot-hate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the zero-shot baseline used for the initial error analysis already outperforms commercial systems and fine-tuned BERT-based hate speech detection models on HateCheck.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypothesis-engineering-for-zero-shot-hate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPARC: Sparse Render-and-Compare for CAD model alignment in a single RGB image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparc-sparse-render-and-compare-for-cad-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This combined information is the input to a pose prediction network, SPARC-Net which we train to predict a 9 DoF CAD model pose update.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparc-sparse-render-and-compare-for-cad-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Multimodal Change Detection Based on Structural Relationship Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-multimodal-change-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, the similarity levels of two structural relationships are calculated from learned graph representations and two difference images are generated based on the similarity levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-multimodal-change-detection</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
