<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 21:09:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CycleBNN: Cyclic Precision Training in Binary Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cyclebnn-cyclic-precision-training-in-binary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper works on Binary Neural Networks (BNNs), a promising avenue for efficient deep learning, offering significant reductions in computational overhead and memory footprint to full precision networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cyclebnn-cyclic-precision-training-in-binary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ManiSkill3: GPU Parallelized Robotics Simulation and Rendering for Generalizable Embodied AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maniskill3-gpu-parallelized-robotics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce and open source ManiSkill3, the fastest state-visual GPU parallelized robotics simulator with contact-rich physics targeting generalizable manipulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maniskill3-gpu-parallelized-robotics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enabling Synergistic Full-Body Control in Prompt-Based Co-Speech Motion Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-synergistic-full-body-control-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current co-speech motion generation approaches usually focus on upper body gestures following speech contents only, while lacking supporting the elaborate control of synergistic full-body motion based on text prompts, such as talking while walking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-synergistic-full-body-control-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Privacy Renewable! Generating Privacy-Preserving Faces Supporting Cancelable Biometric Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-privacy-renewable-generating-privacy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a cancelable face generator (CanFG), which removes the physical identity for privacy protection and embeds the virtual identity for face recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-privacy-renewable-generating-privacy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Posterior-Mean Rectified Flow: Towards Minimum MSE Photo-Realistic Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posterior-mean-rectified-flow-towards-minimum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Photo-realistic image restoration algorithms are typically evaluated by distortion measures (e. g., PSNR, SSIM) and by perceptual quality measures (e. g., FID, NIQE), where the desire is to attain the lowest possible distortion without compromising on perceptual quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posterior-mean-rectified-flow-towards-minimum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trainable pruned ternary quantization for medical signal classification models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trainable-pruned-ternary-quantization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of deep learning is renowned for its resource-intensive nature, hence improving its environmental impact is crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trainable-pruned-ternary-quantization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volumetric Conditional Score-based Residual Diffusion Model for PET/MR Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volumetric-conditional-score-based-residual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PET imaging is a powerful modality offering quantitative assessments of molecular and physiological processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volumetric-conditional-score-based-residual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAOcc: 3D Object Detection Assisted Multi-Sensor Fusion for 3D Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/daocc-3d-object-detection-assisted-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose DAOcc, a novel multi-sensor fusion occupancy network that leverages 3D object detection supervision to assist in achieving superior performance, while using a deployment-friendly image feature extraction network and practical input image resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/daocc-3d-object-detection-assisted-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProFD: Prompt-Guided Feature Disentangling for Occluded Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/profd-prompt-guided-feature-disentangling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the occlusion issues in person Re-Identification (ReID) tasks, many methods have been proposed to extract part features by introducing external spatial information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/profd-prompt-guided-feature-disentangling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing interaction recovery of predicted protein-ligand poses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-interaction-recovery-of-predicted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of protein-ligand pose prediction has seen significant advances in recent years, with machine learning-based methods now being commonly used in lieu of classical docking methods or even to predict all-atom protein-ligand complex structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-interaction-recovery-of-predicted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CycleCrash: A Dataset of Bicycle Collision Videos for Collision Prediction and Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cyclecrash-a-dataset-of-bicycle-collision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, we propose VidNeXt, a novel method that leverages a ConvNeXt spatial encoder and a non-stationary transformer to capture the temporal dynamics of videos for the tasks defined in our dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cyclecrash-a-dataset-of-bicycle-collision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RouterDC: Query-Based Router by Dual Contrastive Learning for Assembling Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/routerdc-query-based-router-by-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this, routing is a promising method, which learns a router to select the most suitable LLM for each query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/routerdc-query-based-router-by-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PerCo (SD): Open Perceptual Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perco-sd-open-perceptual-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce PerCo (SD), a perceptual image compression method based on Stable Diffusion v2. 1, targeting the ultra-low bit range.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perco-sd-open-perceptual-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWIM: Short-Window CNN Integrated with Mamba for EEG-Based Auditory Spatial Attention Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swim-short-window-cnn-integrated-with-mamba</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By joint training SW$_\text{CNN}$ and Mamba, the proposed SWIM structure uses both short-term and long-term information and achieves an accuracy of 86. 2%, which reduces the classification errors by a relative 31. 0% compared to the previous state-of-the-art result.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swim-short-window-cnn-integrated-with-mamba</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MemSim: A Bayesian Simulator for Evaluating Memory of LLM-based Personal Assistants</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memsim-a-bayesian-simulator-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLM-based agents have been widely applied as personal assistants, capable of memorizing information from user messages and responding to personal queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memsim-a-bayesian-simulator-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PuzzleBoard: A New Camera Calibration Pattern with Position Encoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puzzleboard-a-new-camera-calibration-pattern</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate camera calibration is a well-known and widely used task in computer vision that has been researched for decades.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puzzleboard-a-new-camera-calibration-pattern</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Non-Maximum Suppression: A Graph Theory Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-non-maximum-suppression-a-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The optimal eQSI-NMS, with only a $0. 3\%$ mAP decrease, achieves $10. 7\times$ speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-non-maximum-suppression-a-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Law of the Weakest Link: Cross Capabilities of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/law-of-the-weakest-link-cross-capabilities-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development and evaluation of Large Language Models (LLMs) have largely focused on individual capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/law-of-the-weakest-link-cross-capabilities-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaskComplexity: A Dataset for Task Complexity Classification with In-Context Learning, FLAN-T5 and GPT-4o Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskcomplexity-a-dataset-for-task-complexity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this issue, a novel dataset containing a total of 4, 112 programming tasks was created by extracting tasks from various websites.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskcomplexity-a-dataset-for-task-complexity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GrokLST: Towards High-Resolution Benchmark and Toolkit for Land Surface Temperature Downscaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/groklst-towards-high-resolution-benchmark-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Land Surface Temperature (LST) is a critical parameter for environmental studies, but obtaining high-resolution LST data remains challenging due to the spatio-temporal trade-off in satellite remote sensing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/groklst-towards-high-resolution-benchmark-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Classification of Near-Surface Shallow-Water Sediments using A Portable Free-Fall Penetrometer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-classification-of-near-surface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The geotechnical evaluation of seabed sediments is important for engineering projects and naval applications, offering valuable insights into sediment properties, behavior, and strength.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-classification-of-near-surface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Textual Training for the Hassle-Free Removal of Unwanted Visual Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textual-training-for-the-hassle-free-removal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the analysis, we propose Hassle-Free Textual Training (HFTT), a streamlined method capable of acquiring detectors for unwanted visual content, using only synthetic textual data in conjunction with pre-trained vision-language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textual-training-for-the-hassle-free-removal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LexEval: A Comprehensive Chinese Legal Benchmark for Evaluating Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexeval-a-comprehensive-chinese-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applying existing LLMs to legal systems without careful evaluation of their potential and limitations could pose significant risks in legal practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexeval-a-comprehensive-chinese-legal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing High-order Interaction Awareness in LLM-based Recommender Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-high-order-interaction-awareness-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated prominent reasoning capabilities in recommendation tasks by transforming them into text-generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-high-order-interaction-awareness-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsyGUARD: An Automated System for Suicide Detection and Risk Assessment in Psychological Counseling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psyguard-an-automated-system-for-suicide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study not only provides an insightful analysis of the effectiveness of automated risk assessment systems based on fine-grained suicide detection but also highlights their potential to improve mental health services on online counseling platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psyguard-an-automated-system-for-suicide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camera Calibration using a Collimator System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camera-calibration-using-a-collimator-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel camera calibration method using a collimator system, which can provide a reliable and controllable calibration environment for cameras with varying working distances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camera-calibration-using-a-collimator-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Graph Embedding by Normalizing Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graph-embedding-by-normalizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reflect uncertainty, we first embed entities/relations as permutations of a set of random variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graph-embedding-by-normalizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HazyDet: Open-source Benchmark for Drone-view Object Detection with Depth-cues in Hazy Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hazydet-open-source-benchmark-for-drone-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By observing the significant variations in object scale and clarity under different depth and haze conditions, we designed a Depth Conditioned Detector (DeCoDet) to incorporate this prior knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hazydet-open-source-benchmark-for-drone-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melody Is All You Need For Music Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melody-is-all-you-need-for-music-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Melody Guided Music Generation (MMGen) model, the first novel approach using melody to guide the music generation that, despite a pretty simple method and extremely limited resources, achieves excellent performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melody-is-all-you-need-for-music-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On The Planning Abilities of OpenAI's o1 Models: Feasibility, Optimality, and Generalizability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-planning-abilities-of-openai-s-o1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in Large Language Models (LLMs) have showcased their ability to perform complex reasoning tasks, but their effectiveness in planning remains underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-planning-abilities-of-openai-s-o1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniSumEval: Towards Unified, Fine-Grained, Multi-Dimensional Summarization Evaluation for LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unisumeval-towards-unified-fine-grained-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing benchmarks for summarization quality evaluation often lack diverse input scenarios, focus on narrowly defined dimensions (e. g., faithfulness), and struggle with subjective and coarse-grained annotation schemes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unisumeval-towards-unified-fine-grained-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-in-One Image Coding for Joint Human-Machine Vision with Multi-Path Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-in-one-image-coding-for-joint-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results show that MPA achieves performance comparable to state-of-the-art methods in both task-specific and multi-objective optimization across human viewing and machine analysis tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-in-one-image-coding-for-joint-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OrientedFormer: An End-to-End Transformer-Based Oriented Object Detector in Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orientedformer-an-end-to-end-transformer-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, directly extending transformers to oriented object detection presents three main issues: 1) objects rotate arbitrarily, necessitating the encoding of angles along with position and size; 2) the geometric relations of oriented objects are lacking in self-attention, due to the absence of interaction between content and positional queries; and 3) oriented objects cause misalignment, mainly between values and positional queries in cross-attention, making accurate classification and localization difficult.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orientedformer-an-end-to-end-transformer-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoT-ST: Enhancing LLM-based Speech Translation with Multimodal Chain-of-Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cot-st-enhancing-llm-based-speech-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose CoT-ST, a speech translation model that utilizes multimodal CoT to decompose speech translation into sequential steps of speech recognition and translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cot-st-enhancing-llm-based-speech-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing Personality Traits: A New Benchmark Dataset for Explainable Personality Recognition on Dialogues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-personality-traits-a-new-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel task named Explainable Personality Recognition, aiming to reveal the reasoning process as supporting evidence of the personality trait.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-personality-traits-a-new-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Diffusion Transformer Architecture for Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-diffusion-transformer-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we design an effective diffusion transformer for image super-resolution (DiT-SR) that achieves the visual quality of prior-based methods, but through a training-from-scratch manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-diffusion-transformer-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafting Distribution Shifts for Validation and Training in Single Source Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crafting-distribution-shifts-for-validation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The method that achieves the best performance on the augmented validation is selected from the proposed family.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crafting-distribution-shifts-for-validation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic debiasing of neural networks via moment-constrained learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-debiasing-of-neural-networks-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal and nonparametric estimands in economics and biostatistics can often be viewed as the mean of a linear functional applied to an unknown outcome regression function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-debiasing-of-neural-networks-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underwater Organism Color Enhancement via Color Code Decomposition, Adaptation and Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/underwater-organism-color-enhancement-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ColorCode offers three key features: 1) color enhancement, producing an enhanced image with a fixed color; 2) color adaptation, enabling controllable adjustments of long-wavelength color components using guidance images; and 3) color interpolation, allowing for the smooth generation of multiple colors through continuous sampling of the color code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/underwater-organism-color-enhancement-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuoGNN: Topology-aware Graph Neural Network with Homophily and Heterophily Interaction-Decoupling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/duognn-topology-aware-graph-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to the local neighborhood aggregation paradigm in message passing which characterizes these models, they inherently suffer from two fundamental limitations: first, indistinguishable node embeddings due to heterophilic node aggregation (known as over-smoothing), and second, impaired message passing due to aggregation through graph bottlenecks (known as over-squashing).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/duognn-topology-aware-graph-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolving Multi-Scale Normalization for Time Series Forecasting under Distribution Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolving-multi-scale-normalization-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Complex distribution shifts are the main obstacle to achieving accurate long-term time series forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolving-multi-scale-normalization-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Mamba for Few-Shot Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-mamba-for-few-shot-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, we aim to devise a cross (attention-like) Mamba to capture inter-sequence dependencies for FSS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-mamba-for-few-shot-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Crucial Role of Samplers in Online Direct Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-crucial-role-of-samplers-in-online-direct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Direct Preference Optimization (DPO) has emerged as a stable, scalable, and efficient solution for language model alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-crucial-role-of-samplers-in-online-direct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple and Fast Distillation of Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-and-fast-distillation-of-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion-based generative models have demonstrated their powerful performance across various tasks, but this comes at a cost of the slow sampling speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-and-fast-distillation-of-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating the Negative Impact of Over-association for Conversational Query Production</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-the-negative-impact-of-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We carefully analyze the negative effects of this phenomenon on pretrained Seq2seq query producers and then propose effective instance-level weighting strategies for training to mitigate these issues from multiple perspectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-the-negative-impact-of-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient is All You Need: Gradient-Based Attention Fusion for Infrared Small Target Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-is-all-you-need-gradient-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Infrared small target detection (IRSTD) is widely used in civilian and military applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-is-all-you-need-gradient-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-based Camera-Agnostic Feature Learning for Intra-camera Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-based-camera-agnostic-feature-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose a novel framework called CLIP-based Camera-Agnostic Feature Learning (CCAFL) for ICS ReID.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-based-camera-agnostic-feature-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Large Language Models Analyze Graphs like Professionals? A Benchmark, Datasets and Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-analyze-graphs-like</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results underscore that the capabilities of LLMs in handling structured data are still under-explored, and show the effectiveness of LLM4Graph in enhancing LLMs' proficiency of graph analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-analyze-graphs-like</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See Detail Say Clear: Towards Brain CT Report Generation via Pathological Clue-driven Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/see-detail-say-clear-towards-brain-ct-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[2) Shifted semantic representing: Limited medical corpus causes difficulties for models to transfer the learned textual representations to generative layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/see-detail-say-clear-towards-brain-ct-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifying Knowledge Editing Types in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-knowledge-editing-types-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, there is a lack of effective measures to prevent the malicious misuse of this technology, which could lead to harmful edits in LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-knowledge-editing-types-in-large</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
