<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 09:15:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>AdaCAD: Adaptively Decoding to Balance Conflicts between Contextual and Parametric Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adacad-adaptively-decoding-to-balance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge conflict arises from discrepancies between information in the context of a large language model (LLM) and the knowledge stored in its parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adacad-adaptively-decoding-to-balance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent Workflow Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-workflow-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the potential of language model-based agents to solve real-world tasks such as web navigation, current methods still struggle with long-horizon tasks with complex action trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-workflow-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ontology-Free General-Domain Knowledge Graph-to-Text Generation Dataset Synthesis using Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontology-free-general-domain-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method proves to be a scalable and effective solution for generating high-quality G2T data, significantly advancing the field of G2T generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontology-free-general-domain-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asymptotics of Stochastic Gradient Descent with Dropout Regularization in Linear Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymptotics-of-stochastic-gradient-descent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes an asymptotic theory for online inference of the stochastic gradient descent (SGD) iterates with dropout regularization in linear regression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymptotics-of-stochastic-gradient-descent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy Filtration in RLHF to Fine-Tune LLM for Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-filtration-in-rlhf-to-fine-tune-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement learning from human feedback (RLHF) is one of the key techniques that helps large language models (LLMs) to follow instructions and provide helpful and harmless responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-filtration-in-rlhf-to-fine-tune-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCFExp: Facial Image Synthesis with Cycle Cross-Fusion Diffusion Model for Facial Paralysis Individuals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccfexp-facial-image-synthesis-with-cycle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial paralysis is a debilitating condition that affects the movement of facial muscles, leading to a significant loss of facial expressions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccfexp-facial-image-synthesis-with-cycle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Fine-grained Sentiment Analysis of App Reviews using Large Language Models: An Evaluation Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fine-grained-sentiment-analysis-of-app</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the volume of user reviews received daily, an automated mechanism to generate feature-level sentiment summaries of user reviews is needed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fine-grained-sentiment-analysis-of-app</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVENet: Evidence-based Ensemble Learning for Uncertainty-aware Brain Parcellation Using Diffusion MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evenet-evidence-based-ensemble-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key innovation of EVENet is the design of an evidential deep learning framework to quantify predictive uncertainty at each voxel during a single inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evenet-evidence-based-ensemble-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diff-VPS: Video Polyp Segmentation via a Multi-task Diffusion Network with Adversarial Temporal Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diff-vps-video-polyp-segmentation-via-a-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We incorporate multi-task supervision into diffusion models to promote the discrimination of diffusion models on pixel-by-pixel segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diff-vps-video-polyp-segmentation-via-a-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER: Evaluating Agents on Setting Up and Executing Tasks from Research Repositories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-evaluating-agents-on-setting-up-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To advance towards this goal, we introduce SUPER, the first benchmark designed to evaluate the capability of LLMs in setting up and executing tasks from research repositories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-evaluating-agents-on-setting-up-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think Together and Work Better: Combining Humans' and LLMs' Think-Aloud Outcomes for Effective Text Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/think-together-and-work-better-combining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study introduces \textbf{InteractEval}, a framework that integrates human expertise and Large Language Models (LLMs) using the Think-Aloud (TA) method to generate attributes for checklist-based text evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/think-together-and-work-better-combining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Contrastive Loss for Self-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-contrastive-loss-for-self-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To benefit from these advantages in a semi-supervised setting, we propose a general framework to enhance self-training methods, which replaces all instances of CE losses with a unique contrastive loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-contrastive-loss-for-self-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Vision-Language Models with a Robust Encoder Against Jailbreak and Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/securing-vision-language-models-with-a-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sim-CLIP+ demonstrates effectiveness against both gradient-based adversarial attacks and various jailbreak techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/securing-vision-language-models-with-a-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hi3D: Pursuing High-Resolution Image-to-3D Generation with Video Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hi3d-pursuing-high-resolution-image-to-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite having tremendous progress in image-to-3D generation, existing methods still struggle to produce multi-view consistent images with high-resolution textures in detail, especially in the paradigm of 2D diffusion that lacks 3D awareness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hi3d-pursuing-high-resolution-image-to-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Augmentation via Latent Diffusion for Saliency Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-via-latent-diffusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel data augmentation method for deep saliency prediction that edits natural images while preserving the complexity and variability of real-world scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-via-latent-diffusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intrapartum Ultrasound Image Segmentation of Pubic Symphysis and Fetal Head Using Dual Student-Teacher Framework with CNN-ViT Collaborative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrapartum-ultrasound-image-segmentation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The teacher model further reinforces learning within this architecture through the imposition of consistency regularization constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrapartum-ultrasound-image-segmentation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TLD-READY: Traffic Light Detection -- Relevance Estimation and Deployment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tld-ready-traffic-light-detection-relevance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the DriveU dataset, this approach results in 96% accuracy in relevance estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tld-ready-traffic-light-detection-relevance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention Down-Sampling Transformer, Relative Ranking and Self-Consistency for Blind Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-down-sampling-transformer-relative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The no-reference image quality assessment is a challenging domain that addresses estimating image quality without the original reference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-down-sampling-transformer-relative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Realistic and Efficient Face Swapping: A Unified Approach with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realistic-and-efficient-face-swapping-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike prior works reliant on multiple off-the-shelf models, ours is a relatively unified approach and so it is resilient to errors in other off-the-shelf models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realistic-and-efficient-face-swapping-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1M-Deepfakes Detection Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1m-deepfakes-detection-challenge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The detection and localization of deepfake content, particularly when small fake segments are seamlessly mixed with real videos, remains a significant challenge in the field of digital media security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1m-deepfakes-detection-challenge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Adapter Routing for Long-Tailed Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-adapter-routing-for-long-tailed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we harness the potent representation capabilities of pre-trained models and introduce AdaPtive Adapter RouTing (APART) as an exemplar-free solution for LTCIL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-adapter-routing-for-long-tailed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic continued pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-continued-pretraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose to bridge this gap with synthetic continued pretraining: using the small domain-specific corpus to synthesize a large corpus more amenable to learning, and then performing continued pretraining on the synthesized corpus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-continued-pretraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Knowledge Drift in LLMs through Misinformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-knowledge-drift-in-llms-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments reveal that an LLM's uncertainty can increase up to 56. 6% when the question is answered incorrectly due to the exposure to false information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-knowledge-drift-in-llms-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying Knee Cartilage Shape and Lesion: From Image to Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-knee-cartilage-shape-and-lesion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we developed a deep-learning-based medical image analysis application for knee cartilage morphometrics, CartiMorph Toolbox (CMT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-knee-cartilage-shape-and-lesion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftShadow: Leveraging Penumbra-Aware Soft Masks for Shadow Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softshadow-leveraging-penumbra-aware-soft</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In view of this, inspired by the physical model of shadow formation, we introduce novel soft shadow masks specifically designed for shadow removal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softshadow-leveraging-penumbra-aware-soft</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PiTe: Pixel-Temporal Alignment for Large Video-Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pite-pixel-temporal-alignment-for-large-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fueled by the Large Language Models (LLMs) wave, Large Visual-Language Models (LVLMs) have emerged as a pivotal advancement, bridging the gap between image and text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pite-pixel-temporal-alignment-for-large-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Representation Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, I show that a similar effect can be achieved by fine-tuning the vectors directly into the model, by use of a dual loss function based on the cosine similarity of residual stream activations to the vectors combined with a standard token-based loss ("representation tuning").]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTDA-HSED: Mutual-Assistance Tuning and Dual-Branch Aggregating for Heterogeneous Sound Event Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtda-hsed-mutual-assistance-tuning-and-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sound Event Detection (SED) plays a vital role in comprehending and perceiving acoustic scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtda-hsed-mutual-assistance-tuning-and-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face Mask Removal with Region-attentive Face Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-mask-removal-with-region-attentive-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, we propose a generative face inpainting method to effectively recover/reconstruct the masked part of a face.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-mask-removal-with-region-attentive-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context Enhancement with Reconstruction as Sequence for Unified Unsupervised Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-enhancement-with-reconstruction-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating the RASFormer block, our RAS method achieves superior contextual awareness capabilities, leading to remarkable performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-enhancement-with-reconstruction-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HybridFC: A Hybrid Fact-Checking Approach for Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybridfc-a-hybrid-fact-checking-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider fact-checking approaches that aim to predict the veracity of assertions in knowledge graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybridfc-a-hybrid-fact-checking-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly-supervised Camera Localization by Ground-to-satellite Image Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-camera-localization-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate this issue, this paper proposes a weakly supervised learning strategy for ground-to-satellite image registration when only noisy pose labels for ground images are available for network training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-camera-localization-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIME-M: Less Is More for Evaluation of MLLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lime-m-less-is-more-for-evaluation-of-mllms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Semi-Automated Screening Process filters out samples that cannot distinguish the model's capabilities by synthesizing various MLLMs and manually evaluating them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lime-m-less-is-more-for-evaluation-of-mllms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mahalanobis k-NN: A Statistical Lens for Robust Point-Cloud Registrations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mahalanobis-k-nn-a-statistical-lens-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we discuss Mahalanobis k-NN: a statistical lens designed to address the challenges of feature matching in learning-based point cloud registration when confronted with an arbitrary density of point clouds, either in the source or target point cloud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mahalanobis-k-nn-a-statistical-lens-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the Role of Small Models in the LLM Era: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-is-the-role-of-small-models-in-the-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have made significant progress in advancing artificial general intelligence (AGI), leading to the development of increasingly large models such as GPT-4 and LLaMA-405B.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-is-the-role-of-small-models-in-the-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniLearn: Enhancing Dynamic Facial Expression Recognition through Unified Pre-Training and Fine-Tuning on Images and Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unilearn-enhancing-dynamic-facial-expression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this, we introduce UniLearn, a novel unified learning paradigm that integrates static facial expression recognition (SFER) data to enhance DFER task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unilearn-enhancing-dynamic-facial-expression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaMA-Omni: Seamless Speech Interaction with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-omni-seamless-speech-interaction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We build our model based on the latest Llama-3. 1-8B-Instruct model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-omni-seamless-speech-interaction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DetailCLIP: Detail-Oriented CLIP for Fine-Grained Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detailclip-detail-oriented-clip-for-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce DetailCLIP: A Detail-Oriented CLIP to address the limitations of contrastive learning-based vision-language models, particularly CLIP, in handling detail-oriented and fine-grained tasks like segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detailclip-detail-oriented-clip-for-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoCalib: Learning Single-image Calibration with Geometric Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geocalib-learning-single-image-calibration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This single-image calibration can benefit various downstream applications like image editing and 3D mapping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geocalib-learning-single-image-calibration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>gsplat: An Open-Source Library for Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gsplat-an-open-source-library-for-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[gsplat is an open-source library designed for training and developing Gaussian Splatting methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gsplat-an-open-source-library-for-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RealisDance: Equip controllable character animation with realistic hands</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realisdance-equip-controllable-character</link>
      <description><![CDATA[2) The hands generated using the DWPose sequence are blurry and unrealistic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realisdance-equip-controllable-character</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Generative Interactive Environments By Trained Agent Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-generative-interactive-environments</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Genie, a recent model, excels at learning from visually diverse environments but relies on costly human-collected data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-generative-interactive-environments</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Source Music Generation with Latent Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-music-generation-with-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The compressed source latent also facilitates more efficient generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-music-generation-with-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Performance Few-Shot Segmentation with Foundation Models: An Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-performance-few-shot-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the performance of these methods is often constrained by models pre-trained on classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-performance-few-shot-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Weaknesses of Backdoor-based Model Watermarking: An Information-theoretic Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-weaknesses-of-backdoor-based-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this discovery, we propose a novel model watermarking scheme, In-distribution Watermark Embedding (IWE), to overcome the limitations of existing method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-weaknesses-of-backdoor-based-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MENSA: A Multi-Event Network for Survival Analysis under Informative Censoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mensa-a-multi-event-network-for-survival</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These events are not mutually exclusive and there are often statistical dependencies between them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mensa-a-multi-event-network-for-survival</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DACAT: Dual-stream Adaptive Clip-aware Time Modeling for Robust Online Surgical Phase Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dacat-dual-stream-adaptive-clip-aware-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the other stream, DACAT fine-tunes a new frame encoder to extract the frame-wise feature at the current moment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dacat-dual-stream-adaptive-clip-aware-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALSS-YOLO: An Adaptive Lightweight Channel Split and Shuffling Network for TIR Wildlife Detection in UAV Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alss-yolo-an-adaptive-lightweight-channel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This improves the extraction of blurry features, crucial for handling jitter-induced blur and overlapping targets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alss-yolo-an-adaptive-lightweight-channel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeXBLEU: Automatic Metric for Evaluate LaTeX Format</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texbleu-automatic-metric-for-evaluate-latex</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LaTeX is highly suited to creating documents with special formatting, particularly in the fields of science, technology, mathematics, and computer science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texbleu-automatic-metric-for-evaluate-latex</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ferret: Federated Full-Parameter Tuning at Scale for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ferret-federated-full-parameter-tuning-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these limitations, we propose federated full-parameter tuning at scale for LLMs (Ferret), the first first-order method with shared randomness to enable scalable full-parameter tuning of LLMs across decentralized data sources while maintaining competitive model accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ferret-federated-full-parameter-tuning-at</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
