<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 09:11:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>RETA-LLM: A Retrieval-Augmented Large Language Model Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reta-llm-a-retrieval-augmented-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To support research in this area and facilitate the development of retrieval-augmented LLM systems, we develop RETA-LLM, a {RET}reival-{A}ugmented LLM toolkit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reta-llm-a-retrieval-augmented-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable Multi-Objective Re-ranking with Policy Hypernetworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-multi-objective-re-ranking-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a framework called controllable multi-objective re-ranking (CMR) which incorporates a hypernetwork to generate parameters for a re-ranking model according to different preference weights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-multi-objective-re-ranking-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gradient-based Approach for Online Robust Deep Neural Network Training with Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-gradient-based-approach-for-online-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel gradient-based approach to enable the detection of noisy labels for the online learning of model parameters, named Online Gradient-based Robust Selection (OGRS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-gradient-based-approach-for-online-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Visual Prompt Tuning for Self-supervised Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-visual-prompt-tuning-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Prompt Tuning (VPT) is an effective tuning method for adapting pretrained Vision Transformers (ViTs) to downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-visual-prompt-tuning-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An adaptive augmented Lagrangian method for training physics and equality constrained artificial neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-augmented-lagrangian-method-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the efficacy of our proposed approach by solving several forward and PDE-constrained inverse problems with noisy data, including simulation of incompressible fluid flows with a primitive-variables formulation of the Navier-Stokes equations up to a Reynolds number of 1000.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-augmented-lagrangian-method-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LCT-1 at SemEval-2023 Task 10: Pre-training and Multi-task Learning for Sexism Detection and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lct-1-at-semeval-2023-task-10-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Misogyny and sexism are growing problems in social media.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lct-1-at-semeval-2023-task-10-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offline Prioritized Experience Replay</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-prioritized-experience-replay</link>
      <description><![CDATA[OPER is a plug-and-play component for offline RL algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-prioritized-experience-replay</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learned spatial data partitioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learned-spatial-data-partitioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the significant increase in the size of spatial data, it is essential to use distributed parallel processing systems to efficiently analyze spatial data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learned-spatial-data-partitioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RDumb: A simple approach that questions our progress in continual test-time adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdumb-a-simple-approach-that-questions-our</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Test-Time Adaptation (TTA) allows to update pretrained models to changing data distributions at deployment time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdumb-a-simple-approach-that-questions-our</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the Loop: Testing ChatGPT to Generate Model Explanations to Improve Human Labelling of Sponsored Content on Social Media</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-loop-testing-chatgpt-to-generate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve annotation accuracy and, thus, the detection of sponsored content, we propose using chatGPT to augment the annotation process with phrases identified as relevant features and brief explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-loop-testing-chatgpt-to-generate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIMIC-IT: Multi-Modal In-Context Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimic-it-multi-modal-in-context-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We release the MIMIC-IT dataset, instruction-response collection pipeline, benchmarks, and the Otter model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimic-it-multi-modal-in-context-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward more accurate and generalizable brain deformation estimators for traumatic brain injury detection with unsupervised domain adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-more-accurate-and-generalizable-brain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning head models (MLHMs) are developed to estimate brain deformation for early detection of traumatic brain injury (TBI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-more-accurate-and-generalizable-brain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedMLSecurity: A Benchmark for Attacks and Defenses in Federated Learning and LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedmlsecurity-a-benchmark-for-attacks-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces FedMLSecurity, a benchmark that simulates adversarial attacks and corresponding defense mechanisms in Federated Learning (FL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedmlsecurity-a-benchmark-for-attacks-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progression Cognition Reinforcement Learning with Prioritized Experience for Multi-Vehicle Pursuit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progression-cognition-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the more challenging problem of pursuing multiple evading vehicles, these algorithms typically select a fixed target evading vehicle for pursuing vehicles without considering dynamic traffic situation, which significantly reduces pursuing success rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progression-cognition-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning A Foundation Language Model for Geoscience Knowledge Understanding and Utilization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-foundation-language-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs)have achieved great success in general domains of natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-foundation-language-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIFS: An End-to-End Variational Inference for Foley Sound Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vifs-an-end-to-end-variational-inference-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from TTS models which generate short pronunciation from phonemes and speaker identity, the category-to-sound problem requires generating diverse sounds just from a category index.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vifs-an-end-to-end-variational-inference-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PandaLM: An Automatic Evaluation Benchmark for LLM Instruction Tuning Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pandalm-an-automatic-evaluation-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To ensure the reliability of PandaLM, we collect a diverse human-annotated test dataset, where all contexts are generated by humans and labels are aligned with human preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pandalm-an-automatic-evaluation-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extensive Evaluation of Transformer-based Architectures for Adverse Drug Events Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extensive-evaluation-of-transformer-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adverse Event (ADE) extraction is one of the core tasks in digital pharmacovigilance, especially when applied to informal texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extensive-evaluation-of-transformer-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Image Anonymization Impact Computer Vision Training?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-image-anonymization-impact-computer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we find that realistic anonymization can mitigate this decrease in performance, where our experiments reflect a minimal performance drop for face anonymization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-image-anonymization-impact-computer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Task Planning Based on Large Language Model Representing Knowledge with Directed Graph Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robot-task-planning-based-on-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional robot task planning methods face challenges when dealing with highly unstructured environments and complex tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robot-task-planning-based-on-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factorized Contrastive Learning: Going Beyond Multi-view Redundancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factorized-contrastive-learning-going-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How can we learn self-supervised multimodal representations to capture both shared and unique information relevant to downstream tasks?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factorized-contrastive-learning-going-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T3L: Translate-and-Test Transfer Learning for Cross-Lingual Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t3l-translate-and-test-transfer-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-lingual text classification leverages text classifiers trained in a high-resource language to perform text classification in other languages with no or minimal fine-tuning (zero/few-shots cross-lingual transfer).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t3l-translate-and-test-transfer-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Time in Causal Algorithmic Recourse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-importance-of-time-in-causal-algorithmic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The application of Algorithmic Recourse in decision-making is a promising field that offers practical solutions to reverse unfavorable decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-importance-of-time-in-causal-algorithmic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and Equivariant Graph Networks for Predicting Quantum Hamiltonian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-equivariant-graph-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the prediction of the Hamiltonian matrix, which finds use in quantum chemistry and condensed matter physics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-equivariant-graph-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stratification of uncertainties recalibrated by isotonic regression and its impact on calibration error statistics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stratification-of-uncertainties-recalibrated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Partitioning of the resulting data into equal-sized bins introduces an aleatoric component to the estimation of bin-based calibration statistics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stratification-of-uncertainties-recalibrated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InvPT++: Inverted Pyramid Multi-Task Transformer for Visual Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invpt-inverted-pyramid-multi-task-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[And then, we design a transformer decoder to establish spatial and cross-task interaction globally, and a novel UP-Transformer block is devised to increase the resolutions of multi-task features gradually and establish cross-task interaction at different scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invpt-inverted-pyramid-multi-task-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixture-of-Domain-Adapters: Decoupling and Injecting Domain Knowledge to Pre-trained Language Models Memories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-domain-adapters-decoupling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained language models (PLMs) demonstrate excellent abilities to understand texts in the generic domain while struggling in a specific domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-domain-adapters-decoupling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yet Another ICU Benchmark: A Flexible Multi-Center Framework for Clinical ML</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yet-another-icu-benchmark-a-flexible-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Datasets and code are not always published, and cohort definitions, preprocessing pipelines, and training setups are difficult to reproduce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yet-another-icu-benchmark-a-flexible-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subject clustering by IF-PCA and several recent methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subject-clustering-by-if-pca-and-several</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also find that IF-PCA is quite competitive, which slightly outperforms Seurat and SC3 over the $8$ single-cell data sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subject-clustering-by-if-pca-and-several</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster Approximation Algorithms for Parameterized Graph Clustering and Edge Labeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-approximation-algorithms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph clustering is a fundamental task in network analysis where the goal is to detect sets of nodes that are well-connected to each other but sparsely connected to the rest of the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-approximation-algorithms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShuttleSet: A Human-Annotated Stroke-Level Singles Dataset for Badminton Tactical Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shuttleset-a-human-annotated-stroke-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the recent progress in sports analytics, deep learning approaches have demonstrated the effectiveness of mining insights into players' tactics for improving performance quality and fan engagement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shuttleset-a-human-annotated-stroke-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-ChatGPT: Towards Detailed Video Understanding via Large Vision and Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-chatgpt-towards-detailed-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversation agents fueled by Large Language Models (LLMs) are providing a new way to interact with visual data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-chatgpt-towards-detailed-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Spherical CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-spherical-cnns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spherical CNNs generalize CNNs to functions on the sphere, by using spherical convolutions as the main linear operation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-spherical-cnns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-collaborative-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Excellent tail performance is crucial for modern machine learning tasks, such as algorithmic fairness, class imbalance, and risk-sensitive decision making, as it ensures the effective handling of challenging samples within a dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-collaborative-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Closed-form Equations for Subgrid-scale Closures from High-fidelity Data: Promises and Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-closed-form-equations-for-subgrid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is growing interest in discovering interpretable, closed-form equations for subgrid-scale (SGS) closures/parameterizations of complex processes in Earth system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-closed-form-equations-for-subgrid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive evaluation of deep and graph learning on drug-drug interactions prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-evaluation-of-deep-and-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances and achievements of artificial intelligence (AI) as well as deep and graph learning models have established their usefulness in biomedical applications, especially in drug-drug interactions (DDIs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-evaluation-of-deep-and-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HQ-50K: A Large-scale, High-quality Dataset for Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hq-50k-a-large-scale-high-quality-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a new large-scale image restoration dataset, called HQ-50K, which contains 50, 000 high-quality images with rich texture details and semantic diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hq-50k-a-large-scale-high-quality-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layer-level activation mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layer-level-activation-mechanism</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel activation mechanism aimed at establishing layer-level activation (LayerAct) functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layer-level-activation-mechanism</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Effectiveness of Out-of-Distribution Data in Self-Supervised Long-Tail Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work shows that the long-tailed learning performance could be boosted by sampling extra in-domain (ID) data for self-supervised training, however, large-scale ID data which can rebalance the minority classes are expensive to collect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Clustering via the Principle of Rate Reduction in the Age of Pretrained Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-clustering-via-the-principle-of-rate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel image clustering pipeline that leverages the powerful feature representation of large pre-trained models such as CLIP and cluster images effectively and efficiently at scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-clustering-via-the-principle-of-rate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matting Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matting-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the Matting Anything Model (MAM), an efficient and versatile framework for estimating the alpha matte of any instance in an image with flexible and interactive visual or linguistic user prompt guidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matting-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mesogeos: A multi-purpose dataset for data-driven wildfire modeling in the Mediterranean</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesogeos-a-multi-purpose-dataset-for-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Mesogeos, a large-scale multi-purpose dataset for wildfire modeling in the Mediterranean.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesogeos-a-multi-purpose-dataset-for-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReliableSwap: Boosting General Face Swapping Via Reliable Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliableswap-boosting-general-face-swapping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To avoid the potential artifacts and drive the distribution of the network output close to the natural one, we reversely take synthetic images as input while the real face as reliable supervision during the training stage of face swapping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliableswap-boosting-general-face-swapping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Multi-Task Scene Analysis with RGB-D Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multi-task-scene-analysis-with-rgb</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we show that the dual CNN-based encoder of EMSANet can be replaced with a single Transformer-based encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multi-task-scene-analysis-with-rgb</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modular Visual Question Answering via Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modular-visual-question-answering-via-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a framework that formulates visual question answering as modular code generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modular-visual-question-answering-via-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Masked Autoencoders via Hierarchical Latent Variable Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-masked-autoencoders-via-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we formally characterize and justify existing empirical insights and provide theoretical guarantees of MAE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-masked-autoencoders-via-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-level Multiple Instance Learning with Transformer for Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-multiple-instance-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The combination of both should provide new insights for deep learning based image diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-multiple-instance-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Negative-Prompt Inversion via Proximal Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-negative-prompt-inversion-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Null-text inversion (NTI) optimizes null embeddings to align the reconstruction and inversion trajectories with larger CFG scales, enabling real image editing with cross-attention control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-negative-prompt-inversion-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic Collapse: How Gradient Noise Attracts SGD Dynamics Towards Simpler Subnetworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-collapse-how-gradient-noise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we reveal a strong implicit bias of stochastic gradient descent (SGD) that drives overly expressive networks to much simpler subnetworks, thereby dramatically reducing the number of independent parameters, and improving generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-collapse-how-gradient-noise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Counterfactual Reasoning over Graph Neural Networks through Inductivity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-counterfactual-reasoning-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) have various practical applications, such as drug discovery, recommendation engines, and chip design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-counterfactual-reasoning-over</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
