<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 09:13:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Perfect Is the Enemy of Test Oracle</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perfect-is-the-enemy-of-test-oracle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents SEER, a learning-based approach that in the absence of test assertions or other types of oracle, can determine whether a unit test passes or fails on a given method under test (MUT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perfect-is-the-enemy-of-test-oracle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Data Scarcity for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-data-scarcity-for-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, pretrained neural language models (PNLMs) have taken the field of natural language processing by storm, achieving new benchmarks and state-of-the-art performances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-data-scarcity-for-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLADIS: A General and Large Acronym Disambiguation Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gladis-a-general-and-large-acronym</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Acronym Disambiguation (AD) is crucial for natural language understanding on various sources, including biomedical reports, scientific papers, and search engine queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gladis-a-general-and-large-acronym</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIQUID: A Framework for List Question Answering Dataset Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/liquid-a-framework-for-list-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Question answering (QA) models often rely on large-scale training datasets, which necessitates the development of a data generation framework to reduce the cost of manual annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/liquid-a-framework-for-list-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ordered GNN: Ordering Message Passing to Deal with Heterophily and Over-smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ordered-gnn-ordering-message-passing-to-deal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is achieved by aligning the hierarchy of the rooted-tree of a central node with the ordered neurons in its node representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ordered-gnn-ordering-message-passing-to-deal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockwise Self-Supervised Learning at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blockwise-self-supervised-learning-at-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current state-of-the-art deep networks are all powered by backpropagation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blockwise-self-supervised-learning-at-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVTNet: A Cross-View Transformer Network for Place Recognition Using LiDAR Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cvtnet-a-cross-view-transformer-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LiDAR-based place recognition (LPR) is one of the most crucial components of autonomous vehicles to identify previously visited places in GPS-denied environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cvtnet-a-cross-view-transformer-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Learnable Typewriter: A Generative Approach to Text Line Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-learnable-typewriter-a-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we demonstrate the potential of our method for new applications, more specifically in the field of paleography, which studies the history and variations of handwriting, and for cipher analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-learnable-typewriter-a-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MorDIFF: Recognition Vulnerability and Attack Detectability of Face Morphing Attacks Created by Diffusion Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mordiff-recognition-vulnerability-and-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Creating morphing attacks is commonly either performed on the image-level or on the representation-level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mordiff-recognition-vulnerability-and-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Contaminated Datasets to Learn Clean-Data Distribution with Purified Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-contaminated-datasets-to-learn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When training on such datasets, existing GANs will learn a mixture distribution of desired and contaminated instances, rather than the desired distribution of desired data only (target distribution).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-contaminated-datasets-to-learn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchically Composing Level Generators for the Creation of Complex Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchically-composing-level-generators-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Procedural content generation (PCG) is a growing field, with numerous applications in the video game industry, and great potential to help create better games at a fraction of the cost of manual creation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchically-composing-level-generators-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyGlove: Efficiently Exchanging ML Ideas as Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyglove-efficiently-exchanging-ml-ideas-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also perform a case study of a large codebase where PyGlove led to an 80% reduction in the number of lines of code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyglove-efficiently-exchanging-ml-ideas-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXTure: Text-Guided Texturing of 3D Shapes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texture-text-guided-texturing-of-3d-shapes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present TEXTure, a novel method for text-guided generation, editing, and transfer of textures for 3D shapes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texture-text-guided-texturing-of-3d-shapes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DilateFormer: Multi-Scale Dilated Transformer for Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilateformer-multi-scale-dilated-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore effective Vision Transformers to pursue a preferable trade-off between the computational complexity and size of the attended receptive field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilateformer-multi-scale-dilated-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SegForestNet: Spatial-Partitioning-Based Aerial Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segforestnet-spatial-partitioning-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aerial image analysis, specifically the semantic segmentation thereof, is the basis for applications such as automatically creating and updating maps, tracking city growth, or tracking deforestation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segforestnet-spatial-partitioning-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Explainability to Inform Statistical Downscaling Based on Deep Learning Beyond Standard Validation Approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-explainability-to-inform-statistical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning (DL) has emerged as a promising tool to downscale climate projections at regional-to-local scales from large-scale atmospheric fields following the perfect-prognosis (PP) approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-explainability-to-inform-statistical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple, Effective and General: A New Backbone for Cross-view Image Geo-localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-effective-and-general-a-new-backbone</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above three challenges for cross-view image matching, we propose a new backbone network, named Simple Attention-based Image Geo-localization network (SAIG).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-effective-and-general-a-new-backbone</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicit Box Detection Unifies End-to-End Multi-Person Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-box-detection-unifies-end-to-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel end-to-end framework with Explicit box Detection for multi-person Pose estimation, called ED-Pose, where it unifies the contextual learning between human-level (global) and keypoint-level (local) information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-box-detection-unifies-end-to-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Case Study for Compliance as Code with Graphs and Language Models: Public release of the Regulatory Knowledge Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-case-study-for-compliance-as-code-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper presents a study on using language models to automate the construction of executable Knowledge Graph (KG) for compliance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-case-study-for-compliance-as-code-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KNOD: Domain Knowledge Distilled Tree Decoder for Automated Program Repair</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knod-domain-knowledge-distilled-tree-decoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[KNOD has two major novelties, including (1) a novel three-stage tree decoder, which directly generates Abstract Syntax Trees of patched code according to the inherent tree structure, and (2) a novel domain-rule distillation, which leverages syntactic and semantic rules and teacher-student distributions to explicitly inject the domain knowledge into the decoding procedure during both the training and inference phases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knod-domain-knowledge-distilled-tree-decoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShadowFormer: Global Context Helps Image Shadow Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadowformer-global-context-helps-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is still challenging for the deep shadow removal model to exploit the global contextual correlation between shadow and non-shadow regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadowformer-global-context-helps-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Committed Private Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/committed-private-information-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A PIR scheme is $v$-verifiable if the client can verify the correctness of the retrieved $x_i$ even when $v \leq k$ servers collude and try to fool the client by sending manipulated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/committed-private-information-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCM: Deep energy method based on the principle of minimum complementary energy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcm-deep-energy-method-based-on-the-principle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we propose the deep energy method based on the principle of minimum complementary energy (DCM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcm-deep-energy-method-based-on-the-principle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tab2KG: Semantic Table Interpretation with Lightweight Semantic Profiles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tab2kg-semantic-table-interpretation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a one-shot learning approach that relies on these profiles to map a tabular dataset containing previously unseen instances to a domain ontology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tab2kg-semantic-table-interpretation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTE: A Dataset for Contextualized Table Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cte-a-dataset-for-contextualized-table</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We define the task of Contextualized Table Extraction (CTE), which aims to extract and define the structure of tables considering the textual context of the document.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cte-a-dataset-for-contextualized-table</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy Expansion for Bridging Offline-to-Online Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-expansion-for-bridging-offline-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With this approach, the policy previously learned offline is fully retained during online learning, thus mitigating the potential issues such as destroying the useful behaviors of the offline policy in the initial stage of online learning while allowing the offline policy participate in the exploration naturally in an adaptive manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-expansion-for-bridging-offline-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PASSerRank: Prediction of Allosteric Sites with Learning to Rank</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/passerrank-prediction-of-allosteric-sites</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Allostery plays a crucial role in regulating protein activity, making it a highly sought-after target in drug development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/passerrank-prediction-of-allosteric-sites</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Metric Learning for Uncertainty Quantification in Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-metric-learning-for-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the first Bayesian encoder for metric learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-metric-learning-for-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Network Architecture for Database Augmentation Using Shared Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-architecture-for-database</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The popularity of learning from data with machine learning and neural networks has lead to the creation of many new datasets for almost every problem domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-architecture-for-database</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paced-Curriculum Distillation with Prediction and Label Uncertainty for Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paced-curriculum-distillation-with-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Purpose: In curriculum learning, the idea is to train on easier samples first and gradually increase the difficulty, while in self-paced learning, a pacing function defines the speed to adapt the training progress.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paced-curriculum-distillation-with-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Efficacy of Differentially Private Few-shot Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-efficacy-of-differentially-private-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To understand under which conditions few-shot DP can be effective, we perform an exhaustive set of experiments that reveals how the accuracy and vulnerability to attack of few-shot DP image classification models are affected as the number of shots per class, privacy level, model architecture, dataset, and subset of learnable parameters in the model vary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-efficacy-of-differentially-private-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Baseline for Direct 2D Multi-Person Head Pose Estimation with Full-range Angles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-baseline-for-direct-2d-multi-person</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present comprehensive comparisons with state-of-the-art single HPE methods on public benchmarks, as well as superior baseline results on our constructed MPHPE datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-baseline-for-direct-2d-multi-person</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over-parameterised Shallow Neural Networks with Asymmetrical Node Scaling: Global Convergence Guarantees and Feature Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/over-parameterised-shallow-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the optimisation of large and shallow neural networks via gradient flow, where the output of each hidden node is scaled by some positive parameter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/over-parameterised-shallow-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laplacian Change Point Detection for Single and Multi-view Dynamic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplacian-change-point-detection-for-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[how to capture temporal dependencies, and iii).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplacian-change-point-detection-for-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-precision regressors for particle physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-precision-regressors-for-particle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the necessary number of data points per simulation is on the order of $10^9$ - $10^{12}$, machine learning regressors can be used in place of physics simulators to significantly reduce this computational burden.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-precision-regressors-for-particle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KST-Mixer: Kinematic Spatio-Temporal Data Mixer For Colon Shape Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kst-mixer-kinematic-spatio-temporal-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Kinematic data of a colonoscope and the colon, including positions and directions of their centerlines, are obtained using electromagnetic and depth sensors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kst-mixer-kinematic-spatio-temporal-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDJIR: Neural Direct and Joint Inverse Rendering for Geometry, Lights, and Materials of Real Object</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ndjir-neural-direct-and-joint-inverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of inverse rendering is to decompose geometry, lights, and materials given pose multi-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ndjir-neural-direct-and-joint-inverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Collapse Inspired Feature-Classifier Alignment for Few-Shot Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-collapse-inspired-feature-classifier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we deal with this misalignment dilemma in FSCIL inspired by the recently discovered phenomenon named neural collapse, which reveals that the last-layer features of the same class will collapse into a vertex, and the vertices of all classes are aligned with the classifier prototypes, which are formed as a simplex equiangular tight frame (ETF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-collapse-inspired-feature-classifier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoE-Fusion: Instance Embedded Mixture-of-Experts for Infrared and Visible Image Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moe-fusion-instance-embedded-mixture-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By embedding the instance-level information learned in the auxiliary network, IE-MoE achieves specialized learning of cross-modal foreground and background features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moe-fusion-instance-embedded-mixture-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Chain-of-Thought Reasoning in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-chain-of-thought-reasoning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating the vision features in both stages, the model is able to generate effective rationales that contribute to answer inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-chain-of-thought-reasoning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exposing the CSI: A Systematic Investigation of CSI-based Wi-Fi Sensing Capabilities and Limitations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposing-the-csi-a-systematic-investigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We leverage our dataset to dissect the performance of a state-of-the-art sensing framework across different environments and individuals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposing-the-csi-a-systematic-investigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Imitation Learning with Patch Rewards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-imitation-learning-with-patch-rewards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we present Adversarial Imitation Learning with Patch Rewards (PatchAIL), which employs a patch-based discriminator to measure the expertise of different local parts from given images and provide patch rewards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-imitation-learning-with-patch-rewards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Coherence Markers for the Early Diagnosis of the Alzheimer Disease</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-coherence-markers-for-the-early</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we explore how language models can be employed to analyze language and discriminate between mentally impaired and healthy subjects through the perplexity metric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-coherence-markers-for-the-early</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenSpike: An OpenRAM SNN Accelerator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openspike-an-openram-snn-accelerator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a spiking neural network (SNN) accelerator made using fully open-source EDA tools, process design kit (PDK), and memory macros synthesized using OpenRAM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openspike-an-openram-snn-accelerator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provably Bounding Neural Network Preimages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-bounding-neural-network-preimages</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most work on the formal verification of neural networks has focused on bounding forward images of neural networks, i. e., the set of outputs of a neural network that correspond to a given set of inputs (for example, bounded perturbations of a nominal input).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-bounding-neural-network-preimages</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphReg: Dynamical Point Cloud Registration with Geometry-aware Graph Signal Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphreg-dynamical-point-cloud-registration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results demonstrate that our proposed method outperforms representative state-of-the-art approaches in terms of accuracy and is more suitable for registering large-scale point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphreg-dynamical-point-cloud-registration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$IC^3$: Image Captioning by Committee Consensus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ic-3-image-captioning-by-committee-consensus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[If you ask a human to describe an image, they might do so in a thousand different ways.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ic-3-image-captioning-by-committee-consensus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning with Scaled Gradient Projection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-with-scaled-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In neural networks, continual learning results in gradient interference among sequential tasks, leading to catastrophic forgetting of old tasks while learning new ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-with-scaled-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avalanche: A PyTorch Library for Deep Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avalanche-a-pytorch-library-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual learning is the problem of learning from a nonstationary stream of data, a fundamental issue for sustainable and efficient training of deep neural networks over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avalanche-a-pytorch-library-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empirical Analysis of the AdaBoost's Error Bound</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-analysis-of-the-adaboost-s-error</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the accuracy limits of machine learning algorithms is essential for data scientists to properly measure performance so they can continually improve their models' predictive capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-analysis-of-the-adaboost-s-error</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
