<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 21:07:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Review on Anchor Assignment and Sampling Heuristics in Deep Learning-based Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-on-anchor-assignment-and-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning-based object detection is a fundamental but challenging problem in computer vision field, has attracted a lot of study in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-on-anchor-assignment-and-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bi-PointFlowNet: Bidirectional Learning for Point Cloud Based Scene Flow Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-pointflownet-bidirectional-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scene flow estimation, which extracts point-wise motion between scenes, is becoming a crucial task in many computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-pointflownet-bidirectional-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Object Tracking and Segmentation via Neural Message Passing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-object-tracking-and-segmentation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We achieve state-of-the-art results for both tracking and segmentation in several publicly available datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-object-tracking-and-segmentation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Systematic Review and Replicability Study of BERT4Rec for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-review-and-replicability-study</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose our own implementation of BERT4Rec based on the Hugging Face Transformers library, which we demonstrate replicates the originally reported results on 3 out 4 datasets, while requiring up to 95% less training time to converge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-review-and-replicability-study</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Probabilistic Autoencoder for Type Ia Supernovae Spectral Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-autoencoder-for-type-ia</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We construct a physically-parameterized probabilistic autoencoder (PAE) to learn the intrinsic diversity of type Ia supernovae (SNe Ia) from a sparse set of spectral time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-autoencoder-for-type-ia</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScaleNet: Searching for the Model to Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalenet-searching-for-the-model-to-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, community has paid increasing attention on model scaling and contributed to developing a model family with a wide spectrum of scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalenet-searching-for-the-model-to-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSolar tracker: towards unsupervised assessment with open-source data of the accuracy of deep learning-based distributed PV mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepsolar-tracker-towards-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, distributed PV generation, which amounts to half of the PV energy generation, makes it increasingly difficult for transmission system operators (TSOs) to balance the load and supply and avoid grid congestions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepsolar-tracker-towards-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short-Term Trajectory Prediction for Full-Immersive Multiuser Virtual Reality with Redirected Walking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/short-term-trajectory-prediction-for-full</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Full-immersive multiuser Virtual Reality (VR) envisions supporting unconstrained mobility of the users in the virtual worlds, while at the same time constraining their physical movements inside VR setups through redirected walking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/short-term-trajectory-prediction-for-full</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameterization of Cross-Token Relations with Relative Positional Encoding for Vision MLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameterization-of-cross-token-relations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[They use token-mixing layers to capture cross-token interactions, as opposed to the multi-head self-attention mechanism used by Transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameterization-of-cross-token-relations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuetFace: Collaborative Privacy-Preserving Face Recognition via Channel Splitting in the Frequency Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/duetface-collaborative-privacy-preserving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To compensate, the method introduces a plug-in interactive block to allow attention transfer from the client-side by producing a feature mask.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/duetface-collaborative-privacy-preserving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning For On-Device Environmental Sound Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-for-on-device</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results on the DCASE 2019 Task 1 and ESC-50 dataset show that our proposed method outperforms baseline continual learning methods on classification accuracy and computational efficiency, indicating our method can efficiently and incrementally learn new classes without the catastrophic forgetting problem for on-device environmental sound classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-for-on-device</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Better Dermoscopic Image Feature Representation Learning for Melanoma Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-dermoscopic-image-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning-based melanoma classification with dermoscopic images has recently shown great potential in automatic early-stage melanoma diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-dermoscopic-image-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Quality and Machine Learning Pipelines through Extended Feature Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-quality-and-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the years, several solutions have been proposed to automate the building of ML pipelines, most of them focused on semantic aspects and characteristics of the input dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-quality-and-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Instances as 1D Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-instances-as-1d-kernels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The idea of instance kernel is inspired by recent success of dynamic convolutions in 2D/3D instance segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-instances-as-1d-kernels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving Face Recognition with Learnable Privacy Budgets in Frequency Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-face-recognition-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a privacy-preserving face recognition method using differential privacy in the frequency domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-face-recognition-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmenting Softmax Information for Selective Classification with Out-of-Distribution Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-softmax-information-for-selective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the performance of detection methods is generally evaluated on the task in isolation, rather than also considering potential downstream tasks in tandem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-softmax-information-for-selective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plex: Towards Reliability using Pretrained Large Model Extensions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plex-towards-reliability-using-pretrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A recent trend in artificial intelligence is the use of pretrained models for language and vision tasks, which have achieved extraordinary performance but also puzzling failures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plex-towards-reliability-using-pretrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithms to estimate Shapley value feature attributions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/algorithms-to-estimate-shapley-value-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the various feature removal approaches, we describe the multiple types of Shapley value feature attributions and methods to calculate each one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/algorithms-to-estimate-shapley-value-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WaveGAN: Frequency-aware GAN for High-Fidelity Few-shot Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavegan-frequency-aware-gan-for-high-fidelity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, we disentangle encoded features into multiple frequency components and perform low-frequency skip connections to preserve outline and structural information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavegan-frequency-aware-gan-for-high-fidelity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outlier detection of vital sign trajectories from COVID-19 patients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-detection-of-vital-sign-trajectories</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also show, descriptively, how epochs transition from normal to abnormal for one such patient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-detection-of-vital-sign-trajectories</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STRIKE-GOLDD 4.0: user-friendly, efficient analysis of structural identifiability and observability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strike-goldd-4-0-user-friendly-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we present STRIKE-GOLDD 4. 0, which includes a new algorithm, ProbObsTest, specifically designed for the analysis of rational models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strike-goldd-4-0-user-friendly-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Non-Cooperative Dialogue: Theoretical and Empirical Insights</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-non-cooperative-dialogue-theoretical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use the tools of learning theory to develop a theoretical model for identifying non-cooperative interlocutors and apply this theory to analyze different communication strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-non-cooperative-dialogue-theoretical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIMO-DoAnet: Multi-channel Input and Multiple Outputs DoA Network with Unknown Number of Sound Sources</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimo-doanet-multi-channel-input-and-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These algorithms are usually achieved by mapping the multi-channel audio input to the single output (i. e. overall spatial pseudo-spectrum (SPS) of all sources), that is called MISO.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimo-doanet-multi-channel-input-and-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ST-P3: End-to-end Vision-based Autonomous Driving via Spatial-Temporal Feature Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/st-p3-end-to-end-vision-based-autonomous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we propose a spatial-temporal feature learning scheme towards a set of more representative features for perception, prediction and planning tasks simultaneously, which is called ST-P3.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/st-p3-end-to-end-vision-based-autonomous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communication-Efficient Diffusion Strategy for Performance Improvement of Federated Learning with Non-IID Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communication-efficient-diffusion-strategy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the aforementioned challenge, we propose a novel diffusion strategy of the machine learning (ML) model (FedDif) to maximize the FL performance with non-IID data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communication-efficient-diffusion-strategy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CheXplaining in Style: Counterfactual Explanations for Chest X-rays using StyleGAN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chexplaining-in-style-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning models used in medical image analysis are prone to raising reliability concerns due to their black-box nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chexplaining-in-style-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3DVerifier: Efficient Robustness Verification for 3D Point Cloud Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dverifier-efficient-robustness-verification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we propose an efficient verification framework, 3DVerifier, to tackle both challenges by adopting a linear relaxation function to bound the multiplication layer and combining forward and backward propagation to compute the certified bounds of the outputs of the point cloud models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dverifier-efficient-robustness-verification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Registration based Few-Shot Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/registration-based-few-shot-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by how humans detect anomalies, i. e., comparing an image in question to normal images, we here leverage registration, an image alignment task that is inherently generalizable across categories, as the proxy task, to train a category-agnostic anomaly detection model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/registration-based-few-shot-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverse Human Motion Prediction via Gumbel-Softmax Sampling from an Auxiliary Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-human-motion-prediction-via-gumbel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel sampling strategy for sampling very diverse results from an imbalanced multimodal distribution learned by a deep generative model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-human-motion-prediction-via-gumbel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-to-Box Network for Accurate Object Detection via Single Point Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-to-box-network-for-accurate-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we introduce a lightweight alternative to the off-the-shelf proposal (OTSP) method and thereby create the Point-to-Box Network (P2BNet), which can construct an inter-objects balanced proposal bag by generating proposals in an anchor-like way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-to-box-network-for-accurate-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoSegNet: Point Cloud Semantic Segmentation via Geometric Encoder-Decoder Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geosegnet-point-cloud-semantic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation of point clouds, aiming to assign each point a semantic category, is critical to 3D scene understanding. Despite of significant advances in recent years, most of existing methods still suffer from either the object-level misclassification or the boundary-level ambiguity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geosegnet-point-cloud-semantic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DavarOCR: A Toolbox for OCR and Multi-Modal Document Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/davarocr-a-toolbox-for-ocr-and-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared with the previous opensource OCR toolbox, DavarOCR has relatively more complete support for the sub-tasks of the cutting-edge technology of document understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/davarocr-a-toolbox-for-ocr-and-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Octuplet Loss: Make Face Recognition Robust to Image Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/octuplet-loss-make-face-recognition-robust-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we propose a novel combination of the popular triplet loss to improve robustness against image resolution via fine-tuning of existing face recognition models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/octuplet-loss-make-face-recognition-robust-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E2FIF: Push the limit of Binarized Deep Imagery Super-resolution using End-to-end Full-precision Information Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e2fif-push-the-limit-of-binarized-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Binary neural network (BNN) provides a promising solution to deploy parameter-intensive deep single image super-resolution (SISR) models onto real devices with limited storage and computational resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e2fif-push-the-limit-of-binarized-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototypical Contrast Adaptation for Domain Adaptive Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-contrast-adaptation-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised Domain Adaptation (UDA) aims to adapt the model trained on the labeled source domain to an unlabeled target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-contrast-adaptation-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ObjectBox: From Centers to Boxes for Anchor-Free Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/objectbox-from-centers-to-boxes-for-anchor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present ObjectBox, a novel single-stage anchor-free and highly generalizable object detection approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/objectbox-from-centers-to-boxes-for-anchor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Background Distraction in Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-background-distraction-in-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-supervised video object segmentation (VOS) aims to densely track certain designated objects in videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-background-distraction-in-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Implicit Templates for Point-Based Clothed Human Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-implicit-templates-for-point-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present FITE, a First-Implicit-Then-Explicit framework for modeling human avatars in clothing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-implicit-templates-for-point-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Modelling with Pixels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-modelling-with-pixels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models are defined over a finite set of inputs, which creates a vocabulary bottleneck when we attempt to scale the number of supported languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-modelling-with-pixels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scene Text Recognition with Permuted Autoregressive Sequence Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scene-text-recognition-with-permuted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Context-aware STR methods typically use internal autoregressive (AR) language models (LM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scene-text-recognition-with-permuted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Grand Unification of Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-grand-unification-of-object-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a unified method, termed Unicorn, that can simultaneously solve four tracking problems (SOT, MOT, VOS, MOTS) with a single network using the same model parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-grand-unification-of-object-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatiotemporal Propagation Learning for Network-Wide Flight Delay Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatiotemporal-propagation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By this means, STPN allows cross-talk of spatial and temporal factors for modeling delay propagation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatiotemporal-propagation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Omni-Vision Representation through the Lens of Visual Realms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-omni-vision-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We benchmark ReCo and other advances in omni-vision representation studies that are different in architectures (from CNNs to transformers) and in learning paradigms (from supervised learning to self-supervised learning) on OmniBenchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-omni-vision-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XMem: Long-Term Video Object Segmentation with an Atkinson-Shiffrin Memory Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xmem-long-term-video-object-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present XMem, a video object segmentation architecture for long videos with unified feature memory stores inspired by the Atkinson-Shiffrin memory model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xmem-long-term-video-object-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Bypasses Are Better Vision Transformer Adapters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-bypasses-are-better-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by parameter-efficient transfer learning (PETL) on language transformers, recent studies attempt to insert lightweight adaptation modules (e. g., adapter layers or prompt tokens) to pretrained ViT and only finetune these modules while the pretrained weights are frozen.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-bypasses-are-better-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedFuse: Multi-modal fusion with clinical time-series data and chest X-ray images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medfuse-multi-modal-fusion-with-clinical-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal fusion approaches aim to integrate information from different data sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medfuse-multi-modal-fusion-with-clinical-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Modality Ovarian Tumor Ultrasound Image Dataset for Unsupervised Cross-Domain Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-modality-ovarian-tumor-ultrasound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve this problem, we propose a Multi-Modality Ovarian Tumor Ultrasound (MMOTU) image dataset containing 1469 2d ultrasound images and 170 contrast enhanced ultrasonography (CEUS) images with pixel-wise and global-wise annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-modality-ovarian-tumor-ultrasound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pose-based Tremor Classification for Parkinson's Disease Diagnosis from Video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-based-tremor-classification-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose to classify Parkinson's tremor since it is one of the most predominant symptoms of PD with strong generalizability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-based-tremor-classification-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Asymmetric Contrastive Loss for Handling Imbalanced Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-asymmetric-contrastive-loss-for-handling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we propose the asymmetric focal contrastive loss (AFCL) as a further generalization of both ACL and focal contrastive loss (FCL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-asymmetric-contrastive-loss-for-handling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PASHA: Efficient HPO with Progressive Resource Allocation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pasha-efficient-hpo-with-progressive-resource</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperparameter optimization (HPO) and neural architecture search (NAS) are methods of choice to obtain the best-in-class machine learning models, but in practice they can be costly to run.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pasha-efficient-hpo-with-progressive-resource</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
