<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 21:06:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DIRECTOR: Generator-Classifiers For Supervised Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/director-generator-classifiers-for-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current language models achieve low perplexity but their resulting generations still suffer from toxic responses, repetitiveness and contradictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/director-generator-classifiers-for-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RecBole 2.0: Towards a More Up-to-Date Recommendation Library</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recbole-2-0-towards-a-more-up-to-date</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to support the study of recent advances in recommender systems, this paper presents an extended recommendation library consisting of eight packages for up-to-date topics and architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recbole-2-0-towards-a-more-up-to-date</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Eve of True Explainability for OWL Ontologies: Description Logic Proofs with Evee and Evonne (Extended Version)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-eve-of-true-explainability-for-owl</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When working with description logic ontologies, understanding entailments derived by a description logic reasoner is not always straightforward.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-eve-of-true-explainability-for-owl</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Generalization in Few-Shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-generalization-in-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Single image-level annotations only correctly describe an often small subset of an image's content, particularly when complex real-world scenes are depicted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-generalization-in-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NatGen: Generative pre-training by "Naturalizing" source code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natgen-generative-pre-training-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained Generative Language models (e. g. PLBART, CodeT5, SPT-Code) for source code yielded strong results on several tasks in the past few years, including code generation and translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natgen-generative-pre-training-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Reliable Evaluation of Adversarial Robustness with Minimum-Margin Attack</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-reliable-evaluation-of-adversarial-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The AutoAttack (AA) has been the most reliable method to evaluate adversarial robustness when considerable computational resources are available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-reliable-evaluation-of-adversarial-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SIGMORPHON 2022 Shared Task on Morpheme Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-sigmorphon-2022-shared-task-on-morpheme</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The SIGMORPHON 2022 shared task on morpheme segmentation challenged systems to decompose a word into a sequence of morphemes and covered most types of morphology: compounds, derivations, and inflections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-sigmorphon-2022-shared-task-on-morpheme</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A smile is all you need: Predicting limiting activity coefficients from SMILES with natural language processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-smile-is-all-you-need-predicting-limiting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This training strategy enables SPT to accurately predict limiting activity coefficients even for unknown molecules, cutting the mean prediction error in half compared to state-of-the-art models for activity coefficient predictions such as COSMO-RS, UNIFAC, and improving on recent machine learning approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-smile-is-all-you-need-predicting-limiting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Data Mixing Prior for Improving Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-data-mixing-prior-for-improving-self-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More notably, our SDMP is the first method that successfully leverages data mixing to improve (rather than hurt) the performance of Vision Transformers in the self-supervised setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-data-mixing-prior-for-improving-self-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating the Optimal Covariance with Imperfect Mean in Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-the-optimal-covariance-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, the generation performance on a subset of timesteps is crucial, which is greatly influenced by the covariance design in DPMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-the-optimal-covariance-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Numerical Integration in Neural Ordinary Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-numerical-integration-in-neural-ordinary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The combination of ordinary differential equations and neural networks, i. e., neural ordinary differential equations (Neural ODE), has been widely studied from various angles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-numerical-integration-in-neural-ordinary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morphence-2.0: Evasion-Resilient Moving Target Defense Powered by Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphence-2-0-evasion-resilient-moving-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also show that, when powered by OOD detection, Morphence-2. 0 is able to precisely make an input-based movement of the model's decision function that leads to higher prediction accuracy on both adversarial and benign queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphence-2-0-evasion-resilient-moving-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SciTweets -- A Dataset and Annotation Framework for Detecting Scientific Online Discourse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scitweets-a-dataset-and-annotation-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientific topics, claims and resources are increasingly debated as part of online discourse, where prominent examples include discourse related to COVID-19 or climate change.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scitweets-a-dataset-and-annotation-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PolyU-BPCoMa: A Dataset and Benchmark Towards Mobile Colorized Mapping Using a Backpack Multisensorial System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyu-bpcoma-a-dataset-and-benchmark-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Color checker boards are pasted in each surveyed area as targets and ground truth data are collected by an advanced terrestrial laser scanner (TLS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyu-bpcoma-a-dataset-and-benchmark-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Discrete Deep Generative Models via Gapped Straight-Through Estimator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-discrete-deep-generative-models-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While deep generative models have succeeded in image processing, natural language processing, and reinforcement learning, training that involves discrete random variables remains challenging due to the high variance of its gradient estimation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-discrete-deep-generative-models-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S\textsuperscript{2}-FPN: Scale-ware Strip Attention Guided Feature Pyramid Network for Real-time Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-textsuperscript-2-fpn-scale-ware-strip</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new model to achieve a trade-off between accuracy/speed for real-time road scene semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-textsuperscript-2-fpn-scale-ware-strip</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Aware End-to-end Mispronunciation Detection and Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-aware-end-to-end-mispronunciation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of assessing the pronunciation quality of constrained speech, the given transcriptions can play the role of a teacher.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-aware-end-to-end-mispronunciation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair Ranking as Fair Division: Impact-Based Individual Fairness in Ranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-ranking-as-fair-division-impact-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our axioms of envy-freeness and dominance over uniform ranking postulate that for a fair ranking policy every item should prefer their own rank allocation over that of any other item, and that no item should be actively disadvantaged by the rankings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-ranking-as-fair-division-impact-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-shot object goal visual navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-object-goal-visual-navigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object goal visual navigation is a challenging task that aims to guide a robot to find the target object only based on its visual observation, and the target is limited to the classes specified in the training stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-object-goal-visual-navigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ParamNet: A Multi-Layer Parametric Network for Joint Channel Estimation and Symbol Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paramnet-a-multi-layer-parametric-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a parametric-based network architecture for joint channel estimation and data detection in communications systems with hardware impairments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paramnet-a-multi-layer-parametric-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prefix Language Models are Unified Modal Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prefix-language-models-are-unified-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the success of vision-language pre-training, we have witnessed the state-of-the-art has been pushed on multi-modal understanding and generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prefix-language-models-are-unified-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LET-3D-AP: Longitudinal Error Tolerant 3D Average Precision for Camera-Only 3D Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-3d-ap-longitudinal-error-tolerant-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The popular object detection metric 3D Average Precision (3D AP) relies on the intersection over union between predicted bounding boxes and ground truth bounding boxes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-3d-ap-longitudinal-error-tolerant-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Why Here and Not There?" -- Diverse Contrasting Explanations of Dimensionality Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-here-and-not-there-diverse-contrasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dimensionality reduction is a popular preprocessing and a widely used tool in data mining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-here-and-not-there-diverse-contrasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Learning of Image Scale and Orientation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-of-image-scale-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of learning to assign a characteristic pose, i. e., scale and orientation, for an image region of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-of-image-scale-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variable Bitrate Neural Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-bitrate-neural-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural approximations of scalar and vector fields, such as signed distance functions and radiance fields, have emerged as accurate, high-quality representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-bitrate-neural-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Emotion Strength Assessment for Seen and Unseen Speech Based on Data-Driven Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-emotion-strength-assessment-for-seen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a data-driven deep learning model, i. e. StrengthNet, to improve the generalization of emotion strength assessment for seen and unseen speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-emotion-strength-assessment-for-seen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards ML Methods for Biodiversity: A Novel Wild Bee Dataset and Evaluations of XAI Methods for ML-Assisted Rare Species Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-ml-methods-for-biodiversity-a-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Insects are a crucial part of our ecosystem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-ml-methods-for-biodiversity-a-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coarse-to-Fine Vision-Language Pre-training with Fusion in the Backbone</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse-to-fine-vision-language-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language (VL) pre-training has recently received considerable attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse-to-fine-vision-language-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XMorpher: Full Transformer for Deformable Medical Image Registration via Cross Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xmorpher-full-transformer-for-deformable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An effective backbone network is important to deep learning-based Deformable Medical Image Registration (DMIR), because it extracts and matches the features between two images to discover the mutual correspondence for fine registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xmorpher-full-transformer-for-deformable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human Eyes Inspired Recurrent Neural Networks are More Robust Against Adversarial Noises</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-eyes-inspired-recurrent-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to human vision, computer vision based on convolutional neural networks (CNN) are more vulnerable to adversarial noises.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-eyes-inspired-recurrent-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Generalization in Few-Shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-generalization-in-few-shot-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Single image-level annotations only correctly describe an often small subset of an image's content, particularly when complex real-world scenes are depicted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-generalization-in-few-shot-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Decoder-free Object Detection with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-decoder-free-object-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A natural usage of ViTs in detection is to replace the CNN-based backbone with a transformer-based backbone, which is straightforward and effective, with the price of bringing considerable computation burden for inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-decoder-free-object-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISLES 2022: A multi-center magnetic resonance imaging stroke lesion segmentation dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isles-2022-a-multi-center-magnetic-resonance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The test dataset will be used for model validation only and will not be released to the public.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isles-2022-a-multi-center-magnetic-resonance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Easy Example Mining for Weakly-supervised Gland Segmentation from Histology Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-easy-example-mining-for-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing weakly-supervised semantic segmentation methods in computer vision achieve degenerative results for gland segmentation, since the characteristics and problems of glandular datasets are different from general object datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-easy-example-mining-for-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformers are Meta-Reinforcement Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-are-meta-reinforcement-learners-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present TrMRL (Transformers for Meta-Reinforcement Learning), a meta-RL agent that mimics the memory reinstatement mechanism using the transformer architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-are-meta-reinforcement-learners-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label Matching Semi-Supervised Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-matching-semi-supervised-object-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To remedy this issue, we present a novel label assignment mechanism for self-training framework, namely proposal self-assignment, which injects the proposals from student into teacher and generates accurate pseudo labels to match each proposal in the student model accordingly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-matching-semi-supervised-object-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Enhanced Representations for Tabular Data via Neighborhood Propagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-enhanced-representations-for-tabular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prediction over tabular data is an essential and fundamental problem in many important downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-enhanced-representations-for-tabular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Isolation Forest for Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-isolation-forest-for-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method offers a comprehensive isolation method that can arbitrarily partition the data at any random direction and angle on subspaces of any size, effectively avoiding the algorithmic bias in the linear partition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-isolation-forest-for-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RF-Next: Efficient Receptive Field Search for Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rf-next-efficient-receptive-field-search-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our search scheme exploits both global search to find the coarse combinations and local search to get the refined receptive field combinations further.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rf-next-efficient-receptive-field-search-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Best Combination for Efficient N:M Sparsity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-best-combination-for-efficient-n-m</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show that the N:M learning can be naturally characterized as a combinatorial problem which searches for the best combination candidate within a finite collection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-best-combination-for-efficient-n-m</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Provably Robust Meta-Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-provably-robust-meta-bayesian-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that both algorithms are asymptotically no-regret even when some or all previous tasks are dissimilar to the current task, and show that RM-GP-UCB enjoys a better theoretical robustness than RM-GP-TS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-provably-robust-meta-bayesian-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprehending and Ordering Semantics for Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehending-and-ordering-semantics-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new recipe of Transformer-style structure, namely Comprehending and Ordering Semantics Networks (COS-Net), that novelly unifies an enriched semantic comprehending and a learnable semantic ordering processes into a single architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehending-and-ordering-semantics-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating histopathology transfer learning with ChampKit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-histopathology-transfer-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Histopathology remains the gold standard for diagnosis of various cancers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-histopathology-transfer-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stand-Alone Inter-Frame Attention in Video Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stand-alone-inter-frame-attention-in-video-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new recipe of inter-frame attention block, namely Stand-alone Inter-Frame Attention (SIFA), that novelly delves into the deformation across frames to estimate local self-attention on each spatial location.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stand-alone-inter-frame-attention-in-video-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAVENDER: Unifying Video-Language Understanding as Masked Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lavender-unifying-video-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore a unified VidL framework LAVENDER, where Masked Language Modeling (MLM) is used as the common interface for all pre-training and downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lavender-unifying-video-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVIDHunter: COVID-19 pandemic wave prediction and mitigation via seasonality-aware modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covidhunter-covid-19-pandemic-wave-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce COVIDHunter, a flexible and accurate COVID-19 outbreak simulation model that evaluates the current mitigation measures that are applied to a region, predicts COVID-19 statistics (the daily number of cases, hospitalizations, and deaths), and provides suggestions on what strength the upcoming mitigation measure should be.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covidhunter-covid-19-pandemic-wave-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shopping Queries Dataset: A Large-Scale ESCI Benchmark for Improving Product Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shopping-queries-dataset-a-large-scale-esci</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the "Shopping Queries Dataset", a large dataset of difficult Amazon search queries and results, publicly released with the aim of fostering research in improving the quality of search results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shopping-queries-dataset-a-large-scale-esci</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReCo: Retrieve and Co-segment for Zero-shot Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reco-retrieve-and-co-segment-for-zero-shot-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation has a broad range of applications, but its real-world impact has been significantly limited by the prohibitive annotation costs necessary to enable deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reco-retrieve-and-co-segment-for-zero-shot-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantitative Imaging Principles Improves Medical Image Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantitative-imaging-principles-improves</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Differences between image types are primarily due to the imaging modality and medical images utilize a wide range of physics based techniques while natural images are captured using only visible light.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantitative-imaging-principles-improves</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Structure of Large Networked Systems Obeying Conservation Laws</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-structure-of-large-networked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many networked systems such as electric networks, the brain, and social networks of opinion dynamics are known to obey conservation laws.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-structure-of-large-networked</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
