<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:12:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Flexible Error Mitigation of Quantum Processes with Data Augmentation Empowered Neural Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-error-mitigation-of-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks have shown their effectiveness in various tasks in the realm of quantum computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-error-mitigation-of-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Common Ground: Annotating and Predicting Common Ground in Spoken Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-common-ground-annotating-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An important part of cognitive state is the common ground, which is the content the speaker believes, and the speaker believes the audience believes, and so on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-common-ground-annotating-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better with Less: A Data-Active Perspective on Pre-Training Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-with-less-a-data-active-perspective-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed pre-training pipeline is called the data-active graph pre-training (APT) framework, and is composed of a graph selector and a pre-training model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-with-less-a-data-active-perspective-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Unified Perspective For Fast Shapley Value Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-unified-perspective-for-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Shapley values have emerged as a widely accepted and trustworthy tool, grounded in theoretical axioms, for addressing challenges posed by black-box models like deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-unified-perspective-for-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPAL-ID: Indonesian Language Reasoning with Local Culture and Nuances</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copal-id-indonesian-language-reasoning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present publicly available COPAL-ID, a novel Indonesian language common sense reasoning dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copal-id-indonesian-language-reasoning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IndoToD: A Multi-Domain Indonesian Benchmark For End-to-End Task-Oriented Dialogue Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indotod-a-multi-domain-indonesian-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Task-oriented dialogue (ToD) systems have been mostly created for high-resource languages, such as English and Chinese.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indotod-a-multi-domain-indonesian-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaussian Mixture Solvers for Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-mixture-solvers-for-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our investigation suggests that this is because the Gaussian assumption in the reverse transition kernel is frequently violated (even in the case of simple mixture data) given a limited number of discretization steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-mixture-solvers-for-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Large Language Model for Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-large-language-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, there is a growing interest in developing next-generation recommender systems (RSs) based on pretrained large language models (LLMs), fully utilizing their encoded knowledge and reasoning ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-large-language-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheating Depth: Enhancing 3D Surface Anomaly Detection via Depth Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cheating-depth-enhancing-3d-surface-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(ii) We tackle the lack of diverse industrial depth datasets by introducing a simulation process for learning informative depth features in the depth encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cheating-depth-enhancing-3d-surface-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tailoring Mixup to Data using Kernel Warping functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-mixup-to-data-using-kernel-warping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data augmentation is an essential building block for learning efficient deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-mixup-to-data-using-kernel-warping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Language Models Be Tricked by Language Illusions? Easier with Syntax, Harder with Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-language-models-be-tricked-by-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We found that probabilities represented by LMs were more likely to align with human judgments of being "tricked" by the NPI illusion which examines a structural dependency, compared to the comparative and the depth-charge illusions which require sophisticated semantic understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-language-models-be-tricked-by-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DP-Mix: Mixup-based Data Augmentation for Differentially Private Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dp-mix-mixup-based-data-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data augmentation techniques, such as simple image transformations and combinations, are highly effective at improving the generalization of computer vision models, especially when training data is limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dp-mix-mixup-based-data-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bi-Preference Learning Heterogeneous Hypergraph Networks for Session-based Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-preference-learning-heterogeneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, price preference and interest preference are interdependent and collectively determine user choice, necessitating that we jointly consider both price and interest preference for intent modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-preference-learning-heterogeneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Operational Mathematical Derivations in Latent Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-operational-mathematical-derivations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce different multi-operational representation paradigms, modelling mathematical operations as explicit geometric transformations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-operational-mathematical-derivations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combating Bilateral Edge Noise for Robust Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combating-bilateral-edge-noise-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this dilemma, we propose an information-theory-guided principle, Robust Graph Information Bottleneck (RGIB), to extract reliable supervision signals and avoid representation collapse.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combating-bilateral-edge-noise-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video2Music: Suitable Music Generation from Videos using an Affective Multimodal Transformer model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video2music-suitable-music-generation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These distinct features are then employed as guiding input to our music generation model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video2music-suitable-music-generation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Deepfakes Without Seeing Any</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-deepfakes-without-seeing-any</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We therefore introduce the concept of "fact checking", adapted from fake news detection, for detecting zero-day deepfake attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-deepfakes-without-seeing-any</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATHENA: Mathematical Reasoning with Thought Expansion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/athena-mathematical-reasoning-with-thought</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Solving math word problems depends on how to articulate the problems, the lens through which models view human linguistic expressions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/athena-mathematical-reasoning-with-thought</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concatenated Masked Autoencoders as Spatial-Temporal Learner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concatenated-masked-autoencoders-as-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning representations from videos requires understanding continuous motion and visual correspondences between frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concatenated-masked-autoencoders-as-spatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Information-Guided Network using Contrastive Learning for Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-information-guided-network-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we first incorporate the projected images from the point clouds and fuse the cross-modal features using the attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-information-guided-network-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invariant-Feature Subspace Recovery: A New Class of Provable Domain Generalization Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-feature-subspace-recovery-a-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, in the binary classification setup of Rosenfeld et al. (2021), we show that our first algorithm, ISR-Mean, can identify the subspace spanned by invariant features from the first-order moments of the class-conditional distributions, and achieve provable domain generalization with $d_s+1$ training environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-feature-subspace-recovery-a-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Together: Enhancing Generative Knowledge Graph Completion with Language Models and Neighborhood Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-together-enhancing-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose to include node neighborhoods as additional information to improve KGC methods based on language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-together-enhancing-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AeroPath: An airway segmentation benchmark dataset with challenging pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aeropath-an-airway-segmentation-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce a new public benchmark dataset (AeroPath), consisting of 27 CT images from patients with pathologies ranging from emphysema to large tumors, with corresponding trachea and bronchi annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aeropath-an-airway-segmentation-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning A Multi-Task Transformer Via Unified And Customized Instruction Tuning For Chest Radiograph Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-multi-task-transformer-via-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first compose a multi-task training dataset comprising 13. 4 million instruction and ground-truth pairs (with approximately one million radiographs) for the customized tuning, involving both image- and pixel-level tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-multi-task-transformer-via-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Relation Learning for Cross-domain Few-shot Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-relation-learning-for-cross-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, it adopts a transformer based cross-attention learning module to learn the set-level sample relations and acquire the attentions from query samples to support samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-relation-learning-for-cross-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distance-Based Propagation for Efficient Knowledge Graph Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-based-propagation-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A new class of methods have been proposed to tackle this problem by aggregating path information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-based-propagation-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention based Dual-Branch Complex Feature Fusion Network for Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-based-dual-branch-complex-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental evidence show that SE block improves the models overall accuracy by almost 1\%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-based-dual-branch-complex-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling Out-of-Distribution Robustness from Vision-Language Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-out-of-distribution-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a conceptually simple and lightweight framework for improving the robustness of vision models through the combination of knowledge distillation and data augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-out-of-distribution-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Multimodal Information Bottleneck for Multimodality Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-multimodal-information-bottleneck-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our information bottleneck module serves to filter out the task-irrelevant information and noises in the fused feature, and we further introduce a sufficiency loss to prevent dropping of task-relevant information, thus explicitly preserving the sufficiency of prediction information in the distilled feature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-multimodal-information-bottleneck-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision-Language Interpreter for Robot Task Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-language-interpreter-for-robot-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The aim is to generate a problem description (PD), a machine-readable file used by the planners to find a plan.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-language-interpreter-for-robot-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sim2Real Bilevel Adaptation for Object Surface Classification using Vision-Based Tactile Sensors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim2real-bilevel-adaptation-for-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our evaluation is conducted on a dataset of tactile images obtained from a set of ten 3D printed YCB objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim2real-bilevel-adaptation-for-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaboration and Transition: Distilling Item Transitions into Multi-Query Self-Attention for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaboration-and-transition-distilling-item</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we develop a transition-aware embedding distillation module that distills global item-to-item transition patterns into item embeddings, which enables the model to memorize and leverage transitional signals and serves as a calibrator for collaborative signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaboration-and-transition-distilling-item</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating QM1B with PySCF$_{\text{IPU}}$</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-qm1b-with-pyscf-text-ipu</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Similar benefits are yet to be unlocked for quantum chemistry, where the potential of deep learning is constrained by comparatively small datasets with 100k to 20M training examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-qm1b-with-pyscf-text-ipu</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Models for Reinforcement Learning: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-for-reinforcement-learning-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have emerged as a prominent class of generative models, surpassing previous methods regarding sample quality and training stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-for-reinforcement-learning-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Robustness via Tilted Exponential Layer: A Communication-Theoretic Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-robustness-via-tilted-exponential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art techniques for enhancing robustness of deep networks mostly rely on empirical risk minimization with suitable data augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-robustness-via-tilted-exponential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Series Anomaly Detection using Diffusion-based Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-anomaly-detection-using-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our models outperform the baselines on synthetic datasets and are competitive on real-world datasets, illustrating the potential of diffusion-based methods for AD in multivariate time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-anomaly-detection-using-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task-Agnostic Low-Rank Adapters for Unseen English Dialects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-agnostic-low-rank-adapters-for-unseen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are trained on corpora disproportionally weighted in favor of Standard American English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-agnostic-low-rank-adapters-for-unseen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H-NeXt: The next step towards roto-translation invariant networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h-next-the-next-step-towards-roto-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The widespread popularity of equivariant networks underscores the significance of parameter efficient models and effective use of training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h-next-the-next-step-towards-roto-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VCISR: Blind Single Image Super-Resolution with Video Compression Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vcisr-blind-single-image-super-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we for the first time, present a video compression-based degradation model to synthesize low-resolution image data in the blind SISR task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vcisr-blind-single-image-super-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Large Language Models for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-large-language-models-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated abilities including understanding context, logical reasoning, and generating answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-large-language-models-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AiluRus: A Scalable ViT Framework for Dense Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ailurus-a-scalable-vit-framework-for-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, at the intermediate layer of the ViT, we utilize a spatial-aware density-based clustering algorithm to select representative tokens from the token sequence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ailurus-a-scalable-vit-framework-for-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Chain of Thought Reasoning via Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-chain-of-thought-reasoning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore an alternative reasoning approach: instead of explicitly producing the chain of thought reasoning steps, we use the language model's internal hidden states to perform implicit reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-chain-of-thought-reasoning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offline Imitation from Observation via Primal Wasserstein State Occupancy Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-imitation-from-observation-via-primal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we propose Primal Wasserstein DICE (PW-DICE), which minimizes the primal Wasserstein distance between the expert and learner state occupancies with a pessimistic regularizer and leverages a contrastively learned distance as the underlying metric for the Wasserstein distance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-imitation-from-observation-via-primal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resilient Multiple Choice Learning: A learned scoring scheme with application to audio scene analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resilient-multiple-choice-learning-a-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiple Choice Learning is a simple framework to tackle multimodal density estimation, using the Winner-Takes-All (WTA) loss for a set of hypotheses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resilient-multiple-choice-learning-a-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Human-AI Teams via Learned Natural Language Rules and Onboarding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-human-ai-teams-via-learned-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our novel region discovery algorithm finds local regions in the data as neighborhoods in an embedding space that corrects the human prior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-human-ai-teams-via-learned-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Solution for Offline Imitation from Observations and Examples with Possibly Incomplete Trajectories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-solution-for-offline-imitation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Offline imitation from observations aims to solve MDPs where only task-specific expert states and task-agnostic non-expert state-action pairs are available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-solution-for-offline-imitation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight super resolution network for point cloud geometry compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-super-resolution-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an approach for compressing point cloud geometry by leveraging a lightweight super-resolution network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-super-resolution-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation Measures of Individual Item Fairness for Recommender Systems: A Critical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-measures-of-individual-item</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our knowledge, this is the first critical comparison of individual item fairness measures in recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-measures-of-individual-item</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SatBird: Bird Species Distribution Modeling with Remote Sensing and Citizen Science Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/satbird-bird-species-distribution-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The wide availability of remote sensing data and the growing adoption of citizen science tools to collect species observations data at low cost offer an opportunity for improving biodiversity monitoring and enabling the modelling of complex ecosystems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/satbird-bird-species-distribution-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Transport-Guided Conditional Score-Based Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-guided-conditional-score</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conditional score-based diffusion model (SBDM) is for conditional generation of target data with paired data as condition, and has achieved great success in image translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-guided-conditional-score</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
