<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:06:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Mixture of Prototypes for Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-mixture-of-prototypes-for-out</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these issues, we propose PrototypicAl Learning with a Mixture of prototypes (PALM) which models each class with multiple prototypes to capture the sample diversities, and learns more faithful and compact samples embeddings to enhance OOD detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-mixture-of-prototypes-for-out</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM Agents in Interaction: Measuring Personality Consistency and Linguistic Alignment in Interacting Populations of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-agents-in-interaction-measuring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While both agent interaction and personalisation are vibrant topics in research on large language models (LLMs), there has been limited focus on the effect of language interaction on the behaviour of persona-conditioned LLM agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-agents-in-interaction-measuring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BGE M3-Embedding: Multi-Lingual, Multi-Functionality, Multi-Granularity Text Embeddings Through Self-Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bge-m3-embedding-multi-lingual-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It can simultaneously perform the three common retrieval functionalities of embedding model: dense retrieval, multi-vector retrieval, and sparse retrieval, which provides a unified model foundation for real-world IR applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bge-m3-embedding-multi-lingual-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CT-based Anatomical Segmentation for Thoracic Surgical Planning: A Benchmark Study for 3D U-shaped Deep Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ct-based-anatomical-segmentation-for-thoracic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct the first benchmark study for variants of 3D U-shaped models (3DUNet, STUNet, AttentionUNet, SwinUNETR, FocalSegNet, and a novel 3D SwinUnet with four variants) with a focus on CT-based anatomical segmentation for thoracic surgery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ct-based-anatomical-segmentation-for-thoracic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Sounds Sound for Phylogenetic Reconstruction?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-sounds-sound-for-phylogenetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In traditional studies on language evolution, scholars often emphasize the importance of sound laws and sound correspondences for phylogenetic inference of language family trees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-sounds-sound-for-phylogenetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Define Your Terms" : Enhancing Efficient Offensive Speech Classification with Definition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/define-your-terms-enhancing-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The propagation of offensive content through social media channels has garnered attention of the research community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/define-your-terms-enhancing-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List-aware Reranking-Truncation Joint Model for Search and Retrieval-augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/list-aware-reranking-truncation-joint-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, it is hard to share the contextual information of the ranking list between the two tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/list-aware-reranking-truncation-joint-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-dimensional Bayesian Optimization via Covariance Matrix Adaptation Strategy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-bayesian-optimization-via-5</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, a promising solution is to use a local search strategy that partitions the search domain into local regions with high likelihood of containing the global optimum, and then use BO to optimize the objective function within these regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-bayesian-optimization-via-5</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACER: An LLM-powered Methodology for Scalable Analysis of Semi-structured Mental Health Interviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/racer-an-llm-powered-methodology-for-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-structured interviews (SSIs) are a commonly employed data-collection method in healthcare research, offering in-depth qualitative insights into subject experiences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/racer-an-llm-powered-methodology-for-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and Guiding Weakly Supervised Entity Alignment with Potential Isomorphism Propagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-guiding-weakly-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a propagation perspective to analyze weakly supervised EA and explain the existing aggregation-based EA models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-guiding-weakly-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Compositional Generalization via Compositional Feature Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-compositional-generalization-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To delve into the CG challenge, we develop CG-Bench, a suite of CG benchmarks derived from existing real-world image datasets, and observe that the prevalent pretraining-finetuning paradigm on foundational models, such as CLIP and DINOv2, struggles with the challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-compositional-generalization-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOBSKAPE: A Framework for Generating Synthetic Job Postings to Enhance Skill Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jobskape-a-framework-for-generating-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent approaches in skill matching, employing synthetic training data for classification or similarity model training, have shown promising results, reducing the need for time-consuming and expensive annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jobskape-a-framework-for-generating-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Stationary Latent Auto-Regressive Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-stationary-latent-auto-regressive-bandits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the stochastic multi-armed bandit problem with non-stationary rewards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-stationary-latent-auto-regressive-bandits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate and Well-Calibrated ICD Code Assignment Through Attention Over Diverse Label Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-and-well-calibrated-icd-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the International Classification of Diseases (ICD) has been adopted worldwide, manually assigning ICD codes to clinical text is time-consuming, error-prone, and expensive, motivating the development of automated approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-and-well-calibrated-icd-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty of Thoughts: Uncertainty-Aware Planning Enhances Information Seeking in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-of-thoughts-uncertainty-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the face of uncertainty, the ability to seek information is of fundamental importance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-of-thoughts-uncertainty-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Eliminating Hard Label Constraints in Gradient Inversion Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-eliminating-hard-label-constraints-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even for single-image reconstruction, we still lack an analysis-based algorithm to recover augmented soft labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-eliminating-hard-label-constraints-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeekMath: Pushing the Limits of Mathematical Reasoning in Open Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseekmath-pushing-the-limits-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mathematical reasoning poses a significant challenge for language models due to its complex and structured nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseekmath-pushing-the-limits-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EasyInstruct: An Easy-to-use Instruction Processing Framework for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyinstruct-an-easy-to-use-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, instruction tuning has gained increasing attention and emerged as a crucial technique to enhance the capabilities of Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyinstruct-an-easy-to-use-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the development of a practical Bayesian optimisation algorithm for expensive experiments and simulations with changing environmental conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-development-of-a-practical-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ENVBO finds solutions for the full domain of the environmental variable that outperforms results from optimisation algorithms that only focus on a fixed environmental value in all but one case while using a fraction of their evaluation budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-development-of-a-practical-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimum Description Length and Generalization Guarantees for Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimum-description-length-and-generalization-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rather than the mutual information between the encoder's input and the representation, which is often believed to reflect the algorithm's generalization capability in the related literature but in fact, falls short of doing so, our new bounds involve the "multi-letter" relative entropy between the distribution of the representations (or labels) of the training and test sets and a fixed prior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimum-description-length-and-generalization-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intent-based Prompt Calibration: Enhancing prompt optimization with synthetic boundary cases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intent-based-prompt-calibration-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies have demonstrated the capabilities of LLMs to automatically conduct prompt engineering by employing a meta-prompt that incorporates the outcomes of the last trials and proposes an improved prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intent-based-prompt-calibration-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIDAR: Culturally Relevant Instruction Dataset For Arabic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cidar-culturally-relevant-instruction-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instruction tuning has emerged as a prominent methodology for teaching Large Language Models (LLMs) to follow instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cidar-culturally-relevant-instruction-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Optimization and Architecture for Tiny Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-optimization-and-architecture-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several design formulas are empirically proved especially effective for tiny language models, including tokenizer compression, architecture tweaking, parameter inheritance and multiple-round training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-optimization-and-architecture-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Configuration Performance in Multiple Environments with Sequential Meta-learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-configuration-performance-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through comparing with 15 state-of-the-art models under nine systems, our extensive experimental results demonstrate that SeMPL performs considerably better on 89% of the systems with up to 99% accuracy improvement, while being data-efficient, leading to a maximum of 3. 86x speedup.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-configuration-performance-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Description on IEEE ICME 2024 Grand Challenge: Semi-supervised Acoustic Scene Classification under Domain Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/description-on-ieee-icme-2024-grand-challenge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Acoustic scene classification (ASC) is a crucial research problem in computational auditory scene analysis, and it aims to recognize the unique acoustic characteristics of an environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/description-on-ieee-icme-2024-grand-challenge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model Distilling Medication Recommendation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-distilling-medication</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel approach called Large Language Model Distilling Medication Recommendation (LEADER).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-distilling-medication</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Computational Model for the Assessment of Mutual Intelligibility Among Closely Related Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-computational-model-for-the-assessment-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Closely related languages show linguistic similarities that allow speakers of one language to understand speakers of another language without having actively learned it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-computational-model-for-the-assessment-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embedding Hardware Approximations in Discrete Genetic-based Training for Printed MLPs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embedding-hardware-approximations-in-discrete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the discrete nature of hardware approximation, we propose and implement a genetic-based, approximate, hardware-aware training approach specifically designed for printed MLPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embedding-hardware-approximations-in-discrete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed Noise and Posterior Estimation with Conditional DeepGEM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-noise-and-posterior-estimation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by indirect measurements and applications from nanometrology with a mixed noise model, we develop a novel algorithm for jointly estimating the posterior and the noise parameters in Bayesian inverse problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-noise-and-posterior-estimation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image-Caption Encoding for Improving Zero-Shot Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-caption-encoding-for-improving-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first show that when an OOD data point is misclassified, the correct class can be typically found in the Top-K predicted classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-caption-encoding-for-improving-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Hallucination Detection for Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-hallucination-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant strides in multimodal tasks, Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) are plagued by the critical issue of hallucination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-hallucination-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swin-UMamba: Mamba-based UNet with ImageNet-based pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swin-umamba-mamba-based-unet-with-imagenet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, it is challenging for existing methods to model long-range global information, where convolutional neural networks (CNNs) are constrained by their local receptive fields, and vision transformers (ViTs) suffer from high quadratic complexity of their attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swin-umamba-mamba-based-unet-with-imagenet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VlogQA: Task, Dataset, and Baseline Models for Vietnamese Spoken-Based Machine Reading Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlogqa-task-dataset-and-baseline-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the development process of a Vietnamese spoken language corpus for machine reading comprehension (MRC) tasks and provides insights into the challenges and opportunities associated with using real-world data for machine reading comprehension tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlogqa-task-dataset-and-baseline-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting VAE for Unsupervised Time Series Anomaly Detection: A Frequency Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-vae-for-unsupervised-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To ensure an accurate AD, FCVAE exploits an innovative approach to concurrently integrate both the global and local frequency features into the condition of Conditional Variational Autoencoder (CVAE) to significantly increase the accuracy of reconstructing the normal data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-vae-for-unsupervised-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViewFusion: Learning Composable Diffusion Models for Novel View Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/viewfusion-learning-composable-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning is providing a wealth of new approaches to the old problem of novel view synthesis, from Neural Radiance Field (NeRF) based approaches to end-to-end style architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/viewfusion-learning-composable-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Teaching Regularization: Generalizable Correlations Should be Easy to Imitate</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-teaching-regularization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The student learners are trained by the main model and improve the main model to capture more generalizable and teachable correlations by providing feedback.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-teaching-regularization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISPA: Inter-Species Phonetic Alphabet for Transcribing Animal Sounds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ispa-inter-species-phonetic-alphabet-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditionally, bioacoustics has relied on spectrograms and continuous, per-frame audio representations for the analysis of animal sounds, also serving as input to machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ispa-inter-species-phonetic-alphabet-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transcending Adversarial Perturbations: Manifold-Aided Adversarial Examples with Legitimate Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transcending-adversarial-perturbations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks were significantly vulnerable to adversarial examples manipulated by malicious tiny perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transcending-adversarial-perturbations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Representation Surgery for Multi-Task Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-surgery-for-multi-task-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[That is, there is a significant discrepancy in the representation distribution between the merged and individual models, resulting in poor performance of merged MTL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-surgery-for-multi-task-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayes-Optimal Fair Classification with Linear Disparity Constraints via Pre-, In-, and Post-processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayes-optimal-fair-classification-with-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we develop methods for Bayes-optimal fair classification, aiming to minimize classification error subject to given group fairness constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayes-optimal-fair-classification-with-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Citation needed] Data usage and citation practices in medical imaging conferences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citation-needed-data-usage-and-citation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We applied both tools on a study of the usage of 20 publicly available medical datasets in papers from MICCAI and MIDL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citation-needed-data-usage-and-citation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KIVI: A Tuning-Free Asymmetric 2bit Quantization for KV Cache</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kivi-a-tuning-free-asymmetric-2bit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This memory demand increases with larger batch sizes and longer context lengths.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kivi-a-tuning-free-asymmetric-2bit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InteractiveVideo: User-Centric Controllable Video Generation with Synergistic Multimodal Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactivevideo-user-centric-controllable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce $\textit{InteractiveVideo}$, a user-centric framework for video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactivevideo-user-centric-controllable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good Teachers Explain: Explanation-Enhanced Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/good-teachers-explain-explanation-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Distillation (KD) has proven effective for compressing large teacher models into smaller student models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/good-teachers-explain-explanation-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putting Context in Context: the Impact of Discussion Structure on Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/putting-context-in-context-the-impact-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also experiment with different amounts of training data and analyse the topology of local discussion networks in a privacy-compliant way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/putting-context-in-context-the-impact-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptRR: Diffusion Models as Prompt Generators for Single Image Reflection Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptrr-diffusion-models-as-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the prompt generation, we first propose a prompt pre-training strategy to train a frequency prompt encoder that encodes the ground-truth image into LF and HF prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptrr-diffusion-models-as-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Transformer RNNs with Multiple Temporal Perspectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-transformer-rnns-with-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, the additional parameters necessary for the multiple temporal perspectives are fine-tuned with minimal computational overhead, avoiding the need for a full pre-training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-transformer-rnns-with-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neur2BiLO: Neural Bilevel Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neur2bilo-neural-bilevel-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bilevel optimization deals with nested problems in which a leader takes the first decision to minimize their objective function while accounting for a follower's best-response reaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neur2bilo-neural-bilevel-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Spectral Improvement for Unsupervised Image Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-spectral-improvement-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the fact that not all channels of the feature map extracted from a self-supervised backbone contain sufficient information for instance segmentation purposes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-spectral-improvement-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Low-level Representations for Ultra-Fast Road Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-low-level-representations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The spatial detail branch is firstly designed to extract low-level feature representation for the road by the first stage of ResNet-18.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-low-level-representations-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
