<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 09:13:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing Hierarchical Structure of Leaf Venations in Plant Science via Label-Efficient Segmentation: Dataset and Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-hierarchical-structure-of-leaf</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hierarchical leaf vein segmentation is a crucial but under-explored task in agricultural sciences, where analysis of the hierarchical structure of plant leaf venation can contribute to plant breeding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-hierarchical-structure-of-leaf</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4D Panoptic Scene Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4d-panoptic-scene-graph-generation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate research in this new area, we build a richly annotated PSG-4D dataset consisting of 3K RGB-D videos with a total of 1M frames, each of which is labeled with 4D panoptic segmentation masks as well as fine-grained, dynamic scene graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4d-panoptic-scene-graph-generation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiverGen: Improving Instance Segmentation by Learning Wider Data Distribution with More Diverse Generative Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divergen-improving-instance-segmentation-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instance segmentation is data-hungry, and as model capacity increases, data scale becomes crucial for improving the accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divergen-improving-instance-segmentation-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Far Are We From AGI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-are-we-from-agi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The evolution of artificial intelligence (AI) has profoundly impacted human society, driving significant advancements in multiple sectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-are-we-from-agi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Semantics in Multimodal Chain of Thought via Soft Negative Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-semantics-in-multimodal-chain-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Five methods were applied to generate soft negative samples that shared highly similar text but had different semantics from the original.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-semantics-in-multimodal-chain-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Algorithmic Bias in Models for Predicting Academic Performance of Filipino Students</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-algorithmic-bias-in-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The best-performing model reached AUC of 0. 75 and weighted F1-score of 0. 79.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-algorithmic-bias-in-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning for Misbehaviour Detection with Variational Autoencoders and Gaussian Mixture Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-for-misbehaviour-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) has become an attractive approach to collaboratively train Machine Learning (ML) models while data sources' privacy is still preserved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-for-misbehaviour-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Size-invariance Matters: Rethinking Metrics and Losses for Imbalanced Multi-object Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/size-invariance-matters-rethinking-metrics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the size-invariance of evaluation metrics in Salient Object Detection (SOD), especially when multiple targets of diverse sizes co-exist in the same image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/size-invariance-matters-rethinking-metrics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influence Maximization in Hypergraphs using Multi-Objective Evolutionary Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/influence-maximization-in-hypergraphs-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Among the various methods for solving the IM problem, evolutionary algorithms (EAs) have been shown to be particularly effective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/influence-maximization-in-hypergraphs-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Federated Learning via Informed Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-federated-learning-via-informed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, its application on edge devices is hindered by limited computational capabilities and data communication challenges, compounded by the inherent complexity of Deep Learning (DL) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-federated-learning-via-informed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMLP: Symbolic Machine Learning Prover (User Manual)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smlp-symbolic-machine-learning-prover-user</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SMLP: Symbolic Machine Learning Prover an open source tool for exploration and optimization of systems represented by machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smlp-symbolic-machine-learning-prover-user</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iDRAMA-Scored-2024: A Dataset of the Scored Social Media Platform from 2020 to 2023</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idrama-scored-2024-a-dataset-of-the-scored</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online web communities often face bans for violating platform policies, encouraging their migration to alternative platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idrama-scored-2024-a-dataset-of-the-scored</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PL-MTEB: Polish Massive Text Embedding Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pl-mteb-polish-massive-text-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce the Polish Massive Text Embedding Benchmark (PL-MTEB), a comprehensive benchmark for text embeddings in Polish.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pl-mteb-polish-massive-text-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many-Shot In-Context Learning in Multimodal Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/many-shot-in-context-learning-in-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that batching up to 50 queries can lead to performance improvements under zero-shot and many-shot ICL, with substantial gains in the zero-shot setting on multiple datasets, while drastically reducing per-query cost and latency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/many-shot-in-context-learning-in-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Learning with Fully Bayesian Neural Networks for Discontinuous and Nonstationary Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-with-fully-bayesian-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we assess the suitability and performance of FBNNs with the No-U-Turn Sampler for active learning tasks in the 'small data' regime, highlighting their potential to enhance predictive accuracy and reliability on test functions relevant to problems in physical sciences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-with-fully-bayesian-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HW-GPT-Bench: Hardware-Aware Architecture Benchmark for Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hw-gpt-bench-hardware-aware-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose HW-GPT-Bench, a hardware-aware language model surrogate benchmark, where we leverage weight-sharing techniques from Neural Architecture Search (NAS) to efficiently train a supernet proxy, encompassing language models of varying scales in a single model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hw-gpt-bench-hardware-aware-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whole-Song Hierarchical Generation of Symbolic Music Using Cascaded Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whole-song-hierarchical-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A cascaded diffusion model is trained to model the hierarchical language, where each level is conditioned on its upper levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whole-song-hierarchical-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Deep Audio-Text Retrieval Through the Lens of Transportation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-deep-audio-text-retrieval-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Learning-to-match (LTM) framework proves to be an effective inverse optimal transport approach for learning the underlying ground metric between two sources of data, facilitating subsequent matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-deep-audio-text-retrieval-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CatCMA : Stochastic Optimization for Mixed-Category Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/catcma-stochastic-optimization-for-mixed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CatCMA updates the parameters of the joint probability distribution in the natural gradient direction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/catcma-stochastic-optimization-for-mixed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-Oriented Semantic Latent Representation for Image Transmission</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-oriented-semantic-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the new paradigm of semantic communication (SC), the focus is on delivering meanings behind bits by extracting semantic information from raw data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-oriented-semantic-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Aggregation of Prediction Intervals under Unsupervised Domain Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-aggregation-of-prediction-intervals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose methodologies for aggregating prediction intervals to obtain one with minimal width and adequate coverage on the target domain under unsupervised domain shift, under which we have labeled samples from a related source domain and unlabeled covariates from the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-aggregation-of-prediction-intervals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bilateral Event Mining and Complementary for Event Stream Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilateral-event-mining-and-complementary-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a bilateral event mining and complementary network (BMCNet) to fully leverage the potential of each event and capture the shared information to complement each other simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilateral-event-mining-and-complementary-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffAM: Diffusion-based Adversarial Makeup Transfer for Facial Privacy Protection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffam-diffusion-based-adversarial-makeup</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel face protection approach, dubbed DiffAM, which leverages the powerful generative ability of diffusion models to generate high-quality protected face images with adversarial makeup transferred from reference images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffam-diffusion-based-adversarial-makeup</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIR: Remote Sensing Image-Text Retrieval with Prior Instruction Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pir-remote-sensing-image-text-retrieval-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continuing with the above, we propose PIR-CLIP, a domain-specific CLIP-based framework for remote sensing image-text retrieval, to address semantic noise in remote sensing vision-language representations and further improve open-domain retrieval performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pir-remote-sensing-image-text-retrieval-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LFED: A Literary Fiction Evaluation Dataset for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lfed-a-literary-fiction-evaluation-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid evolution of large language models (LLMs) has ushered in the need for comprehensive assessments of their performance across various dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lfed-a-literary-fiction-evaluation-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROCOv2: Radiology Objects in COntext Version 2, an Updated Multimodal Image Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rocov2-radiology-objects-in-context-version-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dataset is suitable for training image annotation models based on image-caption pairs, or for multi-label image classification using Unified Medical Language System (UMLS) concepts provided with each image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rocov2-radiology-objects-in-context-version-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeMeViT: Efficient Vision Transformer with Learnable Meta Tokens for Remote Sensing Image Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lemevit-efficient-vision-transformer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results in classification and dense prediction tasks show that LeMeViT has a significant $1. 7 \times$ speedup, fewer parameters, and competitive performance compared to the baseline models, and achieves a better trade-off between efficiency and performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lemevit-efficient-vision-transformer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalarisation-based risk concepts for robust multi-objective optimisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalarisation-based-risk-concepts-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robustification refers to the strategy that is used to marginalise over the uncertainty in the problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalarisation-based-risk-concepts-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manifold Integrated Gradients: Riemannian Geometry for Feature Attribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manifold-integrated-gradients-riemannian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we dive into the reliability concerns of Integrated Gradients (IG), a prevalent feature attribution method for black-box deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manifold-integrated-gradients-riemannian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keep It Private: Unsupervised Privatization of Online Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/keep-it-private-unsupervised-privatization-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Authorship obfuscation techniques hold the promise of helping people protect their privacy in online communications by automatically rewriting text to hide the identity of the original author.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/keep-it-private-unsupervised-privatization-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Region of Interest Detection in Melanocytic Skin Tumor Whole Slide Images -- Nevus &amp; Melanoma</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/region-of-interest-detection-in-melanocytic-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated region of interest detection in histopathological image analysis is a challenging and important topic with tremendous potential impact on clinical practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/region-of-interest-detection-in-melanocytic-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransMI: A Framework to Create Strong Baselines from Multilingual Pretrained Language Models for Transliterated Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transmi-a-framework-to-create-strong</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We applied TransMI to three recent strong mPLMs, and our experiments demonstrate that TransMI not only preserves their ability to handle non-transliterated data, but also enables the models to effectively process transliterated data: the results show a consistent improvement of 3% to 34%, varying across different models and tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transmi-a-framework-to-create-strong</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Unlearning for Any Identity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-unlearning-for-any-identity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the generative identity unlearning, we target the following objectives: (i) preventing the generation of images with a certain identity, and (ii) preserving the overall quality of the generative model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-unlearning-for-any-identity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Attention Graph for Scientific Document Summarization in Global and Local Level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-attention-graph-for-scientific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The long input hinders the simultaneous effective modeling of both global high-order relations between sentences and local intra-sentence relations which is the most critical step in extractive summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-attention-graph-for-scientific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Histopathology Foundation Models Enable Accurate Ovarian Cancer Subtype Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histopathology-foundation-models-enable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Five-class classification performance was evaluated through five-fold cross-validation, and these cross-validation models were ensembled for evaluation on a hold-out test set and an external set from the Transcanadian study.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histopathology-foundation-models-enable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Static Calibration: The Impact of User Preference Dynamics on Calibrated Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-static-calibration-the-impact-of-user</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Calibration in recommender systems is an important performance criterion that ensures consistency between the distribution of user preference categories and that of recommendations generated by the system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-static-calibration-the-impact-of-user</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Extractive Dialogue Summarization in Hyperdimensional Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-extractive-dialogue</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present HyperSum, an extractive summarization framework that captures both the efficiency of traditional lexical summarization and the accuracy of contemporary neural approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-extractive-dialogue</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRSRMamba: Infrared Image Super-Resolution via Mamba-based Wavelet Transform Feature Modulation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irsrmamba-infrared-image-super-resolution-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research advances IR super-resolution and demonstrates the potential of Mamba-based models in IR image processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irsrmamba-infrared-image-super-resolution-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DocuMint: Docstring Generation for Python using Small Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/documint-docstring-generation-for-python</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Effective communication, specifically through documentation, is the beating heart of collaboration among contributors in software development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/documint-docstring-generation-for-python</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Task-Compatible Compressible Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-task-compatible-compressible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate the impact of this idea in the context of input reconstruction more rigorously and extended it to other computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-task-compatible-compressible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grounding DINO 1.5: Advance the "Edge" of Open-Set Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-dino-1-5-advance-the-edge-of-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirical results demonstrate the effectiveness of Grounding DINO 1. 5, with the Grounding DINO 1. 5 Pro model attaining a 54. 3 AP on the COCO detection benchmark and a 55. 7 AP on the LVIS-minival zero-shot transfer benchmark, setting new records for open-set object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-dino-1-5-advance-the-edge-of-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MarkLLM: An Open-Source Toolkit for LLM Watermarking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/markllm-an-open-source-toolkit-for-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the abundance of LLM watermarking algorithms, their intricate mechanisms, and the complex evaluation procedures and perspectives pose challenges for researchers and the community to easily experiment with, understand, and assess the latest advancements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/markllm-an-open-source-toolkit-for-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Libra: Building Decoupled Vision System on Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/libra-building-decoupled-vision-system-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we incorporate a routed visual expert with a cross-modal bridge module into a pretrained LLM to route the vision and language flows during attention computing to enable different attention patterns in inner-modal modeling and cross-modal interaction scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/libra-building-decoupled-vision-system-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SecureLLM: Using Compositionality to Build Provably Secure Language Models for Private, Sensitive, and Secret Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/securellm-using-compositionality-to-build</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We reflect the compositional nature of such security mechanisms back into the structure of LLMs to build a provably secure LLM; that we term SecureLLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/securellm-using-compositionality-to-build</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Space Learning for Cross-Color Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-space-learning-for-cross-color-person</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The primary color profile of the same identity is assumed to remain consistent in typical Person Re-identification (Person ReID) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-space-learning-for-cross-color-person</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illumination Histogram Consistency Metric for Quantitative Assessment of Video Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illumination-histogram-consistency-metric-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a illumination histogram consistency (IHC) metric to quantitatively and automatically evaluate the illumination consistency of the video sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illumination-histogram-consistency-metric-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeCoDEx: Confounder Detector Guidance for Improved Diffusion-based Counterfactual Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decodex-confounder-detector-guidance-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning classifiers are prone to latching onto dominant confounders present in a dataset rather than on the causal markers associated with the target class, leading to poor generalization and biased predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decodex-confounder-detector-guidance-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaze-DETR: Using Expert Gaze to Reduce False Positives in Vulvovaginal Candidiasis Screening</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaze-detr-using-expert-gaze-to-reduce-false</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate detection of vulvovaginal candidiasis is critical for women's health, yet its sparse distribution and visually ambiguous characteristics pose significant challenges for accurate identification by pathologists and neural networks alike.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaze-detr-using-expert-gaze-to-reduce-false</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lens functions for exploring UMAP Projections with Domain Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lens-functions-for-exploring-umap-projections</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The effectiveness of the lens functions is demonstrated in two use cases and their computational cost is analysed in a synthetic benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lens-functions-for-exploring-umap-projections</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenGait: A Comprehensive Benchmark Study for Gait Recognition towards Better Practicality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opengait-a-comprehensive-benchmark-study-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we first develop OpenGait, a flexible and efficient gait recognition platform.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opengait-a-comprehensive-benchmark-study-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
