<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 21:09:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Table2Image: Interpretable Tabular data Classification with Realistic Image Transformations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/table2image-interpretable-tabular-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in deep learning for tabular data have demonstrated promising performance, yet interpretable models remain limited, with many relying on complex and large-scale architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/table2image-interpretable-tabular-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Splatter-360: Generalizable 360$^{\circ}$ Gaussian Splatting for Wide-baseline Panoramic Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/splatter-360-generalizable-360-circ-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wide-baseline panoramic images are frequently used in applications like VR and simulations to minimize capturing labor costs and storage needs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/splatter-360-generalizable-360-circ-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEX: Data Channel Extension for Efficient CNN Inference on Tiny AI Accelerators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dex-data-channel-extension-for-efficient-cnn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By leveraging underutilized processors and data memory for channel extension, DEX facilitates parallel execution without increasing inference latency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dex-data-channel-extension-for-efficient-cnn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iLLaVA: An Image is Worth Fewer Than 1/3 Input Tokens in Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illava-an-image-is-worth-fewer-than-1-3-input</link>
      <description><![CDATA[iLLaVA can nearly 2$\times$ the throughput, and reduce the memory costs by half with only a 0. 2\% - 0. 5\% performance drop across models of different scales including 7B, 13B and 34B.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illava-an-image-is-worth-fewer-than-1-3-input</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Normalizing Flows are Capable Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normalizing-flows-are-capable-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Normalizing Flows (NFs) are likelihood-based models for continuous inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normalizing-flows-are-capable-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Free Backdoor Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-free-backdoor-attacks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing backdoor attacks require either retraining the classifier with some clean data or modifying the model's architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-free-backdoor-attacks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inverting Visual Representations with Detection Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverting-visual-representations-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the mechanisms underlying deep neural networks in computer vision remains a fundamental challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverting-visual-representations-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gated Delta Networks: Improving Mamba2 with Delta Rule</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gated-delta-networks-improving-mamba2-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Linear Transformers have gained attention as efficient alternatives to standard Transformers, but their performance in retrieval and long-context tasks has been limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gated-delta-networks-improving-mamba2-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driv3R: Learning Dense 4D Reconstruction for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/driv3r-learning-dense-4d-reconstruction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Realtime 4D reconstruction for dynamic scenes remains a crucial challenge for autonomous driving perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/driv3r-learning-dense-4d-reconstruction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query-Efficient Planning with Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-efficient-planning-with-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first uses LLMs as a heuristic within a search-based planner to select promising nodes to expand and propose promising actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-efficient-planning-with-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimuDICE: Offline Policy Optimization Through World Model Updates and DICE Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simudice-offline-policy-optimization-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In offline reinforcement learning, deriving an effective policy from a pre-collected set of experiences is challenging due to the distribution mismatch between the target policy and the behavioral policy used to collect the data, as well as the limited sample size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simudice-offline-policy-optimization-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lightweight U-like Network Utilizing Neural Memory Ordinary Differential Equations for Slimming the Decoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-u-like-network-utilizing-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, advanced U-like networks have demonstrated remarkable performance in medical image segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-u-like-network-utilizing-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PolytopeWalk: Sparse MCMC Sampling over Polytopes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polytopewalk-sparse-mcmc-sampling-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High dimensional sampling is an important computational tool in statistics and other computational disciplines, with applications ranging from Bayesian statistical uncertainty quantification, metabolic modeling in systems biology to volume computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polytopewalk-sparse-mcmc-sampling-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Controllable Speech Synthesis in the Era of Large Language Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-controllable-speech-synthesis-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we conduct a comprehensive survey of controllable TTS, covering approaches ranging from basic control techniques to methods utilizing natural language prompts, aiming to provide a clear understanding of the current state of research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-controllable-speech-synthesis-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyPulse: A Python Library for Biosignal Imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pypulse-a-python-library-for-biosignal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce PyPulse, a Python package for imputation of biosignals in both clinical and wearable sensor settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pypulse-a-python-library-for-biosignal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proactive Agents for Multi-Turn Text-to-Image Generation Under Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proactive-agents-for-multi-turn-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose a design for proactive T2I agents equipped with an interface to (1) actively ask clarification questions when uncertain, and (2) present their understanding of user intent as an understandable belief graph that a user can edit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proactive-agents-for-multi-turn-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Divide: Reconsidering Softmax and Linear Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-divide-reconsidering-softmax-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Widely adopted in modern Vision Transformer designs, Softmax attention can effectively capture long-range visual information; however, it incurs excessive computational cost when dealing with high-resolution inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-divide-reconsidering-softmax-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Uncertainty to Trust: Enhancing Reliability in Vision-Language Models with Uncertainty-Guided Dropout Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-uncertainty-to-trust-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large vision-language models (LVLMs) demonstrate remarkable capabilities in multimodal tasks but are prone to misinterpreting visual inputs, often resulting in hallucinations and unreliable outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-uncertainty-to-trust-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMOv2: Pushing 5M Vision Model Frontier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emov2-pushing-5m-vision-model-frontier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our goal is to set up the new frontier of the 5M magnitude lightweight model on various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emov2-pushing-5m-vision-model-frontier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annotations for Exploring Food Tweets From Multiple Aspects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/annotations-for-exploring-food-tweets-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research builds upon the Latvian Twitter Eater Corpus (LTEC), which is focused on the narrow domain of tweets related to food, drinks, eating and drinking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/annotations-for-exploring-food-tweets-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ranking-aware adapter for text-driven image ordering with CLIP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ranking-aware-adapter-for-text-driven-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, our approach primarily focuses on ranking images with a single instruction, which provides a natural and generalized way of learning from visual differences across images, bypassing the need for extensive text prompts tailored to individual tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ranking-aware-adapter-for-text-driven-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MASK] is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-is-all-you-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In summary, by leveraging [MASK] in discrete-state models, we can bridge Masked Generative and Non-autoregressive Diffusion models, as well as generative and discriminative tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-is-all-you-need</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactile DreamFusion: Exploiting Tactile Sensing for 3D Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tactile-dreamfusion-exploiting-tactile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We design a lightweight 3D texture field to synthesize visual and tactile textures, guided by 2D diffusion model priors on both visual and tactile domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tactile-dreamfusion-exploiting-tactile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphNeuralNetworks.jl: Deep Learning on Graphs with Julia</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphneuralnetworks-jl-deep-learning-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GraphNeuralNetworks. jl is an open-source framework for deep learning on graphs, written in the Julia programming language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphneuralnetworks-jl-deep-learning-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HSDA: High-frequency Shuffle Data Augmentation for Bird's-Eye-View Map Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hsda-high-frequency-shuffle-data-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate the potential of frequency domain data augmentation for camera-based BEV map segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hsda-high-frequency-shuffle-data-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnable Evolutionary Multi-Objective Combinatorial Optimization via Sequence-to-Sequence Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-evolutionary-multi-objective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in learnable evolutionary algorithms have demonstrated the importance of leveraging population distribution information and historical evolutionary trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-evolutionary-multi-objective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delve into Visual Contrastive Decoding for Hallucination Mitigation of Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delve-into-visual-contrastive-decoding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we first explore various methods for contrastive decoding to change visual contents, including image downsampling and editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delve-into-visual-contrastive-decoding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copyright-Protected Language Generation via Adaptive Model Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copyright-protected-language-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, CP-Fuse adaptively aggregates the model outputs to minimize the reproduction of copyrighted content, adhering to a crucial balancing property that prevents the regurgitation of memorized data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copyright-protected-language-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoDCWorkflow: LLM-based Data Cleaning Workflow Auto-Generation and Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autodcworkflow-llm-based-data-cleaning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we propose a data cleaning benchmark to evaluate the capability of LLM agents to automatically generate workflows that address data cleaning purposes of varying difficulty levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autodcworkflow-llm-based-data-cleaning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PediaBench: A Comprehensive Chinese Pediatric Dataset for Benchmarking Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pediabench-a-comprehensive-chinese-pediatric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through an in-depth analysis of experimental results, we offer insights into the ability of LLMs to answer pediatric questions in the Chinese context, highlighting their limitations for further improvements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pediabench-a-comprehensive-chinese-pediatric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning for Segment Anything Model Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-for-segment-anything-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driven by the practical need, in this paper, we first propose a novel Continual SAM adaptation (CoSAM) benchmark with 8 different task domains and carefully analyze the limitations of the existing SAM one-step adaptation methods in the continual segmentation scenario.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-for-segment-anything-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOPy: A Framework for Black-box Vector Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vopy-a-framework-for-black-box-vector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce VOPy, an open-source Python library designed to address black-box vector optimization, where multiple objectives must be optimized simultaneously with respect to a partial order induced by a convex cone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vopy-a-framework-for-black-box-vector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BatchTopK Sparse Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batchtopk-sparse-autoencoders</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A popular approach is the TopK SAE, that uses a fixed number of the most active latents per sample to reconstruct the model activations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batchtopk-sparse-autoencoders</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaVA-SpaceSGG: Visual Instruct Tuning for Open-vocabulary Scene Graph Generation with Enhanced Spatial Relations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-spacesgg-visual-instruct-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scene Graph Generation (SGG) converts visual scenes into structured graph representations, providing deeper scene understanding for complex vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-spacesgg-visual-instruct-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMedPO: Aligning Medical Vision-Language Models with Clinical-Aware Multimodal Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmedpo-aligning-medical-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous attempts to enhance modality alignment in Med-LVLMs through preference optimization have inadequately mitigated clinical relevance in preference data, making these samples easily distinguishable and reducing alignment effectiveness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmedpo-aligning-medical-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Annotations for Object Detection in Art through Stable Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-annotations-for-object-detection-in-art</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object detection in art is a valuable tool for the digital humanities, as it allows for faster identification of objects in artistic and historical images compared to humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-annotations-for-object-detection-in-art</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holmes-VAU: Towards Long-term Video Anomaly Understanding at Any Granularity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holmes-vau-towards-long-term-video-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For efficient anomaly detection in long videos, we propose the Anomaly-focused Temporal Sampler (ATS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holmes-vau-towards-long-term-video-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class Balance Matters to Active Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-balance-matters-to-active-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then for each cluster, we employ greedy selection strategy to ensure that the Gaussian distribution of the sampled features closely matches the Gaussian distribution of all unlabeled features within the cluster.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-balance-matters-to-active-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Scalars: Concept-Based Alignment Analysis in Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-scalars-concept-based-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our methodological contributions address two key prerequisites for concept-based alignment: 1) For a description of the representation in terms of concepts that faithfully capture the geometry of the feature space, we define concepts as the most general structure they can possibly form - arbitrary manifolds, allowing hidden features to be described by their proximity to these manifolds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-scalars-concept-based-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Order Theory in the Context of Machine Learning: an application</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/order-theory-in-the-context-of-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also prove that the assignment from a poset to an order polytope (and to certain tropical polynomials) is one to one, and we define the structure of algebra over the operad of posets on tropical polynomials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/order-theory-in-the-context-of-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Learning with Probabilistic Density Labeling for Rainfall Probability Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-with-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerical weather prediction (NWP) models are fundamental in meteorology for simulating and forecasting the behavior of various atmospheric variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-with-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KaSA: Knowledge-Aware Singular-Value Adaptation of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kasa-knowledge-aware-singular-value</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing sizes of large language models (LLMs) result in significant computational overhead and memory usage when adapting these models to specific tasks or domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kasa-knowledge-aware-singular-value</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Source Acceleration of Stable-Diffusion.cpp</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-acceleration-of-stable-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, stable-diffusion. cpp (Sdcpp) emerges as an efficient inference framework to accelerate the diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-acceleration-of-stable-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Diffusion Posterior Sampling via Sequential Monte Carlo for Zero-Shot Scaffolding of Protein Motifs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-diffusion-posterior-sampling-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The latter is possible by pairing reconstruction guidance with $\mathrm{SE}(3)$-invariant potentials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-diffusion-posterior-sampling-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DapperFL: Domain Adaptive Federated Learning with Model Fusion Pruning for Edge Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dapperfl-domain-adaptive-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We implement DapperFL on a realworld FL platform with heterogeneous clients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dapperfl-domain-adaptive-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MG-3D: Multi-Grained Knowledge-Enhanced 3D Medical Vision-Language Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mg-3d-multi-grained-knowledge-enhanced-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on both internal and external datasets demonstrate the superior transferability, scalability, and generalization of MG-3D, showcasing its potential in advancing feature representation for 3D medical image analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mg-3d-multi-grained-knowledge-enhanced-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Modeling Data Quality and Machine Learning Model Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-modeling-data-quality-and-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the effect of uncertainty and noise in data on machine learning models (MLM) is crucial in developing trust and measuring performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-modeling-data-quality-and-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiDM: Pushing the Limit of Quantization for Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidm-pushing-the-limit-of-quantization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models (DMs) have been significantly developed and widely used in various applications due to their excellent generative qualities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidm-pushing-the-limit-of-quantization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time 3D Object Detection Using InnovizOne LiDAR and Low-Power Hailo-8 AI Accelerator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-3d-object-detection-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present the feasibility of performing real-time 3D object detection of cars using 3D point clouds from a LiDAR sensor, processed and deployed on a low-power Hailo-8 AI accelerator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-3d-object-detection-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSUniVLM: A Unified Vision Language Model for Remote Sensing via Granularity-oriented Mixture of Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsunivlm-a-unified-vision-language-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enhance the model's ability to capture visual information at different levels without increasing model size, we design a novel architecture called Granularity-oriented Mixture of Experts to constraint the model to about 1 billion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsunivlm-a-unified-vision-language-model-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
