<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 21:08:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Taming Data and Transformers for Audio Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-data-and-transformers-for-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating ambient sounds and effects is a challenging problem due to data scarcity and often insufficient caption quality, making it difficult to employ large-scale generative models for the task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-data-and-transformers-for-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test-Time Generative Augmentation for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-generative-augmentation-for-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach to enhance medical image segmentation during test time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-generative-augmentation-for-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedMNIST-C: Comprehensive benchmark and improved classifier robustness by simulating realistic image corruptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medmnist-c-comprehensive-benchmark-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The integration of neural-network-based systems into clinical practice is limited by challenges related to domain generalization and robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medmnist-c-comprehensive-benchmark-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Thorough Performance Benchmarking on Lightweight Embedding-based Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-thorough-performance-benchmarking-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art RSs primarily depend on categorical features, which ecoded by embedding vectors, resulting in excessively large embedding tables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-thorough-performance-benchmarking-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leave No Document Behind: Benchmarking Long-Context LLMs with Extended Multi-Doc QA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leave-no-document-behind-benchmarking-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long-context modeling capabilities have garnered widespread attention, leading to the emergence of Large Language Models (LLMs) with ultra-context windows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leave-no-document-behind-benchmarking-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval Augmented Instruction Tuning for Open NER with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-instruction-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The strong capability of large language models (LLMs) has been applied to information extraction (IE) through either retrieval augmented prompting or instruction tuning (IT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-instruction-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SE-VGAE: Unsupervised Disentangled Representation Learning for Interpretable Architectural Layout Design Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/se-vgae-unsupervised-disentangled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we contribute a new benchmark large-scale architectural layout graph dataset extracted from real-world floor plan images to facilitate the exploration of graph data-based architectural design representation space interpretation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/se-vgae-unsupervised-disentangled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Recursive Encoding for Cuneiform Signs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-recursive-encoding-for-cuneiform-signs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the most significant problems in cuneiform pedagogy is the process of looking up unknown signs, which often involves a tedious page-by-page search through a sign list.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-recursive-encoding-for-cuneiform-signs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRIP: Trainable Region-of-Interest Prediction for Hardware-Efficient Neuromorphic Processing on Event-based Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trip-trainable-region-of-interest-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduced extensive hardware-aware optimizations for TRIP and implemented the hardware-optimized algorithm on the SENECA neuromorphic processor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trip-trainable-region-of-interest-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Cross-Task Interaction for Survival Analysis in Whole Slide Pathological Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-cross-task-interaction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the joint representation of pathological images and genomic data, we further introduce a Transport-Guided Attention (TGA) module that uses optimal transport theory to model the correlation between subtype classification and survival analysis tasks, effectively transferring potential information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-cross-task-interaction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Universal Medical Image Registration via Sharpness-Aware Meta-Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-universal-medical-image-registration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current deep learning approaches in medical image registration usually face the challenges of distribution shift and data collection, hindering real-world deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-universal-medical-image-registration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MG-LLaVA: Towards Multi-Granularity Visual Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mg-llava-towards-multi-granularity-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the integration of an additional high-resolution visual encoder to capture fine-grained details, which are then fused with base visual features through a Conv-Gate fusion network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mg-llava-towards-multi-granularity-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Admission Control and Resource Allocation of Virtual Network Embedding via Hierarchical Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-admission-control-and-resource</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the whole VNE process is decomposed into an upper-level policy for deciding whether to admit the arriving VNR or not and a lower-level policy for allocating resources of the physical network to meet the requirement of VNR through the HRL approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-admission-control-and-resource</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LumberChunker: Long-Form Narrative Document Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lumberchunker-long-form-narrative-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern NLP tasks increasingly rely on dense retrieval methods to access up-to-date and relevant contextual information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lumberchunker-long-form-narrative-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask-Guided Attention U-Net for Enhanced Neonatal Brain Extraction and Image Preprocessing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-guided-attention-u-net-for-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The network employs a common encoder and two decoders: one for brain mask extraction and the other for brain region reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-guided-attention-u-net-for-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grass: Compute Efficient Low-Memory LLM Training with Structured Sparse Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grass-compute-efficient-low-memory-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language model (LLM) training and finetuning are often bottlenecked by limited GPU memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grass-compute-efficient-low-memory-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Programming Language and Natural Language: Exploring Design Choices in Multi-Modal Transformer-Based Embedding for Bug Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-programming-language-and-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bug localization refers to the identification of source code files which is in a programming language and also responsible for the unexpected behavior of software using the bug report, which is a natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-programming-language-and-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurgeMOD: Translating image-space tissue motions into vision-based surgical forces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgemod-translating-image-space-tissue</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using internal movements generated by natural processes like breathing or the cardiac cycle, we infer the image-space basis of the motion on the frequency domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgemod-translating-image-space-tissue</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the Big Five Personality Traits in Chinese Counselling Dialogues Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-big-five-personality-traits-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study exams whether Large Language Models (LLMs) can predict the Big Five personality traits directly from counseling dialogues and introduces an innovative framework to perform the task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-big-five-personality-traits-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Distributional to Overton Pluralism: Investigating Large Language Model Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-distributional-to-overton-pluralism</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Alignment suppresses irrelevant and unhelpful content while shifting the output distribution toward longer responses that cover information spanning several responses from the base LLM, essentially presenting diverse information in a single response.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-distributional-to-overton-pluralism</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models are Interpretable Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the proposed LLM-based Symbolic Programs (LSPs), the pretrained LLM with natural language prompts provides a massive set of interpretable modules that can transform raw input into natural language concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaLMQA: Exploring culturally specific long-form question answering across 23 languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calmqa-exploring-culturally-specific-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are commonly used for long-form question answering, which requires them to generate paragraph-length answers to complex questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calmqa-exploring-culturally-specific-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Image Segmentation Using Directional Window Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-image-segmentation-using-directional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The focus of our design is the introduction of Dwin block within DwinFormer that effectively captures local and global information along the horizontal, vertical, and depthwise directions of the input feature map by separately performing attention in each of these directional volumes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-image-segmentation-using-directional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DocParseNet: Advanced Semantic Segmentation and OCR Embeddings for Efficient Scanned Document Annotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docparsenet-advanced-semantic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automating the annotation of scanned documents is challenging, requiring a balance between computational efficiency and accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docparsenet-advanced-semantic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALPBench: A Benchmark for Active Learning Pipelines on Tabular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpbench-a-benchmark-for-active-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This particularly holds for the combination of query strategies with different learning algorithms into active learning pipelines and examining the impact of the learning algorithm choice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpbench-a-benchmark-for-active-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TopoGCL: Topological Graph Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topogcl-topological-graph-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph contrastive learning (GCL) has recently emerged as a new concept which allows for capitalizing on the strengths of graph neural networks (GNNs) to learn rich representations in a wide variety of applications which involve abundant unlabeled information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topogcl-topological-graph-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-SAM: Promptable 3D Segmentation Model for Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-sam-promptable-3d-segmentation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of 2D foundation models for image segmentation has been significantly advanced by the Segment Anything Model (SAM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-sam-promptable-3d-segmentation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XAMI -- A Benchmark Dataset for Artefact Detection in XMM-Newton Optical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xami-a-benchmark-dataset-for-artefact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hand-annotated a sample of 1000 images with artefacts which we use to train automated ML methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xami-a-benchmark-dataset-for-artefact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director3D: Real-world Camera Trajectory and 3D Scene Generation from Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/director3d-real-world-camera-trajectory-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this, (1) we first utilize a Trajectory Diffusion Transformer, acting as the Cinematographer, to model the distribution of camera trajectories based on textual descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/director3d-real-world-camera-trajectory-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DARG: Dynamic Evaluation of Large Language Models via Adaptive Reasoning Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/darg-dynamic-evaluation-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Dynamic Evaluation of LLMs via Adaptive Reasoning Graph Evolvement (DARG) to dynamically extend current benchmarks with controlled complexity and diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/darg-dynamic-evaluation-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Space Knowledge Distillation for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-space-knowledge-distillation-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, this discrepancy also hinders the KD process between models with different vocabularies, which is common for current LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-space-knowledge-distillation-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPT-Tree: Speculative Decoding with Adaptive Draft Tree Structure</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opt-tree-speculative-decoding-with-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It searches the optimal tree structure that maximizes the mathematical expectation of the acceptance length in each decoding step.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opt-tree-speculative-decoding-with-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANQAS: Kolmogorov Arnold Network for Quantum Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kanqas-kolmogorov-arnold-network-for-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a noiseless scenario, the probability of success and the number of optimal quantum circuit configurations to generate the multi-qubit maximally entangled states are significantly higher than MLPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kanqas-kolmogorov-arnold-network-for-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Continual Learning Abilities in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-continual-learning-abilities-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we introduce $\textbf{MIGU}$ ($\textbf{M}$agn$\textbf{I}$tude-based $\textbf{G}$radient $\textbf{U}$pdating for continual learning), a rehearsal-free and task-label-free method that only updates the model parameters with large magnitudes of output in LMs' linear layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-continual-learning-abilities-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled Motion Modeling for Video Frame Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-motion-modeling-for-video-frame</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, they require complex training and large computational cost for modeling on the pixel space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-motion-modeling-for-video-frame</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal-Channel Modeling in Multi-head Self-Attention for Synthetic Speech Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-channel-modeling-in-multi-head-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent synthetic speech detectors leveraging the Transformer model have superior performance compared to the convolutional neural network counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-channel-modeling-in-multi-head-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Graph Neural Networks Great Again: A Generic Integration Paradigm of Topology-Free Patterns for Traffic Speed Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-graph-neural-networks-great-again-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this challenge, we propose a generic model for enabling the current GNN-based methods to preserve topology-free patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-graph-neural-networks-great-again-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DreamBench++: A Human-Aligned Benchmark for Personalized Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreambench-a-human-aligned-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized image generation holds great promise in assisting humans in everyday work and life due to its impressive function in creatively generating personalized content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreambench-a-human-aligned-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GC-Bench: A Benchmark Framework for Graph Condensation with New Insights</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gc-bench-a-benchmark-framework-for-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental findings provide a deeper insights into the GC process and the characteristics of condensed graphs, guiding future efforts in enhancing performance and exploring new applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gc-bench-a-benchmark-framework-for-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long Context Transfer from Language to Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-context-transfer-from-language-to-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By simply extrapolating the context length of the language backbone, we enable LMMs to comprehend orders of magnitude more visual tokens without any video training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-context-transfer-from-language-to-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EHRCon: Dataset for Checking Consistency between Unstructured Notes and Structured Tables in Electronic Health Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ehrcon-dataset-for-checking-consistency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we developed EHRCon, a new dataset and task specifically designed to ensure data consistency between structured tables and unstructured notes in EHRs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ehrcon-dataset-for-checking-consistency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MD tree: a model-diagnostic tree grown on loss landscape</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/md-tree-a-model-diagnostic-tree-grown-on-loss</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper considers "model diagnosis", which we formulate as a classification problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/md-tree-a-model-diagnostic-tree-grown-on-loss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LangSuitE: Planning, Controlling and Interacting with Large Language Models in Embodied Text Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/langsuite-planning-controlling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in Large Language Models (LLMs) have shown inspiring achievements in constructing autonomous agents that rely on language descriptions as inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/langsuite-planning-controlling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User Story Tutor (UST) to Support Agile Software Developers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-story-tutor-ust-to-support-agile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applying UST to assist in the construction of User Stories is a viable technique that, at the very least, can be used by agile developments to complement and enhance current User Story creation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-story-tutor-ust-to-support-agile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOGCAN++: Local-global class-aware network for semantic segmentation of remote sensing images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logcan-local-global-class-aware-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we introduce affine transformations in the LCA module for adaptive extraction of local class representations to effectively tolerate scale and orientation variations in remotely sensed images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logcan-local-global-class-aware-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GPT-WritingPrompts Dataset: A Comparative Analysis of Character Portrayal in Short Stories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-gpt-writingprompts-dataset-a-comparative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that generated stories differ significantly from human stories along all six dimensions, and that human and machine generations display similar biases when grouped according to the narrative point-of-view and gender of the main protagonist.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-gpt-writingprompts-dataset-a-comparative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Cross-Domain Few-Shot Classification via Frequency-Aware Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-cross-domain-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most existing methods pay more attention to learning domain-adaptive inductive bias (meta-knowledge) through feature-wise manipulation or task diversity improvement while neglecting the phenomenon that deep networks tend to rely more on high-frequency cues to make the classification decision, which thus degenerates the robustness of learned inductive bias since high-frequency information is vulnerable and easy to be disturbed by noisy information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-cross-domain-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FASTC: A Fast Attentional Framework for Semantic Traversability Classification Using Point Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastc-a-fast-attentional-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Producing traversability maps and understanding the surroundings are crucial prerequisites for autonomous navigation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastc-a-fast-attentional-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShadowLLM: Predictor-based Contextual Sparsity for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadowllm-predictor-based-contextual-sparsity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We developed a novel predictor called ShadowLLM, which can shadow the LLM behavior and enforce better sparsity patterns, resulting in over 15% improvement in end-to-end accuracy without increasing latency compared to previous methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadowllm-predictor-based-contextual-sparsity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of Language Models in the Medical Context Under Resource-Constrained Settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-language-models-in-the-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we selected a subset of these models for thorough evaluation, focusing on classification and text generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-language-models-in-the-medical</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
