<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 09:14:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Versatile Diffusion: Text, Images and Variations All in One Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/versatile-diffusion-text-images-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through our experiments, we demonstrate that VD and its underlying framework have the following merits: a) VD handles all subtasks with competitive quality; b) VD initiates novel extensions and applications such as disentanglement of style and semantic, image-text dual-guided generation, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/versatile-diffusion-text-images-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scene-to-Patch Earth Observation: Multiple Instance Learning for Land Cover Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scene-to-patch-earth-observation-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Land cover classification (LCC), and monitoring how land use changes over time, is an important process in climate change mitigation and adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scene-to-patch-earth-observation-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Cascade RCNN: High Quality Object Detection in Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-cascade-rcnn-high-quality-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress on 2D object detection has featured Cascade RCNN, which capitalizes on a sequence of cascade detectors to progressively improve proposal quality, towards high-quality object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-cascade-rcnn-high-quality-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Bayesian Network Understudy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-bayesian-network-understudy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian Networks may be appealing for clinical decision-making due to their inclusion of causal knowledge, but their practical adoption remains limited as a result of their inability to deal with unstructured data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-bayesian-network-understudy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Faithfulness of Saliency-based Explanations for Deep Learning Models for Temporal Colour Constancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-faithfulness-of-saliency-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The opacity of deep learning models constrains their debugging and improvement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-faithfulness-of-saliency-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Label Quantification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-label-quantification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While many quantification methods have been proposed in the past for binary problems and, to a lesser extent, single-label multiclass problems, the multi-label setting (i. e., the scenario in which the classes of interest are not mutually exclusive) remains by and large unexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-label-quantification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mechanistic Mode Connectivity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mechanistic-mode-connectivity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We define a notion of $\textit{mechanistic similarity}$ and demonstrate that lack of linear connectivity between two minimizers implies the corresponding models use dissimilar mechanisms for making their predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mechanistic-mode-connectivity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Temporal Filtering in Video Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-temporal-filtering-in-video-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pre-determined kernel size severely limits the temporal receptive fields and the fixed weights treat each spatial location across frames equally, resulting in sub-optimal solution for long-range temporal modeling in natural scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-temporal-filtering-in-video-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Factual Consistency of Large Language Models Through Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-factual-consistency-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To generate summaries that are factually inconsistent, we generate summaries from a suite of summarization models that we have manually annotated as factually inconsistent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-factual-consistency-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine learning for interpreting coherent X-ray speckle patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-for-interpreting-coherent-x</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speckle patterns produced by coherent X-ray have a close relationship with the internal structure of materials but quantitative inversion of the relationship to determine structure from images is challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-for-interpreting-coherent-x</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPE-Net: Boosting Point Cloud Analysis via Rotation Robustness Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spe-net-boosting-point-cloud-analysis-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel deep architecture tailored for 3D point cloud applications, named as SPE-Net.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spe-net-boosting-point-cloud-analysis-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Inference of the Lensing Convergence from Photometric Catalogs with Bayesian Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-inference-of-the-lensing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For each test set of 1, 000 sightlines, the BGNN infers the individual $\kappa$ posteriors, which we combine in a hierarchical Bayesian model to yield constraints on the hyperparameters governing the population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-inference-of-the-lensing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Study of Question Answering over Knowledge Bases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In that, we study various question types, properties, languages, and domains to provide insights on where existing systems struggle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmark and Dataset for Post-OCR text correction in Sanskrit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-and-dataset-for-post-ocr-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Keeping this in mind, we release a multi-domain dataset, from areas as diverse as astronomy, medicine and mathematics, with some of them as old as 18 centuries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-and-dataset-for-post-ocr-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CardiacGen: A Hierarchical Deep Generative Model for Cardiac Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cardiacgen-a-hierarchical-deep-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present CardiacGen, a Deep Learning framework for generating synthetic but physiologically plausible cardiac signals like ECG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cardiacgen-a-hierarchical-deep-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPAIR: REnormalizing Permuted Activations for Interpolation Repair</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repair-renormalizing-permuted-activations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we look into the conjecture of Entezari et al.(2021) which states that if the permutation invariance of neural networks is taken into account, then there is likely no loss barrier to the linear interpolation between SGD solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repair-renormalizing-permuted-activations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling interpretable development-specific gene signatures in the developing human prefrontal cortex with ICGS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-interpretable-development-specific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, to unveil interpretable development-specific gene signatures in human PFC, we propose a novel gene selection method, named Interpretable Causality Gene Selection (ICGS), which adopts a Bayesian Network (BN) to represent causality between multiple gene variables and a development variable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-interpretable-development-specific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music Instrument Classification Reprogrammed</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/music-instrument-classification-reprogrammed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of approaches to Music Instrument Classification, a popular task in Music Information Retrieval, is often impacted and limited by the lack of availability of annotated data for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/music-instrument-classification-reprogrammed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Locate-News: Multimodal Focus Location Estimation in News</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-locate-news-multimodal-focus-location</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, a novel dataset called Multimodal Focus Location of News (MM-Locate-News) is introduced.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-locate-news-multimodal-focus-location</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model free Shapley values for high dimensional data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-free-shapley-values-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On a problem from high energy physics we verify that IGCS has nearly the same AUCs as CS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-free-shapley-values-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Phrase-based Sequence-to-Sequence Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-phrase-based-sequence-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe a neural transducer that maintains the flexibility of standard sequence-to-sequence (seq2seq) models while incorporating hierarchical phrases as a source of inductive bias during training and as explicit constraints during inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-phrase-based-sequence-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Inferring User Socioeconomic Status with Mobility Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-inferring-user-socioeconomic-status-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The DeepSEI model incorporates two networks called deep network and recurrent network, which extract the features of the mobility records from three aspects, namely spatiality, temporality and activity, one at a coarse level and the other at a detailed level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-inferring-user-socioeconomic-status-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harmonization Benchmarking Tool for Neuroimaging Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harmonization-benchmarking-tool-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A major data pre-processing step for large, multi-site studies is to handle site effects by harmonizing data, generating a dataset that enables more powerful analyses and more robust algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harmonization-benchmarking-tool-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characterizing the Spectrum of the NTK via a Power Series Expansion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-the-spectrum-of-the-ntk-via-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe faster decay of the Hermite coefficients leads to faster decay in the NTK coefficients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-the-spectrum-of-the-ntk-via-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Deep Metric Learning for Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-deep-metric-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose to learn a global probabilistic distribution for each pixel in the patch and a probabilistic metric to model the distance between distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-deep-metric-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galactica: A Large Language Model for Science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galactica-a-large-language-model-for-science</link>
      <description><![CDATA[And despite not being trained on a general corpus, Galactica outperforms BLOOM and OPT-175B on BIG-bench.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galactica-a-large-language-model-for-science</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Evaluation of Excavator Operators using Learned Reward Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-evaluation-of-excavator-operators</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training novice users to operate an excavator for learning different skills requires the presence of expert teachers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-evaluation-of-excavator-operators</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring cell-specific lncRNA regulation with single-cell RNA-sequencing data in the developing human neocortex</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-cell-specific-lncrna-regulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, to analyze lncRNA regulation regarding individual cells, we focus on single-cell RNA-sequencing (scRNA-seq) data instead of bulk data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-cell-specific-lncrna-regulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly Detection in Multiplex Dynamic Networks: from Blockchain Security to Brain Disease Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomaly-detection-in-multiplex-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The problem of identifying anomalies in dynamic networks is a fundamental task with a wide range of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomaly-detection-in-multiplex-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual and Multimodal Topic Modelling with Pretrained Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-and-multimodal-topic-modelling-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents M3L-Contrast -- a novel multimodal multilingual (M3L) neural topic model for comparable data that maps texts from multiple languages and images into a shared topic space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-and-multimodal-topic-modelling-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show Me the Instruments: Musical Instrument Retrieval from Mixture Audio</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-me-the-instruments-musical-instrument</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Single-Instrument Encoder is trained to classify the instruments used in single-track audio, and we take its penultimate layer's activation as the instrument embedding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-me-the-instruments-musical-instrument</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards an objective characterization of an individual's facial movements using Self-Supervised Person-Specific-Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-objective-characterization-of-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose self-supervised Person-Specific Models (PSMs), in which one model per individual can learn to extract an embedding of the facial movements independently of the person's identity and other structural facial characteristics from unlabeled facial video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-objective-characterization-of-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Face Recognition using Unlabeled Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-face-recognition-using-unlabeled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an unsupervised face recognition model based on unlabeled synthetic data (USynthFace).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-face-recognition-using-unlabeled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Evaluation in Medical Datasets Over Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-evaluation-in-medical-datasets-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning models deployed in healthcare systems face data drawn from continually evolving environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-evaluation-in-medical-datasets-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Reconstruction and Differential Testing of Excised mRNA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-reconstruction-and-differential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that BREM achieves higher F1 score for reconstruction tasks and improved accuracy and sensitivity in differential splicing when compared with four state-of-the-art transcript and local splicing methods on simulated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-reconstruction-and-differential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal patterns in insulin needs for Type 1 diabetes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-patterns-in-insulin-needs-for-type-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Type 1 Diabetes (T1D) is a chronic condition where the body produces little or no insulin, a hormone required for the cells to use blood glucose (BG) for energy and to regulate BG levels in the body.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-patterns-in-insulin-needs-for-type-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaKRec: Collaborative Meta-Knowledge Enhanced Recommender System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metakrec-collaborative-meta-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill this gap, in this paper, we explore the rich, heterogeneous relationship among items and propose a new KG-enhanced recommendation model called Collaborative Meta-Knowledge Enhanced Recommender System (MetaKRec).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metakrec-collaborative-meta-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal EHR Federated Learning Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-ehr-federated-learning-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) is the most practical multi-source learning method for electronic healthcare records (EHR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-ehr-federated-learning-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedleyVox: An Evaluation Dataset for Multiple Singing Voices Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medleyvox-an-evaluation-dataset-for-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an evaluation dataset and provide baseline studies for multiple singing voices separation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medleyvox-an-evaluation-dataset-for-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeded iterative clustering for histology region identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seeded-iterative-clustering-for-histology</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Annotations are necessary to develop computer vision algorithms for histopathology, but dense annotations at a high resolution are often time-consuming to make.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seeded-iterative-clustering-for-histology</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CST5: Data Augmentation for Code-Switched Semantic Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cst5-data-augmentation-for-code-switched-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To aid further research in this area, we are also releasing (a) Hinglish-TOP, the largest human annotated code-switched semantic parsing dataset to date, containing 10k human annotated Hindi-English (Hinglish) code-switched utterances, and (b) Over 170K CST5 generated code-switched utterances from the TOPv2 dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cst5-data-augmentation-for-code-switched-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redeeming Intrinsic Rewards via Constrained Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redeeming-intrinsic-rewards-via-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such methods can lead to excellent results on hard exploration tasks but can suffer from intrinsic reward bias and underperform when compared to an agent trained using only task rewards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redeeming-intrinsic-rewards-via-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talent Recommendation on LinkedIn User Profiles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/talent-recommendation-on-linkedin-user</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increasing amount of information on the Internet, recommender systems are becoming increasingly crucial in supporting people to find and explore relevant content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/talent-recommendation-on-linkedin-user</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MT4SSL: Boosting Self-Supervised Speech Representation Learning by Integrating Multiple Targets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mt4ssl-boosting-self-supervised-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide a new perspective on self-supervised speech models from how the self-training targets are obtained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mt4ssl-boosting-self-supervised-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dealing with missing data using attention and latent space regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dealing-with-missing-data-using-attention-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most practical data science problems encounter missing data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dealing-with-missing-data-using-attention-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Follow the Clairvoyant: an Imitation Learning Approach to Optimal Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/follow-the-clairvoyant-an-imitation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider control of dynamical systems through the lens of competitive analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/follow-the-clairvoyant-an-imitation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Images are More Memorable to Machines?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-images-are-more-memorable-to-machines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the problem of measuring and predicting how memorable an image is to pattern recognition machines, as a path to explore machine intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-images-are-more-memorable-to-machines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CabViT: Cross Attention among Blocks for Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cabvit-cross-attention-among-blocks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed CabViT enhances the interactions of tokens across blocks with potentially different semantics, and encourages more information flows to the lower levels, which together improves model performance and model convergence with limited extra cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cabvit-cross-attention-among-blocks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaptKeyBERT: An Attention-Based approach towards Few-Shot \&amp; Zero-Shot Domain Adaptation of KeyBERT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptkeybert-an-attention-based-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Downstream training for keyword extractors is a lengthy process and requires a significant amount of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptkeybert-an-attention-based-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Autoregressive Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-autoregressive-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we demonstrate that a major limitation of regression using a mean-squared error loss is its sensitivity to the scale of its targets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-autoregressive-regression</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
