<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 21:08:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>BAD: Bidirectional Auto-regressive Diffusion for Text-to-Motion Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bad-bidirectional-auto-regressive-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoregressive models excel in modeling sequential dependencies by enforcing causal constraints, yet they struggle to capture complex bidirectional patterns due to their unidirectional nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bad-bidirectional-auto-regressive-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SkinMamba: A Precision Skin Lesion Segmentation Architecture with Cross-Scale Global State Modeling and Frequency Boundary Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skinmamba-a-precision-skin-lesion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Skin lesion segmentation is a crucial method for identifying early skin cancer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skinmamba-a-precision-skin-lesion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promptriever: Instruction-Trained Retrievers Can Be Prompted Like Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptriever-instruction-trained-retrievers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instruction-tuned language models (LM) are able to respond to imperative commands, providing a more natural user interface compared to their base counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptriever-instruction-trained-retrievers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ULOC: Learning to Localize in Complex Large-Scale Environments with Ultra-Wideband Ranges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uloc-learning-to-localize-in-complex-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While UWB-based methods can achieve high localization accuracy in small-scale areas, their accuracy and reliability are significantly challenged in large-scale environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uloc-learning-to-localize-in-complex-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Down-Sampling Inter-Layer Adapter for Parameter and Computation Efficient Ultra-Fine-Grained Image Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/down-sampling-inter-layer-adapter-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ultra-fine-grained image recognition (UFGIR) categorizes objects with extremely small differences between classes, such as distinguishing between cultivars within the same species, as opposed to species-level classification in fine-grained image recognition (FGIR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/down-sampling-inter-layer-adapter-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynthSOD: Developing an Heterogeneous Dataset for Orchestra Music Source Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthsod-developing-an-heterogeneous-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in music source separation have significantly progressed, particularly in isolating vocals, drums, and bass elements from mixed tracks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthsod-developing-an-heterogeneous-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoMath: A Mathematical Reasoning Benchmark in Romanian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/romath-a-mathematical-reasoning-benchmark-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mathematics has long been conveyed through natural language, primarily for human understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/romath-a-mathematical-reasoning-benchmark-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOAP: Improving and Stabilizing Shampoo using Adam</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soap-improving-and-stabilizing-shampoo-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, since SOAP is equivalent to running Adam in a rotated space, it introduces only one additional hyperparameter (the preconditioning frequency) compared to Adam.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soap-improving-and-stabilizing-shampoo-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PReLU: Yet Another Single-Layer Solution to the XOR Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prelu-yet-another-single-layer-solution-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper demonstrates that a single-layer neural network using Parametric Rectified Linear Unit (PReLU) activation can solve the XOR problem, a simple fact that has been overlooked so far.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prelu-yet-another-single-layer-solution-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORE-Bench: Fostering the Credibility of Published Research Through a Computational Reproducibility Agent Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/core-bench-fostering-the-credibility-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces such a benchmark, designed to measure the accuracy of AI agents in tackling a crucial yet surprisingly challenging aspect of scientific research: computational reproducibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/core-bench-fostering-the-credibility-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring and Enhancing Trustworthiness of LLMs in RAG through Grounded Attributions and Learning to Refuse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-and-enhancing-trustworthiness-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While many studies focus on evaluating the quality of end-to-end RAG systems, there is a lack of research on understanding the appropriateness of an LLM for the RAG task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-and-enhancing-trustworthiness-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning Graph Enhanced Exemplars Retrieval for In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-graph-enhanced-exemplars-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models(LLMs) have exhibited remarkable few-shot learning capabilities and unified the paradigm of NLP tasks through the in-context learning(ICL) technique.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-graph-enhanced-exemplars-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KALE: An Artwork Image Captioning System Augmented with Heterogeneous Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kale-an-artwork-image-captioning-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Exploring the narratives conveyed by fine-art paintings is a challenge in image captioning, where the goal is to generate descriptions that not only precisely represent the visual content but also offer a in-depth interpretation of the artwork's meaning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kale-an-artwork-image-captioning-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relative Representations: Topological and Geometric Perspectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relative-representations-topological-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on insights of topological and geometric nature, we propose two improvements to relative representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relative-representations-topological-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versatile Incremental Learning: Towards Class and Domain-Agnostic Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/versatile-incremental-learning-towards-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we consider a more challenging and realistic but under-explored IL scenario, named Versatile Incremental Learning (VIL), in which a model has no prior of which of the classes or domains will increase in the next task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/versatile-incremental-learning-towards-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Propulsion: Steering LLM with Tiny Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/propulsion-steering-llm-with-tiny-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancements in Large Language Models (LLMs) have revolutionized natural language processing (NLP) and related fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/propulsion-steering-llm-with-tiny-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Analysis of the OpenAI O1-Preview Model in Solving Random K-SAT Problem: Does the LLM Solve the Problem Itself or Call an External SAT Solver?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-analysis-of-the-openai-o1-preview-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this manuscript I present an analysis on the performance of OpenAI O1-preview model in solving random K-SAT instances for K$\in {2, 3, 4}$ as a function of $\alpha=M/N$ where $M$ is the number of clauses and $N$ is the number of variables of the satisfiable problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-analysis-of-the-openai-o1-preview-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sample Complexity Bounds for Linear System Identification from a Finite Set</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-complexity-bounds-for-linear-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper considers a finite sample perspective on the problem of identifying an LTI system from a finite set of possible systems using trajectory data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-complexity-bounds-for-linear-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAST: Cross-modal Alignment Similarity Test for Vision Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cast-cross-modal-alignment-similarity-test</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Good VQA performance is taken as evidence that the model will perform well on a broader range of tasks that require both visual and language inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cast-cross-modal-alignment-similarity-test</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM2Latent: Text-to-facial image generation and editing in GANs with multimodal assistance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm2latent-text-to-facial-image-generation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a practical framework - MM2Latent - for multimodal image generation and editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm2latent-text-to-facial-image-generation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spontaneous Informal Speech Dataset for Punctuation Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spontaneous-informal-speech-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Presently, punctuation restoration models are evaluated almost solely on well-structured, scripted corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spontaneous-informal-speech-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrasformer: A Brain Network Contrastive Transformer for Neurodegenerative Condition Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrasformer-a-brain-network-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It generates a prior-knowledge-enhanced contrast graph to address the distribution shifts across sub-populations by a two-stream attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrasformer-a-brain-network-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultrasound Image Enhancement with the Variance of Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultrasound-image-enhancement-with-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel approach that integrates adaptive beamforming with denoising diffusion-based variance imaging to address this challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultrasound-image-enhancement-with-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Graph Reordering Speed Up Graph Neural Network Training? An Experimental Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-graph-reordering-speed-up-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that graph reordering is effective in reducing training time for CPU- and GPU-based training, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-graph-reordering-speed-up-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sounds of Home: A Speech-Removed Residential Audio Dataset for Sound Event Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-sounds-of-home-a-speech-removed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a residential audio dataset to support sound event detection research for smart home applications aimed at promoting wellbeing for older adults.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-sounds-of-home-a-speech-removed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSDNet: Multi-Scale Decoder for Few-Shot Semantic Segmentation via Transformer-Guided Prototyping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msdnet-multi-scale-decoder-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach introduces the spatial transformer decoder and the contextual mask generation module to improve the relational understanding between support and query images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msdnet-multi-scale-decoder-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control-flow Reconstruction Attacks on Business Process Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/control-flow-reconstruction-attacks-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Process models may be automatically generated from event logs that contain as-is data of a business process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/control-flow-reconstruction-attacks-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reactive Environments for Active Inference Agents with RxEnvironments.jl</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reactive-environments-for-active-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Active Inference is a framework that emphasizes the interaction between agents and their environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reactive-environments-for-active-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Fields for Adaptive Photoacoustic Computed Tomography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-fields-for-adaptive-photoacoustic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Photoacoustic computed tomography (PACT) is a non-invasive imaging modality with wide medical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-fields-for-adaptive-photoacoustic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LC-Protonets: Multi-label Few-shot learning for world music audio tagging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lc-protonets-multi-label-few-shot-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Label-Combination Prototypical Networks (LC-Protonets) to address the problem of multi-label few-shot classification, where a model must generalize to new classes based on only a few available examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lc-protonets-multi-label-few-shot-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient-free Post-hoc Explainability Using Distillation Aided Learnable Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-free-post-hoc-explainability-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a framework, named distillation aided explainability (DAX), that attempts to generate a saliency-based explanation in a model agnostic gradient free application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-free-post-hoc-explainability-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OmniGen: Unified Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnigen-unified-image-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce OmniGen, a new diffusion model for unified image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnigen-unified-image-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lite-FBCN: Lightweight Fast Bilinear Convolutional Network for Brain Disease Classification from MRI Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lite-fbcn-lightweight-fast-bilinear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Achieving high accuracy with computational efficiency in brain disease classification from Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI) scans is challenging, particularly when both coarse and fine-grained distinctions are crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lite-fbcn-lightweight-fast-bilinear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STCMOT: Spatio-Temporal Cohesion Learning for UAV-Based Multiple Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stcmot-spatio-temporal-cohesion-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiple object tracking (MOT) in Unmanned Aerial Vehicle (UAV) videos is important for diverse applications in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stcmot-spatio-temporal-cohesion-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal As a Plugin: Unsupervised Video Denoising with Pre-Trained Image Denoisers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-as-a-plugin-unsupervised-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in deep learning have shown impressive results in image and video denoising, leveraging extensive pairs of noisy and noise-free data for supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-as-a-plugin-unsupervised-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Physics Informed Neural Network (PINN) Methodology for Coupled Moving Boundary PDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-physics-informed-neural-network-pinn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Physics-Informed Neural Network (PINN) is a novel multi-task learning framework useful for solving physical problems modeled using differential equations (DEs) by integrating the knowledge of physics and known constraints into the components of deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-physics-informed-neural-network-pinn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can GPT-O1 Kill All Bugs? An Evaluation of GPT-Family LLMs on QuixBugs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-gpt-o1-kill-all-bugs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLMs have long demonstrated remarkable effectiveness in automatic program repair (APR), with OpenAI's ChatGPT being one of the most widely used models in this domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-gpt-o1-kill-all-bugs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SelECT-SQL: Self-correcting ensemble Chain-of-Thought for Text-to-SQL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/select-sql-self-correcting-ensemble-chain-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, Text-to-SQL, the problem of automatically converting questions posed in natural language to formal SQL queries, has emerged as an important problem at the intersection of natural language processing and data management research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/select-sql-self-correcting-ensemble-chain-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Multi-candidate Speculative Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-multi-candidate-speculative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speculative Decoding (SD) is a technique to accelerate the inference of Large Language Models (LLMs) by using a lower complexity draft model to propose candidate tokens verified by a larger target model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-multi-candidate-speculative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoPET Challenge III: Testing the Robustness of Generalized Dice Focal Loss trained 3D Residual UNet for FDG and PSMA Lesion Segmentation from Whole-Body PET/CT Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopet-challenge-iii-testing-the-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, creating an effective segmentation model for routine PET/CT image analysis is challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopet-challenge-iii-testing-the-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Diagram of Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-diagram-of-thought</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Diagram of Thought (DoT), a framework that models iterative reasoning in large language models (LLMs) as the construction of a directed acyclic graph (DAG) within a single model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-diagram-of-thought</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical and Asymptotically Optimal Quantization of High-Dimensional Vectors in Euclidean Space for Approximate Nearest Neighbor Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-and-asymptotically-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a new quantization method to address this limitation by extending RaBitQ.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-and-asymptotically-optimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RetrievalAttention: Accelerating Long-Context LLM Inference via Vector Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrievalattention-accelerating-long-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the quadratic time complexity of attention operation poses a significant challenge for scaling to longer contexts due to the extremely high inference latency and GPU memory consumption for caching key-value (KV) vectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrievalattention-accelerating-long-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AceParse: A Comprehensive Dataset with Diverse Structured Texts for Academic Literature Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aceparse-a-comprehensive-dataset-with-diverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the development of data-centric AI, the focus has shifted from model-driven approaches to improving data quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aceparse-a-comprehensive-dataset-with-diverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Measures of Anticipation and Responsivity in Online Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-measures-of-anticipation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a generalization of classic information-theoretic measures of predictive uncertainty in online language processing, based on the simulation of expected continuations of incremental linguistic contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-measures-of-anticipation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2S-ODIS: Two-Stage Omni-Directional Image Synthesis by Geometric Distortion Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2s-odis-two-stage-omni-directional-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, two-stage structure was adopted to first create a global coarse image in ERP and then refine the image by integrating multiple local NFoV images in the higher resolution to compensate the distortions in ERP, both of which are based on the pre-trained VQGAN model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2s-odis-two-stage-omni-directional-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kolmogorov-Arnold Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kolmogorov-arnold-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce the Kolmogorov-Arnold Transformer (KAT), a novel architecture that replaces MLP layers with Kolmogorov-Arnold Network (KAN) layers to enhance the expressiveness and performance of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kolmogorov-arnold-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Centric Strategies for Overcoming PET/CT Heterogeneity: Insights from the AutoPET III Lesion Segmentation Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-centric-strategies-for-overcoming-pet-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The third autoPET challenge introduced a new data-centric task this year, shifting the focus from model development to improving metastatic lesion segmentation on PET/CT images through data quality and handling strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-centric-strategies-for-overcoming-pet-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WaveMixSR-V2: Enhancing Super-resolution with Higher Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavemixsr-v2-enhancing-super-resolution-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in single image super-resolution have been predominantly driven by token mixers and transformer architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavemixsr-v2-enhancing-super-resolution-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trustworthiness in Retrieval-Augmented Generation Systems: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trustworthiness-in-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) has quickly grown into a pivotal paradigm in the development of Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trustworthiness-in-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
