<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 09:11:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ReCoMIF: Reading comprehension based multi-source information fusion network for Chinese spoken language understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recomif-reading-comprehension-based-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It usually includes slot filling and intent detection (SFID) tasks aiming at semantic parsing of utterances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recomif-reading-comprehension-based-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Synthesis under Limited Data: A Survey and Taxonomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-synthesis-under-limited-data-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite numerous efforts to enhance training stability and synthesis quality in the limited data scenarios, there is a lack of a systematic survey that provides 1) a clear problem definition, critical challenges, and taxonomy of various tasks; 2) an in-depth analysis on the pros, cons, and remain limitations of existing literature; as well as 3) a thorough discussion on the potential applications and future directions in the field of image synthesis under limited data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-synthesis-under-limited-data-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Super-Resolution Head for Human Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-super-resolution-head-for-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first propose the SR head, which predicts heatmaps with a spatial resolution higher than the input feature maps (or even consistent with the input image) by super-resolution, to effectively reduce the quantization error and the dependence on further post-processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-super-resolution-head-for-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Structure from Point Clouds: Geometric Attention is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-structure-from-point-clouds-geometric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The use of graph neural networks has produced significant advances in point cloud problems, such as those found in high energy physics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-structure-from-point-clouds-geometric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting the Parameter Efficiency of Adapters from the Perspective of Precision Redundancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-parameter-efficiency-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current state-of-the-art results in computer vision depend in part on fine-tuning large pre-trained vision models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-parameter-efficiency-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Learning for API Aspect Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-for-api-aspect-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For impact analysis, we performed empirical and developer study.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-for-api-aspect-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformal PID Control for Time Series Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-pid-control-for-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of uncertainty quantification for time series prediction, with the goal of providing easy-to-use algorithms with formal guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-pid-control-for-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camoscio: an Italian Instruction-tuned LLaMA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camoscio-an-italian-instruction-tuned-llama</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years Large Language Models (LLMs) have increased the state of the art on several natural language processing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camoscio-an-italian-instruction-tuned-llama</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Sentence Embeddings with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-sentence-embeddings-with-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also fine-tune LLMs with current contrastive learning approach, and the 2. 7B OPT model, incorporating our prompt-based method, surpasses the performance of 4. 8B ST5, achieving the new state-of-the-art results on STS tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-sentence-embeddings-with-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAGRID: A Human-LLM Collaborative Dataset for Generative Information-Seeking with Attribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hagrid-a-human-llm-collaborative-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a new dataset, HAGRID (Human-in-the-loop Attributable Generative Retrieval for Information-seeking Dataset) for building end-to-end generative information-seeking models that are capable of retrieving candidate quotes and generating attributed explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hagrid-a-human-llm-collaborative-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDG-Net: Discriminability-Driven Graph Network for Weakly-supervised Temporal Action Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddg-net-discriminability-driven-graph-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering this phenomenon, we propose Discriminability-Driven Graph Network (DDG-Net), which explicitly models ambiguous snippets and discriminative snippets with well-designed connections, preventing the transmission of ambiguous information and enhancing the discriminability of snippet-level representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddg-net-discriminability-driven-graph-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does fine-tuning GPT-3 with the OpenAI API leak personally-identifiable information?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-fine-tuning-gpt-3-with-the-openai-api</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we simulate a privacy attack on GPT-3 using OpenAI's fine-tuning API.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-fine-tuning-gpt-3-with-the-openai-api</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal-learn: Causal Discovery in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-learn-causal-discovery-in-python</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal discovery aims at revealing causal relations from observational data, which is a fundamental task in science and engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-learn-causal-discovery-in-python</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Out-of-distribution Objects Using Neuron Activation Patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-out-of-distribution-objects-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object detection is essential to many perception algorithms used in modern robotics applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-out-of-distribution-objects-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmark for Understanding Dialogue Safety in Mental Health Support</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-understanding-dialogue-safety</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study reveals that ChatGPT struggles to detect safety categories with detailed safety definitions in a zero- and few-shot paradigm, whereas the fine-tuned model proves to be more suitable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-understanding-dialogue-safety</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Adaptation for Medical Image Segmentation using Transformation-Invariant Self-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptation-for-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the unreliability of pseudo labels can hinder the capability of self-training techniques to induce abstract representation from the unlabeled target dataset, especially in the case of large distribution gaps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptation-for-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffProsody: Diffusion-based Latent Prosody Generation for Expressive Speech Synthesis with Prosody Conditional Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffprosody-diffusion-based-latent-prosody</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Expressive text-to-speech systems have undergone significant advancements owing to prosody modeling, but conventional methods can still be improved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffprosody-diffusion-based-latent-prosody</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classifying multilingual party manifestos: Domain transfer across country, time, and genre</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classifying-multilingual-party-manifestos</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore the potential of domain transfer across geographical locations, languages, time, and genre in a large-scale database of political manifestos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classifying-multilingual-party-manifestos</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Dynamic Range Image Reconstruction via Deep Explicit Polynomial Curve Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dynamic-range-image-reconstruction-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, since all current datasets do not provide the corresponding relationship between the tone mapping function and the LDR image, we construct a new dataset with both synthetic and real images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dynamic-range-image-reconstruction-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transferable Attack for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferable-attack-for-semantic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation models are known vulnerable to small input perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferable-attack-for-semantic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VacancySBERT: the approach for representation of titles and skills for semantic similarity search in the recruitment domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vacancysbert-the-approach-for-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article semantic similarity search to find candidates for title normalization has been used.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vacancysbert-the-approach-for-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ToolLLM: Facilitating Large Language Models to Master 16000+ Real-world APIs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toolllm-facilitating-large-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first present ToolBench, an instruction-tuning dataset for tool use, which is created automatically using ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toolllm-facilitating-large-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniVTG: Towards Unified Video-Language Temporal Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/univtg-towards-unified-video-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most methods in this direction develop taskspecific models that are trained with type-specific labels, such as moment retrieval (time interval) and highlight detection (worthiness curve), which limits their abilities to generalize to various VTG tasks and labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/univtg-towards-unified-video-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking and Analyzing Robust Point Cloud Recognition: Bag of Tricks for Defending Adversarial Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-and-analyzing-robust-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we first establish a comprehensive, and rigorous point cloud adversarial robustness benchmark to evaluate adversarial robustness, which can provide a detailed understanding of the effects of the defense and attack methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-and-analyzing-robust-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOTR: 3D Joint Contrastive Learning with Transformers for Occluded Human Mesh Recovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jotr-3d-joint-contrastive-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method includes an encoder-decoder transformer architecture to fuse 2D and 3D representations for achieving 2D$\&$3D aligned results in a coarse-to-fine manner and a novel 3D joint contrastive learning approach for adding explicitly global supervision for the 3D feature space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jotr-3d-joint-contrastive-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Collaborative Perception from the Spatial-Temporal Importance of Semantic Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-collaborative-perception-from-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing collaborative perception methods tend to focus solely on the spatial features of semantic information, while neglecting the importance of the temporal dimension in collaborator selection and semantic information fusion, which instigates performance degradation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-collaborative-perception-from-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Random Sub-Samples Generation for Self-Supervised Real Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-sub-samples-generation-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With sufficient paired training samples, the supervised deep learning methods have attracted much attention in image denoising because of their superior performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-sub-samples-generation-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Value-Informed Skill Chaining for Policy Learning of Long-Horizon Tasks with Surgical Robot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/value-informed-skill-chaining-for-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this value function, a chaining policy is learned to instruct subtask policies to terminate at the state with the highest value so that all subsequent policies are more likely to be connected for accomplishing the task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/value-informed-skill-chaining-for-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BearingPGA-Net: A Lightweight and Deployable Bearing Fault Diagnosis Network via Decoupled Knowledge Distillation and FPGA Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bearingpga-net-a-lightweight-and-deployable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this is the first instance of deploying a CNN-based bearing fault diagnosis model on an FPGA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bearingpga-net-a-lightweight-and-deployable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RCS-YOLO: A Fast and High-Accuracy Object Detector for Brain Tumor Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rcs-yolo-a-fast-and-high-accuracy-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With an excellent balance between speed and accuracy, cutting-edge YOLO frameworks have become one of the most efficient algorithms for object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rcs-yolo-a-fast-and-high-accuracy-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subspace Distillation for Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subspace-distillation-for-continual-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate forgetting prior knowledge, we propose a novel knowledge distillation technique that takes into the account the manifold structure of the latent/output space of a neural network in learning novel tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subspace-distillation-for-continual-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L3DMC: Lifelong Learning using Distillation via Mixed-Curvature Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l3dmc-lifelong-learning-using-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the problem, we propose a distillation strategy named L3DMC that operates on mixed-curvature spaces to preserve the already-learned knowledge by modeling and maintaining complex geometrical structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l3dmc-lifelong-learning-using-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Decomposition Networks for Bias Field Correction in MR Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-decomposition-networks-for-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many retrospective algorithms were developed to facilitate the bias correction, to which the deep learning-based methods outperformed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-decomposition-networks-for-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StarSRGAN: Improving Real-World Blind Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/starsrgan-improving-real-world-blind-super-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The aim of blind super-resolution (SR) in computer vision is to improve the resolution of an image without prior knowledge of the degradation process that caused the image to be low-resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/starsrgan-improving-real-world-blind-super-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure-Preserving Synthesis: MaskGAN for Unpaired MR-CT Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-preserving-synthesis-maskgan-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate that MaskGAN outperforms state-of-the-art synthesis methods on a challenging pediatric dataset, where MR and CT scans are heavily misaligned due to rapid growth in children.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-preserving-synthesis-maskgan-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmented Math: Authoring AR-Based Explorable Explanations by Augmenting Static Math Textbooks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmented-math-authoring-ar-based-explorable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This empowers non-technical users, such as teachers or students, to transform existing math textbooks and handouts into on-demand and personalized explorable explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmented-math-authoring-ar-based-explorable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do LLMs Possess a Personality? Making the MBTI Test an Amazing Evaluation for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-llms-possess-a-personality-making-the-mbti</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of large language models (LLMs) has made significant progress, and their knowledge storage capacity is approaching that of human beings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-llms-possess-a-personality-making-the-mbti</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting delays in Indian lower courts using AutoML and Decision Forests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-delays-in-indian-lower-courts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a classification model that predicts delays in Indian lower courts based on case information available at filing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-delays-in-indian-lower-courts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Knowledge-enhanced Two-stage Generative Framework for Medical Dialogue Information Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-knowledge-enhanced-two-stage-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these generative methods output a whole sequence consisting of term-status pairs in one stage and ignore integrating prior knowledge, which demands a deeper understanding to model the relationship between terms and infer the status of each term.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-knowledge-enhanced-two-stage-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mesh Density Adaptation for Template-based Shape Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesh-density-adaptation-for-template-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In 3D shape reconstruction based on template mesh deformation, a regularization, such as smoothness energy, is employed to guide the reconstruction into a desirable direction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesh-density-adaptation-for-template-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Uncertainly Missing and Ambiguous Visual Modality in Multi-Modal Entity Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-uncertainly-missing-and-ambiguous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a crucial extension of entity alignment (EA), multi-modal entity alignment (MMEA) aims to identify identical entities across disparate knowledge graphs (KGs) by exploiting associated visual information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-uncertainly-missing-and-ambiguous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEED-Bench: Benchmarking Multimodal LLMs with Generative Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seed-bench-benchmarking-multimodal-llms-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on powerful Large Language Models (LLMs), recent generative Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) have gained prominence as a pivotal research area, exhibiting remarkable capability for both comprehension and generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seed-bench-benchmarking-multimodal-llms-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Neural Representation in Medical Imaging: A Comparative Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-neural-representation-in-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizing the potential of INRs beyond these domains, this survey aims to provide a comprehensive overview of INR models in the field of medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-neural-representation-in-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthesizing Event-centric Knowledge Graphs of Daily Activities Using Virtual Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesizing-event-centric-knowledge-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) is expected to be embodied in software agents, robots, and cyber-physical systems that can understand the various contextual information of daily life in the home environment to support human behavior and decision making in various situations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesizing-event-centric-knowledge-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Model for Image, Video, Audio and Language Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-model-for-image-video-audio-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model is efficiently pretrained on many tasks, based on task balancing and multimodal curriculum learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-model-for-image-video-audio-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoseNNa: A performant, portable library for neural network inference with application to computational fluid dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rosenna-a-performant-portable-library-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RoseNNa is a non-invasive, lightweight (1000 lines), and performant tool for neural network inference, with focus on the smaller networks used to augment PDE solvers, like those of CFD, which are typically written in C/C++ or Fortran.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rosenna-a-performant-portable-library-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning with State Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-multi-agent-reinforcement-learning-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then we propose a robust multi-agent Q-learning (RMAQ) algorithm to find such an equilibrium, with convergence guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-multi-agent-reinforcement-learning-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving TTS for Shanghainese: Addressing Tone Sandhi via Word Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-tts-for-shanghainese-addressing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tone is a crucial component of the prosody of Shanghainese, a Wu Chinese variety spoken primarily in urban Shanghai.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-tts-for-shanghainese-addressing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Unrolling Networks with Recurrent Momentum Acceleration for Nonlinear Inverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-unrolling-networks-with-recurrent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide experimental results on two nonlinear inverse problems: a nonlinear deconvolution problem, and an electrical impedance tomography problem with limited boundary measurements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-unrolling-networks-with-recurrent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variance Control for Distributional Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variance-control-for-distributional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although distributional reinforcement learning (DRL) has been widely examined in the past few years, very few studies investigate the validity of the obtained Q-function estimator in the distributional setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variance-control-for-distributional</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
