<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 21:06:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>${\rm E}(3)$-Equivariant Actor-Critic Methods for Cooperative Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rm-e-3-equivariant-actor-critic-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identification and analysis of symmetrical patterns in the natural world have led to significant discoveries across various scientific fields, such as the formulation of gravitational laws in physics and advancements in the study of chemical structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rm-e-3-equivariant-actor-critic-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Prediction of Audio Event and Annoyance Rating in an Urban Soundscape by Hierarchical Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-prediction-of-audio-event-and-annoyance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sound events in daily life carry rich information about the objective world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-prediction-of-audio-event-and-annoyance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OFVL-MS: Once for Visual Localization across Multiple Indoor Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ofvl-ms-once-for-visual-localization-across</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we seek to predict camera poses across scenes with a multi-task learning manner, where we view the localization of each scene as a new task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ofvl-ms-once-for-visual-localization-across</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Challenges of Machine Learning for Trust and Safety: A Case Study on Misinformation Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-challenges-of-machine-learning-for-trust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We systematize literature on automated detection of misinformation across a corpus of 270 well-cited papers in the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-challenges-of-machine-learning-for-trust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverse Policies Converge in Reward-free Markov Decision Processe</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-policies-converge-in-reward-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under such a framework, we also propose a provably efficient diversity reinforcement learning algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-policies-converge-in-reward-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A multiobjective continuation method to compute the regularization path of deep neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multiobjective-continuation-method-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparsity is a highly desired feature in deep neural networks (DNNs) since it ensures numerical efficiency, improves the interpretability of models (due to the smaller number of relevant features), and robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multiobjective-continuation-method-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating the Wikidata Taxonomy into YAGO</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-the-wikidata-taxonomy-into-yago</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wikidata is one of the largest public general-purpose Knowledge Bases (KBs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-the-wikidata-taxonomy-into-yago</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LFS-GAN: Lifelong Few-Shot Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lfs-gan-lifelong-few-shot-image-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Surprisingly, we find that our LFS-GAN even outperforms the existing few-shot GANs in the few-shot image generation task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lfs-gan-lifelong-few-shot-image-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIPN for Zero-Shot OOD Detection: Teaching CLIP to Say No</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clipn-for-zero-shot-ood-detection-teaching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, we introduce two loss functions: the image-text binary-opposite loss and the text semantic-opposite loss, which we use to teach CLIPN to associate images with "no" prompts, thereby enabling it to identify unknown samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clipn-for-zero-shot-ood-detection-teaching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Privacy-Supporting Fall Detection via Deep Unsupervised RGB2Depth Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-privacy-supporting-fall-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a privacy-supporting solution that makes the RGB-trained model applicable in depth domain and utilizes depth data at test time for fall detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-privacy-supporting-fall-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Bottleneck Transformer for Event Image-Voxel Feature Fusion based Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-bottleneck-transformer-for-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, a bottleneck Transformer is introduced to facilitate the fusion of the dual-stream information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-bottleneck-transformer-for-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Value of Assistance for Mobile Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/value-of-assistance-for-mobile-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In some settings, it may be possible to perform assistive actions that reduce uncertainty about a robot's location.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/value-of-assistance-for-mobile-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IncreLoRA: Incremental Parameter Allocation Method for Parameter-Efficient Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/increlora-incremental-parameter-allocation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach is different from the pruning method as it is not limited by the initial number of training parameters, and each parameter matrix has a higher rank upper bound for the same training overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/increlora-incremental-parameter-allocation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SILT: Shadow-aware Iterative Label Tuning for Learning to Detect Shadows from Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/silt-shadow-aware-iterative-label-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing shadow detection datasets often contain missing or mislabeled shadows, which can hinder the performance of deep learning models trained directly on such data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/silt-shadow-aware-iterative-label-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion-to-Matching: A Mixed Paradigm for 3D Single Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-to-matching-a-mixed-paradigm-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D single object tracking with LiDAR points is an important task in the computer vision field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-to-matching-a-mixed-paradigm-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>System Identification Using the Signed Cumulative Distribution Transform In Structural Health Monitoring Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/system-identification-using-the-signed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel, data-driven approach to identifying partial differential equation (PDE) parameters of a dynamical system in structural health monitoring applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/system-identification-using-the-signed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPPNet: A Single-Point Prompt Network for Nuclei Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sppnet-a-single-point-prompt-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to the segment anything model, SPPNet shows roughly 20 times faster inference, with 1/70 parameters and computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sppnet-a-single-point-prompt-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Multilingual Models Pivot Zero-Shot Multimodal Learning across Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-multilingual-models-pivot-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building a competitive counterpart in other languages is highly challenging due to the low-resource nature of non-English multimodal data (i. e., lack of large-scale, high-quality image-text data).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-multilingual-models-pivot-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt2Model: Generating Deployable Models from Natural Language Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt2model-generating-deployable-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Prompt2Model, a general-purpose method that takes a natural language task description like the prompts provided to LLMs, and uses it to train a special-purpose model that is conducive to deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt2model-generating-deployable-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Language Models Can Perform Many Tasks with Scaling and Instruction-Finetuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-language-models-can-perform-many</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then reprogram pretrained masked language models into diffusion language models via diffusive adaptation, wherein task-specific finetuning and instruction finetuning are explored to unlock their versatility in solving general language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-language-models-can-perform-many</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-driven decision-focused surrogate modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-decision-focused-surrogate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the concept of decision-focused surrogate modeling for solving computationally challenging nonlinear optimization problems in real-time settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-decision-focused-surrogate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing Selection Bias in Computerized Adaptive Testing: A User-Wise Aggregate Influence Function Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-selection-bias-in-computerized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Indeed, when naively training the diagnostic model using CAT response data, we observe that item profiles deviate significantly from the ground-truth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-selection-bias-in-computerized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic landslide susceptibility mapping over recent three decades to uncover variations in landslide causes in subtropical urban mountainous areas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-landslide-susceptibility-mapping-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The chosen study area is Lantau Island, Hong Kong, where we conducted a comprehensive dynamic LSA spanning from 1992 to 2019.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-landslide-susceptibility-mapping-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CgT-GAN: CLIP-guided Text GAN for Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cgt-gan-clip-guided-text-gan-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, we use adversarial training to teach CgT-GAN to mimic the phrases of an external text corpus and CLIP-based reward to provide semantic guidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cgt-gan-clip-guided-text-gan-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PREFER: Prompt Ensemble Learning via Feedback-Reflect-Refine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prefer-prompt-ensemble-learning-via-feedback</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, to enhance stability of the prompt effect evaluation, we propose a novel prompt bagging method involving forward and backward thinking, which is superior to majority voting and is beneficial for both feedback and weight calculation in boosting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prefer-prompt-ensemble-learning-via-feedback</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development and external validation of a lung cancer risk estimation tool using gradient-boosting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/development-and-external-validation-of-a-lung</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a machine learning (ML) tool trained on data from the PLCO Cancer Screening Trial and validated on the NLST to estimate the likelihood of lung cancer occurrence within five years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/development-and-external-validation-of-a-lung</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masking Strategies for Background Bias Removal in Computer Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masking-strategies-for-background-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Models for fine-grained image classification tasks, where the difference between some classes can be extremely subtle and the number of samples per class tends to be low, are particularly prone to picking up background-related biases and demand robust methods to handle potential examples with out-of-distribution (OOD) backgrounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masking-strategies-for-background-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MKL-$L_{0/1}$-SVM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mkl-l-0-1-svm-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a Multiple Kernel Learning (abbreviated as MKL) framework for the Support Vector Machine (SVM) with the $(0, 1)$ loss function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mkl-l-0-1-svm-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Large Language Models into the Debugging C Compiler for generating contextual error explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-large-language-models-into-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a method for Large Language Models (LLM) to produce enhanced compiler error explanations, in simple language, within our Debugging C Compiler (DCC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-large-language-models-into-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LKPNR: LLM and KG for Personalized News Recommendation Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lkpnr-llm-and-kg-for-personalized-news</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional methods are usually difficult to grasp the complex semantic information in news texts, resulting in unsatisfactory recommendation results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lkpnr-llm-and-kg-for-personalized-news</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ULDP-FL: Federated Learning with Across Silo User-Level Differential Privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uldp-fl-federated-learning-with-across-silo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we present ULDP-FL, a novel FL framework designed to guarantee user-level DP in cross-silo FL where a single user's data may belong to multiple silos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uldp-fl-federated-learning-with-across-silo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Framework for 3D Point Cloud Visual Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-framework-for-3d-point-cloud-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This elegant design enables 3DRefTR to achieve both well-performing 3DRES and 3DREC capacities with only a 6% additional latency compared to the original 3DREC model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-framework-for-3d-point-cloud-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Safe Am I Given What I See? Calibrated Prediction of Safety Chances for Image-Controlled Autonomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-safe-am-i-given-what-i-see-calibrated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[End-to-end learning has emerged as a major paradigm for developing autonomous systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-safe-am-i-given-what-i-see-calibrated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DR-Tune: Improving Fine-tuning of Pretrained Visual Models by Distribution Regularization with Semantic Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dr-tune-improving-fine-tuning-of-pretrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, to alleviate the interference by semantic drift, we develop the semantic calibration (SC) module to align the global shape and class centers of the pretrained and downstream feature distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dr-tune-improving-fine-tuning-of-pretrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instruction Position Matters in Sequence Generation with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-position-matters-in-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are capable of performing conditional sequence generation tasks, such as translation or summarization, through instruction fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-position-matters-in-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Change Detection for the Romanian Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-change-detection-for-the-romanian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic semantic change methods try to identify the changes that appear over time in the meaning of words by analyzing their usage in diachronic corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-change-detection-for-the-romanian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modal Multi-Task (3MT) Road Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-multi-task-3mt-road-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The inference times obtained in all experiments are very promising for real-time experiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-multi-task-3mt-road-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying degeneracy in singular models via the learning coefficient</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-degeneracy-in-singular-models-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNN) are singular statistical models which exhibit complex degeneracies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-degeneracy-in-singular-models-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MolGrapher: Graph-based Visual Recognition of Chemical Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molgrapher-graph-based-visual-recognition-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we introduce a large-scale benchmark of annotated real molecule images, USPTO-30K, to spur research on this critical topic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molgrapher-graph-based-visual-recognition-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Reward Modulation for Pretraining Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-reward-modulation-for-pretraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using learned reward functions (LRFs) as a means to solve sparse-reward reinforcement learning (RL) tasks has yielded some steady progress in task-complexity through the years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-reward-modulation-for-pretraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head-Tail Cooperative Learning Network for Unbiased Scene Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/head-tail-cooperative-learning-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose a self-supervised learning approach to enhance the prediction ability of the tail-prefer feature representation branch by constraining tail-prefer predicate features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/head-tail-cooperative-learning-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlexKBQA: A Flexible LLM-Powered Framework for Few-Shot Knowledge Base Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexkbqa-a-flexible-llm-powered-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge base question answering (KBQA) is a critical yet challenging task due to the vast number of entities within knowledge bases and the diversity of natural language questions posed by users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexkbqa-a-flexible-llm-powered-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manipulating Embeddings of Stable Diffusion Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manipulating-embeddings-of-stable-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(3) Changing the embedding of the prompt to include information that the user has seen in a particular seed but finds difficult to describe in the prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manipulating-embeddings-of-stable-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMIT: Source-Free Adaptation of Uni-Modal Models to Multi-Modal Targets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/summit-source-free-adaptation-of-uni-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we relax both of these assumptions by addressing the problem of adapting a set of models trained independently on uni-modal data to a target domain consisting of unlabeled multi-modal data, without having access to the original source dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/summit-source-free-adaptation-of-uni-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Objective Optimization for Sparse Deep Neural Network Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-optimization-for-sparse-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a Multi-Objective Optimization algorithm using a modified Weighted Chebyshev scalarization for training Deep Neural Networks (DNNs) with respect to several tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-optimization-for-sparse-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Data Perturbation and Model Stabilization for Semi-supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-data-perturbation-and-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Studies on semi-supervised medical image segmentation (SSMIS) have seen fast progress recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-data-perturbation-and-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMRec: Benchmarking Large Language Models on Recommendation Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmrec-benchmarking-large-language-models-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The benchmark results indicate that LLMs displayed only moderate proficiency in accuracy-based tasks such as sequential and direct recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmrec-benchmarking-large-language-models-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topical-Chat: Towards Knowledge-Grounded Open-Domain Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topical-chat-towards-knowledge-grounded-open-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Topical-Chat, a knowledge-grounded human-human conversation dataset where the underlying knowledge spans 8 broad topics and conversation partners don't have explicitly defined roles, to help further research in open-domain conversational AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topical-chat-towards-knowledge-grounded-open-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSGPT_Vision: Commanding Robots Using Only Language Models' Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rosgpt-vision-commanding-robots-using-only</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ROSGPT_Vision allows the execution of a robotic task using only two prompts: a Visual and an LLM prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rosgpt-vision-commanding-robots-using-only</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object Detection Difficulty: Suppressing Over-aggregation for Faster and Better Video Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-detection-difficulty-suppressing-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ODD score enhances the VOD system in two ways: 1) it enables the VOD system to select superior global reference frames, thereby improving overall accuracy; and 2) it serves as an indicator in the newly designed ODD Scheduler to eliminate the aggregation of frames that are easy to detect, thus accelerating the VOD process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-detection-difficulty-suppressing-over</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
