<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:12:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Consistency Training by Synthetic Question Generation for Conversational Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-training-by-synthetic-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our novel model-agnostic approach, referred to as CoTaH (Consistency-Trained augmented History), we augment the historical information with synthetic questions and subsequently employ consistency training to train a model that utilizes both real and augmented historical data to implicitly make the reasoning robust to irrelevant history.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-training-by-synthetic-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JointViT: Modeling Oxygen Saturation Levels with Joint Supervision on Long-Tailed OCTA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jointvit-modeling-oxygen-saturation-levels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The oxygen saturation level in the blood (SaO2) is crucial for health, particularly in relation to sleep-related breathing disorders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jointvit-modeling-oxygen-saturation-levels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sampling-based Pseudo-Likelihood for Membership Inference Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampling-based-pseudo-likelihood-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a Sampling-based Pseudo-Likelihood (\textbf{SPL}) method for MIA (\textbf{SaMIA}) that calculates SPL using only the text generated by an LLM to detect leaks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampling-based-pseudo-likelihood-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoccerNet Game State Reconstruction: End-to-End Athlete Tracking and Identification on a Minimap</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soccernet-game-state-reconstruction-end-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This tracking and identification process is crucial for reconstructing the game state, defined by the athletes' positions and identities on a 2D top-view of the pitch, (i. e. a minimap).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soccernet-game-state-reconstruction-end-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FairSSD: Understanding Bias in Synthetic Speech Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairssd-understanding-bias-in-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we examine bias in existing synthetic speech detectors to determine if they will unfairly target a particular gender, age and accent group.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairssd-understanding-bias-in-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inductive Cognitive Diagnosis for Fast Student Learning in Web-Based Online Intelligent Education Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inductive-cognitive-diagnosis-for-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, this paper proposes an inductive cognitive diagnosis model (ICDM) for fast new students' mastery levels inference in WOIESs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inductive-cognitive-diagnosis-for-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>arcjetCV: an open-source software to analyze material ablation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arcjetcv-an-open-source-software-to-analyze</link>
      <description><![CDATA[arcjetCV is an open-source Python software designed to automate time-resolved measurements of heatshield material recession and recession rates from arcjet test video footage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arcjetcv-an-open-source-software-to-analyze</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Data-Driven Representation for Sign Language Production</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-driven-representation-for-sign</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By applying Vector Quantisation (VQ) to sign language data, we first learn a codebook of short motions that can be combined to create a natural sequence of sign.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-driven-representation-for-sign</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closely Interactive Human Reconstruction with Proxemics and Physics-Guided Adaption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closely-interactive-human-reconstruction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we first design a latent representation based on Vector Quantised-Variational AutoEncoder (VQ-VAE) to model human interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closely-interactive-human-reconstruction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Examination of Entity Linking in Absence of Candidate Sets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-examination-of-entity-linking-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite remarkable strides made in the development of entity linking systems in recent years, a comprehensive comparative analysis of these systems using a unified framework is notably absent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-examination-of-entity-linking-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Causal Chambers: Real Physical Systems as a Testbed for AI Methodology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-causal-chambers-real-physical-systems-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The devices, which we call causal chambers, are computer-controlled laboratories that allow us to manipulate and measure an array of variables from these physical systems, providing a rich testbed for algorithms from a variety of fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-causal-chambers-real-physical-systems-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky-GVIO: an enhanced GNSS/INS/Vision navigation with FCN-based sky-segmentation in urban canyon</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sky-gvio-an-enhanced-gnss-ins-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon this, a novel NLOS detection and mitigation algorithm (named S-NDM) is extended to the tightly coupled Global Navigation Satellite Systems (GNSS), Inertial Measurement Units (IMU), and visual feature system which is called Sky-GVIO, with the aim of achieving continuous and accurate positioning in urban canyon environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sky-gvio-an-enhanced-gnss-ins-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LMEraser: Large Model Unlearning through Adaptive Prompt Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmeraser-large-model-unlearning-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the growing demand for privacy protection in machine learning, we propose a novel and efficient machine unlearning approach for \textbf{L}arge \textbf{M}odels, called \textbf{LM}Eraser.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmeraser-large-model-unlearning-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeClass: A Human-Annotated Relevance-based Headline Classification and Generation Dataset for Telugu</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teclass-a-human-annotated-relevance-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further demonstrate the impact of this work by fine-tuning various headline generation models using TeClass dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teclass-a-human-annotated-relevance-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled Cascaded Graph Convolution Networks for Multi-Behavior Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-cascaded-graph-convolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, these models overlook the personalized nature of user behavioral preferences by employing uniform transformation networks for all users and items.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-cascaded-graph-convolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational quantization for state space models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-quantization-for-state-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main challenge is to model a rich variety of time series, leverage any available external signals and provide sharp predictions with statistical guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-quantization-for-state-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Victim and The Beneficiary: Exploiting a Poisoned Model to Train a Clean Model on Poisoned Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-victim-and-the-beneficiary-exploiting-a-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This inspires us to propose a novel dual-network training framework: The Victim and The Beneficiary (V&B), which exploits a poisoned model to train a clean model without extra benign samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-victim-and-the-beneficiary-exploiting-a-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Coarse-to-Fine Evaluation of Inference Efficiency for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-coarse-to-fine-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In real world, large language models (LLMs) can serve as the assistant to help users accomplish their jobs, and also support the development of advanced applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-coarse-to-fine-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTIRE 2024 Challenge on Short-form UGC Video Quality Assessment: Methods and Results</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntire-2024-challenge-on-short-form-ugc-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper reviews the NTIRE 2024 Challenge on Shortform UGC Video Quality Assessment (S-UGC VQA), where various excellent solutions are submitted and evaluated on the collected dataset KVQ from popular short-form video platform, i. e., Kuaishou/Kwai Platform.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntire-2024-challenge-on-short-form-ugc-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-resolution Rescored ByteTrack for Video Object Detection on Ultra-low-power Embedded Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-resolution-rescored-bytetrack-for-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces Multi-Resolution Rescored Byte-Track (MR2-ByteTrack), a novel video object detection framework for ultra-low-power embedded processors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-resolution-rescored-bytetrack-for-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentKit: Flow Engineering with Graphs, not Coding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentkit-flow-engineering-with-graphs-not</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The chains of nodes can be designed to explicitly enforce a naturally structured "thought process".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentkit-flow-engineering-with-graphs-not</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Ended Wargames with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-ended-wargames-with-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce "Snow Globe," an LLM-powered multi-agent system for playing qualitative wargames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-ended-wargames-with-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CorrNet+: Sign Language Recognition and Translation via Spatial-Temporal Correlation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/corrnet-sign-language-recognition-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In specific, CorrNet+ employs a correlation module and an identification module to build human body trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/corrnet-sign-language-recognition-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TiNO-Edit: Timestep and Noise Optimization for Robust Diffusion-Based Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tino-edit-timestep-and-noise-optimization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous approaches have focused on either fine-tuning pre-trained T2I models on specific datasets to generate certain kinds of images (e. g., with a specific object or person), or on optimizing the weights, text prompts, and/or learning features for each input image in an attempt to coax the image generator to produce the desired result.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tino-edit-timestep-and-noise-optimization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VG4D: Vision-Language Model Goes 4D Video Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vg4d-vision-language-model-goes-4d-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By transferring the knowledge of the VLM to the 4D encoder and combining the VLM, our VG4D achieves improved recognition performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vg4d-vision-language-model-goes-4d-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyper Evidential Deep Learning to Quantify Composite Classification Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyper-evidential-deep-learning-to-quantify</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel framework called Hyper-Evidential Neural Network (HENN) that explicitly models predictive uncertainty due to composite class labels in training data in the context of the belief theory called Subjective Logic (SL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyper-evidential-deep-learning-to-quantify</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KI-GAN: Knowledge-Informed Generative Adversarial Networks for Enhanced Multi-Vehicle Trajectory Forecasting at Signalized Intersections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ki-gan-knowledge-informed-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reliable prediction of vehicle trajectories at signalized intersections is crucial to urban traffic management and autonomous driving systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ki-gan-knowledge-informed-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models meet Collaborative Filtering: An Efficient All-round LLM-based Recommender System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-meet-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their effectiveness under cold scenarios, we observe that they underperform simple traditional collaborative filtering models under warm scenarios due to the lack of collaborative knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-meet-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Highly Realistic Artistic Style Transfer via Stable Diffusion with Step-aware and Layer-aware Prompt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-highly-realistic-artistic-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above problems, we propose a novel pre-trained diffusion-based artistic style transfer method, called LSAST, which can generate highly realistic artistic stylized images while preserving the content structure of input content images well, without bringing obvious artifacts and disharmonious style patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-highly-realistic-artistic-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Following the Human Thread in Social Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/following-the-human-thread-in-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the first Social Dynamics Adaptation model (SDA) based on the robot's state-action history to infer the social dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/following-the-human-thread-in-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices for a Handwritten Text Recognition System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/best-practices-for-a-handwritten-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Handwritten text recognition has been developed rapidly in the recent years, following the rise of deep learning and its applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/best-practices-for-a-handwritten-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Unlabelled Data with Transformers: Domain Adaptation for Semantic Segmentation of High Resolution Aerial Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-unlabelled-data-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we develop a new model for semantic segmentation of unlabelled images, the Non-annotated Earth Observation Semantic Segmentation (NEOS) model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-unlabelled-data-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Semantic Segmentation-guided Approach for Ground-to-Aerial Image Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semantic-segmentation-guided-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nowadays the accurate geo-localization of ground-view images has an important role across domains as diverse as journalism, forensics analysis, transports, and Earth Observation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semantic-segmentation-guided-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Bayesian Last Layers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-bayesian-last-layers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a deterministic variational formulation for training Bayesian last layer neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-bayesian-last-layers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfoMatch: Entropy Neural Estimation for Semi-Supervised Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infomatch-entropy-neural-estimation-for-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-supervised image classification, leveraging pseudo supervision and consistency regularization, has demonstrated remarkable success.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infomatch-entropy-neural-estimation-for-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Bias and Unfairness in Information Retrieval: A Survey of Challenges and Opportunities with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-bias-and-unfairness-in-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid advancement of large language models (LLMs), information retrieval (IR) systems, such as search engines and recommender systems, have undergone a significant paradigm shift.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-bias-and-unfairness-in-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Heart Disease Detection via ECG Digital Twin Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-heart-disease-detection-via-ecg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Heart diseases rank among the leading causes of global mortality, demonstrating a crucial need for early diagnosis and intervention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-heart-disease-detection-via-ecg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paraphrase and Solve: Exploring and Exploiting the Impact of Surface Form on Mathematical Reasoning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paraphrase-and-solve-exploring-and-exploiting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the relationship between the surface form of a mathematical problem and its solvability by large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paraphrase-and-solve-exploring-and-exploiting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Causal Nature of Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-causal-nature-of-sentiment-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sentiment analysis (SA) aims to identify the sentiment expressed in a text, such as a product review.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-causal-nature-of-sentiment-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consisaug: A Consistency-based Augmentation for Polyp Detection in Endoscopy Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consisaug-a-consistency-based-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Colorectal cancer (CRC), which frequently originates from initially benign polyps, remains a significant contributor to global cancer-related mortality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consisaug-a-consistency-based-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedPFT: Federated Proxy Fine-Tuning of Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedpft-federated-proxy-fine-tuning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adapting Foundation Models (FMs) for downstream tasks through Federated Learning (FL) emerges a promising strategy for protecting data privacy and valuable FMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedpft-federated-proxy-fine-tuning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Transferability of Visual Prompting for Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-transferability-of-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this, we propose Transferable Visual Prompting (TVP), a simple and effective approach to generate visual prompts that can transfer to different models and improve their performance on downstream tasks after trained on only one model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-transferability-of-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Specific Block Selection and Paired-View Pseudo-Labeling for Online Test-Time Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-specific-block-selection-and-paired</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After blocks are adjusted for current test domain, we generate pseudo-labels by averaging given test images and corresponding flipped counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-specific-block-selection-and-paired</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decomposing and Editing Predictions by Modeling Model Computation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decomposing-and-editing-predictions-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of component modeling is to decompose an ML model's prediction in terms of its components -- simple functions (e. g., convolution filters, attention heads) that are the "building blocks" of model computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decomposing-and-editing-predictions-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Procedural Dilemma Generation for Evaluating Moral Reasoning in Humans and Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procedural-dilemma-generation-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We collected moral permissibility and intention judgments from human participants for a subset of our items and compared these judgments to those from two language models (GPT-4 and Claude-2) across eight conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procedural-dilemma-generation-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMCBE: Multi-modality Dataset for Crop Biomass Estimation and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmcbe-multi-modality-dataset-for-crop-biomass</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing this gap, we introduce a new dataset in this domain, i. e. Multi-modality dataset for crop biomass estimation (MMCBE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmcbe-multi-modality-dataset-for-crop-biomass</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Key Point Analysis with Pairwise Generation and Graph Partitioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-key-point-analysis-with-pairwise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our objective is to train a generative model that can simultaneously provide a score indicating the presence of shared key point between a pair of arguments and generate the shared key point.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-key-point-analysis-with-pairwise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Context Learning State Vector with Inner and Momentum Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-learning-state-vector-with-inner</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we address this gap by presenting a comprehensive analysis of these compressed vectors, drawing parallels to the parameters trained with gradient descent, and introduce the concept of state vector.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-learning-state-vector-with-inner</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VDTuner: Automated Performance Tuning for Vector Data Management Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vdtuner-automated-performance-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to the inherent characteristics of VDMS, automatic performance tuning for VDMS faces several critical challenges, which cannot be well addressed by the existing auto-tuning methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vdtuner-automated-performance-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Context Merging: Better Long Context Understanding for Pre-trained LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-context-merging-better-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown remarkable performance in various natural language processing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-context-merging-better-long</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
