<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 09:11:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Shotgun crystal structure prediction using machine-learned formation energies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shotgun-crystal-structure-prediction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stable or metastable crystal structures of assembled atoms can be predicted by finding the global or local minima of the energy surface with respect to the atomic configurations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shotgun-crystal-structure-prediction-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Being Parameter-Efficient: A Stratified Sparsely Activated Transformer with Dynamic Capacity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-being-parameter-efficient-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, recent studies have established that MoE models are inherently parameter-inefficient as the improvement in performance diminishes with an increasing number of experts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-being-parameter-efficient-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Data Augmentation for Image Captioning using Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-data-augmentation-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image captioning, an important vision-language task, often requires a tremendous number of finely labeled image-caption pairs for learning the underlying alignment between images and texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-data-augmentation-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-train and Search: Efficient Embedding Table Sharding with Pre-trained Neural Cost Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-train-and-search-efficient-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore a "pre-train, and search" paradigm for efficient sharding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-train-and-search-efficient-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lightweight CNN-Transformer Model for Learning Traveling Salesman Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-cnn-transformer-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model consumes approximately 20% less GPU memory usage and has 45% faster inference time compared with other state-of-the-art Transformer-based models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-cnn-transformer-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Exploration of Conditioning Methods in Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-exploration-of-conditioning-methods-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The flexibility and effectiveness of message passing based graph neural networks (GNNs) induced considerable advances in deep learning on graph-structured data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-exploration-of-conditioning-methods-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Supervised Segmentation of Functional Tissue Units at the Cellular Level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-segmentation-of-functional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new method for functional tissue unit segmentation at the cellular level, which utilizes the latest deep learning semantic segmentation approaches together with domain adaptation and semi-supervised learning techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-segmentation-of-functional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zenseact Open Dataset: A large-scale and diverse multimodal dataset for autonomous driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zenseact-open-dataset-a-large-scale-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing datasets for autonomous driving (AD) often lack diversity and long-range capabilities, focusing instead on 360{\deg} perception and temporal reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zenseact-open-dataset-a-large-scale-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Neural Divide-and-Conquer Reasoning Framework for Image Retrieval from Linguistically Complex Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-divide-and-conquer-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the Divide-and-Conquer algorithm and dual-process theory, in this paper, we regard linguistically complex texts as compound proposition texts composed of multiple simple proposition sentences and propose an end-to-end Neural Divide-and-Conquer Reasoning framework, dubbed NDCR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-divide-and-conquer-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Sparse Training with Structured Sparsity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-sparse-training-with-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DST methods achieve state-of-the-art results in sparse neural network training, matching the generalization of dense models while enabling sparse training and inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-sparse-training-with-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Contrastive Learning of Sentence Embeddings from AI Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-contrastive-learning-of-sentence-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method utilizes AI feedback from large pre-trained language models (LLMs) to construct sample pairs with fine-grained sample similarity scores to improve contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-contrastive-learning-of-sentence-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AttenWalker: Unsupervised Long-Document Question Answering via Attention-based Graph Walking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attenwalker-unsupervised-long-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate the problem, it might be possible to generate long-document QA pairs via unsupervised question answering (UQA) methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attenwalker-unsupervised-long-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeGen2: Lessons for Training LLMs on Programming and Natural Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codegen2-lessons-for-training-llms-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we attempt to render the training of LLMs for program synthesis more efficient by unifying four key components: (1) model architectures, (2) learning methods, (3) infill sampling, and, (4) data distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codegen2-lessons-for-training-llms-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bicubic++: Slim, Slimmer, Slimmest -- Designing an Industry-Grade Super-Resolution Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bicubic-slim-slimmer-slimmest-designing-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a real-time and lightweight single-image super-resolution (SR) network named Bicubic++.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bicubic-slim-slimmer-slimmest-designing-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DocLangID: Improving Few-Shot Training to Identify the Language of Historical Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doclangid-improving-few-shot-training-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose DocLangID, a transfer learning approach to identify the language of unlabeled historical documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doclangid-improving-few-shot-training-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding cirrus clouds using explainable machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-cirrus-clouds-using-explainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Their dependencies on meteorological and aerosol conditions are among the largest uncertainties in global climate models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-cirrus-clouds-using-explainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of Label-Description Training for Zero-Shot Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-benefits-of-label-description-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models have improved zero-shot text classification by allowing the transfer of semantic knowledge from the training data in order to classify among specific label sets in downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-benefits-of-label-description-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Glitch in the Matrix!": A Large Scale Benchmark for Content Driven Audio-Visual Forgery Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glitch-in-the-matrix-a-large-scale-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed baseline method, Boundary Aware Temporal Forgery Detection (BA-TFD), is a 3D Convolutional Neural Network-based architecture which efficiently captures multimodal manipulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glitch-in-the-matrix-a-large-scale-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causality-aware Concept Extraction based on Knowledge-guided Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-aware-concept-extraction-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prompt adopts the topic of the given entity from the existing knowledge in KGs to mitigate the spurious co-occurrence correlations between entities and biased concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-aware-concept-extraction-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling-up Remote Sensing Segmentation Dataset with Segment Anything Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-remote-sensing-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of the Segment Anything Model (SAM) demonstrates the significance of data-centric machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-remote-sensing-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Natural Language Watermarking through Invariant Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-natural-language-watermarking-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have witnessed a proliferation of valuable original natural language contents found in subscription-based media outlets, web novel platforms, and outputs of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-natural-language-watermarking-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NorQuAD: Norwegian Question Answering Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/norquad-norwegian-question-answering-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present NorQuAD: the first Norwegian question answering dataset for machine reading comprehension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/norquad-norwegian-question-answering-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Local to Global: Navigating Linguistic Diversity in the African Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-local-to-global-navigating-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The focus is on critical problems in NLP related to linguistic diversity and variation across the African continent, specifically with regards to African local di- alects and Arabic dialects that have received little attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-local-to-global-navigating-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Machine Learning for Science with PySR and SymbolicRegression.jl</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-machine-learning-for-science</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PySR was developed to democratize and popularize symbolic regression for the sciences, and is built on a high-performance distributed back-end, a flexible search algorithm, and interfaces with several deep learning packages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-machine-learning-for-science</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Neurons in a Haystack: Case Studies with Sparse Probing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-neurons-in-a-haystack-case-studies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite rapid adoption and deployment of large language models (LLMs), the internal computations of these models remain opaque and poorly understood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-neurons-in-a-haystack-case-studies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster OreFSDet : A Lightweight and Effective Few-shot Object Detector for Ore Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-orefsdet-a-lightweight-and-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the ore particle size detection, obtaining a sizable amount of high-quality ore labeled data is time-consuming and expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-orefsdet-a-lightweight-and-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geometric Latent Diffusion Models for 3D Molecule Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-latent-diffusion-models-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative models, especially diffusion models (DMs), have achieved promising results for generating feature-rich geometries and advancing foundational science problems such as molecule design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-latent-diffusion-models-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Dataset Distillation via Deep Generative Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-dataset-distillation-via-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dataset Distillation aims to distill an entire dataset's knowledge into a few synthetic images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-dataset-distillation-via-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Unleash the Power of Large Language Models for Few-shot Relation Extraction?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-unleash-the-power-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scaling language models have revolutionized widespread NLP tasks, yet little comprehensively explored few-shot relation extraction with large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-unleash-the-power-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Generalization Ability of Deep Learning Algorithms: A Kernelized Renyi's Entropy Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-generalization-ability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the current generalization error bounds within this framework are still far from optimal, while substantial improvements on these bounds are quite challenging due to the intractability of high-dimensional information quantities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-generalization-ability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLTUNET: A Simple Unified Model for Sign Language Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sltunet-a-simple-unified-model-for-sign-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose SLTUNET, a simple unified neural model designed to support multiple SLTrelated tasks jointly, such as sign-to-gloss, gloss-to-text and sign-to-text translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sltunet-a-simple-unified-model-for-sign-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Procedural Planning via Dual Text-Image Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-procedural-planning-via-dual-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key challenges of MPP are to ensure the informativeness, temporal coherence, and accuracy of plans across modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-procedural-planning-via-dual-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stratified Adversarial Robustness with Rejection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stratified-adversarial-robustness-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We theoretically analyze the stratified rejection setting and propose a novel defense method -- Adversarial Training with Consistent Prediction-based Rejection (CPR) -- for building a robust selective classifier.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stratified-adversarial-robustness-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PGrad: Learning Principal Gradients For Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgrad-learning-principal-gradients-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop a novel DG training strategy, we call PGrad, to learn a robust gradient direction, improving models' generalization ability on unseen domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgrad-learning-principal-gradients-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory of recurrent networks: Do we compute it right?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-of-recurrent-networks-do-we-compute-it</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerical evaluations of the memory capacity (MC) of recurrent neural networks reported in the literature often contradict well-established theoretical bounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-of-recurrent-networks-do-we-compute-it</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Factored Action Spaces for Efficient Offline Reinforcement Learning in Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-factored-action-spaces-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the theoretical properties of our approach, identifying scenarios where it is guaranteed to lead to zero bias when used to approximate the Q-function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-factored-action-spaces-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data valuation: The partial ordinal Shapley value for machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-valuation-the-partial-ordinal-shapley</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data valuation using Shapley value has emerged as a prevalent research domain in machine learning applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-valuation-the-partial-ordinal-shapley</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expressive Mortality Models through Gaussian Process Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressive-mortality-models-through-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a flexible Gaussian Process (GP) framework for learning the covariance structure of Age- and Year-specific mortality surfaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressive-mortality-models-through-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Summarizing Multiple Documents with Hierarchical Relationships</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-summarizing-multiple-documents-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing multi-document summarization (MDS) datasets lack human-generated and genuine (i. e., not synthetic) summaries or source documents with explicit inter-document relationships that a summary must capture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-summarizing-multiple-documents-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt as Triggers for Backdoor Attack: Examining the Vulnerability in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-as-triggers-for-backdoor-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method does not require external triggers and ensures correct labeling of poisoned samples, improving the stealthy nature of the backdoor attack.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-as-triggers-for-backdoor-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Stop Pretraining? Make Prompt-based Fine-tuning Powerful Learner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-stop-pretraining-make-prompt-based-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models (LMs) trained on vast quantities of unlabelled data have greatly advanced the field of natural language processing (NLP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-stop-pretraining-make-prompt-based-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil Spill Segmentation using Deep Encoder-Decoder models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oil-spill-segmentation-using-deep-encoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even though oil spills are in and themselves difficult to clean up, the first and foremost challenge is to detect spills.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oil-spill-segmentation-using-deep-encoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pick-a-Pic: An Open Dataset of User Preferences for Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pick-a-pic-an-open-dataset-of-user</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using this web app we build Pick-a-Pic, a large, open dataset of text-to-image prompts and real users' preferences over generated images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pick-a-pic-an-open-dataset-of-user</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Mask Annotation for Video Text Spotting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-mask-annotation-for-video-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video text spotting refers to localizing, recognizing, and tracking textual elements such as captions, logos, license plates, signs, and other forms of text within consecutive video frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-mask-annotation-for-video-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiLegalSBD: A Multilingual Legal Sentence Boundary Detection Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilegalsbd-a-multilingual-legal-sentence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sentence Boundary Detection (SBD) is one of the foundational building blocks of Natural Language Processing (NLP), with incorrectly split sentences heavily influencing the output quality of downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilegalsbd-a-multilingual-legal-sentence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PU-EdgeFormer: Edge Transformer for Dense Prediction in Point Cloud Upsampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pu-edgeformer-edge-transformer-for-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We employ graph convolution using EdgeConv, which learns the local geometry and global structure of point cloud better than existing point-to-feature method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pu-edgeformer-edge-transformer-for-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sample Efficient Model-free Reinforcement Learning from LTL Specifications with Optimality Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-efficient-model-free-reinforcement-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Linear Temporal Logic (LTL) is widely used to specify high-level objectives for system policies, and it is highly desirable for autonomous systems to learn the optimal policy with respect to such specifications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-efficient-model-free-reinforcement-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Tailed Recognition by Mutual Information Maximization between Latent Features and Ground-Truth Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-recognition-by-mutual-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although contrastive learning methods have shown prevailing performance on a variety of representation learning tasks, they encounter difficulty when the training dataset is long-tailed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-recognition-by-mutual-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlimiformer: Long-Range Transformers with Unlimited Length Input</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlimiformer-long-range-transformers-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This way, we can index extremely long input sequences, while every attention head in every decoder layer retrieves its top-$k$ keys, instead of attending to every key.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlimiformer-long-range-transformers-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Guided Traversal for Fast Learned Sparse Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-guided-traversal-for-fast-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies show that BM25-driven dynamic index skipping can greatly accelerate MaxScore-based document retrieval based on the learned sparse representation derived by DeepImpact.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-guided-traversal-for-fast-learned</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
