<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 09:15:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervision Can Be a Good Few-Shot Learner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervision-can-be-a-good-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we maximize the mutual information (MI) of instances and their representations with a low-bias MI estimator to perform self-supervised pre-training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervision-can-be-a-good-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single Stage Virtual Try-on via Deformable Attention Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-stage-virtual-try-on-via-deformable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Virtual try-on aims to generate a photo-realistic fitting result given an in-shop garment and a reference person image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-stage-virtual-try-on-via-deformable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balancing the trade-off between cost and reliability for wireless sensor networks: a multi-objective optimized deployment method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-the-trade-off-between-cost-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, this work fully considers the heterogeneity of SNs (i. e. differentiated sensing range and deployment cost) and three-dimensional (3-D) deployment scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-the-trade-off-between-cost-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Informative knowledge distillation for image anomaly segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/informative-knowledge-distillation-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, rare attention has been paid to the overfitting problem caused by the inconsistency between the capacity of the neural network and the amount of knowledge in this scheme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/informative-knowledge-distillation-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Pixel Restoration as a Pretext Task for Transferable Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-pixel-restoration-as-a-pretext</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transferable adversarial attacks optimize adversaries from a pretrained surrogate model and known label space to fool the unknown black-box models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-pixel-restoration-as-a-pretext</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Partition Implicit with Surface Codes for 3D Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-partition-implicit-with-surface-codes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our insight here is that both the part learning and the part blending can be conducted much easier in the latent space than in the spatial space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-partition-implicit-with-surface-codes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time End-to-End Video Text Spotter with Contrastive Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-end-to-end-video-text-spotter-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our contributions are three-fold: 1) CoText simultaneously address the three tasks (e. g., text detection, tracking, recognition) in a real-time end-to-end trainable framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-end-to-end-video-text-spotter-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Video Super Resolution with Patch-Based Temporal Redundancy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-video-super-resolution-with-patch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop two simple yet effective plug and play methods to improve the performance of existing local and non-local propagation-based VSR algorithms on widely-used public videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-video-super-resolution-with-patch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label2Label: A Language Modeling Framework for Multi-Attribute Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label2label-a-language-modeling-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As each sample is annotated with multiple attribute labels, these "words" will naturally form an unordered but meaningful "sentence", which depicts the semantic information of the corresponding sample.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label2label-a-language-modeling-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DID-M3D: Decoupling Instance Depth for Monocular 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/did-m3d-decoupling-instance-depth-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose to reformulate the instance depth to the combination of the instance visual surface depth (visual depth) and the instance attribute depth (attribute depth).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/did-m3d-decoupling-instance-depth-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Novelty Detection via Relational Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-novelty-detection-via-relational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We claim that a tailored representation learning strategy may be the right solution for effective and efficient semantic novelty detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-novelty-detection-via-relational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dense Cross-Query-and-Support Attention Weighted Mask Aggregation for Few-Shot Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-cross-query-and-support-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key to this challenging task is to fully utilize the information in the support images by exploiting fine-grained correlations between the query and support images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-cross-query-and-support-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-shot Fine-grained Image Classification via Multi-Frequency Neighborhood and Double-cross Modulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-fine-grained-image-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The comprehensive experiments on three fine-grained benchmark datasets for two few-shot tasks verify that FicNet has excellent performance compared to the state-of-the-art methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-fine-grained-image-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class-incremental Novel Class Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-incremental-novel-class-discovery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the new task of class-incremental Novel Class Discovery (class-iNCD), which refers to the problem of discovering novel categories in an unlabelled data set by leveraging a pre-trained model that has been trained on a labelled data set containing disjoint yet related categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-incremental-novel-class-discovery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniFormer: Unified Multi-view Fusion Transformer for Spatial-Temporal Representation in Bird's-Eye-View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniformer-unified-multi-view-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bird's eye view (BEV) representation is a new perception formulation for autonomous driving, which is based on spatial fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniformer-unified-multi-view-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Distributed Image Compression with Cross-Attention Feature Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-distributed-image-compression-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed decoder extracts useful information common between the images solely from the available side information, as well as a latent representation of the side information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-distributed-image-compression-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Alignment in Video Super-Resolution Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-alignment-in-video-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we rethink the role of alignment in VSR Transformers and make several counter-intuitive observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-alignment-in-video-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latency-Aware Collaborative Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latency-aware-collaborative-perception</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Collaborative perception has recently shown great potential to improve perception capabilities over single-agent perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latency-aware-collaborative-perception</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully trainable Gaussian derivative convolutional layer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-trainable-gaussian-derivative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Gaussian kernel and its derivatives have already been employed for Convolutional Neural Networks in several previous works.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-trainable-gaussian-derivative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CACTUSS: Common Anatomical CT-US Space for US examinations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cactuss-common-anatomical-ct-us-space-for-us</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Abdominal aortic aneurysm (AAA) is a vascular disease in which a section of the aorta enlarges, weakening its walls and potentially rupturing the vessel.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cactuss-common-anatomical-ct-us-space-for-us</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHGE: Dual-view Hyper-Relational Knowledge Graph Embedding for Link Prediction and Entity Typing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dhge-dual-view-hyper-relational-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the existing hyper-relational KG embedding methods in a single view are limited in application due to weakening the hierarchical structure representing the affiliation between entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dhge-dual-view-hyper-relational-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Feature Alignment Network for Unsupervised Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-feature-alignment-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optical flow is an easily conceived and precious cue for advancing unsupervised video object segmentation (UVOS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-feature-alignment-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TokenMix: Rethinking Image Mixing for Data Augmentation in Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenmix-rethinking-image-mixing-for-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel data augmentation technique TokenMix to improve the performance of vision transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenmix-rethinking-image-mixing-for-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The role of regular asymptomatic testing in reducing the impact of a COVID-19 wave</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-role-of-regular-asymptomatic-testing-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since regular asymptomatic testing requires only those with a positive result to reduce contact, while lockdown measures require the whole population to reduce contact, any policy decision that seeks to trade off harms from infection against other harms will not automatically favour one over the other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-role-of-regular-asymptomatic-testing-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards High-Fidelity Single-view Holistic Reconstruction of Indoor Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-high-fidelity-single-view-holistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new framework to reconstruct holistic 3D indoor scenes including both room background and indoor objects from single-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-high-fidelity-single-view-holistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOAL: Towards Benchmarking Few-Shot Sports Game Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goal-towards-benchmarking-few-shot-sports</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sports game summarization aims to generate sports news based on real-time commentaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goal-towards-benchmarking-few-shot-sports</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLEAM: Greedy Learning for Large-Scale Accelerated MRI Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gleam-greedy-learning-for-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, they require several iterations of a large neural network to handle high-dimensional imaging tasks such as 3D MRI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gleam-greedy-learning-for-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A General Framework for Pairwise Unbiased Learning to Rank</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-framework-for-pairwise-unbiased</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pairwise debiasing is one of the most effective strategies in reducing position bias in learning-to-rank (LTR) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-framework-for-pairwise-unbiased</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Data Augmentation for Robust Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-data-augmentation-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, to guarantee augmented samples have reasonable ground-truth answers, they manually design a set of heuristic rules for several question types, which extremely limits its generalization abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-data-augmentation-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Lift Pooling for Continuous Sign Language Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-lift-pooling-for-continuous-sign</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we derive temporal lift pooling (TLP) from the Lifting Scheme in signal processing to intelligently downsample features of different temporal hierarchies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-lift-pooling-for-continuous-sign</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Diverse and Faithful One-shot Adaption of Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-diverse-and-faithful-one-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel one-shot generative domain adaption method, i. e., DiFa, for diverse generation and faithful adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-diverse-and-faithful-one-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SelectionConv: Convolutional Neural Networks for Non-rectilinear Image Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selectionconv-convolutional-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This network can then operate on any data that can be represented as a positional graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selectionconv-convolutional-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entity-enhanced Adaptive Reconstruction Network for Weakly Supervised Referring Expression Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entity-enhanced-adaptive-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, most previous weakly supervised REG methods ignore the discriminative location and context of the referent, causing difficulties in distinguishing the target from other same-category objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entity-enhanced-adaptive-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FakeCLR: Exploring Contrastive Learning for Solving Latent Discontinuity in Data-Efficient GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fakeclr-exploring-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since data augmentation strategies have largely alleviated the training instability, how to further improve the generative performance of DE-GANs becomes a hotspot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fakeclr-exploring-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiFormer: Hierarchical Multi-scale Representations Using Transformers for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiformer-hierarchical-multi-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose HiFormer, a novel method that efficiently bridges a CNN and a transformer for medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiformer-hierarchical-multi-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Meta-Reinforcement Learning Algorithm for Causal Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-meta-reinforcement-learning-algorithm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal discovery is a major task with the utmost importance for machine learning since causal structures can enable models to go beyond pure correlation-based inference and significantly boost their performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-meta-reinforcement-learning-algorithm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CausNet : Generational orderings based search for optimal Bayesian networks via dynamic programming with parent set constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causnet-generational-orderings-based-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finding a globally optimal Bayesian Network using exhaustive search is a problem with super-exponential complexity, which severely restricts the number of variables that it can work for.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causnet-generational-orderings-based-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FunQG: Molecular Representation Learning Via Quotient Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/funqg-molecular-representation-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An idea to overcome these problems is to simplify a molecular graph into a small, rich, and informative one, which is more efficient and less challenging to train GNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/funqg-molecular-representation-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPIB: An MPI-Based Bokeh Rendering Framework for Realistic Partial Occlusion Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpib-an-mpi-based-bokeh-rendering-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Partial occlusion effects are a phenomenon that blurry objects near a camera are semi-transparent, resulting in partial appearance of occluded background.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpib-an-mpi-based-bokeh-rendering-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ir_metadata: An Extensible Metadata Schema for IR Experiments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ir-metadata-an-extensible-metadata-schema-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we curate a dataset with run files derived from experiments with different instantiations of PRIMAD components and annotate these with the corresponding metadata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ir-metadata-an-extensible-metadata-schema-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Repair of Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-repair-of-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method is able to search for a new, safe NN representation, by modifying only a few of its weight values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-repair-of-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Temporal Action Detection via Vision-Language Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-temporal-action-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such a novel design effectively eliminates the dependence between localization and classification by breaking the route for error propagation in-between.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-temporal-action-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Qubits to Sing: Mission Impossible?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-qubits-to-sing-mission-impossible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It extracts sequencing rules from input music and uses these rules to generate new tunes, which are sung by a vocal synthesiser.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-qubits-to-sing-mission-impossible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gigapixel Whole-Slide Images Classification using Locally Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gigapixel-whole-slide-images-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Histopathology whole slide images (WSIs) play a very important role in clinical studies and serve as the gold standard for many cancer diagnoses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gigapixel-whole-slide-images-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast-MoCo: Boost Momentum-based Contrastive Learning with Combinatorial Patches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-moco-boost-momentum-based-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive-based self-supervised learning methods achieved great success in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-moco-boost-momentum-based-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Temporal Spatial Cubism for Cross-Dataset Skeleton-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-temporal-spatial-cubism-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from the conventional adversarial learning-based approaches for UDA, we utilize a self-supervision scheme to reduce the domain shift between two skeleton-based action datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-temporal-spatial-cubism-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FashionViL: Fashion-Focused Vision-and-Language Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fashionvil-fashion-focused-vision-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We thus propose a Multi-View Contrastive Learning task for pulling closer the visual representation of one image to the compositional multimodal representation of another image+text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fashionvil-fashion-focused-vision-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermark Vaccine: Adversarial Attacks to Prevent Watermark Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watermark-vaccine-adversarial-attacks-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the vulnerability of DNNs on adversarial perturbations, we propose a novel defence mechanism by adversarial machine learning for good.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watermark-vaccine-adversarial-attacks-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELECTRA is a Zero-Shot Learner, Too</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/electra-is-a-zero-shot-learner-too</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerically, compared to MLM-RoBERTa-large and MLM-BERT-large, our RTD-ELECTRA-large has an average of about 8. 4% and 13. 7% improvement on all 15 tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/electra-is-a-zero-shot-learner-too</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United States Politicians' Tone Became More Negative with 2016 Primary Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/united-states-politicians-tone-became-more</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a widespread belief that the tone of US political language has become more negative recently, in particular when Donald Trump entered politics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/united-states-politicians-tone-became-more</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
