<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 21:06:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Thai Capital Market Linkages: Part III. Vine Copula and Monte Carlo Value-at-Risk/Expected Shortfall</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-thai-capital-market-linkages-part-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analytically thorough understanding of financial-market dynamics is fundamental to the promotion of capital-market innovation, efficiency, and resilience; innovative, efficient, and resilient capital market, in turn, is fundamental to the sustainable economic development of the nation and the robust financial stability of its economy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-thai-capital-market-linkages-part-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Stochastic Proximal Polyak Step Size</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stochastic-proximal-polyak-step-size</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Developing a proximal variant of SPS is particularly important, since SPS requires a lower bound of the objective function to work well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stochastic-proximal-polyak-step-size</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Triplet: An Open Challenge for Intervention-centric Causal Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-triplet-an-open-challenge-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have seen a surge of interest in learning high-level causal representations from low-level image pairs under interventions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-triplet-an-open-challenge-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This book is the result of a seminar in which we reviewed multimodal approaches and attempted to create a solid overview of the field, starting with the current state-of-the-art approaches in the two subfields of Deep Learning individually.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharpening Ponzi Schemes Detection on Ethereum with Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharpening-ponzi-schemes-detection-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Blockchain technology has been successfully exploited for deploying new economic applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharpening-ponzi-schemes-detection-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dataset of Kurdish (Sorani) Named Entities -- An Amendment to Kurdish-BLARK Named Entities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dataset-of-kurdish-sorani-named-entities-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Named Entity Recognition (NER) is one of the essential applications of Natural Language Processing (NLP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dataset-of-kurdish-sorani-named-entities-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Density-based clustering with fully-convolutional networks for crowd flow detection from drones</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/density-based-clustering-with-fully</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a crowd flow detection method for video sequences shot by a drone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/density-based-clustering-with-fully</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Correction Learning for Semi-Supervised Biomedical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-correction-learning-for-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the two tasks rely on similar feature information, the unlabeled data effectively enhances the representation of the network to the lesion regions and further improves the segmentation performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-correction-learning-for-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlideVQA: A Dataset for Document Visual Question Answering on Multiple Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slidevqa-a-dataset-for-document-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual question answering on document images that contain textual, visual, and layout information, called document VQA, has received much attention recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slidevqa-a-dataset-for-document-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Context Selection for Polyp Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-context-selection-for-polyp</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these issues, we propose an adaptive context selection based encoder-decoder framework which is composed of Local Context Attention (LCA) module, Global Context Module (GCM) and Adaptive Selection Module (ASM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-context-selection-for-polyp</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ImMesh: An Immediate LiDAR Localization and Meshing Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/immesh-an-immediate-lidar-localization-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This voxel-wise meshing operation is delicately designed for the purpose of efficiency; it first performs a dimension reduction by projecting 3D points to a 2D local plane contained in the voxel, and then executes the meshing operation with pull, commit and push steps for incremental reconstruction of triangle facets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/immesh-an-immediate-lidar-localization-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEA-Net: Single image dehazing based on detail-enhanced convolution and content-guided attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dea-net-single-image-dehazing-based-on-detail</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, a detail-enhanced attention block (DEAB) consisting of the detail-enhanced convolution (DEConv) and the content-guided attention (CGA) is proposed to boost the feature learning for improving the dehazing performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dea-net-single-image-dehazing-based-on-detail</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improvement of Computational Performance of Evolutionary AutoML in a Heterogeneous Environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improvement-of-computational-performance-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Resource-intensive computations are a major factor that limits the effectiveness of automated machine learning solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improvement-of-computational-performance-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Adaptation for French Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-adaptation-for-french-named</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a Transformer-based NER approach for French, using adversarial adaptation to similar domain or general corpora to improve feature extraction and enable better generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-adaptation-for-french-named</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is the State of Neural Network Pruning so Confusing? On the Fairness, Comparison Setup, and Trainability in Network Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-is-the-state-of-neural-network-pruning-so</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The state of neural network pruning has been noticed to be unclear and even confusing for a while, largely due to "a lack of standardized benchmarks and metrics" [3].]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-is-the-state-of-neural-network-pruning-so</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesion-aware Dynamic Kernel for Polyp Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesion-aware-dynamic-kernel-for-polyp</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic and accurate polyp segmentation plays an essential role in early colorectal cancer diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesion-aware-dynamic-kernel-for-polyp</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine-learning Analysis of Opioid Use Disorder Informed by MOR, DOR, KOR, NOR and ZOR-Based Interactome Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-analysis-of-opioid-use</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite that a few pharmacological agents have been approved for OUD treatment, the efficacy of said agents for OUD requires further improvement in order to provide safer and more effective pharmacological and psychosocial treatments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-analysis-of-opioid-use</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head-Free Lightweight Semantic Segmentation with Linear Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/head-free-lightweight-semantic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the ADE20K dataset, our model achieves 41. 8 mIoU and 4. 6 GFLOPs, which is 4. 4 mIoU higher than Segformer, with 45% less GFLOPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/head-free-lightweight-semantic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT as Knowledge Worker: A Zero-Shot Evaluation of (AI)CPA Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-as-knowledge-worker-a-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The global economy is increasingly dependent on knowledge workers to meet the needs of public and private organizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-as-knowledge-worker-a-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diving Deep into Modes of Fact Hallucinations in Dialogue Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diving-deep-into-modes-of-fact-hallucinations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Graph(KG) grounded conversations often use large pre-trained models and usually suffer from fact hallucination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diving-deep-into-modes-of-fact-hallucinations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic data generation method for data-free knowledge distillation in regression neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-data-generation-method-for-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge distillation is the technique of compressing a larger neural network, known as the teacher, into a smaller neural network, known as the student, while still trying to maintain the performance of the larger neural network as much as possible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-data-generation-method-for-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast spline detection in high density microscopy data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-spline-detection-in-high-density</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computer-aided analysis of biological microscopy data has seen a massive improvement with the utilization of general-purpose deep learning techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-spline-detection-in-high-density</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A prediction and behavioural analysis of machine learning methods for modelling travel mode choice</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-prediction-and-behavioural-analysis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The answer to this question goes beyond simple predictive performance, and is instead a balance of many factors, including behavioural interpretability and explainability, computational complexity, and data efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-prediction-and-behavioural-analysis-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaPoinTr: Diverse Point Cloud Completion with Adaptive Geometry-Aware Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapointr-diverse-point-cloud-completion-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new method that reformulates point cloud completion as a set-to-set translation problem and design a new model, called PoinTr, which adopts a Transformer encoder-decoder architecture for point cloud completion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapointr-diverse-point-cloud-completion-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Tri-stream Clustering Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-tri-stream-clustering-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive deep clustering has recently gained significant attention with its ability of joint contrastive learning and clustering via deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-tri-stream-clustering-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pyssam -- a Python library for statistical modelling of biomedical shape and appearance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyssam-a-python-library-for-statistical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[pyssam is a Python library for creating statistical shape and appearance models (SSAMs) for biological (and other) shapes such as bones, lungs or other organs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyssam-a-python-library-for-statistical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaptSLAM: Edge-Assisted Adaptive SLAM with Resource Constraints via Uncertainty Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptslam-edge-assisted-adaptive-slam-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Edge computing is increasingly proposed as a solution for reducing resource consumption of mobile devices running simultaneous localization and mapping (SLAM) algorithms, with most edge-assisted SLAM systems assuming the communication resources between the mobile device and the edge server to be unlimited, or relying on heuristics to choose the information to be transmitted to the edge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptslam-edge-assisted-adaptive-slam-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Scanner Canine Cutaneous Squamous Cell Carcinoma Histopathology Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scanner-canine-cutaneous-squamous-cell</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, to quantify the inherent scanner-induced domain shift, we train a tumor segmentation network on each scanner subset and evaluate the performance both in- and cross-domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scanner-canine-cutaneous-squamous-cell</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SensePOLAR: Word sense aware interpretability for pre-trained contextual word embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensepolar-word-sense-aware-interpretability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we present SensePOLAR, an extension of the original POLAR framework that enables word-sense aware interpretability for pre-trained contextual word embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensepolar-word-sense-aware-interpretability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WuYun: Exploring hierarchical skeleton-guided melody generation using knowledge-enhanced deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wuyun-exploring-hierarchical-skeleton-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although deep learning has revolutionized music generation, existing methods for structured melody generation follow an end-to-end left-to-right note-by-note generative paradigm and treat each note equally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wuyun-exploring-hierarchical-skeleton-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optirank: classification for RNA-Seq data with optimal ranking reference genes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optirank-classification-for-rna-seq-data-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On those real tasks, optirank performs at least as well as the vanilla logistic regression on classical ranks, while producing sparser solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optirank-classification-for-rna-seq-data-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Inverse Cloze Task for Knowledge-based Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-inverse-cloze-task-for-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new pre-training method, Multimodal Inverse Cloze Task, for Knowledge-based Visual Question Answering about named Entities (KVQAE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-inverse-cloze-task-for-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the functional form of the radial acceleration relation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-functional-form-of-the-radial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply a new method for learning equations from data -- Exhaustive Symbolic Regression (ESR) -- to late-type galaxy dynamics as encapsulated in the radial acceleration relation (RAR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-functional-form-of-the-radial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast conformational clustering of extensive molecular dynamics simulation data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-conformational-clustering-of-extensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this approach we combine two dimensionality reduction algorithms (cc\_analysis and encodermap) with a density-based spatial clustering algorithm (HDBSCAN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-conformational-clustering-of-extensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Online Multi-Task Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-online-multi-task-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove a minimax lower bound of $\Omega(K\sqrt{DSAH})$ on the regret of any learning algorithm and an instance-specific lower bound of $\Omega(\frac{K}{\lambda^2})$ in sample complexity for a class of uniformly-good cluster-then-learn algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-online-multi-task-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning under Heterogeneous and Correlated Client Availability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-under-heterogeneous-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this purpose, CA-Fed dynamically adapts the weight given to each client and may ignore clients with low availability and large correlation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-under-heterogeneous-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClimaBench: A Benchmark Dataset For Climate Change Text Understanding in English</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/climabench-a-benchmark-dataset-for-climate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The topic of Climate Change (CC) has received limited attention in NLP despite its real world urgency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/climabench-a-benchmark-dataset-for-climate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinyHD: Efficient Video Saliency Prediction with Heterogeneous Decoders using Hierarchical Maps Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyhd-efficient-video-saliency-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video saliency prediction has recently attracted attention of the research community, as it is an upstream task for several practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyhd-efficient-video-saliency-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LENet: Lightweight And Efficient LiDAR Semantic Segmentation Using Multi-Scale Convolution Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lenet-lightweight-and-efficient-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose LENet, a lightweight and efficient projection-based LiDAR semantic segmentation network, which has an encoder-decoder architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lenet-lightweight-and-efficient-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARD: Semantic Segmentation with Efficient Class-Aware Regularized Decoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/card-semantic-segmentation-with-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments and ablation studies conducted on multiple benchmark datasets demonstrate that the proposed CAR can boost the accuracy of all baseline models by up to 2. 23% mIOU with superior generalization ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/card-semantic-segmentation-with-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Kinodynamic Planning on the Constraint Manifold with Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-kinodynamic-planning-on-the-constraint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motion planning is a mature area of research in robotics with many well-established methods based on optimization or sampling the state space, suitable for solving kinematic motion planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-kinodynamic-planning-on-the-constraint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHUNIT: Style Harmonization for Unpaired Image-to-Image Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shunit-style-harmonization-for-unpaired-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our SHUNIT generates a new style by harmonizing the target domain style retrieved from a class memory and an original source image style.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shunit-style-harmonization-for-unpaired-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HADA: A Graph-based Amalgamation Framework in Image-text Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hada-a-graph-based-amalgamation-framework-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is not easy to propose a new model with a novel architecture and intensively train it on a massive dataset with many GPUs to surpass many SOTA models, which are already available to use on the Internet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hada-a-graph-based-amalgamation-framework-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Continuous Mesh Representation with Spherical Implicit Surface</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-continuous-mesh-representation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to learn a continuous representation for meshes with fixed topology, a common and practical setting in many faces-, hand-, and body-related applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-continuous-mesh-representation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tieval: An Evaluation Framework for Temporal Information Extraction Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tieval-an-evaluation-framework-for-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[All in all, these problems have limited the fair comparison between approaches and consequently, the development of temporal extraction systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tieval-an-evaluation-framework-for-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Efficient Drifters Deployment Strategy to Evaluate Water Current Velocity Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-drifters-deployment-strategy-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we consider a common approach for water current prediction that uses Lagrangian floaters for water current prediction by interpolating the trajectory of the elements to reflect the velocity field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-drifters-deployment-strategy-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Human Identity Anonymization using Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-human-identity-anonymization-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many outdoor autonomous mobile platforms require more human identity anonymized data to power their data-driven algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-human-identity-anonymization-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Perceive in Deep Model-Free Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-perceive-in-deep-model-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate whether a model with these characteristics is capable of achieving similar performance to state-of-the-art model-free RL agents that access the full input observation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-perceive-in-deep-model-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Hateful Discussions on Reddit using Graph Transformer Networks and Communal Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-hateful-discussions-on-reddit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a system to predict harmful discussions on social media platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-hateful-discussions-on-reddit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RedMule: A Mixed-Precision Matrix-Matrix Operation Engine for Flexible and Energy-Efficient On-Chip Linear Algebra and TinyML Training Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redmule-a-mixed-precision-matrix-matrix</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing interest in TinyML, i. e., near-sensor machine learning on power budgets of a few tens of mW, is currently pushing toward enabling TinyML-class training as opposed to inference only.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redmule-a-mixed-precision-matrix-matrix</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
