<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 09:12:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>HB-net: Holistic bursting cell cluster integrated network for occluded multi-objects recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hb-net-holistic-bursting-cell-cluster</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although in high-noise settings, standard CNNs exhibit slightly greater robustness when compared to HB-net models, the models that combine the HB framework and EA mechanism achieve a comparable level of accuracy and resilience to ResNet50, despite having only three convolutional layers and approximately $1/30$ of the parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hb-net-holistic-bursting-cell-cluster</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototype-based HyperAdapter for Sample-Efficient Multi-task Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-based-hyperadapter-for-sample</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parameter-efficient fine-tuning (PEFT) has shown its effectiveness in adapting the pre-trained language models to downstream tasks while only updating a small number of parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-based-hyperadapter-for-sample</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Generate or Not? Safety-Driven Unlearned Diffusion Models Are Still Easy To Generate Unsafe Images ... For Now</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-generate-or-not-safety-driven-unlearned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this uncertainty, we propose an evaluation framework built upon adversarial attacks (also referred to as adversarial prompts), in order to discern the trustworthiness of these safety-driven unlearned DMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-generate-or-not-safety-driven-unlearned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-shot Faithfulness Evaluation for Text Summarization with Foundation Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-faithfulness-evaluation-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite tremendous improvements in natural language generation, summarization models still suffer from the unfaithfulness issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-faithfulness-evaluation-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT-guided Semantics for Zero-shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-guided-semantics-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we enrich word vectors by combining the word embeddings from class names and descriptions generated by ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-guided-semantics-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISAR: A Multimodal Instructional System with Augmented Reality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/misar-a-multimodal-instructional-system-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Augmented reality (AR) requires the seamless integration of visual, auditory, and linguistic channels for optimized human-computer interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/misar-a-multimodal-instructional-system-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Generalized Face Anti-Spoofing with Unknown Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalized-face-anti-spoofing-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although face anti-spoofing (FAS) methods have achieved remarkable performance on specific domains or attack types, few studies have focused on the simultaneous presence of domain changes and unknown attacks, which is closer to real application scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalized-face-anti-spoofing-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixEdit: Revisiting Data Augmentation and Beyond for Grammatical Error Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixedit-revisiting-data-augmentation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to clarify how data augmentation improves GEC models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixedit-revisiting-data-augmentation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perceptual Measurements, Distances and Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perceptual-measurements-distances-and-metrics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we demonstrate the value of measuring the perceptual scale of classical (spatial frequency, orientation) and less classical physical variables (interpolation between textures) by embedding it in recent probabilistic modeling of perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perceptual-measurements-distances-and-metrics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PREM: A Simple Yet Effective Approach for Node-Level Graph Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prem-a-simple-yet-effective-approach-for-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comprising two modules - a pre-processing module and an ego-neighbor matching module - PREM eliminates the necessity for message-passing propagation during training, and employs a simple contrastive loss, leading to considerable reductions in training time and memory usage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prem-a-simple-yet-effective-approach-for-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Pronouns: Interpretability Informs Gender Bias Mitigation for Fairer Instruction-Tuned Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tale-of-pronouns-interpretability-informs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In MT, this might lead to misgendered translations, resulting, among other harms, in the perpetuation of stereotypes and prejudices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tale-of-pronouns-interpretability-informs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Transferable Adversarial Image Examples: Attack Categorization, Evaluation Guidelines, and New Insights</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-transferable-adversarial-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transferable adversarial examples raise critical security concerns in real-world, black-box attack scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-transferable-adversarial-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can bin-wise scaling improve consistency and adaptivity of prediction uncertainty for machine learning regression ?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-bin-wise-scaling-improve-consistency-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Binwise Variance Scaling (BVS) has recently been proposed as a post hoc recalibration method for prediction uncertainties of machine learning regression problems that is able of more efficient corrections than uniform variance (or temperature) scaling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-bin-wise-scaling-improve-consistency-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Evaluation of Large Language Models on Legal Judgment Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-evaluation-of-large-language-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated great potential for domain-specific applications, such as the law domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-evaluation-of-large-language-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Contrastive Learning for Entity Typing over Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-contrastive-learning-for-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge graph entity typing (KGET) aims at inferring plausible types of entities in knowledge graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-contrastive-learning-for-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Scale Decomposition MLP-Mixer for Time Series Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-scale-decomposition-mlp-mixer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series data, often characterized by unique composition and complex multi-scale temporal variations, requires special consideration of decomposition and multi-scale modeling in its analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-scale-decomposition-mlp-mixer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfoDiffusion: Information Entropy Aware Diffusion Process for Non-Autoregressive Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infodiffusion-information-entropy-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have garnered considerable interest in the field of text generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infodiffusion-information-entropy-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating semantic subspaces of Transformer sentence embeddings through linear structural probing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-semantic-subspaces-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The question of what kinds of linguistic information are encoded in different layers of Transformer-based language models is of considerable interest for the NLP community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-semantic-subspaces-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Bootstrapping for Uncertainty Quantification in Imaging Inverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-bootstrapping-for-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientific imaging problems are often severely ill-posed, and hence have significant intrinsic uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-bootstrapping-for-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recasting Continual Learning as Sequence Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recasting-continual-learning-as-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[That is, we propose to formulate continual learning as a sequence modeling problem, allowing advanced sequence models to be utilized for continual learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recasting-continual-learning-as-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold: A Global and Local-aware Denoising Framework for Commonsense Knowledge Graph Noise Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gold-a-global-and-local-aware-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Commonsense Knowledge Graphs (CSKGs) are crucial for commonsense reasoning, yet constructing them through human annotations can be costly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gold-a-global-and-local-aware-denoising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Long Document Topic Segmentation Models With Enhanced Coherence Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-long-document-topic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach improves $F_{1}$ of old SOTA by 3. 42 (73. 74 -> 77. 16) and reduces $P_{k}$ by 1. 11 points (15. 0 -> 13. 89) on WIKI-727K and achieves an average reduction of 0. 83 points on $P_{k}$ on WikiSection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-long-document-topic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Siren's Song: Towards Reliable Fact-Conflicting Hallucination Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-siren-s-song-towards-reliable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs), such as ChatGPT/GPT-4, have garnered widespread attention owing to their myriad of practical applications, yet their adoption has been constrained by issues of fact-conflicting hallucinations across web platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-siren-s-song-towards-reliable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyze Mass Spectrometry data with Artificial Intelligence to assist the understanding of past habitability of Mars and provide insights for future missions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyze-mass-spectrometry-data-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an application of artificial intelligence on mass spectrometry data for detecting habitability potential of ancient Mars.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyze-mass-spectrometry-data-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerated Policy Gradient: On the Nesterov Momentum for Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerated-policy-gradient-on-the-nesterov</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demonstrate the potential of APG in achieving faster global convergence, we formally show that with the true gradient, APG with softmax policy parametrization converges to an optimal policy at a $\tilde{O}(1/t^2)$ rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerated-policy-gradient-on-the-nesterov</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take the aTrain. Introducing an Interface for the Accessible Transcription of Interviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-the-atrain-introducing-an-interface-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[If an entry-level graphics card is available, the transcription speed increases to 20% of the audio duration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-the-atrain-introducing-an-interface-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORE: A Few-Shot Company Relation Classification Dataset for Robust Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/core-a-few-shot-company-relation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the performance of state-of-the-art RC models on the CORE dataset, we conduct experiments in the few-shot domain adaptation setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/core-a-few-shot-company-relation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Dataset Cartography for Improved Compositional Generalization in Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-dataset-cartography-for-improved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks have revolutionized language modeling and excelled in various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-dataset-cartography-for-improved</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulating Users in Interactive Web Table Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-users-in-interactive-web-table</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our multi-perspective evaluation scheme reveals new insights about query strategies, the impact of modalities, and different user types in simulated WTR search sessions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-users-in-interactive-web-table</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Relevance to Utility: Evidence Retrieval with Feedback for Fact Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-relevance-to-utility-evidence-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that, rather than relevance, for FV we need to focus on the utility that a claim verifier derives from the retrieved evidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-relevance-to-utility-evidence-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Structure-guided Network for Tooth Alignment in 2D Photograph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-structure-guided-network-for-tooth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a 3D structure-guided tooth alignment network that takes 2D photographs as input (e. g., photos captured by smartphones) and aligns the teeth within the 2D image space to generate an orthodontic comparison photograph featuring aesthetically pleasing, aligned teeth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-structure-guided-network-for-tooth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balance Act: Mitigating Hubness in Cross-Modal Retrieval with Query and Gallery Banks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balance-act-mitigating-hubness-in-cross-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a post-processing solution to address the hubness problem in cross-modal retrieval, a phenomenon where a small number of gallery data points are frequently retrieved, resulting in a decline in retrieval performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balance-act-mitigating-hubness-in-cross-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KG-GPT: A General Framework for Reasoning on Knowledge Graphs Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kg-gpt-a-general-framework-for-reasoning-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While large language models (LLMs) have made considerable advancements in understanding and generating unstructured text, their application in structured data remains underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kg-gpt-a-general-framework-for-reasoning-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoMPosT: Characterizing and Evaluating Caricature in LLM Simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compost-characterizing-and-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work has aimed to capture nuances of human behavior by using LLMs to simulate responses from particular demographics in settings like social science experiments and public opinion surveys.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compost-characterizing-and-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reflection-Equivariant Diffusion for 3D Structure Determination from Isotopologue Rotational Spectra in Natural Abundance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reflection-equivariant-diffusion-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[KREED's top-1 predictions identify the correct 3D structure with >98% accuracy on the QM9 and GEOM datasets when provided with substitution coordinates of all heavy atoms with natural isotopic abundance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reflection-equivariant-diffusion-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenEval: An Object-Focused Framework for Evaluating Text-to-Image Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geneval-an-object-focused-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent breakthroughs in diffusion models, multimodal pretraining, and efficient finetuning have led to an explosion of text-to-image generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geneval-an-object-focused-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Class-incremental Learning in the Era of Large Pre-trained Models via Test-Time Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-class-incremental-learning-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, we propose "Test-Time Adaptation for Class-Incremental Learning" (TTACIL) that first fine-tunes Layer Norm parameters of the PTM on each test instance for learning task-specific features, and then resets them back to the base model to preserve stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-class-incremental-learning-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TK-KNN: A Balanced Distance-Based Pseudo Labeling Approach for Semi-Supervised Intent Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tk-knn-a-balanced-distance-based-pseudo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the present work, we describe Top-K K-Nearest Neighbor (TK-KNN), which uses a more robust pseudo-labeling approach based on distance in the embedding space while maintaining a balanced set of pseudo-labeled examples across classes through a ranking-based approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tk-knn-a-balanced-distance-based-pseudo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BasahaCorpus: An Expanded Linguistic Resource for Readability Assessment in Central Philippine Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/basahacorpus-an-expanded-linguistic-resource</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current research on automatic readability assessment (ARA) has focused on improving the performance of models in high-resource languages such as English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/basahacorpus-an-expanded-linguistic-resource</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Soups: Personalized Large Language Model Alignment via Post-hoc Parameter Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-soups-personalized-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study Reinforcement Learning from Personalized Human Feedback (RLPHF) problem, wherein LLMs are aligned to multiple (sometimes conflicting) preferences by modeling alignment as a Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning (MORL) problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-soups-personalized-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficiently Visualizing Large Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiently-visualizing-large-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Performing SPLEE to obtain a high-dimensional embedding of the large-scale graph and then using t-SGNE to reduce its dimension for visualization, we are able to visualize graphs with up to 300K nodes and 1M edges within 5 minutes and achieve approximately 10% improvement in visualization quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiently-visualizing-large-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Generic Semi-Supervised Framework for Volumetric Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-generic-semi-supervised-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, there is growing interest in using semi-supervised learning (SSL) techniques to train models with limited labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-generic-semi-supervised-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Pairwise Encodings for Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-pairwise-encodings-for-link</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, a new class of methods has emerged that combines the advantages of message-passing neural networks (MPNN) and heuristics methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-pairwise-encodings-for-link</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study of Translation Hypothesis Ensembling with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-translation-hypothesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are becoming a one-fits-many solution, but they sometimes hallucinate or produce unreliable output.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-translation-hypothesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse-DySta: Sparsity-Aware Dynamic and Static Scheduling for Sparse Multi-DNN Workloads</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-dysta-sparsity-aware-dynamic-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Running multiple deep neural networks (DNNs) in parallel has become an emerging workload in both edge devices, such as mobile phones where multiple tasks serve a single user for daily activities, and data centers, where various requests are raised from millions of users, as seen with large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-dysta-sparsity-aware-dynamic-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMTLab: An Open-Source Platform for Building, Evaluating, and Diagnosing Interactive Machine Translation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imtlab-an-open-source-platform-for-building</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present IMTLab, an open-source end-to-end interactive machine translation (IMT) system platform that enables researchers to quickly build IMT systems with state-of-the-art models, perform an end-to-end evaluation, and diagnose the weakness of systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imtlab-an-open-source-platform-for-building</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A voxel-level approach to brain age prediction: A method to assess regional brain aging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-voxel-level-approach-to-brain-age</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Brain aging is a regional phenomenon, a facet that remains relatively under-explored within the realm of brain age prediction research using machine learning methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-voxel-level-approach-to-brain-age</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QADYNAMICS: Training Dynamics-Driven Synthetic QA Diagnostic for Zero-Shot Commonsense Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qadynamics-training-dynamics-driven-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zero-shot commonsense Question-Answering (QA) requires models to reason about general situations beyond specific benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qadynamics-training-dynamics-driven-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instilling Inductive Biases with Subnetworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instilling-inductive-biases-with-subnetworks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method discovers a functional subnetwork that implements a particular subtask within a trained model and uses it to instill inductive biases towards solutions utilizing that subtask.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instilling-inductive-biases-with-subnetworks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probing the Creativity of Large Language Models: Can models produce divergent semantic association?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-the-creativity-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models possess remarkable capacity for processing language, but it remains unclear whether these models can further generate creative content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-the-creativity-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
