<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 21:07:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models as Corporate Lobbyists</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-as-corporate-lobbyists</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the bills the model deems as relevant, the model drafts a letter to the sponsor of the bill in an attempt to persuade the congressperson to make changes to the proposed legislation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-as-corporate-lobbyists</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invalidator: Automated Patch Correctness Assessment via Semantic and Syntactic Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invalidator-automated-patch-correctness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel technique, namely INVALIDATOR, to automatically assess the correctness of APR-generated patches via semantic and syntactic reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invalidator-automated-patch-correctness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross Modal Transformer via Coordinates Encoding for 3D Object Dectection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-transformer-via-coordinates</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a robust 3D detector, named Cross Modal Transformer (CMT), for end-to-end 3D multi-modal detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-transformer-via-coordinates</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computing the Performance of A New Adaptive Sampling Algorithm Based on The Gittins Index in Experiments with Exponential Rewards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computing-the-performance-of-a-new-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing experiments often requires balancing between learning about the true treatment effects and earning from allocating more samples to the superior treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computing-the-performance-of-a-new-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xDeepInt: a hybrid architecture for modeling the vector-wise and bit-wise feature interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xdeepint-a-hybrid-architecture-for-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new model, xDeepInt, based on a novel network architecture called polynomial interaction network (PIN) which learns higher-order vector-wise interactions recursively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xdeepint-a-hybrid-architecture-for-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vocabulary-informed Zero-shot and Open-set Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vocabulary-informed-zero-shot-and-open-set</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant progress in object categorization, in recent years, a number of important challenges remain; mainly, the ability to learn from limited labeled data and to recognize object classes within large, potentially open, set of labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vocabulary-informed-zero-shot-and-open-set</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Image Segmentation via Cascaded Attention Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-image-segmentation-via-cascaded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel attention-based decoder, namely CASCaded Attention DEcoder (CASCADE), which leverages the multiscale features of hierarchical vision transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-image-segmentation-via-cascaded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Mobile Block for Efficient Neural Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-mobile-block-for-efficient-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper focuses on designing efficient models with low parameters and FLOPs for dense predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-mobile-block-for-efficient-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Complex Dynamical Systems via Nonconvex Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-complex-dynamical-systems-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cataloging the complex behaviors of dynamical systems can be challenging, even when they are well-described by a simple mechanistic model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-complex-dynamical-systems-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average Is Not Enough: Caveats of Multilingual Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/average-is-not-enough-caveats-of-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This position paper discusses the problem of multilingual evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/average-is-not-enough-caveats-of-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Imbalanced Semantic Segmentation Through Neural Collapse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-imbalanced-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our empirical and theoretical analysis, we point out that semantic segmentation naturally brings contextual correlation and imbalanced distribution among classes, which breaks the equiangular and maximally separated structure of neural collapse for both feature centers and classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-imbalanced-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGTAB: A Multi-Relational Graph-Based Twitter Account Detection Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgtab-a-multi-relational-graph-based-twitter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in addition to low annotation quality, existing benchmarks generally have incomplete user relationships, suppressing graph-based account detection research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgtab-a-multi-relational-graph-based-twitter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinyMIM: An Empirical Study of Distilling MIM Pre-trained Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinymim-an-empirical-study-of-distilling-mim</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our TinyMIM model of tiny size achieves 79. 6% top-1 accuracy on ImageNet-1K image classification, which sets a new record for small vision models of the same size and computation budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinymim-an-empirical-study-of-distilling-mim</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Further Improving Weakly-supervised Object Localization via Causal Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/further-improving-weakly-supervised-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly-supervised object localization aims to indicate the category as well as the scope of an object in an image given only the image-level labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/further-improving-weakly-supervised-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PMT-IQA: Progressive Multi-task Learning for Blind Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pmt-iqa-progressive-multi-task-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To verify the effectiveness of the proposed PMT-IQA model, we conduct experiments on four widely used public datasets, and the experimental results indicate that the performance of PMT-IQA is superior to the comparison approaches, and both MS and PMT modules improve the model's performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pmt-iqa-progressive-multi-task-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RELIANT: Fair Knowledge Distillation for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliant-fair-knowledge-distillation-for-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Distillation (KD) is a common solution to compress GNNs, where a light-weighted model (i. e., the student model) is encouraged to mimic the behavior of a computationally expensive GNN (i. e., the teacher GNN model).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliant-fair-knowledge-distillation-for-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PanopticPartFormer++: A Unified and Decoupled View for Panoptic Part Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panopticpartformer-a-unified-and-decoupled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thirdly, inspired by Mask2Former, based on our meta-architecture, we propose Panoptic-PartFormer++ and design a new part-whole cross attention scheme to further boost part segmentation qualities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panopticpartformer-a-unified-and-decoupled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Acoustic Embeddings And Their Transferability Across Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-acoustic-embeddings-and-their</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In speech recognition, it is essential to model the phonetic content of the input signal while discarding irrelevant factors such as speaker variations and noise, which is challenging in low-resource settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-acoustic-embeddings-and-their</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correlation Loss: Enforcing Correlation between Classification and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-loss-enforcing-correlation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(ii) Motivated by our observations, e. g., that NMS-free detectors can also benefit from correlation, we propose Correlation Loss, a novel plug-in loss function that improves the performance of various object detectors by directly optimizing correlation coefficients: E. g., Correlation Loss on Sparse R-CNN, an NMS-free method, yields 1. 6 AP gain on COCO and 1. 8 AP gain on Cityscapes dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-loss-enforcing-correlation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OccluMix: Towards De-Occlusion Virtual Try-on by Semantically-Guided Mixup</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occlumix-towards-de-occlusion-virtual-try-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image Virtual try-on aims at replacing the cloth on a personal image with a garment image (in-shop clothes), which has attracted increasing attention from the multimedia and computer vision communities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occlumix-towards-de-occlusion-virtual-try-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backdoor Attacks Against Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backdoor-attacks-against-dataset-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A model trained on this smaller distilled dataset can attain comparable performance to a model trained on the original training dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backdoor-attacks-against-dataset-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cluster-guided Contrastive Graph Clustering Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-guided-contrastive-graph-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, guided by the high-confidence clustering information, we carefully select and construct the positive samples from the same high-confidence cluster in two views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-guided-contrastive-graph-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUD: An Expert-Annotated Legal NLP Dataset for Merger Agreement Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maud-an-expert-annotated-legal-nlp-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reading comprehension of legal text can be a particularly challenging task due to the length and complexity of legal clauses and a shortage of expert-annotated datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maud-an-expert-annotated-legal-nlp-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Follow the Timeline! Generating Abstractive and Extractive Timeline Summary in Chronological Order</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/follow-the-timeline-generating-abstractive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nowadays, time-stamped web documents related to a general news query floods spread throughout the Internet, and timeline summarization targets concisely summarizing the evolution trajectory of events along the timeline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/follow-the-timeline-generating-abstractive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConvNeXt V2: Co-designing and Scaling ConvNets with Masked Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convnext-v2-co-designing-and-scaling-convnets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This co-design of self-supervised learning techniques and architectural improvement results in a new model family called ConvNeXt V2, which significantly improves the performance of pure ConvNets on various recognition benchmarks, including ImageNet classification, COCO detection, and ADE20K segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convnext-v2-co-designing-and-scaling-convnets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task-specific Scene Structure Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-specific-scene-structure-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the informative structures of scenes is essential for low-level vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-specific-scene-structure-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysing Discrete Self Supervised Speech Representation for Spoken Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysing-discrete-self-supervised-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Following the findings of such an analysis, we propose practical improvements to the discrete unit for the GSLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysing-discrete-self-supervised-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Maximize Mutual Information for Dynamic Feature Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-maximize-mutual-information-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Feature selection helps reduce data acquisition costs in ML, but the standard approach is to train models with static feature subsets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-maximize-mutual-information-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tsetlin Machine Embedding: Representing Words Using Logical Expressions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsetlin-machine-embedding-representing-words</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also visualize word clusters in vector space, demonstrating how our logical embedding co-locate similar words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsetlin-machine-embedding-representing-words</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRT2: Inductive Linking and Ranking in Knowledge Graphs of Varying Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irt2-inductive-linking-and-ranking-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our focus is on inductive link prediction models as a basis for practical tools that support knowledge engineers with exploring text collections and discovering and linking new (so-called open-world) entities to the knowledge graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irt2-inductive-linking-and-ranking-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OF-AE: Oblique Forest AutoEncoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/of-ae-oblique-forest-autoencoders</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the present work we propose an unsupervised ensemble method consisting of oblique trees that can address the task of auto-encoding, namely Oblique Forest AutoEncoders (briefly OF-AE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/of-ae-oblique-forest-autoencoders</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PCRLv2: A Unified Visual Information Preservation Framework for Self-supervised Pre-training in Medical Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcrlv2-a-unified-visual-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in self-supervised learning (SSL) in computer vision are primarily comparative, whose goal is to preserve invariant and discriminative semantics in latent representations by comparing siamese image views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcrlv2-a-unified-visual-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Driven Optimization of Directed Information over Discrete Alphabets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-optimization-of-directed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Directed information (DI) is a fundamental measure for the study and analysis of sequential stochastic models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-optimization-of-directed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Undesirable Dependence on Frequency of Gender Bias Metrics Based on Word Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-undesirable-dependence-on-frequency-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we study the effect of frequency when measuring female vs. male gender bias with word embedding-based bias quantification methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-undesirable-dependence-on-frequency-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Credible Remote Sensing Scene Classification Using Evidential Fusion on Aerial-Ground Dual-view Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/credible-remote-sensing-scene-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this uncertainty, a novel decision-level fusion strategy is proposed to ensure that the view with lower risk obtains more weight, making the classification more credible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/credible-remote-sensing-scene-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argoverse 2: Next Generation Datasets for Self-Driving Perception and Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/argoverse-2-next-generation-datasets-for-self-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Models are tasked with the prediction of future motion for "scored actors" in each scenario and are provided with track histories that capture object location, heading, velocity, and category.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/argoverse-2-next-generation-datasets-for-self-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep reinforcement learning for irrigation scheduling using high-dimensional sensor feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-reinforcement-learning-for-irrigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results were compared against the benchmark profits obtained using irrigation schedules optimised individually for each of the considered years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-reinforcement-learning-for-irrigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Probabilistic Models for Scene-Scale 3D Categorical Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-probabilistic-models-for-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, our work is the first to apply discrete and latent diffusion for 3D categorical data on a scene-scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-probabilistic-models-for-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusing Models for Prognostics and Health Management of Lithium-Ion Batteries Based on Physics-Informed Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusing-models-for-prognostics-and-health</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Physics-Informed Neural Network (PINN) is an efficient tool to fuse empirical or physical dynamic models with data-driven models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusing-models-for-prognostics-and-health</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P3DC-Shot: Prior-Driven Discrete Data Calibration for Nearest-Neighbor Few-Shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p3dc-shot-prior-driven-discrete-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the distribution calibration technique which utilizes the distribution or statistics of the base classes to calibrate the data for few-shot tasks, we propose a novel discrete data calibration operation which is more suitable for NN-based few-shot classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p3dc-shot-prior-driven-discrete-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-Driven Universal Model for Organ Segmentation and Tumor Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-driven-universal-model-for-organ</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model is developed from an assembly of 14 datasets with 3, 410 CT scans and evaluated on 6, 162 external CT scans from 3 datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-driven-universal-model-for-organ</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamically Modular and Sparse General Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamically-modular-and-sparse-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-world applications often require learning continuously from a stream of data under ever-changing conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamically-modular-and-sparse-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Invariance from Generated Variance for Unsupervised Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-invariance-from-generated-variance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work focuses on unsupervised representation learning in person re-identification (ReID).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-invariance-from-generated-variance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EmoGator: A New Open Source Vocal Burst Dataset with Baseline Machine Learning Classification Methodologies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emogator-a-new-open-source-vocal-burst</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vocal Bursts -- short, non-speech vocalizations that convey emotions, such as laughter, cries, sighs, moans, and groans -- are an often-overlooked aspect of speech emotion recognition, but an important aspect of human vocal communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emogator-a-new-open-source-vocal-burst</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Image Inpainting by Stripe Window Transformer with Joint Attention to CNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-image-inpainting-by-stripe-window</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image inpainting is an important task in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-image-inpainting-by-stripe-window</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game of Intelligent Life</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/game-of-intelligent-life</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This new branch of CA is called neural cellular automata [1].]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/game-of-intelligent-life</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Adaptive Kernel Approach to Federated Learning of Heterogeneous Causal Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-kernel-approach-to-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new causal inference framework to learn causal effects from multiple, decentralized data sources in a federated setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-kernel-approach-to-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTNeuro: A Benchmark for Evaluating Representations of Brain Structure Across Multiple Levels of Abstraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtneuro-a-benchmark-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce a new dataset, annotations, and multiple downstream tasks that provide diverse ways to readout information about brain structure and architecture from the same image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtneuro-a-benchmark-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EvidenceCap: Towards trustworthy medical image segmentation via evidential identity cap</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evidencecap-towards-trustworthy-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image segmentation (MIS) is essential for supporting disease diagnosis and treatment effect assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evidencecap-towards-trustworthy-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skew Class-balanced Re-weighting for Unbiased Scene Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skew-class-balanced-re-weighting-for-unbiased</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An unbiased scene graph generation (SGG) algorithm referred to as Skew Class-balanced Re-weighting (SCR) is proposed for considering the unbiased predicate prediction caused by the long-tailed distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skew-class-balanced-re-weighting-for-unbiased</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
