<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 21:07:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Schema Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-schema-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Starting from the assumption that a large proportion of semantic content is necessarily relational, we introduce a neural language model that discovers networks of symbols (schemata) from text datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-schema-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mining Discriminative Food Regions for Accurate Food Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-discriminative-food-regions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Taking inspiration from Adversarial Erasing, a strategy that progressively discovers discriminative object regions for weakly supervised semantic segmentation, we propose a novel network architecture in which a primary network maintains the base accuracy of classifying an input image, an auxiliary network adversarially mines discriminative food regions, and a region network classifies the resulting mined regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-discriminative-food-regions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Implicit Dictionary via Mixture-of-Expert Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-implicit-dictionary-via-mixture-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a generic INR framework that achieves both data and training efficiency by learning a Neural Implicit Dictionary (NID) from a data collection and representing INR as a functional combination of basis sampled from the dictionary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-implicit-dictionary-via-mixture-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning High-quality Proposals for Acne Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-high-quality-proposals-for-acne</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Acne detection is crucial for interpretative diagnosis and precise treatment of skin disease.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-high-quality-proposals-for-acne</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Efficiency Study for SPLADE Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficiency-study-for-splade-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SPLADE efficiency can be controlled via a regularization factor, but solely controlling this regularization has been shown to not be efficient enough.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficiency-study-for-splade-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crake: Causal-Enhanced Table-Filler for Question Answering over Large Scale Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crake-causal-enhanced-table-filler-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic parsing solves knowledge base (KB) question answering (KBQA) by composing a KB query, which generally involves node extraction (NE) and graph composition (GC) to detect and connect related nodes in a query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crake-causal-enhanced-table-filler-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning for Anomaly Detection in Log Data: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-anomaly-detection-in-log</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic log file analysis enables early detection of relevant incidents such as system failures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-anomaly-detection-in-log</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ControlBurn: Nonlinear Feature Selection with Sparse Tree Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlburn-nonlinear-feature-selection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ControlBurn is a Python package to construct feature-sparse tree ensembles that support nonlinear feature selection and interpretable machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlburn-nonlinear-feature-selection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Non-isotropic Probabilistic Take on Proxy-based Deep Metric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-non-isotropic-probabilistic-take-on-proxy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We model images as directional von Mises-Fisher (vMF) distributions on the hypersphere that can reflect image-intrinsic uncertainties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-non-isotropic-probabilistic-take-on-proxy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Harvard USPTO Patent Dataset: A Large-Scale, Well-Structured, and Multi-Purpose Corpus of Patent Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-harvard-uspto-patent-dataset-a-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Innovation is a major driver of economic and social development, and information about many kinds of innovation is embedded in semi-structured data from patents and patent applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-harvard-uspto-patent-dataset-a-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperTickets: Drawing Task-Agnostic Lottery Tickets from Supernets via Jointly Architecture Searching and Parameter Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supertickets-drawing-task-agnostic-lottery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we discover for the first time that both efficient DNNs and their lottery subnetworks (i. e., lottery tickets) can be directly identified from a supernet, which we term as SuperTickets, via a two-in-one training scheme with jointly architecture searching and parameter pruning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supertickets-drawing-task-agnostic-lottery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalization-Memorization Machines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalization-memorization-machines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under this mechanism, error-based learning machines improve their memorization abilities of training data without over-fitting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalization-memorization-machines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Dialog as Conversation about Objects Living in Space-Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-dialog-as-conversation-about-objects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these challenges we present a new object-centric framework for video dialog that supports neural reasoning dubbed COST - which stands for Conversation about Objects in Space-Time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-dialog-as-conversation-about-objects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforced Lin-Kernighan-Helsgaun Algorithms for the Traveling Salesman Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforced-lin-kernighan-helsgaun-algorithms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Lin-Kernighan-Helsgaun (LKH) algorithm is one of the state-of-the-art local search algorithms for the TSP, and LKH-3 is a powerful extension of LKH that can solve many TSP variants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforced-lin-kernighan-helsgaun-algorithms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SETSum: Summarization and Visualization of Student Evaluations of Teaching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/setsum-summarization-and-visualization-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ten university professors from diverse departments serve as evaluators of the system and all agree that SETSum helps them interpret SET results more efficiently; and 6 out of 10 instructors prefer our system over the standard static PDF report (while the remaining 4 would like to have both).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/setsum-summarization-and-visualization-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-free Online Change-point Detection: A Novel Neural Network Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-free-online-change-point-detection-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that ALACPD, on average, ranks first among state-of-the-art CPD algorithms in terms of quality of the time series segmentation, and it is on par with the best performer in terms of the accuracy of the estimated change-points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-free-online-change-point-detection-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bounding Box Disparity: 3D Metrics for Object Detection With Full Degree of Freedom</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bounding-box-disparity-3d-metrics-for-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The most popular evaluation metric for object detection in 2D images is Intersection over Union (IoU).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bounding-box-disparity-3d-metrics-for-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Sequential Descriptors for Sequence-based Visual Place Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-sequential-descriptors-for-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In robotics, Visual Place Recognition is a continuous process that receives as input a video stream to produce a hypothesis of the robot's current position within a map of known places.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-sequential-descriptors-for-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TGRMPT: A Head-Shoulder Aided Multi-Person Tracker and a New Large-Scale Dataset for Tour-Guide Robot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tgrmpt-a-head-shoulder-aided-multi-person</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A service robot serving safely and politely needs to track the surrounding people robustly, especially for Tour-Guide Robot (TGR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tgrmpt-a-head-shoulder-aided-multi-person</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reproducing sensory induced hallucinations via neural fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducing-sensory-induced-hallucinations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we focus on pattern formation in the visual cortex when the cortical activity is driven by a geometric visual hallucination-like stimulus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducing-sensory-induced-hallucinations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detection of Furigana Text in Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-of-furigana-text-in-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This project focuses on detecting furigana in Japanese books and comics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-of-furigana-text-in-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>k-means Mask Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-means-mask-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we observe that most existing transformer-based vision models simply borrow the idea from NLP, neglecting the crucial difference between languages and images, particularly the extremely large sequence length of spatially flattened pixel features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-means-mask-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-tasking Model of Speaker-Keyword Classification for Keeping Human in the Loop of Drone-assisted Inspection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-tasking-model-of-speaker-keyword</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A base model for a group of five authorized subjects is trained and tested on the inspection keyword dataset collected by this study.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-tasking-model-of-speaker-keyword</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Inference of overparameterized Bayesian Neural Networks: a theoretical and empirical study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-inference-of-overparameterized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the Variational Inference (VI) used for training Bayesian Neural Networks (BNN) in the overparameterized regime, i. e., when the number of neurons tends to infinity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-inference-of-overparameterized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GT4SD: Generative Toolkit for Scientific Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gt4sd-generative-toolkit-for-scientific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the growing availability of data within various scientific domains, generative models hold enormous potential to accelerate scientific discovery at every step of the scientific method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gt4sd-generative-toolkit-for-scientific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Pretraining Objectives for Tabular Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-pretraining-objectives-for-tabular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent deep learning models for tabular data currently compete with the traditional ML models based on decision trees (GBDT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-pretraining-objectives-for-tabular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A unified interpretable intelligent learning diagnosis framework for smart education</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-interpretable-intelligent-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intelligent learning diagnosis is a critical engine of smart education, which aims to estimate learners' current knowledge mastery status and predict their future learning performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-interpretable-intelligent-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do We Really Need Inertia?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-we-really-need-inertia</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emphasis on inertia for system stability has been a long-held tradition in conventional grids.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-we-really-need-inertia</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large Scale Search Dataset for Unbiased Learning to Rank</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-search-dataset-for-unbiased</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The unbiased learning to rank (ULTR) problem has been greatly advanced by recent deep learning techniques and well-designed debias algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-search-dataset-for-unbiased</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Stein critics with staged $L^2$-regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-stein-critics-with-staged-l-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Theoretically, we relate the training dynamic with large regularization weight to the kernel regression optimization of "lazy training" regime in early training times.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-stein-critics-with-staged-l-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One for All: Simultaneous Metric and Preference Learning over Multiple Users</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-for-all-simultaneous-metric-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates simultaneous preference and metric learning from a crowd of respondents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-for-all-simultaneous-metric-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpansionNet: exploring the sequence length bottleneck in the Transformer for Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expansionnet-exploring-the-sequence-length</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most recent state of art architectures rely on combinations and variations of three approaches: convolutional, recurrent and self-attentive methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expansionnet-exploring-the-sequence-length</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ACII 2022 Affective Vocal Bursts Workshop &amp; Competition: Understanding a critically understudied modality of emotional expression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-acii-2022-affective-vocal-bursts-workshop</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ACII Affective Vocal Bursts Workshop & Competition is focused on understanding multiple affective dimensions of vocal bursts: laughs, gasps, cries, screams, and many other non-linguistic vocalizations central to the expression of emotion and to human communication more generally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-acii-2022-affective-vocal-bursts-workshop</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VeriDark: A Large-Scale Benchmark for Authorship Verification on the Dark Web</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/veridark-a-large-scale-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The DarkWeb represents a hotbed for illicit activity, where users communicate on different market forums in order to exchange goods and services.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/veridark-a-large-scale-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TFCNs: A CNN-Transformer Hybrid Network for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tfcns-a-cnn-transformer-hybrid-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image segmentation is one of the most fundamental tasks concerning medical information analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tfcns-a-cnn-transformer-hybrid-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Rotation Correction without Angle Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-rotation-correction-without-angle-prior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new and practical task, named Rotation Correction, to automatically correct the tilt with high content fidelity in the condition that the rotated angle is unknown.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-rotation-correction-without-angle-prior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The DynaSig-ML Python package: automated learning of biomolecular dynamics-function relationships</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dynasig-ml-python-package-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Summary: The DynaSig-ML (Dynamical Signatures - Machine Learning) Python package allows the efficient, user-friendly exploration of 3D dynamics-function relationships in biomolecules, using datasets of experimental measures from large numbers of sequence variants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dynasig-ml-python-package-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Learning from Spatio-Temporal Mixed Skeleton Sequences for Self-Supervised Skeleton-Based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-from-spatio-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, SkeleMix utilizes the topological information of skeleton data to mix two skeleton sequences by randomly combing the cropped skeleton fragments (the trimmed view) with the remaining skeleton sequences (the truncated view).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-from-spatio-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Stream Transformer for Generic Event Boundary Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-stream-transformer-for-generic-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes our champion solution for the CVPR2022 Generic Event Boundary Captioning (GEBC) competition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-stream-transformer-for-generic-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic optimal well control in subsurface reservoirs using reinforcement learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-optimal-well-control-in-subsurface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this problem, the system is partially observed since the data is only available at well locations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-optimal-well-control-in-subsurface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring Structural Parameters of Low-Surface-Brightness-Galaxies with Uncertainty Quantification using Bayesian Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-structural-parameters-of-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Measuring the structural parameters (size, total brightness, light concentration, etc.)]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-structural-parameters-of-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust optimal well control using an adaptive multi-grid reinforcement learning framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-optimal-well-control-using-an-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RL control policies are initially learned using computationally efficient low fidelity simulations using coarse grid discretization of the underlying partial differential equations (PDEs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-optimal-well-control-using-an-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SC2EGSet: StarCraft II Esport Replay and Game-state Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sc2egset-starcraft-ii-esport-replay-and-game</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on initial investigation of available StarCraft II datasets, we observed that our dataset is the largest publicly available source of StarCraft II esports data upon its publication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sc2egset-starcraft-ii-esport-replay-and-game</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Gap between Object and Image-level Representations for Open-Vocabulary Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-object-and-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two popular forms of weak-supervision used in open-vocabulary detection (OVD) include pretrained CLIP model and image-level supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-object-and-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCTS with Refinement for Proposals Selection Games in Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcts-with-refinement-for-proposals-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also introduce a novel differentiable method for rendering the polygonal shapes of these proposals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcts-with-refinement-for-proposals-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HierarchicalForecast: A Python Benchmarking Framework for Hierarchical Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchicalforecast-a-python-benchmarking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large collections of time series data are commonly organized into cross-sectional structures with different levels of aggregation; examples include product and geographical groupings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchicalforecast-a-python-benchmarking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Stream Computer-Generated Image Detection Network Based On Channel Joint And Softpool</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-stream-computer-generated-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed network architecture includes a residual module for extracting image noise information and a joint channel information extraction module for capturing the shallow semantic information of image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-stream-computer-generated-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D2HNet: Joint Denoising and Deblurring with Hierarchical Network for Robust Night Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d2hnet-joint-denoising-and-deblurring-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Night imaging with modern smartphone cameras is troublesome due to low photon count and unavoidable noise in the imaging system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d2hnet-joint-denoising-and-deblurring-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Additive Instance-Wise Approach to Multi-class Model Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-additive-instance-wise-approach-to-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interpretable machine learning offers insights into what factors drive a certain prediction of a black-box system and whether to trust it for high-stakes decisions or large-scale deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-additive-instance-wise-approach-to-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BibleTTS: a large, high-fidelity, multilingual, and uniquely African speech corpus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bibletts-a-large-high-fidelity-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BibleTTS is a large, high-quality, open speech dataset for ten languages spoken in Sub-Saharan Africa.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bibletts-a-large-high-fidelity-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
