<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 09:10:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>TencentLLMEval: A Hierarchical Evaluation of Real-World Capabilities for Human-Aligned LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tencentllmeval-a-hierarchical-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We construct a hierarchical task tree encompassing 7 major areas covering over 200 categories and over 800 tasks, which covers diverse capabilities such as question answering, reasoning, multiturn dialogue, and text generation, to evaluate LLMs in a comprehensive and in-depth manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tencentllmeval-a-hierarchical-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Aware Bayes' Rule and Its Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-bayes-rule-and-its</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Philosophically, the key is to balance the relative importance of prior and data distributions when calculating posterior distributions: if prior (resp.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-bayes-rule-and-its</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Large Language Models in Medicine: Progress, Application, and Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-large-language-models-in-medicine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, the application of LLMs in medicine to assist physicians and patient care emerges as a promising research direction in both artificial intelligence and clinical medicine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-large-language-models-in-medicine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3DStyle-Diffusion: Pursuing Fine-grained Text-driven 3D Stylization with 2D Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dstyle-diffusion-pursuing-fine-grained-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new 3DStyle-Diffusion model that triggers fine-grained stylization of 3D meshes with additional controllable appearance and geometric guidance from 2D Diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dstyle-diffusion-pursuing-fine-grained-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynFacePAD 2023: Competition on Face Presentation Attack Detection Based on Privacy-aware Synthetic Training Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synfacepad-2023-competition-on-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a summary of the Competition on Face Presentation Attack Detection Based on Privacy-aware Synthetic Training Data (SynFacePAD 2023) held at the 2023 International Joint Conference on Biometrics (IJCB 2023).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synfacepad-2023-competition-on-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Performance Transformers for Table Structure Recognition Need Early Convolutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-performance-transformers-for-table</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This allows it to "see" an appropriate portion of the table and "store" the complex table structure within sufficient context length for the subsequent transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-performance-transformers-for-table</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Coefficient Makes SVRG Effective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-coefficient-makes-svrg-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stochastic Variance Reduced Gradient (SVRG), introduced by Johnson & Zhang (2013), is a theoretically compelling optimization method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-coefficient-makes-svrg-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Parallelization Layouts for Large-Scale Distributed Model Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-parallelization-layouts-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we conduct a comprehensive ablation study of possible training configurations for large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-parallelization-layouts-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>meta4: semantically-aligned generation of metaphoric gestures using self-supervised text and speech representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta4-semantically-aligned-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach is the first method for generating speech driven metaphoric gestures while leveraging the potential of Image Schemas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta4-semantically-aligned-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Task-Specific Graph Network Simulators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-task-specific-graph-network-simulators</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Movement primitives further allow us to accommodate various types of context data, as demonstrated through the utilization of point clouds during inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-task-specific-graph-network-simulators</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Ensembling and Meta-Learning Improve Outlier Detection in Randomized Controlled Trials?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-ensembling-and-meta-learning-improve</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We began by empirically evaluating 6 modern machine learning-based outlier detection algorithms on the task of identifying irregular data in 838 datasets from 7 real-world MCRCTs with a total of 77, 001 patients from over 44 countries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-ensembling-and-meta-learning-improve</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mirror: A Universal Framework for Various Information Extraction Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mirror-a-universal-framework-for-various</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sharing knowledge between information extraction tasks has always been a challenge due to the diverse data formats and task variations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mirror-a-universal-framework-for-various</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accuracy of a Vision-Language Model on Challenging Medical Cases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accuracy-of-a-vision-language-model-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conclusions: GPT-4V outperformed human respondents on challenging medical cases and was able to synthesize information from both images and text, but performance deteriorated when images were added to highly informative text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accuracy-of-a-vision-language-model-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRODIGy: a PROfile-based DIalogue Generation dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prodigy-a-profile-based-dialogue-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Providing dialogue agents with a profile representation can improve their consistency and coherence, leading to better conversations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prodigy-a-profile-based-dialogue-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactually Fair Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactually-fair-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It was shown in \cite{kusner2017counterfactual} that a sufficient condition for satisfying CF is to \textbf{not} use features that are descendants of sensitive attributes in the causal graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactually-fair-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EEG-DG: A Multi-Source Domain Generalization Framework for Motor Imagery EEG Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eeg-dg-a-multi-source-domain-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel multi-source domain generalization framework called EEG-DG, which leverages multiple source domains with different statistical distributions to build generalizable models on unseen target EEG data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eeg-dg-a-multi-source-domain-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LCM-LoRA: A Universal Stable-Diffusion Acceleration Module</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lcm-lora-a-universal-stable-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Latent Consistency Models (LCMs) have achieved impressive performance in accelerating text-to-image generative tasks, producing high-quality images with minimal inference steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lcm-lora-a-universal-stable-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FigStep: Jailbreaking Large Vision-language Models via Typographic Visual Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/figstep-jailbreaking-large-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Above all, our experimental results reveal that VLMs are vulnerable to jailbreaking attacks, which highlights the necessity of novel safety alignments between visual and textual modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/figstep-jailbreaking-large-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAPID: Training-free Retrieval-based Log Anomaly Detection with PLM considering Token-level information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-training-free-retrieval-based-log</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce RAPID, a model that capitalizes on the inherent features of log data to enable anomaly detection without training delays, ensuring real-time capability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-training-free-retrieval-based-log</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear Gaussian Bounding Box Representation and Ring-Shaped Rotated Convolution for Oriented Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-gaussian-bounding-box-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, current rotation-sensitive feature extraction methods based on convolutions can only extract features under a local receptive field, which is slow in aggregating rotation-sensitive features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-gaussian-bounding-box-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly-supervised Deep Cognate Detection Framework for Low-Resourced Languages Using Morphological Knowledge of Closely-Related Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-deep-cognate-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We train an encoder to gain morphological knowledge of a language and transfer the knowledge to perform unsupervised and weakly-supervised cognate detection tasks with and without the pivot language for the closely-related languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-deep-cognate-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-modal Prompts: Adapting Large Pre-trained Models for Audio-Visual Downstream Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-prompts-adapting-large-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This mechanism leverages audio and visual modalities as soft prompts to dynamically adjust the parameters of pre-trained models based on the current multi-modal input features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-prompts-adapting-large-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conic10K: A Challenging Math Problem Understanding and Reasoning Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conic10k-a-challenging-math-problem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the dataset only involves a narrow range of knowledge, it is easy to separately analyse the knowledge a model possesses and the reasoning ability it has.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conic10k-a-challenging-math-problem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outlier-Robust Wasserstein DRO</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-robust-wasserstein-dro</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Geometric uncertainty due to sampling or localized perturbations of data points is captured by Wasserstein DRO (WDRO), which seeks to learn a model that performs uniformly well over a Wasserstein ball centered around the observed data distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-robust-wasserstein-dro</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Valuation and Detections in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-valuation-and-detections-in-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) enables collaborative model training without sharing raw data, demanding abundant, high-quality data for optimal model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-valuation-and-detections-in-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Deep Learning Method for Simultaneous Denoising and Missing Wedge Reconstruction in Cryogenic Electron Tomography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-method-for-simultaneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tomograms reconstructed with conventional methods, such as filtered back-projection, suffer from the noise, and from artifacts and anisotropic resolution due to the missing wedge of information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-method-for-simultaneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POISE: Pose Guided Human Silhouette Extraction under Occlusions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poise-pose-guided-human-silhouette-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human silhouette extraction is a fundamental task in computer vision with applications in various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poise-pose-guided-human-silhouette-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counter-Empirical Attacking based on Adversarial Reinforcement Learning for Time-Relevant Scoring System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counter-empirical-attacking-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To establish such scoring systems, several "empirical criteria" are firstly determined, followed by dedicated top-down design for each factor of the score, which usually requires enormous effort to adjust and tune the scoring function in the new application scenario.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counter-empirical-attacking-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Road with GPT-4V(ision): Early Explorations of Visual-Language Model on Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-road-with-gpt-4v-ision-early</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This has been a significant bottleneck, particularly in the development of common sense reasoning and nuanced scene understanding necessary for safe and reliable autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-road-with-gpt-4v-ision-early</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inference for Probabilistic Dependency Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-for-probabilistic-dependency-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Probabilistic dependency graphs (PDGs) are a flexible class of probabilistic graphical models, subsuming Bayesian Networks and Factor Graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-for-probabilistic-dependency-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Online Federated Learning with Multiple Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-online-federated-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning enables a group of learners (called clients) to train an MKL model on the data distributed among clients to perform online non-linear function approximation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-online-federated-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Byzantine-Tolerant Methods for Distributed Variational Inequalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/byzantine-tolerant-methods-for-distributed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robustness to Byzantine attacks is a necessity for various distributed training scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/byzantine-tolerant-methods-for-distributed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Hierarchical Spatial Transformer for Massive Point Samples in Continuous Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hierarchical-spatial-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, designing a transformer for massive spatial points is non-trivial due to several challenges, including implicit long-range and multi-scale dependency on irregular points in continuous space, a non-uniform point distribution, the potential high computational costs of calculating all-pair attention across massive points, and the risks of over-confident predictions due to varying point density.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hierarchical-spatial-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LooGLE: Can Long-Context Language Models Understand Long Contexts?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loogle-can-long-context-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present LooGLE, a Long Context Generic Language Evaluation benchmark for LLMs' long context understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loogle-can-long-context-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAMEX: Dataset-aware Mixture-of-Experts for visual understanding of mixture-of-datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/damex-dataset-aware-mixture-of-experts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Construction of a universal detector poses a crucial question: How can we most effectively train a model on a large mixture of datasets?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/damex-dataset-aware-mixture-of-experts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepLearningBrasil@LT-EDI-2023: Exploring Deep Learning Techniques for Detecting Depression in Social Media Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deeplearningbrasil-lt-edi-2023-exploring-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we delineate the strategy employed by our team, DeepLearningBrasil, which secured us the first place in the shared task DepSign-LT-EDI@RANLP-2023, achieving a 47. 0% Macro F1-Score and a notable 2. 4% advantage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deeplearningbrasil-lt-edi-2023-exploring-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAIS-DMA: A Decision-Making Assistant for Collaborative AI Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cais-dma-a-decision-making-assistant-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a new methodology to automatically support the decision-making process in CAIS when the system experiences performance degradation after a disruptive event.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cais-dma-a-decision-making-assistant-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Transfer Learning for Efficient Video-Specific Human Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-transfer-learning-for-efficient-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human Pose (HP) estimation is actively researched because of its wide range of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-transfer-learning-for-efficient-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recursion in Recursion: Two-Level Nested Recursion for Length Generalization with Scalability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recursion-in-recursion-two-level-nested</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the inner recursion, we choose Beam Tree RvNNs (BT-RvNN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recursion-in-recursion-two-level-nested</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Abstract Is Linguistic Generalization in Large Language Models? Experiments with Argument Structure</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-abstract-is-linguistic-generalization-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that LLMs perform well in generalizing the distribution of a novel noun argument between related contexts that were seen during pre-training (e. g., the active object and passive subject of the verb spray), succeeding by making use of the semantically-organized structure of the embedding space for word embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-abstract-is-linguistic-generalization-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting and predicting stochastic agent-based models of cell migration with biologically-informed neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-and-predicting-stochastic-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we describe how biologically-informed neural networks (BINNs) can be used to learn BINN-guided PDE models that are capable of accurately predicting ABM behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-and-predicting-stochastic-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discerning and Enhancing the Weighted Sum-Rate Maximization Algorithms in Communications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discerning-and-enhancing-the-weighted-sum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By probing the theoretical underpinnings linking the BCA and MM algorithmic frameworks, we reveal the direct correlations between the equivalent transformation techniques, essential to the development of WMMSE and WSR-FP, and the surrogate functions pivotal to WSR-MM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discerning-and-enhancing-the-weighted-sum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consensus-based construction of high-dimensional free energy surface</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consensus-based-construction-of-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One essential problem in quantifying the collective behaviors of molecular systems lies in the accurate construction of free energy surfaces (FESs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consensus-based-construction-of-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Silo Federated Learning Across Divergent Domains with Iterative Parameter Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-silo-federated-learning-across</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning from the collective knowledge of data dispersed across private sources can provide neural networks with enhanced generalization capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-silo-federated-learning-across</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchically Gated Recurrent Neural Network for Sequence Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchically-gated-recurrent-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have surpassed RNNs in popularity due to their superior abilities in parallel training and long-term dependency modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchically-gated-recurrent-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer learning from a sparsely annotated dataset of 3D medical images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-from-a-sparsely-annotated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A base segmentation model (3D U-Net) was trained on a large and sparsely annotated dataset; its weights were used for transfer learning on four new down-stream segmentation tasks for which a fully annotated dataset was available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-from-a-sparsely-annotated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RDGCN: Reinforced Dependency Graph Convolutional Network for Aspect-based Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdgcn-reinforced-dependency-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aspect-based sentiment analysis (ABSA) is dedicated to forecasting the sentiment polarity of aspect terms within sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdgcn-reinforced-dependency-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The PetShop Dataset -- Finding Causes of Performance Issues across Microservices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-petshop-dataset-finding-causes-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the machine learning and systems research communities have proposed various techniques to tackle this problem, there is currently a lack of standardized datasets for quantitative benchmarking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-petshop-dataset-finding-causes-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lidar Annotation Is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidar-annotation-is-all-you-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the fundamental tasks in computer vision is semantic image segmentation, which is vital for precise object delineation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidar-annotation-is-all-you-need</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Characterizing the Evolution of Embedding Space of Neural Networks using Algebraic Topology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-characterizing-the-evolution-of-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study how the topology of feature embedding space changes as it passes through the layers of a well-trained deep neural network (DNN) through Betti numbers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-characterizing-the-evolution-of-embedding</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
