<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 09:17:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoPulse: Short-Term Cryptocurrency Forecasting with Dual-Prediction and Cross-Correlated Market Indicators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cryptopulse-short-term-cryptocurrency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies fluctuate in markets with high price volatility, posing significant challenges for investors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cryptopulse-short-term-cryptocurrency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poster: Long PHP webshell files detection based on sliding window attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poster-long-php-webshell-files-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a webshell detection method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poster-long-php-webshell-files-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BatteryLife: A Comprehensive Dataset and Benchmark for Battery Life Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batterylife-a-comprehensive-dataset-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, BatteryLife is the first to release battery life datasets of zinc-ion batteries, sodium-ion batteries, and industry-tested large-capacity lithium-ion batteries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batterylife-a-comprehensive-dataset-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nexus: A Lightweight and Scalable Multi-Agent Framework for Complex Tasks Automation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nexus-a-lightweight-and-scalable-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In coding tasks, Nexus-driven MASs achieve a 99% pass rate on HumanEval and a flawless 100% on VerilogEval-Human, outperforming cutting-edge reasoning language models such as o3-mini and DeepSeek-R1.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nexus-a-lightweight-and-scalable-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Graph Tasks with Pure LLMs: A Comprehensive Benchmark and Investigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-graph-tasks-with-pure-llms-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, large language models (LLMs) have emerged as promising candidates for graph tasks, yet most studies focus primarily on performance benchmarks and fail to address their broader potential, including their ability to handle limited data, their transferability across tasks, and their robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-graph-tasks-with-pure-llms-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distill Any Depth: Distillation Creates a Stronger Monocular Depth Estimator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distill-any-depth-distillation-creates-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we systematically analyze the impact of different depth normalization strategies on pseudo-label distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distill-any-depth-distillation-creates-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Know You First and Be You Better: Modeling Human-Like User Simulators via Implicit Profiles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/know-you-first-and-be-you-better-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we adopt a diverse profile sampler to capture the distribution of real-world user profiles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/know-you-first-and-be-you-better-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AKDT: Adaptive Kernel Dilation Transformer for Effective Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/akdt-adaptive-kernel-dilation-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the core of AKDT, the NE is seamlessly integrated within standard Transformer components to form the Noise-Guided Feed-Forward Network (NG-FFN) and Noise-Guided Multi-Headed Self-Attention (NG-MSA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/akdt-adaptive-kernel-dilation-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problem Solved? Information Extraction Design Space for Layout-Rich Documents using LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/problem-solved-information-extraction-design</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper defines and explores the design space for information extraction (IE) from layout-rich documents using large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/problem-solved-information-extraction-design</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Quantification in Retrieval Augmented Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-in-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval augmented Question Answering (QA) helps QA models overcome knowledge gaps by incorporating retrieved evidence, typically a set of passages, alongside the question at test time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-in-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Multiple Large Language Models: A Survey on LLM Ensemble</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-multiple-large-language-models-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLM Ensemble -- which involves the comprehensive use of multiple large language models (LLMs), each aimed at handling user queries during downstream inference, to benefit from their individual strengths -- has gained substantial attention recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-multiple-large-language-models-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WiCkeD: A Simple Method to Make Multiple Choice Benchmarks More Challenging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wicked-a-simple-method-to-make-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of the models drops 12. 1 points on average with respect to the original versions of the datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wicked-a-simple-method-to-make-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLEAN: Generalized Category Discovery with Diverse and Quality-Enhanced LLM Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glean-generalized-category-discovery-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalized Category Discovery (GCD) is a practical and challenging open-world task that aims to recognize both known and novel categories in unlabeled data using limited labeled data from known categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glean-generalized-category-discovery-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoupled Graph Energy-based Model for Node Out-of-Distribution Detection on Heterophilic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-graph-energy-based-model-for-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite extensive research efforts focused on OOD detection on images, OOD detection on nodes in graph learning remains underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-graph-energy-based-model-for-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the convexity assumption: Realistic tabular data generation under quantifier-free real linear constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-the-convexity-assumption-realistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthetic tabular data generation has traditionally been a challenging problem due to the high complexity of the underlying distributions that characterise this type of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-the-convexity-assumption-realistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AirCast: Improving Air Pollution Forecasting Through Multi-Variable Data Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aircast-improving-air-pollution-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce AirCast, a novel multi-variable air pollution forecasting model, by combining weather and air quality variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aircast-improving-air-pollution-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Late Breaking Results: The Art of Beating the Odds with Predictor-Guided Random Design Space Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/late-breaking-results-the-art-of-beating-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces an innovative method for improving combinational digital circuits through random exploration in MIG-based synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/late-breaking-results-the-art-of-beating-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nested Expectations with Kernel Quadrature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nested-expectations-with-kernel-quadrature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper considers the challenging computational task of estimating nested expectations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nested-expectations-with-kernel-quadrature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptMID: Modal Invariant Descriptors Based on Diffusion and Vision Foundation Models for Optical-SAR Image Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptmid-modal-invariant-descriptors-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, effectively leveraging foundation models to improve the generalization of optical-SAR image matching remains challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptmid-modal-invariant-descriptors-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FwNet-ECA: Facilitating Window Attention with Global Receptive Fields through Fourier Filtering Operations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fwnet-eca-facilitating-window-attention-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Windowed attention mechanisms were introduced to mitigate the issue of excessive computation inherent in global attention mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fwnet-eca-facilitating-window-attention-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient Trajectory Prediction: Integrating Clinical Notes with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patient-trajectory-prediction-integrating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current models, primarily based on structured data, struggle to capture the complete medical context of patients, resulting in a loss of valuable information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patient-trajectory-prediction-integrating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escaping The Big Data Paradigm in Self-Supervised Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/escaping-the-big-data-paradigm-in-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce SCOTT (Sparse Convolutional Tokenizer for Transformers), a shallow tokenization architecture that is compatible with Masked Image Modeling (MIM) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/escaping-the-big-data-paradigm-in-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Consistency Models with Variational Noise Coupling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-consistency-models-with-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consistency Training (CT) has recently emerged as a promising alternative to diffusion models, achieving competitive performance in image generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-consistency-models-with-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OmniAlign-V: Towards Enhanced Alignment of MLLMs with Human Preference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnialign-v-towards-enhanced-alignment-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in open-source multi-modal large language models (MLLMs) have primarily focused on enhancing foundational capabilities, leaving a significant gap in human preference alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnialign-v-towards-enhanced-alignment-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VesselSAM: Leveraging SAM for Aortic Vessel Segmentation with LoRA and Atrous Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vesselsam-leveraging-sam-for-aortic-vessel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[VesselSAM incorporates AtrousLoRA, a novel module that combines Atrous Attention with Low-Rank Adaptation (LoRA), to improve segmentation performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vesselsam-leveraging-sam-for-aortic-vessel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LightFC-X: Lightweight Convolutional Tracker for RGB-X Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightfc-x-lightweight-convolutional-tracker</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate this problem, we propose LightFC-X, a family of lightweight convolutional RGB-X trackers that explores a unified convolutional architecture for lightweight multimodal tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightfc-x-lightweight-convolutional-tracker</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIPure: Purification in Latent Space via CLIP for Adversarially Robust Zero-Shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clipure-purification-in-latent-space-via-clip</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose two variants for our CLIPure approach: CLIPure-Diff which models the likelihood of images' latent vectors with the DiffusionPrior module in DaLLE-2 (modeling the generation process of CLIP's latent vectors), and CLIPure-Cos which models the likelihood with the cosine similarity between the embeddings of an image and ``a photo of a.''.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clipure-purification-in-latent-space-via-clip</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FFT Strikes Back: An Efficient Alternative to Self-Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-fft-strikes-back-an-efficient-alternative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional self-attention mechanisms incur quadratic complexity, limiting their scalability on long sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-fft-strikes-back-an-efficient-alternative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Brain Apoptosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-brain-apoptosis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing complexity and parameter count of Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) and Transformers pose challenges in terms of computational efficiency and resource demands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-brain-apoptosis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task Graph Maximum Likelihood Estimation for Procedural Activity Understanding in Egocentric Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-graph-maximum-likelihood-estimation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a gradient-based approach for learning task graphs from procedural activities, improving over hand-crafted methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-graph-maximum-likelihood-estimation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthia: Novel Concept Design with Affordance Composition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthia-novel-concept-design-with-affordance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image (T2I) models enable rapid concept design, making them widely used in AI-driven design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthia-novel-concept-design-with-affordance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViDoRAG: Visual Document Retrieval-Augmented Generation via Dynamic Iterative Reasoning Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vidorag-visual-document-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce ViDoSeek, a novel dataset designed to evaluate RAG performance on visually rich documents requiring complex reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vidorag-visual-document-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Offensive Memes with Social Biases in Singapore Context Using Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-offensive-memes-with-social-biases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional online content moderation systems struggle to classify modern multimodal means of communication, such as memes, a highly nuanced and information-dense medium.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-offensive-memes-with-social-biases</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Network Graph Similarity Computation Based on Graph Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-graph-similarity-computation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By merging the node sequences of graph pairs into a single large graph, our method leverages a global attention mechanism to facilitate interaction computations and to harvest cross-graph insights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-graph-similarity-computation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Structure-Supporting Dependencies via Keypoint Interactive Transformer for General Mammal Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-structure-supporting-dependencies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a Keypoint Interactive Transformer (KIT) to learn instance-level structure-supporting dependencies for general mammal pose estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-structure-supporting-dependencies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Multimodal LLMs Perform Time Series Anomaly Detection?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-multimodal-llms-perform-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Starting with the univariate case (point- and range-wise anomalies), we extend our evaluation to more practical scenarios, including multivariate and irregular time series scenarios, and variate-wise anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-multimodal-llms-perform-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIR: Complex Instruction Generation via Automatic Iterative Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/air-complex-instruction-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the development of large language models, their ability to follow simple instructions has significantly improved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/air-complex-instruction-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Key Factors for Distilling Chain-of-Thought Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-key-factors-for-distilling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) excel in reasoning tasks through Chain-of-Thought (CoT) prompting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-key-factors-for-distilling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Vision to Sound: Advancing Audio Anomaly Detection with Vision-Based Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-vision-to-sound-advancing-audio-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in Visual Anomaly Detection (VAD) have introduced sophisticated algorithms leveraging embeddings generated by pre-trained feature extractors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-vision-to-sound-advancing-audio-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Near-Optimal Approximations for Bayesian Inference in Function Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-optimal-approximations-for-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Exploiting the thus obtained approximate posterior for these $M$ components, we perform inference for $\Pi_{\text{B}}$ by relying on the law of total probability and a sufficiency assumption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-optimal-approximations-for-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpargeAttn: Accurate Sparse Attention Accelerating Any Model Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spargeattn-accurate-sparse-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A universal sparse attention that guarantees both the speedup and end-to-end performance of diverse models remains elusive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spargeattn-accurate-sparse-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MRBTP: Efficient Multi-Robot Behavior Tree Planning and Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mrbtp-efficient-multi-robot-behavior-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These relevant actions can be pre-planned to form long-horizon subtrees, significantly enhancing the planning speed and collaboration efficiency of MRBTP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mrbtp-efficient-multi-robot-behavior-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S-Graphs 2.0 -- A Hierarchical-Semantic Optimization and Loop Closure for SLAM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-graphs-2-0-a-hierarchical-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Works based on localization and mapping do not exploit the inherent semantic-relational information from the environment for faster and efficient management and optimization of the robot poses and its map elements, often leading to pose and map inaccuracies and computational inefficiencies in large scale environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-graphs-2-0-a-hierarchical-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Market for Accuracy: Classification under Competition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-market-for-accuracy-classification-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that our approach benefits the providers as well as the consumers, and find that the timing of market entry and model updates can be crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-market-for-accuracy-classification-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-PoisonRAG: Disrupting Multimodal RAG with Local and Global Poisoning Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-poisonrag-disrupting-multimodal-rag-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal large language models (MLLMs) equipped with Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) leverage both their rich parametric knowledge and the dynamic, external knowledge to excel in tasks such as Question Answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-poisonrag-disrupting-multimodal-rag-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling dynamics of stochastic systems with deep reinforcement learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-dynamics-of-stochastic-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A properly designed controller can help improve the quality of experimental measurements or force a dynamical system to follow a completely new time-evolution path.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-dynamics-of-stochastic-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning atomic forces from uncertainty-calibrated adversarial attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-atomic-forces-from-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By performing geometry optimization for calibrated uncertainty, we reach adversarial structures with the user-assigned target MLIP prediction error.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-atomic-forces-from-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steering Language Model to Stable Speech Emotion Recognition via Contextual Perception and Chain of Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steering-language-model-to-stable-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale audio language models (ALMs), such as Qwen2-Audio, are capable of comprehending diverse audio signal, performing audio analysis and generating textual responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steering-language-model-to-stable-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advantage-Guided Distillation for Preference Alignment in Small Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advantage-guided-distillation-for-preference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of directly applying existing alignment techniques to SLMs, we propose to utilize a well-aligned teacher LLM to guide the alignment process for these models, thereby facilitating the transfer of the teacher's knowledge of human preferences to the student model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advantage-guided-distillation-for-preference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaseGen: A Benchmark for Multi-Stage Legal Case Documents Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/casegen-a-benchmark-for-multi-stage-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, CaseGen is the first benchmark designed to evaluate LLMs in the context of legal case document generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/casegen-a-benchmark-for-multi-stage-legal</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
