<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 09:14:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CSTA: CNN-based Spatiotemporal Attention for Video Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csta-cnn-based-spatiotemporal-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video summarization aims to generate a concise representation of a video, capturing its essential content and key moments while reducing its overall length.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csta-cnn-based-spatiotemporal-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAME-MT Dataset: Formality Awareness Made Easy for Machine Translation Purposes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fame-mt-dataset-formality-awareness-made-easy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[People use language for various purposes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fame-mt-dataset-formality-awareness-made-easy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versatile Teacher: A Class-aware Teacher-student Framework for Cross-domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/versatile-teacher-a-class-aware-teacher</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing the challenge of domain shift between datasets is vital in maintaining model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/versatile-teacher-a-class-aware-teacher</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fennec: Fine-grained Language Model Evaluation and Correction Extended through Branching and Bridging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fennec-fine-grained-language-model-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of large language models has given rise to a plethora of applications across a myriad of real-world tasks, mainly centered on aligning with human intent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fennec-fine-grained-language-model-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinyLLaVA Factory: A Modularized Codebase for Small-scale Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyllava-factory-a-modularized-codebase-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present TinyLLaVA Factory, an open-source modular codebase for small-scale large multimodal models (LMMs) with a focus on simplicity of code implementations, extensibility of new features, and reproducibility of training results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyllava-factory-a-modularized-codebase-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MathBench: Evaluating the Theory and Application Proficiency of LLMs with a Hierarchical Mathematics Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathbench-evaluating-the-theory-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MathBench spans a wide range of mathematical disciplines, offering a detailed evaluation of both theoretical understanding and practical problem-solving skills.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathbench-evaluating-the-theory-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feasibility Consistent Representation Learning for Safe Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feasibility-consistent-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key obstacle in this endeavor is the estimation of safety constraints, which is typically more difficult than estimating a reward metric due to the sparse nature of the constraint signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feasibility-consistent-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-Distribution Detection with a Single Unconditional Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-a-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To that end, we introduce our method, Diffusion Paths, (DiffPath) in this work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-a-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling User Fatigue for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-user-fatigue-for-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to model user Fatigue in interest learning for sequential Recommendations (FRec).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-user-fatigue-for-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DATR: Unsupervised Domain Adaptive Detection Transformer with Dataset-Level Adaptation and Prototypical Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/datr-unsupervised-domain-adaptive-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we propose the Class-wise Prototypes Alignment (CPA) module, which effectively aligns cross-domain features in a class-aware manner by bridging the gap between object detection task and domain adaptation task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/datr-unsupervised-domain-adaptive-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Position-Guided Prompt Learning for Anomaly Detection in Chest X-Rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-guided-prompt-learning-for-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Anomaly detection in chest X-rays is a critical task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-guided-prompt-learning-for-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erasing the Bias: Fine-Tuning Foundation Models for Semi-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/erasing-the-bias-fine-tuning-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-supervised learning (SSL) has witnessed remarkable progress, resulting in the emergence of numerous method variations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/erasing-the-bias-fine-tuning-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEMv3: A Fast and Robust Approach to Table Separation Line Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semv3-a-fast-and-robust-approach-to-table</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The `"split-and-merge" paradigm is a pivotal approach to parse table structure, where the table separation line detection is crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semv3-a-fast-and-robust-approach-to-table</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarially Diversified Rehearsal Memory (ADRM): Mitigating Memory Overfitting Challenge in Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarially-diversified-rehearsal-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, our detailed analysis of features and visualization demonstrates that ADRM mitigates feature drifts in CL memory samples, significantly reducing catastrophic forgetting and resulting in a more resilient CL model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarially-diversified-rehearsal-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATE: Proximity-Aware Time series anomaly Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pate-proximity-aware-time-series-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Proximity-Aware Time series anomaly Evaluation (PATE), a novel evaluation metric that incorporates the temporal relationship between prediction and anomaly intervals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pate-proximity-aware-time-series-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Spatial Similarity Distribution for Few-shot Object Counting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-spatial-similarity-distribution-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a network learning Spatial Similarity Distribution (SSD) for few-shot object counting, which preserves the spatial structure of exemplar features and calculates a 4D similarity pyramid point-to-point between the query features and exemplar features, capturing the complete distribution information for each point in the 4D similarity space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-spatial-similarity-distribution-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaseGNN++: Graph Contrastive Learning for Legal Case Retrieval with Graph Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/casegnn-graph-contrastive-learning-for-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, an edge feature-based graph attention layer (EUGAT) is proposed to comprehensively update node and edge features during graph modelling, resulting in a full utilisation of structural information of legal cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/casegnn-graph-contrastive-learning-for-legal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating and Modeling Social Intelligence: A Comparative Study of Human and AI Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-and-modeling-social-intelligence-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facing the current debate on whether Large Language Models (LLMs) attain near-human intelligence levels (Mitchell & Krakauer, 2023; Bubeck et al., 2023; Kosinski, 2023; Shiffrin & Mitchell, 2023; Ullman, 2023), the current study introduces a benchmark for evaluating social intelligence, one of the most distinctive aspects of human cognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-and-modeling-social-intelligence-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple-Choice Questions are Efficient and Robust LLM Evaluators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-choice-questions-are-efficient-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present GSM-MC and MATH-MC, two multiple-choice (MC) datasets constructed by collecting answers and incorrect predictions on GSM8K and MATH from over 50 open-source models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-choice-questions-are-efficient-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Explainable AI: A Hybrid Approach Combining GradCAM and LRP for CNN Interpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-explainable-ai-a-hybrid-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new technique that explains the output of a CNN-based model using a combination of GradCAM and LRP methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-explainable-ai-a-hybrid-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configurable Mirror Descent: Towards a Unification of Decision Making</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/configurable-mirror-descent-towards-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decision-making problems, categorized as single-agent, e. g., Atari, cooperative multi-agent, e. g., Hanabi, competitive multi-agent, e. g., Hold'em poker, and mixed cooperative and competitive, e. g., football, are ubiquitous in the real world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/configurable-mirror-descent-towards-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling and Manipulating Prompt Influence in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-and-manipulating-prompt-influence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompts play a crucial role in guiding the responses of Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-and-manipulating-prompt-influence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAMBER: A Benchmark of Identifying and Clarifying Ambiguous Information Needs in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clamber-a-benchmark-of-identifying-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce CLAMBER, a benchmark for evaluating LLMs using a well-organized taxonomy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clamber-a-benchmark-of-identifying-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Retinal: Knowledge-Enhanced Foundational Pretraining with Fundus Image-Text Expertise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-retinal-knowledge-enhanced-foundational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current fundus image analysis models are predominantly built for specific tasks relying on individual datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-retinal-knowledge-enhanced-foundational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoSoccerPose: Automated 3D posture Analysis of Soccer Shot Movements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autosoccerpose-automated-3d-posture-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dataset, code, and models are available at: https://github. com/calvinyeungck/3D-Shot-Posture-Dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autosoccerpose-automated-3d-posture-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPPS: Advanced Polyp Segmentation via Edge Information Injection and Selective Feature Decoupling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epps-advanced-polyp-segmentation-via-edge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we introduce a component called Selective Feature Decoupler (SFD) to suppress the influence of noise and extraneous features on the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epps-advanced-polyp-segmentation-via-edge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foundation Model for Chemical Process Modeling: Meta-Learning with Physics-Informed Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-model-for-chemical-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a novel application of foundation models in the domain of nonlinear chemical process modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-model-for-chemical-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Contamination Calibration for Black-box LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-contamination-calibration-for-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancements of Large Language Models (LLMs) tightly associate with the expansion of the training data size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-contamination-calibration-for-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PT43D: A Probabilistic Transformer for Generating 3D Shapes from Single Highly-Ambiguous RGB Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pt43d-a-probabilistic-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments demonstrate that our model outperforms state of the art in both scenarios]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pt43d-a-probabilistic-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling citation worthiness by using attention-based bidirectional long short-term memory networks and interpretable models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-citation-worthiness-by-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This opens the door for our model to check documents during pre-submission and pre-archival procedures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-citation-worthiness-by-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PULL: PU-Learning-based Accurate Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pull-pu-learning-based-accurate-link</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given an edge-incomplete graph, how can we accurately find the missing links?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pull-pu-learning-based-accurate-link</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Temporal Kernels with Orthogonal Polynomials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-temporal-kernels-with-orthogonal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a class of models named PLEIADES (PoLynomial Expansion In Adaptive Distributed Event-based Systems), which contains temporal convolution kernels generated from orthogonal polynomial basis functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-temporal-kernels-with-orthogonal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Multi-agent Reinforcement Learning by Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multi-agent-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on the SMAC benchmark demonstrate that MAZero outperforms model-free approaches in terms of sample efficiency and provides comparable or better performance than existing model-based methods in terms of both sample and computational efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multi-agent-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenRLHF: An Easy-to-use, Scalable and High-performance RLHF Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openrlhf-an-easy-to-use-scalable-and-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, unlike pretraining or fine-tuning a single model, scaling reinforcement learning from human feedback (RLHF) for training large language models poses coordination challenges across four models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openrlhf-an-easy-to-use-scalable-and-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highway Graph to Accelerate Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/highway-graph-to-accelerate-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We focus on improving the training efficiency of RL algorithms by improving the efficiency of the value learning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/highway-graph-to-accelerate-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Token-wise Influential Training Data Retrieval for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-wise-influential-training-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a Large Language Model (LLM) generation, how can we identify which training data led to this generation?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-wise-influential-training-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uni-Mol Docking V2: Towards Realistic and Accurate Binding Pose Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni-mol-docking-v2-towards-realistic-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, machine learning (ML) methods have emerged as promising alternatives for molecular docking, offering the potential for high accuracy without incurring prohibitive computational costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni-mol-docking-v2-towards-realistic-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Cartography-Based Curriculum Learning Method Applied on RoNLI: The First Romanian Natural Language Inference Corpus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-cartography-based-curriculum-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Natural language inference (NLI), the task of recognizing the entailment relationship in sentence pairs, is an actively studied topic serving as a proxy for natural language understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-cartography-based-curriculum-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Swahili Language Scene Text Detection and Recognition Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-first-swahili-language-scene-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a comprehensive dataset of Swahili scene text images and evaluate the dataset on different scene text detection and recognition models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-first-swahili-language-scene-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transcriptomics-guided Slide Representation Learning in Computational Pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transcriptomics-guided-slide-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Across three independent test datasets consisting of 1, 265 breast WSIs, 1, 946 lung WSIs, and 4, 584 liver WSIs, Tangle shows significantly better few-shot performance compared to supervised and SSL baselines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transcriptomics-guided-slide-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Robust Reinforcement Learning with Lipschitz-Bounded Policy Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-robust-reinforcement-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a study of robust policy networks in deep reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-robust-reinforcement-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models are Biased Reinforcement Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-biased</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given their potential use as (autonomous) decision-making agents, it is important to understand how these models perform such reinforcement learning (RL) tasks and the extent to which they are susceptible to biases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-biased</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing 6-DoF Instrument Pose Estimation in Variable X-Ray Imaging Geometries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-6-dof-instrument-pose-estimation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a general-purpose approach of data acquisition for 6-DoF pose estimation tasks in X-ray systems, a novel and general purpose YOLOv5-6D pose architecture for accurate and fast object pose estimation and a complete method for surgical screw pose estimation under acquisition geometry consideration from a monocular cone-beam X-ray image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-6-dof-instrument-pose-estimation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NetMamba: Efficient Network Traffic Classification via Pre-training Unidirectional Mamba</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/netmamba-efficient-network-traffic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, they struggle with model inefficiency due to the quadratic complexity of the widely used Transformer architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/netmamba-efficient-network-traffic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Revenue Prediction using Machine Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/movie-revenue-prediction-using-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the contemporary film industry, accurately predicting a movie's earnings is paramount for maximizing profitability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/movie-revenue-prediction-using-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Coastline Extraction Using Edge Detection Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-coastline-extraction-using-edge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyse the effectiveness of edge detection algorithms for the purpose of automatically extracting coastlines from satellite images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-coastline-extraction-using-edge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reproducibility Study of CDUL: CLIP-Driven Unsupervised Learning for Multi-Label Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducibility-study-of-cdul-clip-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(3) We try to verify the effectiveness of the gradient-alignment training method specified in the original paper, which is used to update the network parameters and pseudo labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducibility-study-of-cdul-clip-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLAB: Efficient Transformers with Simplified Linear Attention and Progressive Re-parameterized Batch Normalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slab-efficient-transformers-with-simplified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, replacing LayerNorm with more efficient BatchNorm in transformer often leads to inferior performance and collapse in training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slab-efficient-transformers-with-simplified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MHPP: Exploring the Capabilities and Limitations of Language Models Beyond Basic Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mhpp-exploring-the-capabilities-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study analyzed two common benchmarks, HumanEval and MBPP, and found that these might not thoroughly evaluate LLMs' code generation capacities due to limitations in quality, difficulty, and granularity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mhpp-exploring-the-capabilities-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emphasizing Crucial Features for Efficient Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emphasizing-crucial-features-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SFAM consists of two modules: the spatial domain attention module (SDAM) and the frequency domain attention module (FDAM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emphasizing-crucial-features-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
