<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 09:14:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>HPix: Generating Vector Maps from Satellite Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hpix-generating-vector-maps-from-satellite</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vector maps find widespread utility across diverse domains due to their capacity to not only store but also represent discrete data boundaries such as building footprints, disaster impact analysis, digitization, urban planning, location points, transport links, and more.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hpix-generating-vector-maps-from-satellite</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TXL-PBC: a freely accessible labeled peripheral blood cell dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/txl-pbc-a-freely-accessible-labeled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we used the YOLOv8n model to train these three datasets, the performance of the TXL-PBC dataset surpass the original two datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/txl-pbc-a-freely-accessible-labeled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmark Agreement Testing Done Right: A Guide for LLM Benchmark Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-agreement-testing-done-right-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the crucial role of BAT for benchmark builders and consumers, there are no standardized procedures for such agreement testing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-agreement-testing-done-right-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlcLaM: Arabic Dialectal Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alclam-arabic-dialectal-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Arabic-specific PLMs are trained predominantly on modern standard Arabic, which compromises their performance on regional dialects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alclam-arabic-dialectal-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Sight and Sound: Advanced Sound Source Localization Through Audio-Visual Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-sight-and-sound-advanced-sound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we introduce new evaluation metrics to rigorously assess sound source localization methods, focusing on accurately evaluating both localization performance and cross-modal interaction ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-sight-and-sound-advanced-sound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANHALTEN: Cross-Lingual Transfer for German Token-Level Reference-Free Hallucination Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anhalten-cross-lingual-transfer-for-german</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Research on token-level reference-free hallucination detection has predominantly focused on English, primarily due to the scarcity of robust datasets in other languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anhalten-cross-lingual-transfer-for-german</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fixed and Adaptive Simultaneous Machine Translation Strategies Using Adapters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fixed-and-adaptive-simultaneous-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The wait-$k$ policy offers a solution by starting to translate after consuming $k$ words, where the choice of the number $k$ directly affects the latency and quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fixed-and-adaptive-simultaneous-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SA-DVAE: Improving Zero-Shot Skeleton-Based Action Recognition by Disentangled Variational Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-dvae-improving-zero-shot-skeleton-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing zero-shot skeleton-based action recognition methods utilize projection networks to learn a shared latent space of skeleton features and semantic embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-dvae-improving-zero-shot-skeleton-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scikit-fingerprints: easy and efficient computation of molecular fingerprints in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scikit-fingerprints-easy-and-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present \textit{scikit-fingerprints}, a Python package for computation of molecular fingerprints for applications in chemoinformatics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scikit-fingerprints-easy-and-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Language of Infographics: Toward Understanding Conceptual Metaphor Use in Scientific Storytelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-language-of-infographics-toward</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our classification of the visual conceptual mappings within scientific representations is based on the breakdown of visual components in existing scientific infographics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-language-of-infographics-toward</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using LLMs to Investigate Correlations of Conversational Follow-up Queries with User Satisfaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-llms-to-investigate-correlations-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From qualitative analysis of 250 conversational turns from an in-lab user evaluation of Naver Cue:, a commercial conversational search engine, we propose a taxonomy of 18 users' follow-up query patterns from conversational search, comprising two major axes: (1) users' motivations behind continuing conversations (N = 7) and (2) actions of follow-up queries (N = 11).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-llms-to-investigate-correlations-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCNv3: Towards Next Generation Deep Cross Network for CTR Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcnv3-towards-next-generation-deep-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep & Cross Network and its derivative models have become an important paradigm in click-through rate (CTR) prediction due to their effective balance between computational cost and performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcnv3-towards-next-generation-deep-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Wrist Abnormality Detection with YOLO: Analysis of State-of-the-art Single-stage Detection Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-wrist-abnormality-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diagnosing and treating abnormalities in the wrist, specifically distal radius, and ulna fractures, is a crucial concern among children, adolescents, and young adults, with a higher incidence rate during puberty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-wrist-abnormality-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkish Delights: a Dataset on Turkish Euphemisms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/turkish-delights-a-dataset-on-turkish</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Euphemisms are a form of figurative language relatively understudied in natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/turkish-delights-a-dataset-on-turkish</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Any Target Can be Offense: Adversarial Example Generation via Generalized Latent Infection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/any-target-can-be-offense-adversarial-example</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, compared with other generative methods, our method achieves an approximately $14. 13\%$ higher attack success rate for unknown classes and an approximately $4. 23\%$ higher success rate for known classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/any-target-can-be-offense-adversarial-example</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeneralAD: Anomaly Detection Across Domains by Attending to Distorted Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalad-anomaly-detection-across-domains-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These features are fed to an attention-based discriminator, which is trained to score every patch in the image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalad-anomaly-detection-across-domains-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectra: A Comprehensive Study of Ternary, Quantized, and FP16 Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectra-a-comprehensive-study-of-ternary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Post-training quantization is the leading method for addressing memory-related bottlenecks in LLM inference, but unfortunately, it suffers from significant performance degradation below 4-bit precision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectra-a-comprehensive-study-of-ternary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weighting Pseudo-Labels via High-Activation Feature Index Similarity and Object Detection for Semi-Supervised Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighting-pseudo-labels-via-high-activation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we unify the predictions from a trained object detector and a semantic segmentation model to identify reliable pseudo-label pixels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighting-pseudo-labels-via-high-activation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AudienceView: AI-Assisted Interpretation of Audience Feedback in Journalism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audienceview-ai-assisted-interpretation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding and making use of audience feedback is important but difficult for journalists, who now face an impractically large volume of audience comments online.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audienceview-ai-assisted-interpretation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfoNorm: Mutual Information Shaping of Normals for Sparse-View Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infonorm-mutual-information-shaping-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D surface reconstruction from multi-view images is essential for scene understanding and interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infonorm-mutual-information-shaping-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLARE: Low Light Image Enhancement via Generative Latent Feature based Codebook Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glare-low-light-image-enhancement-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing Low-light Image Enhancement (LLIE) methods either directly map Low-Light (LL) to Normal-Light (NL) images or use semantic or illumination maps as guides.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glare-low-light-image-enhancement-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-parametric regularization for class imbalance federated medical image classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-parametric-regularization-for-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Limited training data and severe class imbalance pose significant challenges to developing clinically robust deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-parametric-regularization-for-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Frequency Matters: Uncertainty Guided Image Compression with Wavelet Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-frequency-matters-uncertainty-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a wavelet conditional diffusion model for high frequency prediction, followed by a residual codec that compresses and transmits prediction residuals to the decoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-frequency-matters-uncertainty-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reliable and Efficient Concept Erasure of Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliable-and-efficient-concept-erasure-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Reliable and Efficient Concept Erasure (RECE), a novel approach that modifies the model in 3 seconds without necessitating additional fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliable-and-efficient-concept-erasure-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoGuide: Geometric guidance of diffusion models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geoguide-geometric-guidance-of-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although ADM-G successfully generates elements from the given class, there is a significant quality gap compared to a model originally conditioned on this class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geoguide-geometric-guidance-of-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Signal Processing for Cross-Domain Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-signal-processing-for-cross-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-domain recommendation (CDR) extends conventional recommender systems by leveraging user-item interactions from dense domains to mitigate data sparsity and the cold start problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-signal-processing-for-cross-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lacuna Language Learning: Leveraging RNNs for Ranked Text Completion in Digitized Coptic Manuscripts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lacuna-language-learning-leveraging-rnns-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While not suitable for definitive manuscript reconstruction, we argue that our RNN model can help scholars rank the likelihood of textual reconstructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lacuna-language-learning-leveraging-rnns-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstraction Alignment: Comparing Model and Human Conceptual Relationships</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstraction-alignment-comparing-model-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Abstraction -- the process of generalizing specific examples into broad reusable patterns -- is central to how people efficiently process and store information and apply their knowledge to new data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstraction-alignment-comparing-model-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous reasoning for adaptive container image distribution in the cloud-edge continuum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-reasoning-for-adaptive-container</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cloud-edge computing requires applications to operate across diverse infrastructures, often triggered by cyber-physical events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-reasoning-for-adaptive-container</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LMMs-Eval: Reality Check on the Evaluation of Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmms-eval-reality-check-on-the-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To approach this evaluation trilemma, we further introduce LMMS-EVAL LITE, a pruned evaluation toolkit that emphasizes both coverage and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmms-eval-reality-check-on-the-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphMuse: A Library for Symbolic Music Graph Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphmuse-a-library-for-symbolic-music-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing this gap, we present GraphMuse, a graph processing framework and library that facilitates efficient music graph processing and GNN training for symbolic music tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphmuse-a-library-for-symbolic-music-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Calibration with Energy Based Instance-wise Scaling in the Wild Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-calibration-with-energy-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate robust post-hoc uncertainty calibration methods for DNNs within the context of multi-class classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-calibration-with-energy-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating 3D House Wireframes with Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-3d-house-wireframes-with-semantics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new approach for generating 3D house wireframes with semantic enrichment using an autoregressive model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-3d-house-wireframes-with-semantics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global-Local Similarity for Efficient Fine-Grained Image Recognition with Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-local-similarity-for-efficient-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-grained recognition involves the classification of images from subordinate macro-categories, and it is challenging due to small inter-class differences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-local-similarity-for-efficient-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoME: Mixture of Multimodal Experts for Generalist Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mome-mixture-of-multimodal-experts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a mixture of multimodal experts (MoME) to mitigate task interference and obtain a generalist MLLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mome-mixture-of-multimodal-experts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlimFlow: Training Smaller One-Step Diffusion Models with Rectified Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slimflow-training-smaller-one-step-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rectified flow framework trains one-step generative models using two operations, reflow and distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slimflow-training-smaller-one-step-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ER-FSL: Experience Replay with Feature Subspace Learning for Online Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/er-fsl-experience-replay-with-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing replay-based methods mitigate forgetting by replaying buffered samples from old data and learning current samples of new data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/er-fsl-experience-replay-with-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Better Angels of Machine Personality: How Personality Relates to LLM Safety</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-better-angels-of-machine-personality-how</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we discover that LLMs' personality traits are closely related to their safety abilities, i. e., toxicity, privacy, and fairness, based on the reliable MBTI-M scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-better-angels-of-machine-personality-how</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Context-Based Low-Light Image Enhancement via Neural Implicit Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-context-based-low-light-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current deep learning-based low-light image enhancement methods often struggle with high-resolution images, and fail to meet the practical demands of visual perception across diverse and unseen scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-context-based-low-light-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-level Adaptive Self-Labeling for Novel Class Discovery in Point Cloud Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-level-adaptive-self-labeling-for-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We tackle the novel class discovery in point cloud segmentation, which discovers novel classes based on the semantic knowledge of seen classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-level-adaptive-self-labeling-for-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaLog: Post-Training Quantization for Vision Transformers with Adaptive Logarithm Quantizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adalog-post-training-quantization-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose a novel non-uniform quantizer, dubbed the Adaptive Logarithm AdaLog (AdaLog) quantizer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adalog-post-training-quantization-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBAD: A Dataset and Benchmark for Retinal Vessels Branching Angle Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rbad-a-dataset-and-benchmark-for-retinal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting retinal image analysis, particularly the geometrical features of branching points, plays an essential role in diagnosing eye diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rbad-a-dataset-and-benchmark-for-retinal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging the Mahalanobis Distance to enhance Unsupervised Brain MRI Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-the-mahalanobis-distance-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised Anomaly Detection (UAD) methods rely on healthy data distributions to identify anomalies as outliers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-the-mahalanobis-distance-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Models for Parabolic Partial Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/base-models-for-parabolic-partial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is often necessary to compute the solutions or a function of the solutions to a parametric PDE in multiple scenarios corresponding to different parameters of this PDE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/base-models-for-parabolic-partial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoSIGN: Few-Step Guidance of ConSIstency Model to Solve General INverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosign-few-step-guidance-of-consistency-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within comparable NFEs, our method achieves new state-of-the-art in diffusion-based inverse problem solving, showcasing the significant potential of employing prior-based inverse problem solvers for real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosign-few-step-guidance-of-consistency-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProcTag: Process Tagging for Assessing the Efficacy of Document Instruction Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proctag-process-tagging-for-assessing-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An effective evaluation method for document instruction data is crucial in constructing instruction data with high efficacy, which, in turn, facilitates the training of LLMs and MLLMs for document VQA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proctag-process-tagging-for-assessing-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving Adaptive Re-Identification without Image Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-adaptive-re-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Re-Identification systems (Re-ID) are crucial for public safety but face the challenge of having to adapt to environments that differ from their training distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-adaptive-re-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dirac--Bianconi Graph Neural Networks -- Enabling Non-Diffusive Long-Range Graph Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dirac-bianconi-graph-neural-networks-enabling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The geometry of a graph is encoded in dynamical processes on the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dirac-bianconi-graph-neural-networks-enabling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Architecture Design for Efficient Generic Event Boundary Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-architecture-design-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generic event boundary detection (GEBD), inspired by human visual cognitive behaviors of consistently segmenting videos into meaningful temporal chunks, finds utility in various applications such as video editing and.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-architecture-design-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NavGPT-2: Unleashing Navigational Reasoning Capability for Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navgpt-2-unleashing-navigational-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Capitalizing on the remarkable advancements in Large Language Models (LLMs), there is a burgeoning initiative to harness LLMs for instruction following robotic navigation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navgpt-2-unleashing-navigational-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
