<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 09:15:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CityDreamer4D: Compositional Generative Model of Unbounded 4D Cities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citydreamer4d-compositional-generative-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our main insights are 1) 4D city generation should separate dynamic objects (e. g., vehicles) from static scenes (e. g., buildings and roads), and 2) all objects in the 4D scene should be composed of different types of neural fields for buildings, vehicles, and background stuff.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citydreamer4d-compositional-generative-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monte Carlo Tree Search for Comprehensive Exploration in LLM-Based Automatic Heuristic Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-tree-search-for-comprehensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Handcrafting heuristics for solving complex planning tasks (e. g., NP-hard combinatorial optimization (CO) problems) is a common practice but requires extensive domain knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-tree-search-for-comprehensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Diffusion Guidance via Learning Degradation-Aware Models for Blind Super Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-diffusion-guidance-via-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, diffusion-based blind super-resolution (SR) methods have shown great ability to generate high-resolution images with abundant high-frequency detail, but the detail is often achieved at the expense of fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-diffusion-guidance-via-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual WetlandBirds Dataset: Bird Species Identification and Behavior Recognition in Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-wetlandbirds-dataset-bird-species</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The current biodiversity loss crisis makes animal monitoring a relevant field of study.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-wetlandbirds-dataset-bird-species</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Inherent Limits of Pretrained LLMs: The Unexpected Convergence of Instruction Tuning and In-Context Learning Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-inherent-limits-of-pretrained-llms-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs), trained on extensive web-scale corpora, have demonstrated remarkable abilities across diverse tasks, especially as they are scaled up.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-inherent-limits-of-pretrained-llms-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperSAM: Crafting a SAM Supernetwork via Structured Pruning and Unstructured Parameter Prioritization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supersam-crafting-a-sam-supernetwork-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Architecture Search (NAS) is a powerful approach of automating the design of efficient neural architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supersam-crafting-a-sam-supernetwork-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do Generative Models Draw a Software Engineer? A Case Study on Stable Diffusion Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-do-generative-models-draw-a-software</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, if used without consciousness, artificially generated images could reinforce these biases in the SE domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-do-generative-models-draw-a-software</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning-Based Feature Fusion for Emotion Analysis and Suicide Risk Differentiation in Chinese Psychological Support Hotlines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-feature-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mental health is a critical global public health issue, and psychological support hotlines play a pivotal role in providing mental health assistance and identifying suicide risks at an early stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-feature-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ToMATO: Verbalizing the Mental States of Role-Playing LLMs for Benchmarking Theory of Mind</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tomato-verbalizing-the-mental-states-of-role</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These verbalized thoughts serve as answers to questions designed to assess the mental states of characters within conversations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tomato-verbalizing-the-mental-states-of-role</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Karatsuba Matrix Multiplication and its Efficient Custom Hardware Implementations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/karatsuba-matrix-multiplication-and-its</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose the extension of the scalar Karatsuba multiplication algorithm to matrix multiplication, showing how this maintains the reduction in multiplication complexity of the original Karatsuba algorithm while reducing the complexity of the extra additions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/karatsuba-matrix-multiplication-and-its</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANSR-DT: An Adaptive Neuro-Symbolic Learning and Reasoning Framework for Digital Twins</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ansr-dt-an-adaptive-neuro-symbolic-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an Adaptive Neuro-Symbolic Learning Framework for digital twin technology called ``ANSR-DT."]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ansr-dt-an-adaptive-neuro-symbolic-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOTLoc: General Outdoor Text-based Localization Using Scene Graph Retrieval with OpenStreetMap</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gotloc-general-outdoor-text-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, by utilizing publicly available map data, such as OpenStreetMap, which provides global information on outdoor spaces, we eliminate the need for additional effort to create custom map data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gotloc-general-outdoor-text-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yuan: Yielding Unblemished Aesthetics Through A Unified Network for Visual Imperfections Removal in Generated Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yuan-yielding-unblemished-aesthetics-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative AI presents transformative potential across various domains, from creative arts to scientific visualization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yuan-yielding-unblemished-aesthetics-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal LLMs Can Reason about Aesthetics in Zero-Shot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-llms-can-reason-about-aesthetics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the first study on how Multimodal LLMs' (MLLMs) reasoning ability shall be elicited to evaluate the aesthetics of artworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-llms-can-reason-about-aesthetics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge prompt chaining for semantic modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-prompt-chaining-for-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we proposed a novel automatic semantic modeling framework: Knowledge Prompt Chaining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-prompt-chaining-for-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VECT-GAN: A variationally encoded generative model for overcoming data scarcity in pharmaceutical science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vect-gan-a-variationally-encoded-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data scarcity in pharmaceutical research has led to reliance on labour-intensive trial and error approaches for development rather than data driven methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vect-gan-a-variationally-encoded-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing the Alignment of FOL Closeness Metrics with Human Judgement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-alignment-of-fol-closeness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using ground-truth FOLs, we carefully designed various perturbations on the ground-truth to assess metric sensitivity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-alignment-of-fol-closeness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SwinTExCo: Exemplar-based video colorization using Swin Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swintexco-exemplar-based-video-colorization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video colorization represents a compelling domain within the field of Computer Vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swintexco-exemplar-based-video-colorization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Molecular Graph Contrastive Learning with Line Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-graph-contrastive-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trapped by the label scarcity in molecular property prediction and drug design, graph contrastive learning (GCL) came forward.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-graph-contrastive-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complexity Control Facilitates Reasoning-Based Compositional Generalization in Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complexity-control-facilitates-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have demonstrated impressive capabilities across various tasks, yet their performance on compositional problems remains a subject of debate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complexity-control-facilitates-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Score-based 3D molecule generation with neural fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-based-3d-molecule-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using this representation, we propose a new model based on walk-jump sampling for unconditional 3D molecule generation in the continuous space using neural fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-based-3d-molecule-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MonSter: Marry Monodepth to Stereo Unleashes Power</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monster-marry-monodepth-to-stereo-unleashes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The refined monodepth is in turn guides stereo effectively at ill-posed regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monster-marry-monodepth-to-stereo-unleashes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Sampled Softmax with Inverted Multi-Index: Methods, Theory and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-sampled-softmax-with-inverted-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The softmax function is a cornerstone of multi-class classification, integral to a wide range of machine learning applications, from large-scale retrieval and ranking models to advanced large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-sampled-softmax-with-inverted-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Transformation Learning for Equivariant Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-transformation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, current methods depend on transformation labels and thus struggle with interdependency and complex transformations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-transformation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disjoint Processing Mechanisms of Hierarchical and Linear Grammars in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disjoint-processing-mechanisms-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using these grammars, we first observe that language models show distinct behaviors on hierarchical versus linearly structured inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disjoint-processing-mechanisms-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenCSG Chinese Corpus: A Series of High-quality Chinese Datasets for LLM Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opencsg-chinese-corpus-a-series-of-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable capabilities, but their success heavily relies on the quality of pretraining corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opencsg-chinese-corpus-a-series-of-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AfriHate: A Multilingual Collection of Hate Speech and Abusive Language Datasets for African Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/afrihate-a-multilingual-collection-of-hate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These limitations are mainly due to the lack of high-quality data in the local languages and the failure to include local communities in the collection, annotation, and moderation processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/afrihate-a-multilingual-collection-of-hate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Statistical Capacity of Deep Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-statistical-capacity-of-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These results shed light on the limited capacity of common deep generative models to handle heavy tails.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-statistical-capacity-of-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter-Inverted Image Pyramid Networks for Visual Perception and Multimodal Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-inverted-image-pyramid-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For multimodal understanding, our PIIP-LLaVA achieves 73. 0% accuracy on TextVQA and 74. 5% on MMBench with only 2. 8M training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-inverted-image-pyramid-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Motion and Temporal Cues for Unsupervised Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-motion-and-temporal-cues-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we address the challenges in unsupervised video object segmentation (UVOS) by proposing an efficient algorithm, termed MTNet, which concurrently exploits motion and temporal cues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-motion-and-temporal-cues-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Automated Interpretability with Output-Centric Feature Descriptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-automated-interpretability-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated interpretability pipelines generate natural language descriptions for the concepts represented by features in large language models (LLMs), such as plants or the first word in a sentence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-automated-interpretability-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective Attention Merging for low resource tasks: A case study of Child ASR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-attention-merging-for-low-resource</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Speech Foundation Models (SFMs) excel in various speech tasks, their performance for low-resource tasks such as child Automatic Speech Recognition (ASR) is hampered by limited pretraining data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-attention-merging-for-low-resource</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Robustness of Multilingual LLMs on Real-World Noisy Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-robustness-of-multilingual-llms-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, mT5 (13B), was the most robust on average overall, across the 3 tasks, and in 4 of the 6 languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-robustness-of-multilingual-llms-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-situ graph reasoning and knowledge expansion using Graph-PReFLexOR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-situ-graph-reasoning-and-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pursuit of automated scientific discovery has fueled progress from symbolic logic to modern AI, forging new frontiers in reasoning and pattern recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-situ-graph-reasoning-and-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Deep Active Learning for Medical Imaging: Replay-Base Architecture for Context Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-deep-active-learning-for-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results show that RBACA outperforms a baseline framework without CAL, and a state-of-the-art CAL method across various memory sizes and annotation budgets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-deep-active-learning-for-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Performance of Object Detection Models in Electron Microscopy Using Random Forests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-performance-of-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantifying prediction uncertainty when applying object detection models to new, unlabeled datasets is critical in applied machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-performance-of-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poseidon: A ViT-based Architecture for Multi-Frame Pose Estimation with Adaptive Frame Weighting and Multi-Scale Feature Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poseidon-a-vit-based-architecture-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human pose estimation, a vital task in computer vision, involves detecting and localising human joints in images and videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poseidon-a-vit-based-architecture-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Driven Water Segmentation with deep learning models for Enhanced Flood Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-driven-water-segmentation-with-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The UNet, ResNet, and DeepLab v3 architectures are tested to determine their effectiveness in various environmental conditions and geographical locations, and the strengths and limitations of each model are also discussed here, providing insights into their applicability in different scenarios by predicting image segmentation masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-driven-water-segmentation-with-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3UR-LLM: An End-to-End Multimodal Large Language Model for 3D Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3ur-llm-an-end-to-end-multimodal-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal Large Language Models (MLLMs) exhibit impressive capabilities in 2D tasks, yet encounter challenges in discerning the spatial positions, interrelations, and causal logic in scenes when transitioning from 2D to 3D representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3ur-llm-an-end-to-end-multimodal-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHEQ-ing the Box: Safe Variable Impedance Learning for Robotic Polishing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cheq-ing-the-box-safe-variable-impedance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These results highlight the potential of adaptive hybrid RL for real-world, contact-rich tasks trained directly on hardware.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cheq-ing-the-box-safe-variable-impedance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarsier2: Advancing Large Vision-Language Models from Detailed Video Description to Comprehensive Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tarsier2-advancing-large-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Tarsier2, a state-of-the-art large vision-language model (LVLM) designed for generating detailed and accurate video descriptions, while also exhibiting superior general video understanding capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tarsier2-advancing-large-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Semantic Future Prediction through Multimodal Visual Sequence Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-semantic-future-prediction-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach incorporates a multimodal masked visual modeling objective and a novel masking mechanism designed for multimodal training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-semantic-future-prediction-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go-with-the-Flow: Motion-Controllable Video Diffusion Models Using Real-Time Warped Noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/go-with-the-flow-motion-controllable-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The efficiency of our algorithm enables us to fine-tune modern video diffusion base models using warped noise with minimal overhead, and provide a one-stop solution for a wide range of user-friendly motion control: local object motion control, global camera movement control, and motion transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/go-with-the-flow-motion-controllable-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OptiChat: Bridging Optimization Models and Practitioners with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optichat-bridging-optimization-models-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimization models have been applied to solve a wide variety of decision-making problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optichat-bridging-optimization-models-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Analysis of DNN-based White-Box Explainable AI Methods in Network Security</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-analysis-of-dnn-based-white-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[New research focuses on creating artificial intelligence (AI) solutions for network intrusion detection systems (NIDS), drawing its inspiration from the ever-growing number of intrusions on networked systems, increasing its complexity and intelligibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-analysis-of-dnn-based-white-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient Equilibrium in Online Learning: Theory and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-equilibrium-in-online-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new perspective on online learning that we refer to as gradient equilibrium: a sequence of iterates achieves gradient equilibrium if the average of gradients of losses along the sequence converges to zero.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-equilibrium-in-online-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFGraphFR: An attempt at a federated recommendation system based on user text characteristics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufgraphfr-an-attempt-at-a-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by Federated learning, the federated recommendation system has gradually become a new recommendation service architecture that can protect users' privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufgraphfr-an-attempt-at-a-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EmoNeXt: an Adapted ConvNeXt for Facial Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emonext-an-adapted-convnext-for-facial-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial expressions play a crucial role in human communication serving as a powerful and impactful means to express a wide range of emotions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emonext-an-adapted-convnext-for-facial-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVS-Mamba: Exploring Temporal and Multi-modal Mamba for Audio-Visual Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avs-mamba-exploring-temporal-and-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To perform multi-modal fusion, we propose the Modality Aggregation Decoder, leveraging the Vision-to-Audio Fusion Block to integrate visual features into audio features across both frame and temporal levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avs-mamba-exploring-temporal-and-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DM-Mamba: Dual-domain Multi-scale Mamba for MRI reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dm-mamba-dual-domain-multi-scale-mamba-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these, we propose a dual-domain multi-scale Mamba for MRI reconstruction from the following perspectives: (1) We pioneer vision Mamba in k-space learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dm-mamba-dual-domain-multi-scale-mamba-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
