<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 09:14:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Analysing Discrete Self Supervised Speech Representation for Spoken Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysing-discrete-self-supervised-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Following the findings of such an analysis, we propose practical improvements to the discrete unit for the GSLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysing-discrete-self-supervised-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConvNeXt V2: Co-designing and Scaling ConvNets with Masked Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convnext-v2-co-designing-and-scaling-convnets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This co-design of self-supervised learning techniques and architectural improvement results in a new model family called ConvNeXt V2, which significantly improves the performance of pure ConvNets on various recognition benchmarks, including ImageNet classification, COCO detection, and ADE20K segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convnext-v2-co-designing-and-scaling-convnets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argoverse 2: Next Generation Datasets for Self-Driving Perception and Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/argoverse-2-next-generation-datasets-for-self-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Models are tasked with the prediction of future motion for "scored actors" in each scenario and are provided with track histories that capture object location, heading, velocity, and category.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/argoverse-2-next-generation-datasets-for-self-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Credible Remote Sensing Scene Classification Using Evidential Fusion on Aerial-Ground Dual-view Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/credible-remote-sensing-scene-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this uncertainty, a novel decision-level fusion strategy is proposed to ensure that the view with lower risk obtains more weight, making the classification more credible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/credible-remote-sensing-scene-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusing Models for Prognostics and Health Management of Lithium-Ion Batteries Based on Physics-Informed Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusing-models-for-prognostics-and-health</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Physics-Informed Neural Network (PINN) is an efficient tool to fuse empirical or physical dynamic models with data-driven models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusing-models-for-prognostics-and-health</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PCRLv2: A Unified Visual Information Preservation Framework for Self-supervised Pre-training in Medical Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcrlv2-a-unified-visual-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in self-supervised learning (SSL) in computer vision are primarily comparative, whose goal is to preserve invariant and discriminative semantics in latent representations by comparing siamese image views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcrlv2-a-unified-visual-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correlation Clustering Algorithm for Dynamic Complete Signed Graphs: An Index-based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-clustering-algorithm-for-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we reduce the complexity of approximating the correlation clustering problem from $O(m\times\left( 2+ \alpha (G) \right)+n)$ to $O(m+n)$ for any given value of $\varepsilon$ for a complete signed graph with $n$ vertices and $m$ positive edges where $\alpha(G)$ is the arboricity of the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-clustering-algorithm-for-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Readability Using Genetic Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-readability-using-genetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An exhaustive study on a substantial number and diversity of texts confirms that our method was able to optimize the degree of readability in all cases without significantly altering their form or meaning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-readability-using-genetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symbolic Visual Reinforcement Learning: A Scalable Framework with Object-Level Abstraction and Differentiable Expression Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-visual-reinforcement-learning-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning efficient and interpretable policies has been a challenging task in reinforcement learning (RL), particularly in the visual RL setting with complex scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-visual-reinforcement-learning-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Interpretability of Attention Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-interpretability-of-attention-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In trained models with an attention mechanism, the outputs of an intermediate module that encodes the segment of input responsible for the output is often used as a way to peek into the `reasoning` of the network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-interpretability-of-attention-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monge-Kantorovich Optimal Transport Through Constrictions and Flow-rate Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monge-kantorovich-optimal-transport-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We quantify flow-rate constraints via a bound on a sought probability density of the times that mass-elements cross toll stations and cast the transportation scheduling in a Kantorovich-type of formalism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monge-kantorovich-optimal-transport-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Change Intervals with Isolation Distributional Kernel</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-change-intervals-with-isolation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The data-dependent property and finite feature map of IDK enabled iCID to efficiently identify various types of change points in data streams with the tolerance of noise points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-change-intervals-with-isolation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Node-Element Hypergraph Message Passing for Fluid Dynamics Simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/node-element-hypergraph-message-passing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We implement a message-passing network on such a node-element hypergraph and explore the capability of the network for the modeling of fluid flow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/node-element-hypergraph-message-passing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black-box language model explanation by context length probing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/black-box-language-model-explanation-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present context length probing, a novel explanation technique for causal language models, based on tracking the predictions of a model as a function of the length of available context, and allowing to assign differential importance scores to different contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/black-box-language-model-explanation-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Forgery Classifier On Multi-modality Face Forgery Clues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-forgery-classifier-on-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Face forgery detection plays an important role in personal privacy and social security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-forgery-classifier-on-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBIWEAR: An end-to-end, data-driven framework for intelligent physical activity prediction to empower mHealth interventions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ubiwear-an-end-to-end-data-driven-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose UBIWEAR, an end-to-end framework for intelligent physical activity prediction, with the ultimate goal to empower data-driven goal-setting interventions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ubiwear-an-end-to-end-data-driven-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk-Sensitive Policy with Distributional Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-sensitive-policy-with-distributional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Classical reinforcement learning (RL) techniques are generally concerned with the design of decision-making policies driven by the maximisation of the expected outcome.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-sensitive-policy-with-distributional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HPointLoc: Point-based Indoor Place Recognition using Synthetic RGB-D Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hpointloc-point-based-indoor-place</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To study the main stages of solving the place recognition problem on the HPointLoc dataset, we proposed a new modular approach named as PNTR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hpointloc-point-based-indoor-place</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised 4D LiDAR Moving Object Segmentation in Stationary Settings with Multivariate Occupancy Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-4d-lidar-moving-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address the problem of unsupervised moving object segmentation (MOS) in 4D LiDAR data recorded from a stationary sensor, where no ground truth annotations are involved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-4d-lidar-moving-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Against Adversarial Attacks on Audio DeepFake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defense-against-adversarial-attacks-on-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Audio DeepFakes are artificially generated utterances created using deep learning methods with the main aim to fool the listeners, most of such audio is highly convincing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defense-against-adversarial-attacks-on-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Control for 6G Industrial Wireless Subnetworks: A Graph Neural Network Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/power-control-for-6g-industrial-wireless</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interference management techniques such as centralized power control can improve spectral efficiency in dense deployments of such subnetworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/power-control-for-6g-industrial-wireless</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Examining Political Rhetoric with Epistemic Stance Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/examining-political-rhetoric-with-epistemic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Participants in political discourse employ rhetorical strategies -- such as hedging, attributions, or denials -- to display varying degrees of belief commitments to claims proposed by themselves or others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/examining-political-rhetoric-with-epistemic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PanDepth: Joint Panoptic Segmentation and Depth Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pandepth-joint-panoptic-segmentation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding 3D environments semantically is pivotal in autonomous driving applications where multiple computer vision tasks are involved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pandepth-joint-panoptic-segmentation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT Takes the Bar Exam</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-takes-the-bar-exam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nearly all jurisdictions in the United States require a professional license exam, commonly referred to as "the Bar Exam," as a precondition for law practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-takes-the-bar-exam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUSP-SP: Faster Utility Mining on Sequence Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/husp-sp-faster-utility-mining-on-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-utility sequential pattern mining (HUSPM) has emerged as an important topic due to its wide application and considerable popularity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/husp-sp-faster-utility-mining-on-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resolving Task Confusion in Dynamic Expansion Architectures for Class Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resolving-task-confusion-in-dynamic-expansion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dynamic expansion architecture is becoming popular in class incremental learning, mainly due to its advantages in alleviating catastrophic forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resolving-task-confusion-in-dynamic-expansion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Federated Learning for CIoT Devices in Smart Home Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-federated-learning-for-ciot-devices-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper deals with the problem of statistical and system heterogeneity in a cross-silo Federated Learning (FL) framework where there exist a limited number of Consumer Internet of Things (CIoT) devices in a smart building.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-federated-learning-for-ciot-devices-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WL-Align: Weisfeiler-Lehman Relabeling for Aligning Users across Networks via Regularized Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wl-align-weisfeiler-lehman-relabeling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aligning users across networks using graph representation learning has been found effective where the alignment is accomplished in a low-dimensional embedding space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wl-align-weisfeiler-lehman-relabeling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discriminator-Cooperated Feature Map Distillation for GAN Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discriminator-cooperated-feature-map</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to conventional pixel-to-pixel match methods in feature map distillation, our DCD utilizes teacher discriminator as a transformation to drive intermediate results of the student generator to be perceptually close to corresponding outputs of the teacher generator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discriminator-cooperated-feature-map</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleID: Identity Disentanglement for Anonymizing Faces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styleid-identity-disentanglement-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Privacy of machine learning models is one of the remaining challenges that hinder the broad adoption of Artificial Intelligent (AI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styleid-identity-disentanglement-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape-Aware Fine-Grained Classification of Erythroid Cells</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-aware-fine-grained-classification-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BMEC contains 5, 666 images of individual erythroid cells, each of which is extracted from the bone marrow erythroid cell smears and professionally annotated to one of the four types of erythroid cells.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-aware-fine-grained-classification-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Detect Noisy Labels Using Model-Based Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-detect-noisy-labels-using-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Label noise is ubiquitous in various machine learning scenarios such as self-labeling with model predictions and erroneous data annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-detect-noisy-labels-using-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature learning in neural networks and kernel machines that recursively learn features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-learning-in-neural-networks-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we isolate the key mechanism driving feature learning in fully connected neural networks by connecting neural feature learning to the average gradient outer product.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-learning-in-neural-networks-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lexicographic Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexicographic-multi-objective-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we introduce reinforcement learning techniques for solving lexicographic multi-objective problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexicographic-multi-objective-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anxolotl, an Anxiety Companion App -- Stress Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anxolotl-an-anxiety-companion-app-stress</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stress has a great effect on people's lives that can not be understated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anxolotl-an-anxiety-companion-app-stress</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TiG-BEV: Multi-view BEV 3D Object Detection via Target Inner-Geometry Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tig-bev-multi-view-bev-3d-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the learning scheme of Target Inner-Geometry from the LiDAR modality into camera-based BEV detectors for both dense depth and BEV features, termed as TiG-BEV.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tig-bev-multi-view-bev-3d-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Clustering-guided Contrastive Fusion for Multi-view Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-clustering-guided-contrastive-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we utilize a deep fusion network to fuse view-specific representations into the view-common representation, extracting high-level semantics for obtaining robust representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-clustering-guided-contrastive-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynCLay: Interactive Synthesis of Histology Images from Bespoke Cellular Layouts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synclay-interactive-synthesis-of-histology</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tissue image generation based on bespoke cellular layouts through the proposed framework allows users to generate different histological patterns from arbitrary topological arrangement of different types of cells.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synclay-interactive-synthesis-of-histology</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Graph Contrastive Learning with Meta-path Contexts and Weighted Negative Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-contrastive-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We take node embeddings in the coarse view as anchors, and construct positive and negative samples from the fine-grained view.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-contrastive-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable and Lightweight Model for COVID-19 Detection Using Chest Radiology Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-and-lightweight-model-for-covid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning (DL) analysis of Chest X-ray (CXR) and Computed tomography (CT) images has garnered a lot of attention in recent times due to the COVID-19 pandemic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-and-lightweight-model-for-covid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Modeling Hierarchical Time Series Using Autoregressive Transformer and Conditional Normalizing Flow based Reconciliation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-modeling-hierarchical-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multivariate time series forecasting with hierarchical structure is pervasive in real-world applications, demanding not only predicting each level of the hierarchy, but also reconciling all forecasts to ensure coherency, i. e., the forecasts should satisfy the hierarchical aggregation constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-modeling-hierarchical-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cramming: Training a Language Model on a Single GPU in One Day</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cramming-training-a-language-model-on-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent trends in language modeling have focused on increasing performance through scaling, and have resulted in an environment where training language models is out of reach for most researchers and practitioners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cramming-training-a-language-model-on-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part-guided Relational Transformers for Fine-grained Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/part-guided-relational-transformers-for-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This framework, namely PArt-guided Relational Transformers (PART), is proposed to learn the discriminative part features with an automatic part discovery module, and to explore the intrinsic correlations with a feature transformation module by adapting the Transformer models from the field of natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/part-guided-relational-transformers-for-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Recognition and Classification of Future Work Sentences from Academic Articles in a Specific Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-recognition-and-classification-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents methods to automatically extract FWS from academic papers and classify them according to the different future directions embodied in the paper's content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-recognition-and-classification-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Generalizability of Deep Learning Models Using Indian-COVID-19 CT Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-generalizability-of-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the major concerns in using ma-chine learning (ML) approaches for automatic processing of CT scan images in clinical setting is that these methods are trained on limited and biased sub-sets of publicly available COVID-19 data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-generalizability-of-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepCuts: Single-Shot Interpretability based Pruning for BERT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepcuts-single-shot-interpretability-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also analyze our pruning masks and find them to be significantly different from the ones obtained using standard metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepcuts-single-shot-interpretability-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AER: Auto-Encoder with Regression for Time Series Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aer-auto-encoder-with-regression-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then propose AER (Auto-encoder with Regression), a joint model that combines a vanilla auto-encoder and an LSTM regressor to incorporate the successes and address the limitations of each method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aer-auto-encoder-with-regression-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiSpider: Towards Benchmarking Multilingual Text-to-SQL Semantic Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multispider-towards-benchmarking-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-SQL semantic parsing is an important NLP task, which greatly facilitates the interaction between users and the database and becomes the key component in many human-computer interaction systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multispider-towards-benchmarking-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infusing Definiteness into Randomness: Rethinking Composition Styles for Deep Image Matting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infusing-definiteness-into-randomness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by this, we introduce a novel composition style that binds the source and combined foregrounds in a definite triplet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infusing-definiteness-into-randomness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Single-Visit to Multi-Visit Image-Based Models: Single-Visit Models are Enough to Predict Obstructive Hydronephrosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-single-visit-to-multi-visit-image-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous work has shown the potential of deep learning to predict renal obstruction using kidney ultrasound images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-single-visit-to-multi-visit-image-based</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
