<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 21:05:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MAP: A Model-agnostic Pretraining Framework for Click-through Rate Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-a-model-agnostic-pretraining-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The large capacity of neural models helps digest such massive amounts of data under the supervised learning paradigm, yet they fail to utilize the substantial data to its full potential, since the 1-bit click signal is not sufficient to guide the model to learn capable representations of features and instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-a-model-agnostic-pretraining-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisAlign: Dataset for Measuring the Degree of Alignment between AI and Humans in Visual Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visalign-dataset-for-measuring-the-degree-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on the models' visual perception alignment with humans, further referred to as AI-human visual alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visalign-dataset-for-measuring-the-degree-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClassEval: A Manually-Crafted Benchmark for Evaluating LLMs on Class-level Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classeval-a-manually-crafted-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Third, we find that generating the entire class all at once (i. e. holistic generation strategy) is the best generation strategy only for GPT-4 and GPT-3. 5, while method-by-method generation (i. e. incremental and compositional) is better strategies for the other models with limited ability of understanding long instructions and utilizing the middle information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classeval-a-manually-crafted-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circumventing Concept Erasure Methods For Text-to-Image Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circumventing-concept-erasure-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image generative models can produce photo-realistic images for an extremely broad range of concepts, and their usage has proliferated widely among the general public.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circumventing-concept-erasure-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Multiplex Graph Learning with Complementary and Consistent Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-multiplex-graph-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised multiplex graph learning (UMGL) has been shown to achieve significant effectiveness for different downstream tasks by exploring both complementary information and consistent information among multiple graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-multiplex-graph-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Noise Boosts DNN Generalization under Label Noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-noise-boosts-dnn-generalization-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce and theoretically demonstrate a simple feature noise method, which directly adds noise to the features of training data, can enhance the generalization of DNNs under label noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-noise-boosts-dnn-generalization-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniG-Encoder: A Universal Feature Encoder for Graph and Hypergraph Node Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unig-encoder-a-universal-feature-encoder-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, a universal feature encoder for both graph and hypergraph representation learning is designed, called UniG-Encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unig-encoder-a-universal-feature-encoder-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal thinking for decision making on Electronic Health Records: why and how</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-thinking-for-decision-making-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We illustrate the various choices in studying the effect of albumin on sepsis mortality in the Medical Information Mart for Intensive Care database (MIMIC-IV).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-thinking-for-decision-making-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconstructing Three-Dimensional Models of Interacting Humans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructing-three-dimensional-models-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding 3d human interactions is fundamental for fine-grained scene analysis and behavioural modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructing-three-dimensional-models-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthesizing Long-Term Human Motions with Diffusion Models via Coherent Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesizing-long-term-human-motions-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, they cannot directly generate coherent motions and require additional operations such as interpolation to process the generated actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesizing-long-term-human-motions-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>URET: Universal Robustness Evaluation Toolkit (for Evasion)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uret-universal-robustness-evaluation-toolkit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new framework to enable the generation of adversarial inputs irrespective of the input type and task domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uret-universal-robustness-evaluation-toolkit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point2Mask: Point-supervised Panoptic Segmentation via Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point2mask-point-supervised-panoptic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly-supervised image segmentation has recently attracted increasing research attentions, aiming to avoid the expensive pixel-wise labeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point2mask-point-supervised-panoptic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DETR Doesn't Need Multi-Scale or Locality Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detr-doesn-t-need-multi-scale-or-locality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an improved DETR detector that maintains a "plain" nature: using a single-scale feature map and global cross-attention calculations without specific locality constraints, in contrast to previous leading DETR-based detectors that reintroduce architectural inductive biases of multi-scale and locality into the decoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detr-doesn-t-need-multi-scale-or-locality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Link Prediction Explanations for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-link-prediction-explanations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Machine Learning (GML) has numerous applications, such as node/graph classification and link prediction, in real-world domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-link-prediction-explanations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interleaving GANs with knowledge graphs to support design creativity for book covers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interleaving-gans-with-knowledge-graphs-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An attractive book cover is important for the success of a book.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interleaving-gans-with-knowledge-graphs-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby's CoThought: Leveraging Large Language Models for Enhanced Reasoning in Compact Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/baby-s-cothought-leveraging-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) demonstrate remarkable performance on a variety of Natural Language Understanding (NLU) tasks, primarily due to their in-context learning ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/baby-s-cothought-leveraging-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lexicon and Rule-based Word Lemmatization Approach for the Somali Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexicon-and-rule-based-word-lemmatization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lemmatization is a Natural Language Processing (NLP) technique used to normalize text by changing morphological derivations of words to their root forms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexicon-and-rule-based-word-lemmatization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wider and Deeper LLM Networks are Fairer LLM Evaluators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wider-and-deeper-llm-networks-are-fairer-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Each perspective corresponds to the role of a specific LLM neuron in the first layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wider-and-deeper-llm-networks-are-fairer-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Relationship on Learning Mathematical Reasoning with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-relationship-on-learning-mathematical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply supervised fine-tuning (SFT) with different amounts of supervised data and empirically find a log-linear relation between data amount and model performance, and we find better models improve less with enlarged supervised datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-relationship-on-learning-mathematical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMDC: Dynamic-mask-based dual camera design for snapshot Hyperspectral Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dmdc-dynamic-mask-based-dual-camera-design</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, the system learns the spatial feature distribution of the scene based on the RGB images, then instructs the SLM to encode each scene, and finally sends both RGB and CASSI images to the network for reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dmdc-dynamic-mask-based-dual-camera-design</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Large Language Models for Complex Structured Medical Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-large-language-models-for-complex</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces an approach that combines the language reasoning capabilities of large language models (LLMs) with the benefits of local training to tackle complex, domain-specific tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-large-language-models-for-complex</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Estimation Under Distribution Shift: Wasserstein Perturbations and Minimax Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-estimation-under-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under a squared loss for mean estimation and prediction error in linear regression, we find the exact minimax risk, a least favorable perturbation, and show that the sample mean and least squares estimators are respectively optimal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-estimation-under-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Collapse Terminus: A Unified Solution for Class Incremental Learning and Its Variants</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-collapse-terminus-a-unified-solution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Beyond the normal case, long-tail class incremental learning and few-shot class incremental learning are also proposed to consider the data imbalance and data scarcity, respectively, which are common in real-world implementations and further exacerbate the well-known problem of catastrophic forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-collapse-terminus-a-unified-solution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Multi-view Representations Beyond Inductive Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-multi-view-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel multi-view representation disentangling method that aims to go beyond inductive biases, ensuring both interpretability and generalizability of the resulting representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-multi-view-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Visibility in Nighttime Haze Images Using Guided APSF and Gradient Adaptive Convolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-visibility-in-nighttime-haze-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we enhance the visibility from a single nighttime haze image by suppressing glow and enhancing low-light regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-visibility-in-nighttime-haze-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balanced Destruction-Reconstruction Dynamics for Memory-replay Class Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balanced-destruction-reconstruction-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By dynamically manipulating the gradient during training based on these factors, BDR can effectively alleviate knowledge destruction and improve knowledge reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balanced-destruction-reconstruction-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoissonNet: Resolution-Agnostic 3D Shape Reconstruction using Fourier Neural Operators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poissonnet-resolution-agnostic-3d-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we demonstrate that the Poisson surface reconstruction problem is well-posed in the limit case by showing a universal approximation theorem for the solution operator of the Poisson equation with distributional data utilizing the Fourier Neuronal Operator, which provides a theoretical foundation for our numerical results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poissonnet-resolution-agnostic-3d-shape</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NuInsSeg: A Fully Annotated Dataset for Nuclei Instance Segmentation in H&amp;E-Stained Histological Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nuinsseg-a-fully-annotated-dataset-for-nuclei</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we release one of the biggest fully manually annotated datasets of nuclei in Hematoxylin and Eosin (H&E)-stained histological images, called NuInsSeg.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nuinsseg-a-fully-annotated-dataset-for-nuclei</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Training of Denoising Diffusion Model Using Dual Discriminators for High-Fidelity Multi-Speaker TTS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-training-of-denoising-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The evaluation results show that the proposed model outperforms recent state-of-the-art models such as FastSpeech2 and DiffGAN-TTS in various metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-training-of-denoising-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The All-Seeing Project: Towards Panoptic Visual Recognition and Understanding of the Open World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-all-seeing-project-towards-panoptic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the All-Seeing (AS) project: a large-scale data and model for recognizing and understanding everything in the open world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-all-seeing-project-towards-panoptic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is your data alignable? Principled and interpretable alignability testing and integration of single-cell data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-your-data-alignable-principled-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SMAI provides a statistical test to robustly determine the alignability between datasets to avoid misleading inference, and is justified by high-dimensional statistical theory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-your-data-alignable-principled-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-Temporal Branching for Motion Prediction using Motion Increments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-branching-for-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human motion prediction (HMP) has emerged as a popular research topic due to its diverse applications, but it remains a challenging task due to the stochastic and aperiodic nature of future poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-branching-for-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADS-Cap: A Framework for Accurate and Diverse Stylized Captioning with Unpaired Stylistic Corpora</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ads-cap-a-framework-for-accurate-and-diverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating visually grounded image captions with specific linguistic styles using unpaired stylistic corpora is a challenging task, especially since we expect stylized captions with a wide variety of stylistic patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ads-cap-a-framework-for-accurate-and-diverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Context, Less Distraction: Visual Classification by Inferring and Conditioning on Contextual Attributes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-context-less-distraction-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper draws inspiration from the human visual perception process: a modern neuroscience view suggests that in classifying an object, humans first infer its class-independent attributes (e. g., background and orientation) which help separate the foreground object from the background, and then make decisions based on this information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-context-less-distraction-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harder synthetic anomalies to improve OoD detection in Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harder-synthetic-anomalies-to-improve-ood</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method builds upon previous Medical Out-of-Distribution (MOOD) challenge winners that empirically show that synthetic local anomalies generated copying / interpolating foreign patches are useful to train segmentation networks able to generalize to unseen types of anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harder-synthetic-anomalies-to-improve-ood</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planar Friction Modelling with LuGre Dynamics and Limit Surfaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planar-friction-modelling-with-lugre-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contact surfaces in planar motion exhibit a coupling between tangential and rotational friction forces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planar-friction-modelling-with-lugre-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextual Emotion Recognition Using Transformer-Based Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-emotion-recognition-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to increase the precision of emotion identification in text, this research suggests a context-aware emotion recognition system employing transformer models, especially BERT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-emotion-recognition-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point Anywhere: Directed Object Estimation from Omnidirectional Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-anywhere-directed-object-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the intuitive instruction methods in robot navigation is a pointing gesture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-anywhere-directed-object-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fighting Fire with Fire: Can ChatGPT Detect AI-generated Text?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fighting-fire-with-fire-can-chatgpt-detect-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) such as ChatGPT are increasingly being used for various use cases, including text content generation at scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fighting-fire-with-fire-can-chatgpt-detect-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-informed neural networks for blood flow inverse problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-neural-networks-for-blood</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Physics-informed neural networks (PINNs) have emerged as a powerful tool for solving inverse problems, especially in cases where no complete information about the system is known and scatter measurements are available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-neural-networks-for-blood</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training-Free Instance Segmentation from Semantic Image Segmentation Masks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-free-instance-segmentation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TFISeg does not require training a semantic or/and instance segmentation model and avoids the need for instance-level image annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-free-instance-segmentation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Generic: Enhancing Image Captioning with Real-World Knowledge using Vision-Language Pre-Training Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-generic-enhancing-image-captioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering that Vision-Language Pre-Training (VLP) models master massive such knowledge from large-scale web-harvested data, it is promising to utilize the generalizability of VLP models to incorporate knowledge into image descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-generic-enhancing-image-captioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User-Controllable Recommendation via Counterfactual Retrospective and Prospective Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-controllable-recommendation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Acknowledging the recent advancements in explainable recommender systems that enhance users' understanding of recommendation mechanisms, we propose leveraging these advancements to improve user controllability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-controllable-recommendation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUANT: A Minimalist Interval Method for Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quant-a-minimalist-interval-method-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that it is possible to achieve the same accuracy, on average, as the most accurate existing interval methods for time series classification on a standard set of benchmark datasets using a single type of feature (quantiles), fixed intervals, and an 'off the shelf' classifier.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quant-a-minimalist-interval-method-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computing the Distance between unbalanced Distributions -- The flat Metric</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computing-the-distance-between-unbalanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide an implementation to compute the flat metric in any dimension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computing-the-distance-between-unbalanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRNES: Enabling Security and Privacy-aware Experience Sharing in Multiagent Robotic and Autonomous Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brnes-enabling-security-and-privacy-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nevertheless, in a real-world setting, some Byzantine attackers, disguised as advisors, may provide false advice to the advisee and catastrophically degrade the overall learning performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brnes-enabling-security-and-privacy-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FusionAD: Multi-modality Fusion for Prediction and Planning Tasks of Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusionad-multi-modality-fusion-for-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building a multi-modality multi-task neural network toward accurate and robust performance is a de-facto standard in perception task of autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusionad-multi-modality-fusion-for-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Representation Learning for Periodic Time Series with Floss: A Frequency Domain Regularization Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-representation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we propose an unsupervised method called Floss that automatically regularizes learned representations in the frequency domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-representation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs Understand Glass-Box Models, Discover Surprises, and Suggest Repairs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-understand-glass-box-models-discover</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that large language models (LLMs) are remarkably good at working with interpretable models that decompose complex outcomes into univariate graph-represented components.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-understand-glass-box-models-discover</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Sparse to Soft Mixtures of Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-sparse-to-soft-mixtures-of-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse mixture of expert architectures (MoEs) scale model capacity without large increases in training or inference costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-sparse-to-soft-mixtures-of-experts</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
