<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 09:26:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dilated Neighborhood Attention Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilated-neighborhood-attention-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These models typically employ localized attention mechanisms, such as the sliding-window Neighborhood Attention (NA) or Swin Transformer's Shifted Window Self Attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilated-neighborhood-attention-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Complexity Required for Neural Network Pruning? A Case Study on Global Magnitude Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-complexity-required-for-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Surprisingly, we find that vanilla Global MP outperforms all the other SOTA techniques and achieves a new SOTA result.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-complexity-required-for-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proportional Multicalibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proportional-multicalibration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multicalibration is a desirable fairness criteria that constrains calibration error among flexibly-defined groups in the data while maintaining overall calibration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proportional-multicalibration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDIP: Gated Differentiable Image Processing for Object-Detection in Adverse Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gdip-gated-differentiable-image-processing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a Gated Differentiable Image Processing (GDIP) block, a domain-agnostic network architecture, which can be plugged into existing object detection networks (e. g., Yolo) and trained end-to-end with adverse condition images such as those captured under fog and low lighting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gdip-gated-differentiable-image-processing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Where to Look: Attention Similarity Knowledge Distillation for Low Resolution Face Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-where-to-look-attention-similarity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning has achieved outstanding performance for face recognition benchmarks, but performance reduces significantly for low resolution (LR) images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-where-to-look-attention-similarity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>polyBERT: A chemical language model to enable fully machine-driven ultrafast polymer informatics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polybert-a-chemical-language-model-to-enable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[polyBERT is a chemical linguist that treats the chemical structure of polymers as a chemical language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polybert-a-chemical-language-model-to-enable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients' Severity States Classification based on Electronic Health Record (EHR) Data using Multiple Machine Learning and Deep Learning Approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patients-severity-states-classification-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For implementing Deep Learning we employed a feed-forward neural network (multi-layer) and the Fast Large Margin approach for semi-supervised learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patients-severity-states-classification-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compressed Gastric Image Generation Based on Soft-Label Dataset Distillation for Medical Data Sharing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compressed-gastric-image-generation-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, our method can extract essential weights of DCNN models to reduce the memory required to save trained models for efficient medical data sharing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compressed-gastric-image-generation-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intrinsic Dimensionality Estimation within Tight Localities: A Theoretical and Experimental Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsic-dimensionality-estimation-within</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate estimation of Intrinsic Dimensionality (ID) is of crucial importance in many data mining and machine learning tasks, including dimensionality reduction, outlier detection, similarity search and subspace clustering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsic-dimensionality-estimation-within</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAF: Neural Attenuation Fields for Sparse-View CBCT Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naf-neural-attenuation-fields-for-sparse-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel and fast self-supervised solution for sparse-view CBCT reconstruction (Cone Beam Computed Tomography) that requires no external training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naf-neural-attenuation-fields-for-sparse-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Stain Normalization for Computational Pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-stain-normalization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a solution, we propose BottleGAN, a generative model that can computationally align the staining styles of many laboratories and can be trained in a privacy-preserving manner to foster federated learning in computational pathology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-stain-normalization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLO: A Contrastive Learning based Re-ranking Framework for One-Stage Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colo-a-contrastive-learning-based-re-ranking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional training paradigms for extractive and abstractive summarization systems always only use token-level or sentence-level training objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colo-a-contrastive-learning-based-re-ranking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Coarse-to-fine Cascaded Evidence-Distillation Neural Network for Explainable Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-coarse-to-fine-cascaded-evidence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing fake news detection methods aim to classify a piece of news as true or false and provide veracity explanations, achieving remarkable performances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-coarse-to-fine-cascaded-evidence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chandojnanam: A Sanskrit Meter Identification and Utilization System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chandojnanam-a-sanskrit-meter-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Chandoj\~n\=anam, a web-based Sanskrit meter (Chanda) identification and utilization system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chandojnanam-a-sanskrit-meter-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Collapse in Non-Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-collapse-in-non-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive methods have led a recent surge in the performance of self-supervised representation learning (SSL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-collapse-in-non-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SymmNeRF: Learning to Explore Symmetry Prior for Single-View View Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmnerf-learning-to-explore-symmetry-prior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of novel view synthesis of objects from a single image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmnerf-learning-to-explore-symmetry-prior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Equal-Size Hard EM Algorithm for Diverse Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-equal-size-hard-em-algorithm-for-diverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-domain dialogue systems aim to interact with humans through natural language texts in an open-ended fashion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-equal-size-hard-em-algorithm-for-diverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiGress: Discrete Denoising diffusion for graph generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/digress-discrete-denoising-diffusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces DiGress, a discrete denoising diffusion model for generating graphs with categorical node and edge attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/digress-discrete-denoising-diffusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4D-StOP: Panoptic Segmentation of 4D LiDAR using Spatio-temporal Object Proposal Generation and Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4d-stop-panoptic-segmentation-of-4d-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our voting-based tracklet generation method followed by geometric feature-based aggregation generates significantly improved panoptic LiDAR segmentation quality when compared to modeling the entire 4D volume using Gaussian probability distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4d-stop-panoptic-segmentation-of-4d-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online pseudo labeling for polyp segmentation with momentum networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-pseudo-labeling-for-polyp-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a new pseudo labeling strategy that enhances the quality of pseudo labels used for training student networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-pseudo-labeling-for-polyp-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TERMinator: A system for scientific texts processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/terminator-a-system-for-scientific-texts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper is devoted to the extraction of entities and semantic relations between them from scientific texts, where we consider scientific terms as entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/terminator-a-system-for-scientific-texts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human Motion Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-motion-diffusion-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Motion Diffusion Model (MDM), a carefully adapted classifier-free diffusion-based generative model for the human motion domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-motion-diffusion-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Posterior Sampling for General Noisy Inverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-posterior-sampling-for-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have been recently studied as powerful generative inverse problem solvers, owing to their high quality reconstructions and the ease of combining existing iterative solvers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-posterior-sampling-for-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Two-Stage Method for Chinese AMR Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-stage-method-for-chinese-amr-parsing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide a detailed description of our system at CAMRP-2022 evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-stage-method-for-chinese-amr-parsing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perturbations and Subpopulations for Testing Robustness in Token-Based Argument Unit Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perturbations-and-subpopulations-for-testing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Argument Unit Recognition and Classification aims at identifying argument units from text and classifying them as pro or against.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perturbations-and-subpopulations-for-testing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing Positional Variance in Cross-sectional Abdominal CT Slices with Deep Conditional Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-positional-variance-in-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[External experiments on 20 subjects from the Baltimore Longitudinal Study of Aging (BLSA) dataset that contains longitudinal single abdominal slices validate that our method can harmonize the slice positional variance in terms of muscle and visceral fat area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-positional-variance-in-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Compressed Sensing with Multi-scale Dilated Convolutional Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-compressed-sensing-with-multi-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During the measurement period, we directly obtain all measurements from a trained measurement network, which employs fully convolutional structures and is jointly trained with the reconstruction network from the input image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-compressed-sensing-with-multi-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Proxy Models for Concept-Based Model Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-proxy-models-for-concept-based-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core of our proposal is the Causal Proxy Model (CPM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-proxy-models-for-concept-based-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Right: Multimodal Retrieval on Representation of ImaGe witH Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mr-right-multimodal-retrieval-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce Multimodal Retrieval on Representation of ImaGe witH Text (Mr.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mr-right-multimodal-retrieval-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guiding Safe Exploration with Weakest Preconditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-safe-exploration-with-weakest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In reinforcement learning for safety-critical settings, it is often desirable for the agent to obey safety constraints at all points in time, including during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-safe-exploration-with-weakest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising of 3D MR images using a voxel-wise hybrid residual MLP-CNN model to improve small lesion diagnostic confidence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-of-3d-mr-images-using-a-voxel-wise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate the proposed method on 720 T2-FLAIR brain images with small lesions at different noise levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-of-3d-mr-images-using-a-voxel-wise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual Search with Subword TF-IDF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-search-with-subword-tf-idf</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multilingual search can be achieved with subword tokenization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-search-with-subword-tf-idf</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obj2Seq: Formatting Objects as Sequences with Class Prompt for Visual Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/obj2seq-formatting-objects-as-sequences-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Obj2Seq is able to flexibly determine input categories to satisfy customized requirements, and be easily extended to different visual tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/obj2seq-formatting-objects-as-sequences-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LL-GNN: Low Latency Graph Neural Networks on FPGAs for Particle Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ll-gnn-low-latency-graph-neural-networks-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we introduce an outer-product based matrix multiplication approach which is enhanced by the strength reduction for low latency design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ll-gnn-low-latency-graph-neural-networks-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Asynchronous and Error-prone Longitudinal Data via Functional Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-asynchronous-and-error-prone</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many longitudinal settings, time-varying covariates may not be measured at the same time as responses and are often prone to measurement error.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-asynchronous-and-error-prone</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TVLT: Textless Vision-Language Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tvlt-textless-vision-language-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present the Textless Vision-Language Transformer (TVLT), where homogeneous transformer blocks take raw visual and audio inputs for vision-and-language representation learning with minimal modality-specific design, and do not use text-specific modules such as tokenization or automatic speech recognition (ASR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tvlt-textless-vision-language-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Retrieval with WavText5K and CLAP Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-retrieval-with-wavtext5k-and-clap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new collection of web audio-text pairs and a new framework for retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-retrieval-with-wavtext5k-and-clap</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalably learning quantum many-body Hamiltonians from dynamical data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalably-learning-quantum-many-body</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The physics of a closed quantum mechanical system is governed by its Hamiltonian.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalably-learning-quantum-many-body</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing Coarse-to-Fine Deep Learning Models for Optic Disc and Cup Segmentation in Fundus Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-coarse-to-fine-deep-learning-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present a comprehensive analysis of different coarse-to-fine designs for OD/OC segmentation using 5 public databases, both from a standard segmentation perspective and for estimating the vCDR for glaucoma assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-coarse-to-fine-deep-learning-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Methods for Logical Reasoning Over Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-methods-for-logical-reasoning-over-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a set of models that use Neural Networks to create one-point vector embeddings to answer the queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-methods-for-logical-reasoning-over-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who is GPT-3? An Exploration of Personality, Values and Demographics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/who-is-gpt-3-an-exploration-of-personality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that GPT-3 scores similarly to human samples in terms of personality and - when provided with a model response memory - in terms of the values it holds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/who-is-gpt-3-an-exploration-of-personality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Video Temporal Action Segmentation In Real Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-video-temporal-action-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the real-time action segmentation task is different from TAS task, we define it as streaming video real-time temporal action segmentation (SVTAS) task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-video-temporal-action-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient block contrastive learning via parameter-free meta-node approximation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-block-contrastive-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a meta-node based approximation technique that can (a) proxy all negative combinations (b) in quadratic cluster size time complexity, (c) at graph level, not node level, and (d) exploit graph sparsity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-block-contrastive-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Prediction of Spontaneous Humour: A Novel Dataset and First Results</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-prediction-of-spontaneous-humour-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings suggest that for the automatic analysis of humour and its sentiment, facial expressions are most promising, while humour direction can be best modelled via text-based features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-prediction-of-spontaneous-humour-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLink: Linking Black-Box Models from Multiple Domains for Collaborative Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlink-linking-black-box-models-from-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The cost efficiency of model inference is critical to real-world machine learning (ML) applications, especially for delay-sensitive tasks and resource-limited devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlink-linking-black-box-models-from-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Neural Sculpting (3DNS): Editing Neural Signed Distance Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-neural-sculpting-3dns-editing-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, implicit surface representations through neural networks that encode the signed distance have gained popularity and have achieved state-of-the-art results in various tasks (e. g. shape representation, shape reconstruction, and learning shape priors).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-neural-sculpting-3dns-editing-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RuDSI: graph-based word sense induction dataset for Russian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rudsi-graph-based-word-sense-induction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present RuDSI, a new benchmark for word sense induction (WSI) in Russian.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rudsi-graph-based-word-sense-induction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>METS-CoV: A Dataset of Medical Entity and Targeted Sentiment on COVID-19 Related Tweets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mets-cov-a-dataset-of-medical-entity-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further investigate tweet users' attitudes toward specific entities, 4 types of entities (Person, Organization, Drug, and Vaccine) are selected and annotated with user sentiments, resulting in a targeted sentiment dataset with 9, 101 entities (in 5, 278 tweets).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mets-cov-a-dataset-of-medical-entity-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartMocap: Joint Estimation of Human and Camera Motion using Uncalibrated RGB Cameras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartmocap-joint-estimation-of-human-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we learn a probability distribution of short human motion sequences ($\sim$1sec) relative to the ground plane and leverage it to disambiguate between the camera and human motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartmocap-joint-estimation-of-human-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-scale Attention Network for Single Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-attention-network-for-image-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a CNN-based multi-scale attention network (MAN), which consists of multi-scale large kernel attention (MLKA) and a gated spatial attention unit (GSAU), to improve the performance of convolutional SR networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-attention-network-for-image-super</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
