<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 21:07:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ECG signal processing and feature extraction to validate feature significance for arrythmia detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecg-signal-processing-and-feature-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Arrhythmias, such as tachycardia and bradycardia, are prevalent in postoperative patients, especially within the first week after surgery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecg-signal-processing-and-feature-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A cross-sectional study to analyse the presence of low back pain in university students and its relationship with coffee</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cross-sectional-study-to-analyse-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study aims to analyze electromyography (EMG) signals of the multifidus muscles using the BiTalino device to assess chronic LBP in university students.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cross-sectional-study-to-analyse-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Automatic Metrics with Incremental Machine Translation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-automatic-metrics-with-incremental</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a dataset comprising commercial machine translations, gathered weekly over six years across 12 translation directions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-automatic-metrics-with-incremental</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IM-MoCo: Self-supervised MRI Motion Correction using Motion-Guided Implicit Neural Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/im-moco-self-supervised-mri-motion-correction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motion artifacts in Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI) arise due to relatively long acquisition times and can compromise the clinical utility of acquired images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/im-moco-self-supervised-mri-motion-correction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALTER: Augmentation for Large-Table-Based Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alter-augmentation-for-large-table-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While extensive research has explored the use of large language models (LLMs) for table-based reasoning, most approaches struggle with scalability when applied to large tables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alter-augmentation-for-large-table-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Translatotron-V(ison): An End-to-End Model for In-Image Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/translatotron-v-ison-an-end-to-end-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Among them, the target text decoder is used to alleviate the language alignment burden, and the image tokenizer converts long sequences of pixels into shorter sequences of visual tokens, preventing the model from focusing on low-level visual features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/translatotron-v-ison-an-end-to-end-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When big data actually are low-rank, or entrywise approximation of certain function-generated matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-big-data-actually-are-low-rank-or</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide a theoretical explanation of the numerical results presented in support of this argument, describing three narrower classes of functions for which $n \times n$ function-generated matrices can be approximated within an entrywise error of order $\varepsilon$ with rank $\mathcal{O}(\log(n) \varepsilon^{-2} \mathrm{polylog}(\varepsilon^{-1}))$ that is independent of the dimension $m$: (i) functions of the inner product of the two variables, (ii) functions of the squared Euclidean distance between the variables, and (iii) shift-invariant positive-definite kernels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-big-data-actually-are-low-rank-or</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotion and Intent Joint Understanding in Multimodal Conversation: A Benchmarking Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotion-and-intent-joint-understanding-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Together with the release of the dataset, we also develop an Emotion and Intent Interaction (EI$^2$) network as a reference system by modeling the deep correlation between emotion and intent in the multimodal conversation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotion-and-intent-joint-understanding-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Context Modeling in YOLOv8 for Pediatric Wrist Fracture Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-context-modeling-in-yolov8-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Children often suffer wrist injuries in daily life, while fracture injuring radiologists usually need to analyze and interpret X-ray images before surgical treatment by surgeons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-context-modeling-in-yolov8-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformal Prediction for Causal Effects of Continuous Treatments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-prediction-for-causal-effects-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, we are the first to propose conformal prediction for continuous treatments when the propensity score is unknown and must be estimated from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-prediction-for-causal-effects-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PosMLP-Video: Spatial and Temporal Relative Position Encoding for Efficient Video Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posmlp-video-spatial-and-temporal-relative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, vision Transformers and MLPs have demonstrated remarkable performance in image understanding tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posmlp-video-spatial-and-temporal-relative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biomechanics-informed Non-rigid Medical Image Registration and its Inverse Material Property Estimation with Linear and Nonlinear Elasticity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomechanics-informed-non-rigid-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The complex nonlinear elasticity theory is leveraged to formally establish the partial differential equations (PDEs) representing physics laws of biomechanical constraints that need to be satisfied, with which registration and identification tasks are treated as forward (i. e., data-driven solutions of PDEs) and inverse (i. e., parameter estimation) problems under PINNs respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomechanics-informed-non-rigid-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Framework for Quantum Finite-State Languages with Density Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-quantum-finite-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a framework that provides a simple and intuitive way to build QFAs and maximize the simulation accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-quantum-finite-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart City Surveillance Unveiling Indian Person Attributes in Real Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-city-surveillance-unveiling-indian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This project focuses on creating a smart surveillance system for Indian cities that can identify and analyze people's attributes in real time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-city-surveillance-unveiling-indian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoIR: A Comprehensive Benchmark for Code Information Retrieval Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coir-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the substantial success of Information Retrieval (IR) in various NLP tasks, most IR systems predominantly handle queries and corpora in natural language, neglecting the domain of code retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coir-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planetarium: A Rigorous Benchmark for Translating Text to Structured Planning Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planetarium-a-rigorous-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce \benchmarkName, a benchmark designed to evaluate language models' ability to generate PDDL code from natural language descriptions of planning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planetarium-a-rigorous-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Heterogeneous Treatment Effect Estimation across Out-of-Distribution Populations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-heterogeneous-treatment-effect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Heterogeneous treatment effect (HTE) estimation is vital for understanding the change of treatment effect across individuals or subgroups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-heterogeneous-treatment-effect</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Composition using Task Vectors with Learned Anisotropic Scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-composition-using-task-vectors-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we show that (1) learned anisotropic scaling allows task vectors to be more disentangled, causing less interference in composition; (2) task vector composition excels with scarce or no labeled data and is less prone to domain shift, thus leading to better generalisability; (3) mixing the most informative parameter blocks across different task vectors prior to training can reduce the memory footprint and improve the flexibility of knowledge transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-composition-using-task-vectors-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation and Analysis of GPU Algorithms for Vecchia Approximation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implementation-and-analysis-of-gpu-algorithms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that our new method outperforms the other two and then present it in the GpGpU R package.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implementation-and-analysis-of-gpu-algorithms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cactus: Towards Psychological Counseling Conversations using Cognitive Behavioral Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cactus-towards-psychological-counseling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce Cactus, a multi-turn dialogue dataset that emulates real-life interactions using the goal-oriented and structured approach of Cognitive Behavioral Therapy (CBT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cactus-towards-psychological-counseling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Zero-shot Generalization of Learned Prompts via Unsupervised Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-zero-shot-generalization-of-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach, which we call Knowledge Distillation Prompt Learning (KDPL), can be integrated into existing prompt learning techniques and eliminates the need for labeled examples during adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-zero-shot-generalization-of-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TheoremLlama: Transforming General-Purpose LLMs into Lean4 Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theoremllama-transforming-general-purpose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This scarcity results in a paucity of methodologies for training LLMs and techniques to fully utilize their capabilities in composing formal proofs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theoremllama-transforming-general-purpose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DyFADet: Dynamic Feature Aggregation for Temporal Action Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dyfadet-dynamic-feature-aggregation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on DFA, the proposed dynamic encoder layer aggregates the temporal features within the action time ranges and guarantees the discriminability of the extracted representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dyfadet-dynamic-feature-aggregation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Multimodal Image Registration for Plant Phenotyping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-multimodal-image-registration-for-plant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By leveraging depth data, our method mitigates parallax effects and thus facilitates more accurate pixel alignment across camera modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-multimodal-image-registration-for-plant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-Aware Video Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-video-instance-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce the Context-Aware Video Instance Segmentation (CAVIS), a novel framework designed to enhance instance association by integrating contextual information adjacent to each object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-video-instance-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Vision Transformer are Scalable Generative Models for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-vision-transformer-are</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a novel generative method for domain generalization in histopathology images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-vision-transformer-are</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complex Event Recognition with Symbolic Register Transducers: Extended Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-event-recognition-with-symbolic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to address this issue, our system is based on an automaton model which is a combination of symbolic and register automata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-event-recognition-with-symbolic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraCoRe: Benchmarking Graph Comprehension and Complex Reasoning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gracore-benchmarking-graph-comprehension-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating the graph comprehension and reasoning abilities of Large Language Models (LLMs) is challenging and often incomplete.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gracore-benchmarking-graph-comprehension-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistent Point Orientation for Manifold Surfaces via Boundary Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistent-point-orientation-for-manifold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a new approach for generating globally consistent normals for point clouds sampled from manifold surfaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistent-point-orientation-for-manifold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting the Performance of Deep Learning-Based Vulnerability Detection on Realistic Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-performance-of-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite deep learning models being proposed for vulnerability detection, their reliability is questionable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-performance-of-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained Scene Image Classification with Modality-Agnostic Adapter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-scene-image-classification-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new multi-modal feature fusion approach named MAA (Modality-Agnostic Adapter), trying to make the model learn the importance of different modalities in different cases adaptively, without giving a prior setting in the model architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-scene-image-classification-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Scalable Reference-Free Evaluation of Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-scalable-reference-free-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While standard evaluation scores for generative models are mostly reference-based, a reference-dependent assessment of generative models could be generally difficult due to the unavailability of applicable reference datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-scalable-reference-free-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern Neighborhood Components Analysis: A Deep Tabular Baseline Two Decades Later</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modern-neighborhood-components-analysis-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The growing success of deep learning in various domains has prompted investigations into its application to tabular data, where deep models have shown promising results compared to traditional tree-based methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modern-neighborhood-components-analysis-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SegVG: Transferring Object Bounding Box to Segmentation for Visual Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segvg-transferring-object-bounding-box-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose the Multi-layer Multi-task Encoder-Decoder as the target grounding stage, where we learn a regression query and multiple segmentation queries to ground the target by regression and segmentation of the box in each decoding layer, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segvg-transferring-object-bounding-box-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Bias Evaluation for Large Language Models Requires Prompt Variations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-bias-evaluation-for-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the sensitivity of LLMs when changing prompt variations (task instruction and prompt, few-shot examples, debias-prompt) by analyzing task performance and social bias of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-bias-evaluation-for-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedPix 2.0: A Comprehensive Multimodal Biomedical Dataset for Advanced AI Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medpix-2-0-a-comprehensive-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing interest in developing Artificial Intelligence applications in the medical domain, suffers from the lack of high-quality dataset, mainly due to privacy-related issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medpix-2-0-a-comprehensive-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-like Linguistic Biases in Neural Speech Models: Phonetic Categorization and Phonotactic Constraints in Wav2Vec2.0</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-like-linguistic-biases-in-neural-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[What do deep neural speech models know about phonology?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-like-linguistic-biases-in-neural-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerated Proton Resonance Frequency-based Magnetic Resonance Thermometry by Optimized Deep Learning Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerated-proton-resonance-frequency-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In 2-fold acceleration scenario, the RMSE of temperature map patches provided the values of 0. 888 degree centigrade and 1. 145 degree centigrade on phantom and ex vivo testing datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerated-proton-resonance-frequency-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free-SurGS: SfM-Free 3D Gaussian Splatting for Surgical Scene Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-surgs-sfm-free-3d-gaussian-splatting-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, in this paper, we propose the first SfM-free 3DGS-based method for surgical scene reconstruction by jointly optimizing the camera poses and scene representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-surgs-sfm-free-3d-gaussian-splatting-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Value-Penalized Auxiliary Control from Examples for Learning without Rewards or Demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/value-penalized-auxiliary-control-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We resolve this problem, which is exacerbated by learning auxiliary tasks, through the addition of an above-success-level value penalty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/value-penalized-auxiliary-control-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedVH: Towards Systematic Evaluation of Hallucination for Large Vision Language Models in the Medical Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medvh-towards-systematic-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Vision Language Models (LVLMs) have recently achieved superior performance in various tasks on natural image and text data, which inspires a large amount of studies for LVLMs fine-tuning and training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medvh-towards-systematic-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Uncertainty-guided Tiered Self-training Framework for Active Source-free Domain Adaptation in Prostate Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-uncertainty-guided-tiered-self-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning models have exhibited remarkable efficacy in accurately delineating the prostate for diagnosis and treatment of prostate diseases, but challenges persist in achieving robust generalization across different medical centers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-uncertainty-guided-tiered-self-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Adversarial Learning: Vector-Quantized Common Latent Space for Multi-Sequence MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-adversarial-learning-vector-quantized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a generative model that compresses discrete representations of each sequence to estimate the Gaussian distribution of vector-quantized common (VQC) latent space between multiple sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-adversarial-learning-vector-quantized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe Unlearning: A Surprisingly Effective and Generalizable Solution to Defend Against Jailbreak Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-unlearning-a-surprisingly-effective-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLMs are known to be vulnerable to jailbreak attacks, even after safety alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-unlearning-a-surprisingly-effective-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicitly Guided Information Interaction Network for Cross-modal Point Cloud Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicitly-guided-information-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Corresponding author}In this paper, we explore a novel framework, EGIInet (Explicitly Guided Information Interaction Network), a model for View-guided Point cloud Completion (ViPC) task, which aims to restore a complete point cloud from a partial one with a single view image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicitly-guided-information-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MHNet: Multi-view High-order Network for Diagnosing Neurodevelopmental Disorders Using Resting-state fMRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mhnet-multi-view-high-order-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, many models either use graph neural networks (GNN) to construct single-level brain functional networks (BFNs) or employ spatial convolution filtering for local information extraction from rs-fMRI data, often neglecting high-order features crucial for NDD classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mhnet-multi-view-high-order-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Tuning with Divergent Chains of Thought Boosts Reasoning Through Self-Correction in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-with-divergent-chains-of-thought</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In fact, it has been found that instruction tuning on these intermediary reasoning steps improves model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-with-divergent-chains-of-thought</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effect of Prolonged Smartphone Use on Trapezius and Neck Extensor Muscle Activity, Using sEMG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-prolonged-smartphone-use-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intensive use of touchscreen mobile devices has increased musculoskeletal problems, particularly in the neck and shoulders, known as "text-neck."]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-prolonged-smartphone-use-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Collapse Loss for Deep Metric Learning Based on Coding Rate Metric</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anti-collapse-loss-for-deep-metric-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep metric learning (DML) aims to learn a discriminative high-dimensional embedding space for downstream tasks like classification, clustering, and retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anti-collapse-loss-for-deep-metric-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relating CNN-Transformer Fusion Network for Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relating-cnn-transformer-fusion-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While deep learning, particularly convolutional neural networks (CNNs), has revolutionized remote sensing (RS) change detection (CD), existing approaches often miss crucial features due to neglecting global context and incomplete change learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relating-cnn-transformer-fusion-network-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
