<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 09:13:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Real-world image dehazing with improved joint enhancement and exposure fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-world-image-dehazing-with-improved-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The visual and quantitative comparisons between the proposed method and state-of-the-art dehazing methods show that the proposed method has better dehazing performance and has a 50% improvement in terms of the FADE metric compared to the closest result.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-world-image-dehazing-with-improved-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Generalizable Perceptual Representations for Data-Efficient No-Reference Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-generalizable-perceptual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[No-reference (NR) image quality assessment (IQA) is an important tool in enhancing the user experience in diverse visual applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-generalizable-perceptual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMID: A Comprehensive Real-world Dataset for Trademark Infringement Detection in E-Commerce</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tmid-a-comprehensive-real-world-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Annually, e-commerce platforms incur substantial financial losses due to trademark infringements, making it crucial to identify and mitigate potential legal risks tied to merchant information registered to the platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tmid-a-comprehensive-real-world-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radar Perception in Autonomous Driving: Exploring Different Data Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radar-perception-in-autonomous-driving-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This review focuses on exploring different radar data representations utilized in autonomous driving systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radar-perception-in-autonomous-driving-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape-aware Segmentation of the Placenta in BOLD Fetal MRI Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-aware-segmentation-of-the-placenta-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a machine learning segmentation framework for placental BOLD MRI and apply it to segmenting each volume in a time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-aware-segmentation-of-the-placenta-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt-In-Prompt Learning for Universal Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-in-prompt-learning-for-universal-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we devise a novel prompt-to-prompt interaction module to fuse these two prompts into a universal restoration prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-in-prompt-learning-for-universal-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UDiffText: A Unified Framework for High-quality Text Synthesis in Arbitrary Images via Character-aware Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/udifftext-a-unified-framework-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-Image (T2I) generation methods based on diffusion model have garnered significant attention in the last few years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/udifftext-a-unified-framework-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Quantification and Propagation in Surrogate-based Bayesian Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-and-propagation-in-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is a task where the propagation of surrogate uncertainty is especially relevant, because failing to account for it may lead to biased and/or overconfident estimates of the parameters of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-and-propagation-in-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniTSA: A Universal Reinforcement Learning Framework for V2X Traffic Signal Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitsa-a-universal-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traffic congestion is a persistent problem in urban areas, which calls for the development of effective traffic signal control (TSC) systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitsa-a-universal-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Prompt-Based Self-Training With Mapping-Free Automatic Verbalizer for Multi-Class Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-prompt-based-self-training-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, prompt-based fine-tuning has garnered considerable interest as a core technique for few-shot text classification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-prompt-based-self-training-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoology: Measuring and Improving Recall in Efficient Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zoology-measuring-and-improving-recall-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To close the gap between synthetics and real language, we develop a new formalization of the task called multi-query associative recall (MQAR) that better reflects actual language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zoology-measuring-and-improving-recall-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unify Change Point Detection and Segment Classification in a Regression Task for Transportation Mode Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unify-change-point-detection-and-segment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve above-mentioned problems, inspired by YOLO and SSD in object detection, we propose to reframe change point detection and segment classification as a unified regression task instead of the existing classification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unify-change-point-detection-and-segment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DelucionQA: Detecting Hallucinations in Domain-specific Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delucionqa-detecting-hallucinations-in-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hallucination is a well-known phenomenon in text generated by large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delucionqa-detecting-hallucinations-in-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape Matters: Detecting Vertebral Fractures Using Differentiable Point-Based Shape Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-matters-detecting-vertebral-fractures</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we specifically explore the use of shape auto-encoders for vertebrae, taking advantage of advancements in automated multi-label segmentation and the availability of large datasets for unsupervised learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-matters-detecting-vertebral-fractures</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking and Analysis of Unsupervised Object Segmentation from Real-world Single Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-and-analysis-of-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first introduce seven complexity factors to quantitatively measure the distributions of background and foreground object biases in appearance and geometry for datasets with human annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-and-analysis-of-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Explanations to Understand and Repair Embedding-based Entity Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-explanations-to-understand-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present the first framework that can generate explanations for understanding and repairing embedding-based entity alignment results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-explanations-to-understand-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KwaiAgents: Generalized Information-seeking Agent System with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kwaiagents-generalized-information-seeking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driven by curiosity, humans have continually sought to explore and understand the world around them, leading to the invention of various tools to satiate this inquisitiveness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kwaiagents-generalized-information-seeking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformal Prediction in Multi-User Settings: An Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-prediction-in-multi-user-settings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although those strategies are better suited for multi-user systems, they are typically assessed with respect to performance metrics that capture the overall behavior of the models and do not provide any performance guarantees for individual predictions nor they provide any feedback about the predictions' uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-prediction-in-multi-user-settings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seamless: Multilingual Expressive and Streaming Speech Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seamless-multilingual-expressive-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a family of models that enable end-to-end expressive and multilingual translations in a streaming fashion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seamless-multilingual-expressive-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREDSum: A Dialogue Summarization Corpus for French Political Debates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fredsum-a-dialogue-summarization-corpus-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a dataset of French political debates for the purpose of enhancing resources for multi-lingual dialogue summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fredsum-a-dialogue-summarization-corpus-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFLlib: Personalized Federated Learning Algorithm Library</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pfllib-personalized-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Amid the ongoing advancements in Federated Learning (FL), a machine learning paradigm that allows collaborative learning with data privacy protection, personalized FL (pFL) has gained significant prominence as a research direction within the FL domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pfllib-personalized-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffCMR: Fast Cardiac MRI Reconstruction with Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffcmr-fast-cardiac-mri-reconstruction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Performing magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) reconstruction from under-sampled k-space data can accelerate the procedure to acquire MRI scans and reduce patients' discomfort.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffcmr-fast-cardiac-mri-reconstruction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of Context: How important is Local Context in Neural Program Repair?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-context-how-important-is-local-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results indicate that overall repair success increases with the size of the local context (albeit not for all bug types) and confirm the common practice that roughly 50-60% of the input window should be used for context leading the bug.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-context-how-important-is-local-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predictive Chemistry Augmented with Text Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictive-chemistry-augmented-with-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventionally, chemoinformatics models are trained with extensive structured data manually extracted from the literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictive-chemistry-augmented-with-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moirai: Towards Optimal Placement for Distributed Inference on Heterogeneous Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moirai-towards-optimal-placement-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents Moirai that better exploits runtime inter-operator fusion in a model to render a coarsened computation graph, reducing the search space while maintaining the inter-operator optimization provided by inference backends.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moirai-towards-optimal-placement-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PCoQA: Persian Conversational Question Answering Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcoqa-persian-conversational-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our models include baseline models and pre-trained models, which are leveraged to boost the performance of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcoqa-persian-conversational-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nerblackbox: A High-level Library for Named Entity Recognition in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerblackbox-a-high-level-library-for-named</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present nerblackbox, a python library to facilitate the use of state-of-the-art transformer-based models for named entity recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerblackbox-a-high-level-library-for-named</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeanCut: A Greedy-Optimized Graph Clustering via Path-based Similarity and Degree Descent Criterion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meancut-a-greedy-optimized-graph-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the most typical graph clustering method, spectral clustering is popular and attractive due to the remarkable performance, easy implementation, and strong adaptability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meancut-a-greedy-optimized-graph-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Structural-Clustering Based Active Learning for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-structural-clustering-based-active-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we propose the Structural-Clustering PageRank method for improved Active learning (SPA) specifically designed for graph-structured data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-structural-clustering-based-active-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MuRF: Multi-Baseline Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/murf-multi-baseline-radiance-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Multi-Baseline Radiance Fields (MuRF), a general feed-forward approach to solving sparse view synthesis under multiple different baseline settings (small and large baselines, and different number of input views).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/murf-multi-baseline-radiance-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caregiver Talk Shapes Toddler Vision: A Computational Study of Dyadic Play</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caregiver-talk-shapes-toddler-vision-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this we propose a computational model of visual representation learning during dyadic play.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caregiver-talk-shapes-toddler-vision-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Feedback All You Need? Leveraging Natural Language Feedback in Goal-Conditioned Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-feedback-all-you-need-leveraging-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite numerous successes, the field of reinforcement learning (RL) remains far from matching the impressive generalisation power of human behaviour learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-feedback-all-you-need-leveraging-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Area Estimation of Case Growths for Timely COVID-19 Outbreak Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/small-area-estimation-of-case-growths-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we conducted a case study based on outbreak case data from the state of Colorado and showed that the timely detection of outbreaks could have been improved by up to 224% using TLGRF when compared to the decisions made by Colorado's Department of Health and Environment (CDPHE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/small-area-estimation-of-case-growths-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Model Knowledge Distillation for Efficient Question Answering in Spanish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-model-knowledge-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in the development of pre-trained Spanish language models has led to significant progress in many Natural Language Processing (NLP) tasks, such as question answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-model-knowledge-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transferable Candidate Proposal with Bounded Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferable-candidate-proposal-with-bounded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this issue, we introduce a new experimental design, coined as Candidate Proposal, to find transferable data candidates from which active learning algorithms choose the informative subset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferable-candidate-proposal-with-bounded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn to Unlearn for Deep Neural Networks: Minimizing Unlearning Interference with Gradient Projection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-to-unlearn-for-deep-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent data-privacy laws have sparked interest in machine unlearning, which involves removing the effect of specific training samples from a learnt model as if they were never present in the original training dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-to-unlearn-for-deep-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Big to Small Without Losing It All: Text Augmentation with ChatGPT for Efficient Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-big-to-small-without-losing-it-all-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the era of artificial intelligence, data is gold but costly to annotate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-big-to-small-without-losing-it-all-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Knowledge-driven Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-knowledge-driven-autonomous-driving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the emerging knowledge-driven autonomous driving technologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-knowledge-driven-autonomous-driving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constraint Model for the Satellite Image Mosaic Selection Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constraint-model-for-the-satellite-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More precisely, for this problem the input is an area of interest, several satellite images intersecting the area, a list of requirements relative to the image and the mosaic, such as cloud coverage percentage, image resolution, and a list of objectives to optimize.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constraint-model-for-the-satellite-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Surface: Probing LLaMA Across Scales and Layers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-surface-probing-llama-across-scales</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an in-depth analysis of Large Language Models (LLMs), focusing on LLaMA, a prominent open-source foundational model in natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-surface-probing-llama-across-scales</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Registration of Images and LiDAR Point Clouds with VoxelPoint-to-Pixel Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-registration-of-images-and-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these problems, we propose to learn a structured cross-modality latent space to represent pixel features and 3D features via a differentiable probabilistic PnP solver.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-registration-of-images-and-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PrimDiffusion: Volumetric Primitives Diffusion for 3D Human Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/primdiffusion-volumetric-primitives-diffusion-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present PrimDiffusion, the first diffusion-based framework for 3D human generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/primdiffusion-volumetric-primitives-diffusion-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free3D: Consistent Novel View Synthesis without 3D Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free3d-consistent-novel-view-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Free3D, a simple approach designed for open-set novel view synthesis (NVS) from a single image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free3d-consistent-novel-view-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CODEX: A Cluster-Based Method for Explainable Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codex-a-cluster-based-method-for-explainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the impressive feats demonstrated by Reinforcement Learning (RL), these algorithms have seen little adoption in high-risk, real-world applications due to current difficulties in explaining RL agent actions and building user trust.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codex-a-cluster-based-method-for-explainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Scalar Fields for Molecular Docking with Fast Fourier Transforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-scalar-fields-for-molecular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The runtime of our approach can be amortized at several levels of abstraction, and is particularly favorable for virtual screening settings with a common binding pocket.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-scalar-fields-for-molecular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotional Speech-driven 3D Body Animation via Disentangled Latent Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotional-speech-driven-3d-body-animation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Once trained, AMUSE synthesizes 3D human gestures directly from speech with control over the expressed emotions and style by combining the content from the driving speech with the emotion and style of another speech sequence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotional-speech-driven-3d-body-animation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic volumetric speckle suppression in OCT using deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-volumetric-speckle-suppression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a deep learning framework for volumetric speckle reduction in optical coherence tomography (OCT) based on a conditional generative adversarial network (cGAN) that leverages the volumetric nature of OCT data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-volumetric-speckle-suppression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Series2Vec: Similarity-based Self-supervised Representation Learning for Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/series2vec-similarity-based-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our evaluation of Series2Vec on nine large real-world datasets, along with the UCR/UEA archive, shows enhanced performance compared to current state-of-the-art self-supervised techniques for time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/series2vec-similarity-based-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Impact of Multi-dimensional Local Differential Privacy on Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-impact-of-multi-dimensional-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated decision systems are increasingly used to make consequential decisions in people's lives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-impact-of-multi-dimensional-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyThaiNLP: Thai Natural Language Processing in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pythainlp-thai-natural-language-processing-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It provides a wide range of software, models, and datasets for Thai language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pythainlp-thai-natural-language-processing-in</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
