<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 09:13:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>HPix: Generating Vector Maps from Satellite Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hpix-generating-vector-maps-from-satellite</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vector maps find widespread utility across diverse domains due to their capacity to not only store but also represent discrete data boundaries such as building footprints, disaster impact analysis, digitization, urban planning, location points, transport links, and more.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hpix-generating-vector-maps-from-satellite</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmark Agreement Testing Done Right: A Guide for LLM Benchmark Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-agreement-testing-done-right-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the crucial role of BAT for benchmark builders and consumers, there are no standardized procedures for such agreement testing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-agreement-testing-done-right-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TXL-PBC: a freely accessible labeled peripheral blood cell dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/txl-pbc-a-freely-accessible-labeled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we used the YOLOv8n model to train these three datasets, the performance of the TXL-PBC dataset surpass the original two datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/txl-pbc-a-freely-accessible-labeled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SA-DVAE: Improving Zero-Shot Skeleton-Based Action Recognition by Disentangled Variational Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-dvae-improving-zero-shot-skeleton-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing zero-shot skeleton-based action recognition methods utilize projection networks to learn a shared latent space of skeleton features and semantic embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-dvae-improving-zero-shot-skeleton-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANHALTEN: Cross-Lingual Transfer for German Token-Level Reference-Free Hallucination Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anhalten-cross-lingual-transfer-for-german</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Research on token-level reference-free hallucination detection has predominantly focused on English, primarily due to the scarcity of robust datasets in other languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anhalten-cross-lingual-transfer-for-german</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPSFormer: A Global Perception and Local Structure Fitting-based Transformer for Point Cloud Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpsformer-a-global-perception-and-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core of GPSFormer is the Global Perception Module (GPM) and the Local Structure Fitting Convolution (LSFConv).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpsformer-a-global-perception-and-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Sight and Sound: Advanced Sound Source Localization Through Audio-Visual Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-sight-and-sound-advanced-sound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we introduce new evaluation metrics to rigorously assess sound source localization methods, focusing on accurately evaluating both localization performance and cross-modal interaction ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-sight-and-sound-advanced-sound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Language of Infographics: Toward Understanding Conceptual Metaphor Use in Scientific Storytelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-language-of-infographics-toward</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our classification of the visual conceptual mappings within scientific representations is based on the breakdown of visual components in existing scientific infographics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-language-of-infographics-toward</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scikit-fingerprints: easy and efficient computation of molecular fingerprints in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scikit-fingerprints-easy-and-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present \textit{scikit-fingerprints}, a Python package for computation of molecular fingerprints for applications in chemoinformatics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scikit-fingerprints-easy-and-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fixed and Adaptive Simultaneous Machine Translation Strategies Using Adapters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fixed-and-adaptive-simultaneous-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The wait-$k$ policy offers a solution by starting to translate after consuming $k$ words, where the choice of the number $k$ directly affects the latency and quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fixed-and-adaptive-simultaneous-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCNv3: Towards Next Generation Deep Cross Network for CTR Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcnv3-towards-next-generation-deep-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep & Cross Network and its derivative models have become an important paradigm in click-through rate (CTR) prediction due to their effective balance between computational cost and performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcnv3-towards-next-generation-deep-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Temporal Action Localization: Advanced S6 Modeling with Recurrent Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-temporal-action-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal Action Localization (TAL) is a critical task in video analysis, identifying precise start and end times of actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-temporal-action-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heart-Mind Harmony: Predicting Stress from Heart Rate</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heart-mind-harmony-predicting-stress-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[in the end, the findings of this research may additionally have broader implications for improving the satisfactory of existence and basic properly-being of individuals via permitting early pressure detection and intervention thru the analysis of heart price statistics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heart-mind-harmony-predicting-stress-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using LLMs to Investigate Correlations of Conversational Follow-up Queries with User Satisfaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-llms-to-investigate-correlations-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From qualitative analysis of 250 conversational turns from an in-lab user evaluation of Naver Cue:, a commercial conversational search engine, we propose a taxonomy of 18 users' follow-up query patterns from conversational search, comprising two major axes: (1) users' motivations behind continuing conversations (N = 7) and (2) actions of follow-up queries (N = 11).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-llms-to-investigate-correlations-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlcLaM: Arabic Dialectal Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alclam-arabic-dialectal-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Arabic-specific PLMs are trained predominantly on modern standard Arabic, which compromises their performance on regional dialects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alclam-arabic-dialectal-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous reasoning for adaptive container image distribution in the cloud-edge continuum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-reasoning-for-adaptive-container</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cloud-edge computing requires applications to operate across diverse infrastructures, often triggered by cyber-physical events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-reasoning-for-adaptive-container</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lacuna Language Learning: Leveraging RNNs for Ranked Text Completion in Digitized Coptic Manuscripts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lacuna-language-learning-leveraging-rnns-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While not suitable for definitive manuscript reconstruction, we argue that our RNN model can help scholars rank the likelihood of textual reconstructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lacuna-language-learning-leveraging-rnns-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphMuse: A Library for Symbolic Music Graph Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphmuse-a-library-for-symbolic-music-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing this gap, we present GraphMuse, a graph processing framework and library that facilitates efficient music graph processing and GNN training for symbolic music tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphmuse-a-library-for-symbolic-music-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating 3D House Wireframes with Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-3d-house-wireframes-with-semantics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new approach for generating 3D house wireframes with semantic enrichment using an autoregressive model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-3d-house-wireframes-with-semantics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoME: Mixture of Multimodal Experts for Generalist Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mome-mixture-of-multimodal-experts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a mixture of multimodal experts (MoME) to mitigate task interference and obtain a generalist MLLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mome-mixture-of-multimodal-experts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstraction Alignment: Comparing Model and Human Conceptual Relationships</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstraction-alignment-comparing-model-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Abstraction -- the process of generalizing specific examples into broad reusable patterns -- is central to how people efficiently process and store information and apply their knowledge to new data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstraction-alignment-comparing-model-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeneralAD: Anomaly Detection Across Domains by Attending to Distorted Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalad-anomaly-detection-across-domains-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These features are fed to an attention-based discriminator, which is trained to score every patch in the image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalad-anomaly-detection-across-domains-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Wrist Abnormality Detection with YOLO: Analysis of State-of-the-art Single-stage Detection Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-wrist-abnormality-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diagnosing and treating abnormalities in the wrist, specifically distal radius, and ulna fractures, is a crucial concern among children, adolescents, and young adults, with a higher incidence rate during puberty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-wrist-abnormality-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reliable and Efficient Concept Erasure of Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliable-and-efficient-concept-erasure-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Reliable and Efficient Concept Erasure (RECE), a novel approach that modifies the model in 3 seconds without necessitating additional fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliable-and-efficient-concept-erasure-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LMMs-Eval: Reality Check on the Evaluation of Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmms-eval-reality-check-on-the-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To approach this evaluation trilemma, we further introduce LMMS-EVAL LITE, a pruned evaluation toolkit that emphasizes both coverage and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmms-eval-reality-check-on-the-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch-Level Training for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-level-training-for-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As Large Language Models (LLMs) achieve remarkable progress in language understanding and generation, their training efficiency has become a critical concern.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-level-training-for-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMAGDressing-v1: Customizable Virtual Dressing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagdressing-v1-customizable-virtual-dressing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Latest advances have achieved realistic virtual try-on (VTON) through localized garment inpainting using latent diffusion models, significantly enhancing consumers' online shopping experience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagdressing-v1-customizable-virtual-dressing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weighting Pseudo-Labels via High-Activation Feature Index Similarity and Object Detection for Semi-Supervised Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighting-pseudo-labels-via-high-activation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we unify the predictions from a trained object detector and a semantic segmentation model to identify reliable pseudo-label pixels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighting-pseudo-labels-via-high-activation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLARE: Low Light Image Enhancement via Generative Latent Feature based Codebook Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glare-low-light-image-enhancement-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing Low-light Image Enhancement (LLIE) methods either directly map Low-Light (LL) to Normal-Light (NL) images or use semantic or illumination maps as guides.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glare-low-light-image-enhancement-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfoNorm: Mutual Information Shaping of Normals for Sparse-View Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infonorm-mutual-information-shaping-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D surface reconstruction from multi-view images is essential for scene understanding and interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infonorm-mutual-information-shaping-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AudienceView: AI-Assisted Interpretation of Audience Feedback in Journalism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audienceview-ai-assisted-interpretation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding and making use of audience feedback is important but difficult for journalists, who now face an impractically large volume of audience comments online.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audienceview-ai-assisted-interpretation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenRC: Generative 3D Room Completion from Sparse Image Collections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genrc-generative-3d-room-completion-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GenRC outperforms state-of-the-art methods under most appearance and geometric metrics on ScanNet and ARKitScenes datasets, even though GenRC is not trained on these datasets nor using predefined camera trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genrc-generative-3d-room-completion-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Understanding Unsafe Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-understanding-unsafe-video-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the labeled information and the corresponding prompts, we created the first dataset of unsafe videos generated by VGMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-understanding-unsafe-video-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharif-STR at SemEval-2024 Task 1: Transformer as a Regression Model for Fine-Grained Scoring of Textual Semantic Relations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharif-str-at-semeval-2024-task-1-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study focuses on assessing the efficacy of this approach across different languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharif-str-at-semeval-2024-task-1-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentPoison: Red-teaming LLM Agents via Poisoning Memory or Knowledge Bases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentpoison-red-teaming-llm-agents-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we form the trigger generation process as a constrained optimization to optimize backdoor triggers by mapping the triggered instances to a unique embedding space, so as to ensure that whenever a user instruction contains the optimized backdoor trigger, the malicious demonstrations are retrieved from the poisoned memory or knowledge base with high probability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentpoison-red-teaming-llm-agents-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SG-NeRF: Neural Surface Reconstruction with Scene Graph Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sg-nerf-neural-surface-reconstruction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this challenge, we present a novel approach that optimizes radiance fields with scene graphs to mitigate the influence of outlier poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sg-nerf-neural-surface-reconstruction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E5-V: Universal Embeddings with Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e5-v-universal-embeddings-with-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a single modality training approach for E5-V, where the model is trained exclusively on text pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e5-v-universal-embeddings-with-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VCP-CLIP: A visual context prompting model for zero-shot anomaly segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vcp-clip-a-visual-context-prompting-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this end, we propose a visual context prompting model (VCP-CLIP) for ZSAS task based on CLIP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vcp-clip-a-visual-context-prompting-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Context-Based Low-Light Image Enhancement via Neural Implicit Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-context-based-low-light-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current deep learning-based low-light image enhancement methods often struggle with high-resolution images, and fail to meet the practical demands of visual perception across diverse and unseen scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-context-based-low-light-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-level Adaptive Self-Labeling for Novel Class Discovery in Point Cloud Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-level-adaptive-self-labeling-for-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We tackle the novel class discovery in point cloud segmentation, which discovers novel classes based on the semantic knowledge of seen classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-level-adaptive-self-labeling-for-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlimFlow: Training Smaller One-Step Diffusion Models with Rectified Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slimflow-training-smaller-one-step-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rectified flow framework trains one-step generative models using two operations, reflow and distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slimflow-training-smaller-one-step-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaLog: Post-Training Quantization for Vision Transformers with Adaptive Logarithm Quantizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adalog-post-training-quantization-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose a novel non-uniform quantizer, dubbed the Adaptive Logarithm AdaLog (AdaLog) quantizer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adalog-post-training-quantization-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ER-FSL: Experience Replay with Feature Subspace Learning for Online Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/er-fsl-experience-replay-with-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing replay-based methods mitigate forgetting by replaying buffered samples from old data and learning current samples of new data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/er-fsl-experience-replay-with-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Better Angels of Machine Personality: How Personality Relates to LLM Safety</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-better-angels-of-machine-personality-how</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we discover that LLMs' personality traits are closely related to their safety abilities, i. e., toxicity, privacy, and fairness, based on the reliable MBTI-M scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-better-angels-of-machine-personality-how</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HGL: Hierarchical Geometry Learning for Test-time Adaptation in 3D Point Cloud Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgl-hierarchical-geometry-learning-for-test</link>
      <description><![CDATA[HGL comprises three complementary modules from local, global to temporal learning in a bottom-up manner. Technically, we first construct a local geometry learning module for pseudo-label generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgl-hierarchical-geometry-learning-for-test</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Dependency Framework for Enhancing Discourse Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-dependency-framework-for-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By converting both PDTB and RST annotations for the same texts into dependencies, this study also applies ``dependency distance'' metrics to examine the correlation between RST dependencies and PDTB dependencies in English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-dependency-framework-for-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Case2Code: Learning Inductive Reasoning with Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/case2code-learning-inductive-reasoning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we hope to focus on evaluating and teaching LLMs to conduct inductive reasoning, that is, LLMs are supposed to infer underlying rules by observing examples or sequential transformations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/case2code-learning-inductive-reasoning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SafePowerGraph: Safety-aware Evaluation of Graph Neural Networks for Transmission Power Grids</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safepowergraph-safety-aware-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide at https://github. com/yamizi/SafePowerGraph our open-source repository, a comprehensive leaderboard, a dataset and model zoo and expect our framework to standardize and advance research in the critical field of GNN for power systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safepowergraph-safety-aware-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoGuide: Geometric guidance of diffusion models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geoguide-geometric-guidance-of-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although ADM-G successfully generates elements from the given class, there is a significant quality gap compared to a model originally conditioned on this class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geoguide-geometric-guidance-of-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of Length Text Recognition with Sub-String Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-length-text-recognition-with-sub</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we term this the Out of Length (OOL) text recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-length-text-recognition-with-sub</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
