<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 21:09:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>BSAFusion: A Bidirectional Stepwise Feature Alignment Network for Unaligned Medical Image Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bsafusion-a-bidirectional-stepwise-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, this paper proposes an unaligned medical image fusion method called Bidirectional Stepwise Feature Alignment and Fusion (BSFA-F) strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bsafusion-a-bidirectional-stepwise-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InvDiff: Invariant Guidance for Bias Mitigation in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invdiff-invariant-guidance-for-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we employ a lightweight trainable module that automatically preserves invariant semantic information and uses it to guide the diffusion model's sampling process toward unbiased outcomes simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invdiff-invariant-guidance-for-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edge-Splitting MLP: Node Classification on Homophilic and Heterophilic Graphs without Message Passing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge-splitting-mlp-node-classification-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MLP-based models do not use message passing, \eg Graph-MLP incorporates the neighborhood in a separate loss function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge-splitting-mlp-node-classification-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GR-NLP-TOOLKIT: An Open-Source NLP Toolkit for Modern Greek</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gr-nlp-toolkit-an-open-source-nlp-toolkit-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present GR-NLP-TOOLKIT, an open-source natural language processing (NLP) toolkit developed specifically for modern Greek.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gr-nlp-toolkit-an-open-source-nlp-toolkit-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAFIRE: Segment Any Forged Image Region</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safire-segment-any-forged-image-region</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Each point on an image is used to segment the source region containing itself.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safire-segment-any-forged-image-region</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FuzzDistill: Intelligent Fuzzing Target Selection using Compile-Time Analysis and Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fuzzdistill-intelligent-fuzzing-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fuzz testing is a fundamental technique employed to identify vulnerabilities within software systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fuzzdistill-intelligent-fuzzing-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPD-1: Generative Pre-training for Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpd-1-generative-pre-training-for-driving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We represent each scene with ego, agent, and map tokens and formulate autonomous driving as a unified token generation problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpd-1-generative-pre-training-for-driving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeRF-NQA: No-Reference Quality Assessment for Scenes Generated by NeRF and Neural View Synthesis Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerf-nqa-no-reference-quality-assessment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the issues above, we propose NeRF-NQA, the first no-reference quality assessment method for densely-observed scenes synthesized from the NVS and NeRF variants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerf-nqa-no-reference-quality-assessment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmenting Sequential Recommendation with Balanced Relevance and Diversity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-sequential-recommendation-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel Balanced data Augmentation Plugin for Sequential Recommendation (BASRec) to generate data that balance relevance and diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-sequential-recommendation-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NLPineers@ NLU of Devanagari Script Languages 2025: Hate Speech Detection using Ensembling of BERT-based models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlpineers-nlu-of-devanagari-script-languages</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores hate speech detection in Devanagari-scripted languages, focusing on Hindi and Nepali, for Subtask B of the CHIPSAL@COLING 2025 Shared Task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlpineers-nlu-of-devanagari-script-languages</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illusory VQA: Benchmarking and Enhancing Multimodal Models on Visual Illusions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illusory-vqa-benchmarking-and-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, Visual Question Answering (VQA) has made significant strides, particularly with the advent of multimodal models that integrate vision and language understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illusory-vqa-benchmarking-and-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Template Matters: Understanding the Role of Instruction Templates in Multimodal Language Model Evaluation and Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/template-matters-understanding-the-role-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Models tuned on our augmented dataset achieve the best overall performance when compared with the same scale MLMs tuned on at most 75 times the scale of our augmented dataset, highlighting the importance of instruction templates in MLM training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/template-matters-understanding-the-role-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SegFace: Face Segmentation of Long-Tail Classes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segface-face-segmentation-of-long-tail</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Face parsing refers to the semantic segmentation of human faces into key facial regions such as eyes, nose, hair, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segface-face-segmentation-of-long-tail</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Large Vision-Language Models via Directed Scene Graph for Comprehensive Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-vision-language-models-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating detailed captions comprehending text-rich visual content in images has received growing attention for Large Vision-Language Models (LVLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-vision-language-models-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPEAT: Improving Uncertainty Estimation in Representation Learning Explainability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repeat-improving-uncertainty-estimation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[REPEAT leverages the stochasticity of current R-XAI methods to produce multiple estimates of importance, thus considering each pixel in an image as a Bernoulli random variable that is either important or unimportant.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repeat-improving-uncertainty-estimation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Flow Fields in Attention for Controllable Person Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-flow-fields-in-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we show that our loss is model-agnostic and can be used to improve the performance of other diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-flow-fields-in-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDSG: Graph Diffusion-based Solution Generation for Optimization Problems in MEC Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gdsg-graph-diffusion-based-solution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We build GDSG as a multi-task diffusion model utilizing a Graph Neural Network (GNN) to acquire the distribution of high-quality solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gdsg-graph-diffusion-based-solution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TryOffAnyone: Tiled Cloth Generation from a Dressed Person</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tryoffanyone-tiled-cloth-generation-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The fashion industry is increasingly leveraging computer vision and deep learning technologies to enhance online shopping experiences and operational efficiencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tryoffanyone-tiled-cloth-generation-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRL for Restless Multi-Armed Bandits with Applications in Maternal and Child Health</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irl-for-restless-multi-armed-bandits-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this shortcoming, this paper is the first to present the use of inverse reinforcement learning (IRL) to learn desired rewards for RMABs, and we demonstrate improved outcomes in a maternal and child health telehealth program.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irl-for-restless-multi-armed-bandits-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concept Bottleneck Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-bottleneck-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate two essential tasks in the NLP domain: text classification and text generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-bottleneck-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visible and Infrared Image Fusion Using Encoder-Decoder Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visible-and-infrared-image-fusion-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The aim of multispectral image fusion is to combine object or scene features of images with different spectral characteristics to increase the perceptual quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visible-and-infrared-image-fusion-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextRefiner: Internal Visual Feature as Efficient Refiner for Vision-Language Models Prompt Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textrefiner-internal-visual-feature-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce TextRefiner, a plug-and-play method to refine the text prompts of existing methods by leveraging the internal knowledge of VLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textrefiner-internal-visual-feature-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Conversational Mental Manipulation with Intent-Aware Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-conversational-mental-manipulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mental manipulation severely undermines mental wellness by covertly and negatively distorting decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-conversational-mental-manipulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConDSeg: A General Medical Image Segmentation Framework via Contrast-Driven Feature Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/condseg-a-general-medical-image-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the one hand, there is often a ``soft boundary'' between foreground and background in medical images, with poor illumination and low contrast further reducing the distinguishability of foreground and background within the image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/condseg-a-general-medical-image-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Prompt Alignment for Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-prompt-alignment-for-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image generation has advanced rapidly, yet aligning complex textual prompts with generated visuals remains challenging, especially with intricate object relationships and fine-grained details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-prompt-alignment-for-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Classification Using Singular Value Decomposition and Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-classification-using-singular-value</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the applicability of Singular Value Decomposition for the image classification of specific breeds of cats and dogs using fur color as the primary identifying feature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-classification-using-singular-value</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Data Augmentation and Training for Perception DNN in Autonomous Aerial Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-data-augmentation-and-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, synthetic data generation solutions for aerial vehicles are still lacking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-data-augmentation-and-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QAPyramid: Fine-grained Evaluation of Content Selection for Text Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qapyramid-fine-grained-evaluation-of-content</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Pyramid human evaluation protocol, which assesses content selection by breaking the reference summary into sub-units and verifying their presence in the system summary, has been widely adopted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qapyramid-fine-grained-evaluation-of-content</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Potential of Reverse Distillation for Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-potential-of-reverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Distillation (KD) is a promising approach for unsupervised Anomaly Detection (AD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-potential-of-reverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Motion Transfer with Diffusion Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-motion-transfer-with-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose DiTFlow, a method for transferring the motion of a reference video to a newly synthesized one, designed specifically for Diffusion Transformers (DiT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-motion-transfer-with-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-PoE: Multiple Choice Reasoning via. Process of Elimination using Multi-Modal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-poe-multiple-choice-reasoning-via-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Critically, this approach not only broadens the application of the elimination process to multi-modal contexts but also allows few-shot experiments, thereby addressing two principal limitations concerning usage of PoE only in zero-shot settings and only with a language-only framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-poe-multiple-choice-reasoning-via-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hallucination Elimination and Semantic Enhancement Framework for Vision-Language Models in Traffic Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallucination-elimination-and-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large vision-language models (LVLMs) have demonstrated remarkable capabilities in multimodal understanding and generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallucination-elimination-and-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frame Representation Hypothesis: Multi-Token LLM Interpretability and Concept-Guided Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frame-representation-hypothesis-multi-token</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interpretability is a key challenge in fostering trust for Large Language Models (LLMs), which stems from the complexity of extracting reasoning from model's parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frame-representation-hypothesis-multi-token</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maya: An Instruction Finetuned Multilingual Multimodal Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maya-an-instruction-finetuned-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of large Vision-Language Models (VLMs) has led to impressive results on academic benchmarks, primarily in widely spoken languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maya-an-instruction-finetuned-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Federated Learning Framework Against Gradient Inversion Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-federated-learning-framework-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By revisiting the key to privacy exposure in FL under GIA, which lies in the frequent sharing of model gradients that contain private data, we take a new perspective by designing a novel privacy preserve FL framework that effectively ``breaks the direct connection'' between the shared parameters and the local private data to defend against GIA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-federated-learning-framework-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Training Statistical Calibration for Higher Activation Sparsity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-training-statistical-calibration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Statistical Calibrated Activation Pruning (SCAP), a post-training activation pruning framework that (1) generalizes sparsification by input activations of Fully-Connected layers for generic and flexible application across Transformers, and (2) features a simple Mode-Centering technique to pre-calibrate activation distributions for maximizing post-training sparsity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-training-statistical-calibration-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntellectSeeker: A Personalized Literature Management System with the Probabilistic Model and Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intellectseeker-a-personalized-literature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce IntellectSeeker, an innovative and personalized intelligent academic literature management platform to address these challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intellectseeker-a-personalized-literature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EvRepSL: Event-Stream Representation via Self-Supervised Learning for Event-Based Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evrepsl-event-stream-representation-via-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most of the state-of-the-art event-stream representations are manually designed and the quality of these representations cannot be guaranteed due to the noisy nature of event-streams.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evrepsl-event-stream-representation-via-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ArtFormer: Controllable Generation of Diverse 3D Articulated Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artformer-controllable-generation-of-diverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel framework for modeling and conditional generation of 3D articulated objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artformer-controllable-generation-of-diverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Method for Evaluating Hyperparameter Sensitivity in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-method-for-evaluating-hyperparameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of modern reinforcement learning algorithms critically relies on tuning ever-increasing numbers of hyperparameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-method-for-evaluating-hyperparameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granite Guardian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/granite-guardian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Granite Guardian models, a suite of safeguards designed to provide risk detection for prompts and responses, enabling safe and responsible use in combination with any large language model (LLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/granite-guardian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A data-driven learned discretization approach in finite volume schemes for hyperbolic conservation laws and varying boundary conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-driven-learned-discretization-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extend this approach to flux-limited finite volume schemes for hyperbolic scalar and systems of conservation laws.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-driven-learned-discretization-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARP: Hesitation-Aware Reframing in Transformer Inference Pass</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harp-hesitation-aware-reframing-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper aims to improve the performance of large language models by addressing the variable computational demands in inference steps, where some tokens require more computational resources than others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harp-hesitation-aware-reframing-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StoryWeaver: A Unified World Model for Knowledge-Enhanced Story Character Customization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/storyweaver-a-unified-world-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Story visualization has gained increasing attention in artificial intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/storyweaver-a-unified-world-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Sequential Recommendation Models with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-sequential-recommendation-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The nature of the problem, as well as the good performance observed across various domains, has motivated the use of the transformer architecture, which has proven effective in leveraging increasingly larger amounts of training data when accompanied by an increase in the number of model parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-sequential-recommendation-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monte Carlo Tree Search based Space Transfer for Black-box Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-tree-search-based-space-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MCTS-transfer can not only provide a well-performing search space for warm-start but also adaptively identify and leverage the information of similar source tasks to reconstruct the search space during the optimization process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-tree-search-based-space-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting to Non-Stationary Environments: Multi-Armed Bandit Enhanced Retrieval-Augmented Generation on Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-to-non-stationary-environments-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The system utilizes real-time user feedback to adapt to dynamic environments, by selecting the appropriate retrieval method based on input queries and the historical multi-objective performance of each arm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-to-non-stationary-environments-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnable Sparse Customization in Heterogeneous Edge Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-sparse-customization-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, FL still faces two challenges: system heterogeneity (i. e., the diversity of hardware resources across edge devices) and statistical heterogeneity (i. e., non-IID data).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-sparse-customization-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Dual-Exposure Quad-Bayer Patterns for Joint Denoising and Deblurring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-dual-exposure-quad-bayer-patterns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long exposures reduce noise but introduce blur.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-dual-exposure-quad-bayer-patterns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PTSBench: A Comprehensive Post-Training Sparsity Benchmark Towards Algorithms and Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptsbench-a-comprehensive-post-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our PTSBench can provide (1) new observations for a better understanding of the PTS algorithms, (2) in-depth and comprehensive evaluations for the sparsification ability of models, and (3) a well-structured and easy-integrate open-source framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptsbench-a-comprehensive-post-training</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
