<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 21:08:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Parameter Estimation with Incomplete Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-parameter-estimation-with-incomplete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging their computational speed and flexibility, neural networks are also being used to facilitate fast, likelihood-free statistical inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-parameter-estimation-with-incomplete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MB-TaylorFormer V2: Improved Multi-branch Linear Transformer Expanded by Taylor Formula for Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mb-taylorformer-v2-improved-multi-branch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This variant leverages the Taylor expansion to approximate the Softmax-attention and utilizes the concept of norm-preserving mapping to approximate the remainder of the first-order Taylor expansion, resulting in a linear computational complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mb-taylorformer-v2-improved-multi-branch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking High-speed Image Reconstruction Framework with Spike Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-high-speed-image-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spike cameras, as innovative neuromorphic devices, generate continuous spike streams to capture high-speed scenes with lower bandwidth and higher dynamic range than traditional RGB cameras.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-high-speed-image-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grokking at the Edge of Numerical Stability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grokking-at-the-edge-of-numerical-stability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To validate our hypotheses, we introduce two key contributions that address the challenges in grokking tasks: StableMax, a new activation function that prevents SC and enables grokking without regularization, and $\perp$Grad, a training algorithm that promotes quick generalization in grokking tasks by preventing NLM altogether.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grokking-at-the-edge-of-numerical-stability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM4SR: A Survey on Large Language Models for Scientific Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm4sr-a-survey-on-large-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the rapid advancement of Large Language Models (LLMs) has transformed the landscape of scientific research, offering unprecedented support across various stages of the research cycle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm4sr-a-survey-on-large-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Statistical Theory of Contrastive Pre-training and Multimodal Generative AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-statistical-theory-of-contrastive-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal generative AI systems, such as those combining vision and language, rely on contrastive pre-training to learn representations across different modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-statistical-theory-of-contrastive-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RadGPT: Constructing 3D Image-Text Tumor Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radgpt-constructing-3d-image-text-tumor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With over 85 million CT scans performed annually in the United States, creating tumor-related reports is a challenging and time-consuming task for radiologists.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radgpt-constructing-3d-image-text-tumor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid Automated Mapping of Clouds on Titan With Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-automated-mapping-of-clouds-on-titan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite widespread adoption of deep learning models to address a variety of computer vision tasks, planetary science has yet to see extensive utilization of such tools to address its unique problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-automated-mapping-of-clouds-on-titan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Histologic Dataset of Normal and Atypical Mitotic Figures on Human Breast Cancer (AMi-Br)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-histologic-dataset-of-normal-and-atypical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assessment of the density of mitotic figures (MFs) in histologic tumor sections is an important prognostic marker for many tumor types, including breast cancer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-histologic-dataset-of-normal-and-atypical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DispFormer: Pretrained Transformer for Flexible Dispersion Curve Inversion from Global Synthesis to Regional Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dispformer-pretrained-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Surface wave dispersion curve inversion is essential for estimating subsurface Shear-wave velocity ($v_s$), yet traditional methods often struggle to balance computational efficiency with inversion accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dispformer-pretrained-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSAR: Restricted State Angle Resolver and Rotated SAR Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsar-restricted-state-angle-resolver-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach can effectively improve the performance of existing state-of-the-art weakly supervised methods and even surpasses fully supervised models on existing optical benchmarks (i. e., DOTA-v1. 0 dataset).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsar-restricted-state-angle-resolver-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimelineKGQA: A Comprehensive Question-Answer Pair Generator for Temporal Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timelinekgqa-a-comprehensive-question-answer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Question answering over temporal knowledge graphs (TKGs) is crucial for understanding evolving facts and relationships, yet its development is hindered by limited datasets and difficulties in generating custom QA pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timelinekgqa-a-comprehensive-question-answer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Gaussian Test-Time Adaptation of Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-gaussian-test-time-adaptation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that OGA outperforms state-of-the-art methods on most datasets and runs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-gaussian-test-time-adaptation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Entity Detection from GitHub Leveraging Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-entity-detection-from-github</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper follows this recent trend and investigates the potential of leveraging Large Language Models (LLMs) in such scenarios to automatically detect datasets and software within textual content from GitHub repositories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-entity-detection-from-github</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeFusion: An Effective Decoupling Fusion Network for Multi-Modal Pregnancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defusion-an-effective-decoupling-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal embryo images and parental fertility table indicators are both valuable for pregnancy prediction in \textbf{in vitro fertilization embryo transfer} (IVF-ET).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defusion-an-effective-decoupling-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Semantic Partitioning Method for Large-Scale Training of Knowledge Graph Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semantic-partitioning-method-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, knowledge graph embeddings have achieved great success.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semantic-partitioning-method-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Coding for Both Human Perception and Generalized Machine Analytics with CLIP Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-coding-for-both-human-perception-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The image compression model has long struggled with adaptability and generalization, as the decoded bitstream typically serves only human or machine needs and fails to preserve information for unseen visual tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-coding-for-both-human-perception-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCIts -- Deep Convolutional Interpreter for time series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcits-deep-convolutional-interpreter-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an interpretable deep learning model for multivariate time series forecasting that prioritizes both predictive performance and interpretability - key requirements for understanding complex physical phenomena.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcits-deep-convolutional-interpreter-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoDFL: A Scalable and Automated Reputation-Aware Decentralized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autodfl-a-scalable-and-automated-reputation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reputation-aware BFL poses even more challenges, as blockchain validators are tasked with processing federated learning transactions along with the transactions that evaluate FL tasks and aggregate reputations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autodfl-a-scalable-and-automated-reputation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfiGUIAgent: A Multimodal Generalist GUI Agent with Native Reasoning and Reflection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infiguiagent-a-multimodal-generalist-gui</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graphical User Interface (GUI) Agents, powered by multimodal large language models (MLLMs), have shown great potential for task automation on computing devices such as computers and mobile phones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infiguiagent-a-multimodal-generalist-gui</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look on Gender Stereotypes in Movie Recommender Systems and Their Implications with Privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-on-gender-stereotypes-in-movie</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the second phase, four inference algorithms were applied to detect gender stereotypes by combining the findings from the first phase with users' feedback data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-on-gender-stereotypes-in-movie</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA: Neuro-symbolic ARC Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nsa-neuro-symbolic-arc-challenge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Abstraction and Reasoning Corpus (ARC) evaluates general reasoning capabilities that are difficult for both machine learning models and combinatorial search methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nsa-neuro-symbolic-arc-challenge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Before Reasoning: Enhancing Chain-of-Thought with Iterative Summarization Pre-Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-before-reasoning-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chain-of-Thought (CoT) Prompting is a dominant paradigm in Large Language Models (LLMs) to enhance complex reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-before-reasoning-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test-Time Optimization for Domain Adaptive Open Vocabulary Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-optimization-for-domain-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Seg-TTO, a novel framework for zero-shot, open-vocabulary semantic segmentation (OVSS), designed to excel in specialized domain tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-optimization-for-domain-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Examination of Unrolled Networks for Linear Inverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-examination-of-unrolled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unrolled networks have become prevalent in various computer vision and imaging tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-examination-of-unrolled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Plug-and-Play Bregman ADMM Module for Inferring Event Branches in Temporal Point Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-plug-and-play-bregman-admm-module-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we formulate the inference of event branches as an optimization problem for the event transition matrix under sparse and low-rank constraints, which is embedded in existing TPP models or their learning paradigms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-plug-and-play-bregman-admm-module-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining YOLO and Visual Rhythm for Vehicle Counting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-yolo-and-visual-rhythm-for-vehicle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video-based vehicle detection and counting play a critical role in managing transport infrastructure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-yolo-and-visual-rhythm-for-vehicle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are They the Same? Exploring Visual Correspondence Shortcomings of Multimodal LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-they-the-same-exploring-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in multimodal models have shown a strong ability in visual perception, reasoning abilities, and vision-language understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-they-the-same-exploring-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic Mirror: ID-Preserved Video Generation in Video Diffusion Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magic-mirror-id-preserved-video-generation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Magic Mirror, a framework for generating identity-preserved videos with cinematic-level quality and dynamic motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magic-mirror-id-preserved-video-generation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strip R-CNN: Large Strip Convolution for Remote Sensing Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strip-r-cnn-large-strip-convolution-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While witnessed with rapid development, remote sensing object detection remains challenging for detecting high aspect ratio objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strip-r-cnn-large-strip-convolution-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Segmentation: Inducing graph-based learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-segmentation-inducing-graph-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study explores the potential of graph neural networks (GNNs) to enhance semantic segmentation across diverse image modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-segmentation-inducing-graph-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine learning applications in archaeological practices: a review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-applications-in-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This review highlights the importance of well-defined and well-reported structured methodologies and collaborative practices to maximise the potential of applications of machine learning methods in archaeology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-applications-in-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study of Accuracy-Robustness Tradeoff and Training Efficiency in Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-accuracy-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CF-AMC-SSL demonstrates the effectiveness of free adversarial training in reducing training time while simultaneously improving clean accuracy and adversarial robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-accuracy-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic Process Learning via Operator Flow Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-process-learning-via-operator-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Expanding on neural operators, we propose a novel framework for stochastic process learning across arbitrary domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-process-learning-via-operator-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedKD-hybrid: Federated Hybrid Knowledge Distillation for Lithography Hotspot Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedkd-hybrid-federated-hybrid-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) provides novel solutions for machine learning (ML)-based lithography hotspot detection (LHD) under distributed privacy-preserving settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedkd-hybrid-federated-hybrid-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class-Balance Bias in Regularized Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-balance-bias-in-regularized-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that this effect can be mitigated by scaling binary features with their variance in the case of the lasso and standard deviation in the case of ridge regression, but that this comes at the cost of increased variance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-balance-bias-in-regularized-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Dialectal Slot and Intent Detection with Auxiliary Tasks: A Multi-Dialectal Bavarian Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-dialectal-slot-and-intent-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reliable slot and intent detection (SID) is crucial in natural language understanding for applications like digital assistants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-dialectal-slot-and-intent-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activating Associative Disease-Aware Vision Token Memory for LLM-Based X-ray Report Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activating-associative-disease-aware-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[X-ray image based medical report generation achieves significant progress in recent years with the help of the large language model, however, these models have not fully exploited the effective information in visual image regions, resulting in reports that are linguistically sound but insufficient in describing key diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activating-associative-disease-aware-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Reliable Testing for Multiple Information Retrieval System Comparisons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-reliable-testing-for-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Null Hypothesis Significance Testing is the \textit{de facto} tool for assessing effectiveness differences between Information Retrieval systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-reliable-testing-for-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STContext: A Multifaceted Dataset for Developing Context-aware Spatio-temporal Crowd Mobility Prediction Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stcontext-a-multifaceted-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Developing a multifaceted dataset with rich types of contextual features and STCFP scenarios is crucial for establishing a principled context modeling paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stcontext-a-multifaceted-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmological Parameter Estimation with Sequential Linear Simulation-based Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosmological-parameter-estimation-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop the framework of Linear Simulation-based Inference (LSBI), an application of simulation-based inference where the likelihood is approximated by a Gaussian linear function of its parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosmological-parameter-estimation-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Speech Segmentation: A General Approach Using Speech Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-speech-segmentation-a-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike traditional speech and audio segmentation, which mainly focuses on spectral changes in the input signal, e. g., phone segmentation, our approach tries to segment the spoken utterance into chunks with differing acoustic-semantic styles, focusing on acoustic-semantic information that does not translate well into text, e. g., emotion or speaker.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-speech-segmentation-a-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmos World Foundation Model Platform for Physical AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosmos-world-foundation-model-platform-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We position a world foundation model as a general-purpose world model that can be fine-tuned into customized world models for downstream applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosmos-world-foundation-model-platform-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Feature Weaving for Neonatal Echocardiographic Viewpoint Video Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-feature-weaving-for-neonatal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated viewpoint classification in echocardiograms can help under-resourced clinics and hospitals in providing faster diagnosis and screening when expert technicians may not be available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-feature-weaving-for-neonatal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radar Signal Recognition through Self-Supervised Learning and Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radar-signal-recognition-through-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we investigate pre-training masked autoencoders (MAE) on baseband in-phase and quadrature (I/Q) signals from various RF domains and subsequently transfer the learned representation to the radar domain, where annotated data are limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radar-signal-recognition-through-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Molecule Generation Using Latent Space Graph Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-molecule-generation-using-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating molecular graphs is a challenging task due to their discrete nature and the competitive objectives involved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-molecule-generation-using-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-armed Bandit and Backbone boost Lin-Kernighan-Helsgaun Algorithm for the Traveling Salesman Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-armed-bandit-and-backbone-boost-lin</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply our methods to LKH and LKH-3, which is an extension version of LKH that can be used to solve about 40 variant problems of TSP and Vehicle Routing Problem (VRP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-armed-bandit-and-backbone-boost-lin</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTRAG: A Multi-Turn Conversational Benchmark for Evaluating Retrieval-Augmented Generation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtrag-a-multi-turn-conversational-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating them on multi-turn RAG conversations, where the system is asked to generate a response to a question in the context of a preceding conversation is an important and often overlooked task with several additional challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtrag-a-multi-turn-conversational-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-GEN: Enhancing Task Performance Through Targeted Multimodal Data Curation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-gen-enhancing-task-performance-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language models (VLMs) are highly effective but often underperform on specialized tasks; for example, Llava-1. 5 struggles with chart and diagram understanding due to scarce task-specific training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-gen-enhancing-task-performance-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information-Maximized Soft Variable Discretization for Self-Supervised Image Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-maximized-soft-variable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to our variable discretization, the embedding features optimized by IMSVD offer unique explainability at the variable level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-maximized-soft-variable</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
