<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 09:13:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Signal Sampling for Inductive One-Bit Matrix Completion: a Closed-form Solution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-signal-sampling-for-inductive-one-bit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inductive one-bit matrix completion is motivated by modern applications such as recommender systems, where new users would appear at test stage with the ratings consisting of only ones and no zeros.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-signal-sampling-for-inductive-one-bit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatiotemporal Deformation Perception for Fisheye Video Rectification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatiotemporal-deformation-perception-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, we observe that the inter-frame optical flow of the video is facilitated to perceive the local spatial deformation of the fisheye video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatiotemporal-deformation-perception-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Physics-Informed Neural Networks beat the Finite Element Method?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-physics-informed-neural-networks-beat-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In terms of solution time and accuracy, physics-informed neural networks have not been able to outperform the finite element method in our study.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-physics-informed-neural-networks-beat-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Artistic Style Transfer with Conditional Adversaria</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-artistic-style-transfer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generally, a trained NST model specialises in a style, and a single image represents that style.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-artistic-style-transfer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geometric Perception based Efficient Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-perception-based-efficient-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Every Scene Text Recognition (STR) task consists of text localization \& text recognition as the prominent sub-tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-perception-based-efficient-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Code-Related Tasks Through Transformers: The Impact of Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-code-related-tasks-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we pre-train 32 transformers using both (i) generic pre-training objectives usually adopted in SE; and (ii) pre-training objectives tailored to specific code-related tasks subject of our experimentation, namely bug-fixing, code summarization, and code completion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-code-related-tasks-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gibbsian polar slice sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gibbsian-polar-slice-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Polar slice sampling (Roberts & Rosenthal, 2002) is a Markov chain approach for approximate sampling of distributions that is difficult, if not impossible, to implement efficiently, but behaves provably well with respect to the dimension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gibbsian-polar-slice-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Offline Compression: Going Beyond Factorization-based Methods for Transformer Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-offline-compression-going-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent transformer language models achieve outstanding results in many natural language processing (NLP) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-offline-compression-going-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiview Representation Learning from Crowdsourced Triplet Comparisons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiview-representation-learning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Crowdsourcing has been used to collect data at scale in numerous fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiview-representation-learning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMPD: Multi-Domain Mobile Video Physiology Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmpd-multi-domain-mobile-video-physiology</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remote photoplethysmography (rPPG) is an attractive method for noninvasive, convenient and concomitant measurement of physiological vital signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmpd-multi-domain-mobile-video-physiology</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diagnosing and Rectifying Vision Models using Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnosing-and-rectifying-vision-models-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed method can discover high-error data slices, identify influential attributes and further rectify undesirable model behaviors, without requiring any visual data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnosing-and-rectifying-vision-models-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Summary Guidance on Medical Report Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-summary-guidance-on-medical-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study presents three deidentified large medical text datasets, named DISCHARGE, ECHO and RADIOLOGY, which contain 50K, 16K and 378K pairs of report and summary that are derived from MIMIC-III, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-summary-guidance-on-medical-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCRep: Learning Code Change Representations via Pre-Trained Code Model and Query Back</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccrep-learning-code-change-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill this gap, this work proposes a novel Code Change Representation learning approach named CCRep, which can learn to encode code changes as feature vectors for diverse downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccrep-learning-code-change-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prediction approaches for partly missing multi-omics covariate data: A literature review and an empirical comparison study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-approaches-for-partly-missing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Frequently, however, in the training data and the data to which automatic prediction rules should be applied, the test data, the different omics data types are not available for all patients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-approaches-for-partly-missing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining Variational Autoencoders and Physical Bias for Improved Microscopy Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-variational-autoencoders-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Electron and scanning probe microscopy produce vast amounts of data in the form of images or hyperspectral data, such as EELS or 4D STEM, that contain information on a wide range of structural, physical, and chemical properties of materials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-variational-autoencoders-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning as Variational Inference: A Scalable Expectation Propagation Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-as-variational-inference-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A recent alternative formulation instead treats federated learning as a distributed inference problem, where the goal is to infer a global posterior from partitioned client data (Al-Shedivat et al., 2021).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-as-variational-inference-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFGM++: Unlocking the Potential of Physics-Inspired Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pfgm-unlocking-the-potential-of-physics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The new models reduce to PFGM when $D{=}1$ and to diffusion models when $D{\to}\infty$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pfgm-unlocking-the-potential-of-physics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Neural Networks Trained to Identify Words Provide a Good Account of Visual Form Priming Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-trained-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These models tend to include hand-coded orthographic representations with single unit coding for specific forms of knowledge (e. g., units coding for a letter in a given position or a letter sequence).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-trained-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Vector Quantized Approach for Text to Speech Synthesis on Real-World Spontaneous Speech</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-vector-quantized-approach-for-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent Text-to-Speech (TTS) systems trained on reading or acted corpora have achieved near human-level naturalness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-vector-quantized-approach-for-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Layer Retrospective Retrieving via Layer Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-layer-retrospective-retrieving-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, we devise a cross-layer attention mechanism, called multi-head recurrent layer attention (MRLA), that sends a query representation of the current layer to all previous layers to retrieve query-related information from different levels of receptive fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-layer-retrospective-retrieving-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attending to Graph Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attending-to-graph-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, transformer architectures for graphs emerged as an alternative to established techniques for machine learning with graphs, such as graph neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attending-to-graph-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DynGFN: Bayesian Dynamic Causal Discovery using Generative Flow Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dyngfn-bayesian-dynamic-causal-discovery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian causal discovery methods tackle this problem by learning a posterior over the set of admissible graphs given our priors and observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dyngfn-bayesian-dynamic-causal-discovery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training-free Lexical Backdoor Attacks on Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-free-lexical-backdoor-attacks-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose Training-Free Lexical Backdoor Attack (TFLexAttack) as the first training-free backdoor attack on language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-free-lexical-backdoor-attacks-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Attention based on Gaussian Processes for Deep Multiple Instance Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-attention-based-on-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, its probabilistic nature guarantees robustness to overfitting on small datasets and uncertainty estimations for the predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-attention-based-on-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Zero-Shot to Few-Shot Learning: A Step of Embedding-Aware Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-zero-shot-to-few-shot-learning-a-step-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The purpose of this paper is three-fold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-zero-shot-to-few-shot-learning-a-step-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Devil is in the Wrongly-classified Samples: Towards Unified Open-set Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-is-in-the-wrongly-classified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, Unified Open-set Recognition (UOSR) has been proposed to reject not only unknown samples but also known but wrongly classified samples, which tends to be more practical in real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-is-in-the-wrongly-classified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QS-ADN: Quasi-Supervised Artifact Disentanglement Network for Low-Dose CT Image Denoising by Local Similarity Among Unpaired Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qs-adn-quasi-supervised-artifact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning has been successfully applied to low-dose CT (LDCT) image denoising for reducing potential radiation risk.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qs-adn-quasi-supervised-artifact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAT: Improve the Worst-class Robustness in Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wat-improve-the-worst-class-robustness-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose a measurement to evaluate the proposed method in terms of both the average and worst-class accuracies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wat-improve-the-worst-class-robustness-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepVATS: Deep Visual Analytics for Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepvats-deep-visual-analytics-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of Deep Visual Analytics (DVA) has recently arisen from the idea of developing Visual Interactive Systems supported by deep learning techniques, in order to provide them with large-scale data processing capabilities and to unify their implementation across different data modalities and domains of application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepvats-deep-visual-analytics-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy Evaluation in Decentralized POMDPs with Belief Sharing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-evaluation-in-decentralized-pomdps</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a remedy, we propose a fully decentralized belief forming strategy that relies on individual updates and on localized interactions over a communication network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-evaluation-in-decentralized-pomdps</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Joint Learning for Clinical Named Entity Recognition and Relation Extraction Using Fourier Networks: A Use Case in Adverse Drug Events</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-joint-learning-for-clinical-named</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current approaches for clinical information extraction are inefficient in terms of computational costs and memory consumption, hindering their application to process large-scale electronic health records (EHRs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-joint-learning-for-clinical-named</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long Text and Multi-Table Summarization: Dataset and Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-text-and-multi-table-summarization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within a report document, the salient information can be scattered in the textual and non-textual content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-text-and-multi-table-summarization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hardware Impact of Quantization and Pruning for Weights in Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-hardware-impact-of-quantization-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Energy efficient implementations and deployments of Spiking neural networks (SNNs) have been of great interest due to the possibility of developing artificial systems that can achieve the computational powers and energy efficiency of the biological brain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-hardware-impact-of-quantization-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Benefits of Training Expert Language Models over Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-benefits-of-training-expert</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, Language Models (LMs) instruction-tuned on multiple tasks, also known as multitask-prompted fine-tuning (MT), have shown the capability to generalize to unseen tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-benefits-of-training-expert</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long Horizon Temperature Scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-horizon-temperature-scaling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LHTS is compatible with all likelihood-based models, and optimizes for the long-horizon likelihood of samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-horizon-temperature-scaling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robustness Implies Fairness in Casual Algorithmic Recourse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-implies-fairness-in-casual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Algorithmic recourse aims to disclose the inner workings of the black-box decision process in situations where decisions have significant consequences, by providing recommendations to empower beneficiaries to achieve a more favorable outcome.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-implies-fairness-in-casual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HumanMAC: Masked Motion Completion for Human Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humanmac-masked-motion-completion-for-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the training stage, we learn a motion diffusion model that generates motions from random noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humanmac-masked-motion-completion-for-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Effect of Metadata on Scientific Literature Tagging: A Cross-Field Cross-Model Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-metadata-on-scientific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the exponential growth of scientific publications on the Web, there is a pressing need to tag each paper with fine-grained topics so that researchers can track their interested fields of study rather than drowning in the whole literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-metadata-on-scientific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard Prompts Made Easy: Gradient-Based Discrete Optimization for Prompt Tuning and Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-prompts-made-easy-gradient-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the text-to-image setting, the method creates hard prompts for diffusion models, allowing API users to easily generate, discover, and mix and match image concepts without prior knowledge on how to prompt the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-prompts-made-easy-gradient-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An entity-guided text summarization framework with relational heterogeneous graph neural network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-entity-guided-text-summarization-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, entities are leveraged to construct a sentence-entity graph with weighted multi-type edges to model sentence relations, and a relational heterogeneous GNN for summarization is proposed to calculate node encodings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-entity-guided-text-summarization-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concept Algebra for Text-Controlled Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-algebra-for-text-controlled-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a formalization of "what the user intended" in terms of latent concepts implicit to the data generating process that the model was trained on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-algebra-for-text-controlled-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverse Probabilistic Trajectory Forecasting with Admissibility Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-probabilistic-trajectory-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting multiple trajectories for road users is important for automated driving systems: ego-vehicle motion planning indeed requires a clear view of the possible motions of the surrounding agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-probabilistic-trajectory-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Gaussian process regression enables accurate prediction of protein and small molecule properties with uncertainty quantitation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-gaussian-process-regression-enables</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the performance of xGPR with the reported performance of various deep learning models on 20 benchmarks, including small molecule, protein sequence and tabular data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-gaussian-process-regression-enables</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Misinformation Video Detection: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-misinformation-video-detection-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With information consumption via online video streaming becoming increasingly popular, misinformation video poses a new threat to the health of the online information ecosystem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-misinformation-video-detection-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entity-Aware Dual Co-Attention Network for Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entity-aware-dual-co-attention-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fake news and misinformation spread rapidly on the Internet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entity-aware-dual-co-attention-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDANs: Temporal Causal Discovery from Autocorrelated and Non-Stationary Time Series Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdans-temporal-causal-discovery-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed method addresses several limitations of existing causal discovery methods for autocorrelated and non-stationary time series data, such as high dimensionality, the inability to identify lagged causal relationships, and the overlook of changing modules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdans-temporal-causal-discovery-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cluster-Level Contrastive Learning for Emotion Recognition in Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-level-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose a novel low-dimensional Supervised Cluster-level Contrastive Learning (SCCL) method, which first reduces the high-dimensional SCL space to a three-dimensional affect representation space Valence-Arousal-Dominance (VAD), then performs cluster-level contrastive learning to incorporate measurable emotion prototypes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-level-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hebbian and Gradient-based Plasticity Enables Robust Memory and Rapid Learning in RNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hebbian-and-gradient-based-plasticity-enables</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comparing different plasticity rules under the same framework shows that Hebbian plasticity is well-suited for several memory and associative learning tasks; however, it is outperformed by gradient-based plasticity on few-shot regression tasks which require the model to infer the underlying mapping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hebbian-and-gradient-based-plasticity-enables</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Deeper Understanding of Concept Bottleneck Models Through End-to-End Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-deeper-understanding-of-concept</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concept Bottleneck Models (CBMs) first map raw input(s) to a vector of human-defined concepts, before using this vector to predict a final classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-deeper-understanding-of-concept</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identification of Power System Oscillation Modes using Blind Source Separation based on Copula Statistic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identification-of-power-system-oscillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We access the performance of the proposed method on numerical simulation signals and recorded data from a simulation of time domain analysis on the classical 11-Bus 4-Machine test system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identification-of-power-system-oscillation</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
