<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 09:16:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Grid Convolution for Multi-Scale Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-grid-convolution-for-multi-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use a single encoder to extract features and introduce a novel upsampler, Implicit Grid Convolution~(IGConv), which integrates SPConv at all scales within a single module to predict multiple scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-grid-convolution-for-multi-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-UNet:Enhancing Zero-Shot Segmentation of SAM for Universal Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-unet-enhancing-zero-shot-segmentation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We train SAM-UNet on SA-Med2D-16M, the largest 2-dimensional medical image segmentation dataset to date, yielding a universal pretrained model for medical images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-unet-enhancing-zero-shot-segmentation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuFlow v2: High-Efficiency Optical Flow Estimation on Edge Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuflow-v2-high-efficiency-optical-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a highly efficient optical flow method that balances high accuracy with reduced computational demands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuflow-v2-high-efficiency-optical-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMILE: Zero-Shot Sparse Mixture of Low-Rank Experts Construction From Pre-Trained Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smile-zero-shot-sparse-mixture-of-low-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep model training on extensive datasets is increasingly becoming cost-prohibitive, prompting the widespread adoption of deep model fusion techniques to leverage knowledge from pre-existing models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smile-zero-shot-sparse-mixture-of-low-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TDNetGen: Empowering Complex Network Resilience Prediction with Generative Augmentation of Topology and Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tdnetgen-empowering-complex-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting the resilience of complex networks, which represents the ability to retain fundamental functionality amidst external perturbations or internal failures, plays a critical role in understanding and improving real-world complex systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tdnetgen-empowering-complex-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpoMamba: Exploiting Frequency SSM Blocks for Efficient and Effective Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expomamba-exploiting-frequency-ssm-blocks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-light image enhancement remains a challenging task in computer vision, with existing state-of-the-art models often limited by hardware constraints and computational inefficiencies, particularly in handling high-resolution images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expomamba-exploiting-frequency-ssm-blocks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning for Autonomous Driving: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-reinforcement-learning-for-22</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning (RL) is a potent tool for sequential decision-making and has achieved performance surpassing human capabilities across many challenging real-world tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-reinforcement-learning-for-22</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongVILA: Scaling Long-Context Visual Language Models for Long Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longvila-scaling-long-context-visual-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce LongVILA, a full-stack solution for long-context vision-language models, including system, model training, and dataset development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longvila-scaling-long-context-visual-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Multi-resolution and Multi-scale Attention for Underwater Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-multi-resolution-and-multi-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Underwater imagery is often compromised by factors such as color distortion and low contrast, posing challenges for high-level vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-multi-resolution-and-multi-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Reciprocal Recommender Systems: Metrics, Formulation, and Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-reciprocal-recommender-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By utilizing the potential outcome framework, we further develop a model-agnostic causal reciprocal recommendation method that considers the causal effects of recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-reciprocal-recommender-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TraDiffusion: Trajectory-Based Training-Free Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tradiffusion-trajectory-based-training-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a training-free, trajectory-based controllable T2I approach, termed TraDiffusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tradiffusion-trajectory-based-training-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instruction-Based Molecular Graph Generation with Unified Text-Graph Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-based-molecular-graph-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in computational chemistry have increasingly focused on synthesizing molecules based on textual instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-based-molecular-graph-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Label Injection for Imbalanced Industrial Defect Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-label-injection-for-imbalanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a simple yet effective method to tackle the problem of imbalanced multi-class semantic segmentation in deep learning systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-label-injection-for-imbalanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Image, Tell me your story!" Predicting the original meta-context of visual misinformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-tell-me-your-story-predicting-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By explaining what is actually true about the image, fact-checkers can better detect misinformation, focus their efforts on check-worthy visual content, engage in counter-messaging before misinformation spreads widely, and make their explanation more convincing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-tell-me-your-story-predicting-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextual Importance and Utility in Python: New Functionality and Insights with the py-ciu Package</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-importance-and-utility-in-python</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The availability of easy-to-use and reliable software implementations is important for allowing researchers in academia and industry to test, assess and take into use eXplainable AI (XAI) methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-importance-and-utility-in-python</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Molecular Graph Representation Learning Integrating Large Language Models with Domain-specific Small Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-graph-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To leverage the advantages of both approaches in molecular property prediction, we propose a novel Molecular Graph representation learning framework that integrates Large language models and Domain-specific small models (MolGraph-LarDo).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-graph-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anim-Director: A Large Multimodal Model Powered Agent for Controllable Animation Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anim-director-a-large-multimodal-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These images are designed to maintain visual consistency across different scenes using a visual-language prompting method that combines scene descriptions and images of the appearing character and setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anim-director-a-large-multimodal-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perturb-and-Compare Approach for Detecting Out-of-Distribution Samples in Constrained Access Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perturb-and-compare-approach-for-detecting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accessing machine learning models through remote APIs has been gaining prevalence following the recent trend of scaling up model parameters for increased performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perturb-and-compare-approach-for-detecting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sliced Maximal Information Coefficient: A Training-Free Approach for Image Quality Assessment Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliced-maximal-information-coefficient-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Full-reference image quality assessment (FR-IQA) models generally operate by measuring the visual differences between a degraded image and its reference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliced-maximal-information-coefficient-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLIMMER: Incorporating Graph and Lexical Features in Unsupervised Multi-Document Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glimmer-incorporating-graph-and-lexical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained language models are increasingly being used in multi-document summarization tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glimmer-incorporating-graph-and-lexical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R2GenCSR: Retrieving Context Samples for Large Language Model based X-ray Medical Report Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r2gencsr-retrieving-context-samples-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[They usually adopt a Transformer to extract the visual features of a given X-ray image, and then, feed them into the LLM for text generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r2gencsr-retrieving-context-samples-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event Stream based Human Action Recognition: A High-Definition Benchmark Dataset and Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-stream-based-human-action-recognition-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a large-scale, high-definition ($1280 \times 800$) human action recognition dataset based on the CeleX-V event camera, termed CeleX-HAR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-stream-based-human-action-recognition-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segment-Anything Models Achieve Zero-shot Robustness in Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything-models-achieve-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the task of semantic segmentation for autonomous driving, it is significant to study the zero-shot adversarial robustness of SAM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything-models-achieve-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeamLoRA: Boosting Low-Rank Adaptation with Expert Collaboration and Competition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teamlora-boosting-low-rank-adaptation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering this, we introduce an innovative PEFT method, TeamLoRA, consisting of a collaboration and competition module for experts, and thus achieving the right balance of effectiveness and efficiency: (i) For collaboration, a novel knowledge-sharing and -organizing mechanism is devised to appropriately reduce the scale of matrix operations, thereby boosting the training and inference speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teamlora-boosting-low-rank-adaptation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pedestrian Attribute Recognition: A New Benchmark Dataset and A Large Language Model Augmented Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pedestrian-attribute-recognition-a-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, this paper proposes a new large-scale, cross-domain pedestrian attribute recognition dataset to fill the data gap, termed MSP60K.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pedestrian-attribute-recognition-a-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Learning on Augmented Gene Expression Profiles for Enhanced Lung Cancer Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-on-augmented-gene-expression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply this framework to well-established deep learning methodologies and employ four distinct datasets for the meta-learning tasks, where one as the target dataset and the rest as source datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-on-augmented-gene-expression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VrdONE: One-stage Video Visual Relation Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vrdone-one-stage-video-visual-relation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video Visual Relation Detection (VidVRD) focuses on understanding how entities interact over time and space in videos, a key step for gaining deeper insights into video scenes beyond basic visual tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vrdone-one-stage-video-visual-relation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Graph Learning with Structure Proxy Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-graph-learning-with-structure-proxy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, FGL also encounters a unique challenge for the node classification task: the nodes from a minority class in a client are more likely to have biased neighboring information, which prevents FGL from learning expressive node embeddings with Graph Neural Networks (GNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-graph-learning-with-structure-proxy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SkyScript-100M: 1,000,000,000 Pairs of Scripts and Shooting Scripts for Short Drama</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skyscript-100m-1000000000-pairs-of-scripts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We perform keyframe extraction and annotation on each episode to obtain about 10, 000, 000 shooting scripts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skyscript-100m-1000000000-pairs-of-scripts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphSPNs: Sum-Product Networks Benefit From Canonical Orderings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphspns-sum-product-networks-benefit-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep generative models have recently made a remarkable progress in capturing complex probability distributions over graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphspns-sum-product-networks-benefit-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Development as Human-LLM Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/game-development-as-human-llm-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a data synthesis pipeline based on the LLM to generate game script-code pairs and interactions from a few manually crafted seed data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/game-development-as-human-llm-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Necessity of World Knowledge for Mitigating Missing Labels in Extreme Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-necessity-of-world-knowledge-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extreme Classification (XC) aims to map a query to the most relevant documents from a very large document set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-necessity-of-world-knowledge-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flemme: A Flexible and Modular Learning Platform for Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flemme-a-flexible-and-modular-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Flemme, a FLExible and Modular learning platform for MEdical images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flemme-a-flexible-and-modular-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiAgent: Hierarchical Working Memory Management for Solving Long-Horizon Agent Tasks with Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiagent-hierarchical-working-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, HiAgent prompts LLMs to formulate subgoals before generating executable actions and enables LLMs to decide proactively to replace previous subgoals with summarized observations, retaining only the action-observation pairs relevant to the current subgoal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiagent-hierarchical-working-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Lymph Nodes Segmentation Based on Partial Instance Annotations with Pre-trained Dual-branch Network and Pseudo Label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-lymph-nodes-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a pre-trained Dual-Branch network with Dynamically Mixed Pseudo label (DBDMP) to learn from partial instance annotations for lymph nodes segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-lymph-nodes-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$\mathbb{BEHR}$NOULLI: A Binary EHR Data-Oriented Medication Recommendation System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathbb-behr-noulli-a-binary-ehr-data-oriented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we attempt to build the first successful binary EHR data-oriented drug recommendation system by tackling the two difficulties, making sensible drug recommendations solely using the binary EHR medical records.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathbb-behr-noulli-a-binary-ehr-data-oriented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-distribution generalization via composition: a lens through induction heads in Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-generalization-via-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We empirically examined the training dynamics of Transformers on a synthetic example and conducted extensive experiments on a variety of pretrained LLMs, focusing on a type of components known as induction heads.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-generalization-via-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3C: Confidence-Guided Clustering and Contrastive Learning for Unsupervised Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3c-confidence-guided-clustering-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to reduce potential misguidance, including feature bias, noise pseudo-labels and invalid hard samples, accumulated during the learning process, in this pa per, a confidence-guided clustering and contrastive learning (3C) framework is proposed for unsupervised person Re-ID.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3c-confidence-guided-clustering-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PA-LLaVA: A Large Language-Vision Assistant for Human Pathology Image Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pa-llava-a-large-language-vision-assistant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we developed a domain-specific large language-vision assistant (PA-LLaVA) for pathology image understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pa-llava-a-large-language-vision-assistant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVOSE: Open-Vocabulary Semantic Segmentation in Event-Based Cameras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ovose-open-vocabulary-semantic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce OVOSE, the first Open-Vocabulary Semantic Segmentation algorithm for Event cameras.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ovose-open-vocabulary-semantic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G2Face: High-Fidelity Reversible Face Anonymization via Generative and Geometric Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g2face-high-fidelity-reversible-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces G\textsuperscript{2}Face, which leverages both generative and geometric priors to enhance identity manipulation, achieving high-quality reversible face anonymization without compromising data utility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g2face-high-fidelity-reversible-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E-CGL: An Efficient Continual Graph Learner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-cgl-an-efficient-continual-graph-learner</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of continual graph learning, where graphs continuously evolve based on streaming graph data, continual graph learning presents unique challenges that require adaptive and efficient graph learning methods in addition to the problem of catastrophic forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-cgl-an-efficient-continual-graph-learner</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRL-Based Resource Allocation for Motion Blur Resistant Federated Self-Supervised Learning in IoV</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drl-based-resource-allocation-for-motion-blur</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the Internet of Vehicles (IoV), Federated Learning (FL) provides a privacy-preserving solution by aggregating local models without sharing data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drl-based-resource-allocation-for-motion-blur</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vanilla Gradient Descent for Oblique Decision Trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vanilla-gradient-descent-for-oblique-decision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It also enables generalizing capabilities by learning regressors at the leaves simultaneously with the decisions in the tree.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vanilla-gradient-descent-for-oblique-decision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Realistic Extreme Image Rescaling via Generative Latent Space Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realistic-extreme-image-rescaling-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel framework called Latent Space Based Image Rescaling (LSBIR) for extreme image rescaling tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realistic-extreme-image-rescaling-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are CLIP features all you need for Universal Synthetic Image Origin Attribution?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-clip-features-all-you-need-for-universal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The steady improvement of Diffusion Models for visual synthesis has given rise to many new and interesting use cases of synthetic images but also has raised concerns about their potential abuse, which poses significant societal threats.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-clip-features-all-you-need-for-universal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PADetBench: Towards Benchmarking Physical Attacks against Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/padetbench-towards-benchmarking-physical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, physical dynamics and cross-domain transformation are challenging to strictly regulate in the real world, leading to unaligned evaluation and comparison, severely hindering the development of physically robust models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/padetbench-towards-benchmarking-physical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Species Data Integration for Enhanced Layer Segmentation in Kidney Pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-species-data-integration-for-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-species homologous data, such as mouse kidney data, which exhibits high structural and feature similarity to human kidneys, has the potential to enhance model performance on human datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-species-data-integration-for-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective Prompt Anchoring for Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-prompt-anchoring-for-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SPA amplifies the influence of the selected parts in the initial prompt, which we refer to as ``anchored text'', during code generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-prompt-anchoring-for-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual and Synthetic Control Method: Causal Inference with Instrumented Principal Component Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-and-synthetic-control-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthetic control method (SCM) utilizes a weighted average of control units to impute the missing counterfactual for the treated unit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-and-synthetic-control-method</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
