<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 09:15:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic gradient descent with gradient estimator for categorical features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-gradient-descent-with-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Categorical data are present in key areas such as health or supply chain, and this data require specific treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-gradient-descent-with-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Utility of Explainable AI in Ad Hoc Human-Machine Teaming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-utility-of-explainable-ai-in-ad-hoc-human-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, expert performance degrades with the addition of xAI-based support ($p<0. 05$), indicating that the cost of paying attention to the xAI outweighs the benefits obtained from being provided additional information to enhance SA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-utility-of-explainable-ai-in-ad-hoc-human-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simpler is better: Multilevel Abstraction with Graph Convolutional Recurrent Neural Network Cells for Traffic Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simpler-is-better-multilevel-abstraction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, graph neural networks (GNNs) combined with variants of recurrent neural networks (RNNs) have reached state-of-the-art performance in spatiotemporal forecasting tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simpler-is-better-multilevel-abstraction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Feedback Loops: Model-driven Amplification of Dataset Biases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-feedback-loops-model-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Datasets scraped from the internet have been critical to the successes of large-scale machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-feedback-loops-model-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing the Effect of Sampling in GNNs on Individual Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-effect-of-sampling-in-gnns-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate two popular GNN methods: Graph Convolutional Network (GCN), which trains on the entire graph, and GraphSAGE, which uses probabilistic random walks to create subgraphs for mini-batch training, and assess the effects of sub-sampling on individual fairness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-effect-of-sampling-in-gnns-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized One-shot Domain Adaption of Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-one-shot-domain-adaption-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While previous works mainly focus on the style transfer, we propose a novel and concise framework\footnote{\url{https://github. com/thevoidname/Generalized-One-shot-GAN-Adaption}} to address the \textit{generalized one-shot adaption} task for both style and entity transfer, in which a reference image and its binary entity mask are provided.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-one-shot-domain-adaption-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Free Learning of a Natural Language Interface for Pretrained Face Generators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-free-learning-of-a-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Fast text2StyleGAN, a natural language interface that adapts pre-trained GANs for text-guided human face synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-free-learning-of-a-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aerial View Goal Localization with Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aerial-view-goal-localization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many cases the rough location may be known and a UAV can be deployed to explore a given, confined area to precisely localize the missing people.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aerial-view-goal-localization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R$^3$LIVE++: A Robust, Real-time, Radiance reconstruction package with a tightly-coupled LiDAR-Inertial-Visual state Estimator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-3-live-a-robust-real-time-radiance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The LIO subsystem utilizes the measurements from a LiDAR for reconstructing the geometric structure (i. e., the positions of 3D points), while the VIO subsystem simultaneously recovers the radiance information of the geometric structure from the input images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-3-live-a-robust-real-time-radiance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-Driven Program Synthesis via Adaptive Replacement Mutation and Auto-constructed Subprogram Archives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-driven-program-synthesis-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the proposed method with PushGP, as well as a method using subprograms manually extracted by a human.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-driven-program-synthesis-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extractive is not Faithful: An Investigation of Broad Unfaithfulness Problems in Extractive Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extractive-is-not-faithful-an-investigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though extractive summarization is less prone to the common unfaithfulness issues of abstractive summaries, does that mean extractive is equal to faithful?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extractive-is-not-faithful-an-investigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uni-Mol: A Universal 3D Molecular Representation Learning Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni-mol-a-universal-3d-molecular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Uni-Mol is composed of two models with the same SE(3)-equivariant transformer architecture: a molecular pretraining model trained by 209M molecular conformations; a pocket pretraining model trained by 3M candidate protein pocket data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni-mol-a-universal-3d-molecular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Combination of a Genetic Algorithm and Novelty Search for Deep Neuroevolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-combination-of-a-genetic-algorithm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To that end, Novelty Search (NS) has been shown to be able to outperform gradient-following optimizers in some cases, while under-performing in others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-combination-of-a-genetic-algorithm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Representing Camera Response Function by a Single Latent Variable and Fully Connected Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representing-camera-response-function-by-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, a new high-performance camera response model that uses a single latent variable and fully connected neural network is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representing-camera-response-function-by-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLaCLab at SocialDisNER: Using Medical Gazetteers for Named-Entity Recognition of Disease Mentions in Spanish Tweets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/claclab-at-socialdisner-using-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper summarizes the CLaC submission for SMM4H 2022 Task 10 which concerns the recognition of diseases mentioned in Spanish tweets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/claclab-at-socialdisner-using-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AARGH! End-to-end Retrieval-Generation for Task-Oriented Dialog</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aargh-end-to-end-retrieval-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce AARGH, an end-to-end task-oriented dialog system combining retrieval and generative approaches in a single model, aiming at improving dialog management and lexical diversity of outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aargh-end-to-end-retrieval-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Evaluation of Posterior Sampling for Constrained Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-evaluation-of-posterior-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study a posterior sampling approach to efficient exploration in constrained reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-evaluation-of-posterior-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-Training a Graph Recurrent Network for Language Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-a-graph-recurrent-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based pre-trained models have gained much advance in recent years, becoming one of the most important backbones in natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-a-graph-recurrent-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geolocation of Cultural Heritage using Multi-View Knowledge Graph Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geolocation-of-cultural-heritage-using-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Graphs (KGs) have proven to be a reliable way of structuring data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geolocation-of-cultural-heritage-using-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eigenvalue Mapping-based Semi-implicit Discretization of the Generalized Super-Twisting Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigenvalue-mapping-based-semi-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, an eigenvalue mapping-based semi-implicit discretization method is applied to discretize the generalized super-twisting algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigenvalue-mapping-based-semi-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIY-IPS: Towards an Off-the-Shelf Accurate Indoor Positioning System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diy-ips-towards-an-off-the-shelf-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present DIY-IPS - Do It Yourself - Indoor Positioning System, an open-source real-time indoor positioning mobile application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diy-ips-towards-an-off-the-shelf-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Cross-Lingual Generalisation in Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-cross-lingual-generalisation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While several benefits were realized for multilingual vision-language pretrained models, recent benchmarks across various tasks and languages showed poor cross-lingual generalisation when multilingually pre-trained vision-language models are applied to non-English data, with a large gap between (supervised) English performance and (zero-shot) cross-lingual transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-cross-lingual-generalisation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiFuse++: Self-supervised and Efficient Bi-projection Fusion for 360 Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bifuse-self-supervised-and-efficient-bi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, state-of-the-art frameworks for monocular 360 depth estimation such as bi-projection fusion in BiFuse are proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bifuse-self-supervised-and-efficient-bi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effects of Archive Size on Computation Time and Solution Quality for Multi-Objective Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effects-of-archive-size-on-computation-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we examine the effects of the archive size on three aspects: (i) the quality of the selected final solution set, (ii) the total computation time for the archive maintenance and the final solution set selection, and (iii) the required memory size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effects-of-archive-size-on-computation-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Effectiveness of Compact Biomedical Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-compact-biomedical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models pre-trained on biomedical corpora, such as BioBERT, have recently shown promising results on downstream biomedical tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-compact-biomedical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Neural Trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-neural-trees</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This survey aims to present a comprehensive review of NTs and attempts to identify how they enhance the model interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-neural-trees</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSMDFusion: Fusing LiDAR and Camera at Multiple Scales with Multi-Depth Seeds for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msmdfusion-fusing-lidar-and-camera-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fusing LiDAR and camera information is essential for achieving accurate and reliable 3D object detection in autonomous driving systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msmdfusion-fusing-lidar-and-camera-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOv6: A Single-Stage Object Detection Framework for Industrial Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov6-a-single-stage-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The YOLO community has prospered overwhelmingly to enrich its use in a multitude of hardware platforms and abundant scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov6-a-single-stage-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Self-supervised Learning for Out-of-distribution Task via Auxiliary Classifier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-self-supervised-learning-for-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Observing a strong relationship between rotation prediction (self-supervised) accuracy and semantic classification accuracy on OOD tasks, we introduce an additional auxiliary classification head in our multi-task network along with semantic classification and rotation prediction head.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-self-supervised-learning-for-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VGStore: A Multimodal Extension to SPARQL for Querying RDF Scene Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vgstore-a-multimodal-extension-to-sparql-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic Web technology has successfully facilitated many RDF models with rich data representation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vgstore-a-multimodal-extension-to-sparql-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Complementarity between Pre-Training and Random-Initialization for Resource-Rich Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-complementarity-between-pre-training-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-Training (PT) of text representations has been successfully applied to low-resource Neural Machine Translation (NMT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-complementarity-between-pre-training-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Interactive Learning for Text Classification: A Constructive Approach for Contextual Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-interactive-learning-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interactive Machine Learning (IML) shall enable intelligent systems to interactively learn from their end-users, and is quickly becoming more and more important.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-interactive-learning-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-supervised Crowd Counting via Density Agency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-crowd-counting-via-density</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new agency-guided semi-supervised counting approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-crowd-counting-via-density</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Engagement and Cryptocurrency Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-media-engagement-and-cryptocurrency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use this model to estimate engagement coefficients for 48 cryptocurrencies created between 2019 and 2021 using data from Twitter from the first month of the cryptocurrencies' existence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-media-engagement-and-cryptocurrency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VulCurator: A Vulnerability-Fixing Commit Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vulcurator-a-vulnerability-fixing-commit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-source software (OSS) vulnerability management process is important nowadays, as the number of discovered OSS vulnerabilities is increasing over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vulcurator-a-vulnerability-fixing-commit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning for Medical Imaging From Diagnosis Prediction to its Counterfactual Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-medical-imaging-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNN) have achieved unprecedented performance in computer-vision tasks almost ubiquitously in business, technology, and science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-medical-imaging-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantitative probing: Validating causal models using quantitative domain knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantitative-probing-validating-causal-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present quantitative probing as a model-agnostic framework for validating causal models in the presence of quantitative domain knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantitative-probing-validating-causal-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Multimodal Variational Autoencoders: GeBiD Dataset and Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-multimodal-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we present a synthetic bimodal dataset designed for a comprehensive evaluation of the joint generation and cross-generation capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-multimodal-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Illustrator: Translating Raw Descriptions into Images by Prompt-based Cross-Modal Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-illustrator-translating-raw-descriptions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a Prompt-based Cross-Modal Generation Framework (PCM-Frame) to leverage two powerful pre-trained models, including CLIP and StyleGAN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-illustrator-translating-raw-descriptions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Data-dependent Approach for High Dimensional (Robust) Wasserstein Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-dependent-approach-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our framework is a "data-dependent" approach that has the complexity depending on the intrinsic dimension of the input data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-dependent-approach-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoding Demographic un-fairness from Indian Names</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-demographic-un-fairness-from-indian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Demographic classification is essential in fairness assessment in recommender systems or in measuring unintended bias in online networks and voting systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-demographic-un-fairness-from-indian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Textured Shape Recovery with Learned Geometric Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-textured-shape-recovery-with-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D textured shape recovery from partial scans is crucial for many real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-textured-shape-recovery-with-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Learning of Deep Texture and High-Frequency Features for Computer-Generated Image Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-learning-of-deep-texture-and-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the finding that multiple different modules in image acquisition will lead to different sensitivity inconsistencies to the convolutional neural network (CNN)-based rendering in images, we propose a deep texture rendering module for texture difference enhancement and discriminative texture representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-learning-of-deep-texture-and-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shifting Perspective to See Difference: A Novel Multi-View Method for Skeleton based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shifting-perspective-to-see-difference-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our module can work seamlessly with the existing action classification model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shifting-perspective-to-see-difference-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does a platypus look like? Generating customized prompts for zero-shot image classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-does-a-platypus-look-like-generating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike traditional classification models, open vocabulary models classify among any arbitrary set of categories specified with natural language during inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-does-a-platypus-look-like-generating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morphology-preserving Autoregressive 3D Generative Modelling of the Brain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphology-preserving-autoregressive-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Still, the ability to produce high-resolution 3D volumetric imaging data with correct anatomical morphology has been hampered by data scarcity and algorithmic and computational limitations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphology-preserving-autoregressive-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Bias in Chest X-ray Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-of-bias-in-chest-x-ray-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foundation models are considered a breakthrough in all applications of AI, promising robust and reusable mechanisms for feature extraction, alleviating the need for large amounts of high quality training data for task-specific prediction models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-of-bias-in-chest-x-ray-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoPruner: Transformer-Based Call Graph Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopruner-transformer-based-call-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a call graph constructed by traditional static analysis tools, AutoPruner takes a Transformer-based approach to capture the semantic relationships between the caller and callee functions associated with each edge in the call graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopruner-transformer-based-call-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFACT: An Online Human Evaluation Framework for Conversational Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infact-an-online-human-evaluation-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational recommender systems (CRS) are interactive agents that support their users in recommendation-related goals through multi-turn conversations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infact-an-online-human-evaluation-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretations Steered Network Pruning via Amortized Inferred Saliency Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretations-steered-network-pruning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill in this gap, we propose to address the channel pruning problem from a novel perspective by leveraging the interpretations of a model to steer the pruning process, thereby utilizing information from both inputs and outputs of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretations-steered-network-pruning-via</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
