<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 09:11:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Predictors from causal features do not generalize better to new domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictors-from-causal-features-do-not</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our goal is to test the hypothesis that models trained on causal features generalize better across domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictors-from-causal-features-do-not</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MC-DBN: A Deep Belief Network-Based Model for Modality Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mc-dbn-a-deep-belief-network-based-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in multi-modal artificial intelligence (AI) have revolutionized the fields of stock market forecasting and heart rate monitoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mc-dbn-a-deep-belief-network-based-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clifford Group Equivariant Simplicial Message Passing Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clifford-group-equivariant-simplicial-message</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results show that our method is able to outperform both equivariant and simplicial graph neural networks on a variety of geometric tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clifford-group-equivariant-simplicial-message</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIM-Refiner: A Contrastive Learning Boost from Intermediate Pre-Trained Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mim-refiner-a-contrastive-learning-boost-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The motivation behind MIM-Refiner is rooted in the insight that optimal representations within MIM models generally reside in intermediate layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mim-refiner-a-contrastive-learning-boost-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting CSV File Dialects by Table Uniformity Measurement and Data Type Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-csv-file-dialects-by-table</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The human-readable simplicity with which the CSV format was devised, together with the absence of a standard that strictly defines this format, has allowed the proliferation of several variants in the dialects with which these files are written.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-csv-file-dialects-by-table</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to validate average calibration for machine learning regression tasks ?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-validate-average-calibration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Average calibration of the uncertainties of machine learning regression tasks can be tested in two ways.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-validate-average-calibration-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedLion: Faster Adaptive Federated Optimization with Fewer Communication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedlion-faster-adaptive-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Federated Learning (FL), a framework to train machine learning models across distributed data, well-known algorithms like FedAvg tend to have slow convergence rates, resulting in high communication costs during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedlion-faster-adaptive-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Representational Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-representational-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, we find that GRIT matches training on only generative or embedding data, thus we can unify both at no performance loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-representational-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUICK: Quantization-aware Interleaving and Conflict-free Kernel for efficient LLM inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quick-quantization-aware-interleaving-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce QUICK, a group of novel optimized CUDA kernels for the efficient inference of quantized Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quick-quantization-aware-interleaving-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing signal detectability in learning-based CT reconstruction with a model observer inspired loss function</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-signal-detectability-in-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks used for reconstructing sparse-view CT data are typically trained by minimizing a pixel-wise mean-squared error or similar loss function over a set of training images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-signal-detectability-in-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Answer is All You Need: Instruction-following Text Embedding via Answering the Question</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/answer-is-all-you-need-instruction-following</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work aims to build a text embedder that can capture characteristics of texts specified by user instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/answer-is-all-you-need-instruction-following</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio-astronomical Image Reconstruction with Conditional Denoising Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radio-astronomical-image-reconstruction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current techniques, such as CLEAN and PyBDSF, often fail to detect faint sources, highlighting the need for more accurate methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radio-astronomical-image-reconstruction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViGEO: an Assessment of Vision GNNs in Earth Observation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vigeo-an-assessment-of-vision-gnns-in-earth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Satellite missions and Earth Observation (EO) systems represent fundamental assets for environmental monitoring and the timely identification of catastrophic events, long-term monitoring of both natural resources and human-made assets, such as vegetation, water bodies, forests as well as buildings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vigeo-an-assessment-of-vision-gnns-in-earth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Textual Localization: Decomposing Multi-concept Images for Subject-Driven Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textual-localization-decomposing-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subject-driven text-to-image diffusion models empower users to tailor the model to new concepts absent in the pre-training dataset using a few sample images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textual-localization-decomposing-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Trembling House of Cards? Mapping Adversarial Attacks against Language Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-trembling-house-of-cards-mapping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a surprisingly large gap between the speed and scale of their development and deployment and our understanding of their safety risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-trembling-house-of-cards-mapping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVIDHealth: A Benchmark Twitter Dataset and Machine Learning based Web Application for Classifying COVID-19 Discussions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covidhealth-a-benchmark-twitter-dataset-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, our primary objective is to develop a machine learning-based web application for automatically classifying COVID-19-related discussions on social media.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covidhealth-a-benchmark-twitter-dataset-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Potential of Transformers in Time Series Forecasting with Sharpness-Aware Minimization and Channel-Wise Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-potential-of-transformers-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based architectures achieved breakthrough performance in natural language processing and computer vision, yet they remain inferior to simpler linear baselines in multivariate long-term forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-potential-of-transformers-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lester: rotoscope animation through video object segmentation and tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lester-rotoscope-animation-through-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article introduces Lester, a novel method to automatically synthetise retro-style 2D animations from videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lester-rotoscope-animation-through-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Empirical-Theoretical Gap in Neural Network Formal Language Learning Using Minimum Description Length</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-empirical-theoretical-gap-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks offer good approximation to many tasks but consistently fail to reach perfect generalization, even when theoretical work shows that such perfect solutions can be expressed by certain architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-empirical-theoretical-gap-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitDelta: Your Fine-Tune May Only Be Worth One Bit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitdelta-your-fine-tune-may-only-be-worth-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are typically trained in two phases: pre-training on large internet-scale datasets, and fine-tuning for downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitdelta-your-fine-tune-may-only-be-worth-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performative Reinforcement Learning in Gradually Shifting Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performative-reinforcement-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike PRL, our framework allows to model scenarios where the environment gradually adjusts to a deployed policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performative-reinforcement-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Point: Multi-View Information-Enhanced Multi-Modal Self-Supervised 3D Point Cloud Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-point-multi-view-information-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In perception, multiple sensory information is integrated to map visual information from 2D views onto 3D objects, which is beneficial for understanding in 3D environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-point-multi-view-information-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuRating: Selecting High-Quality Data for Training Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qurating-selecting-high-quality-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Selecting high-quality pre-training data is important for creating capable language models, but existing methods rely on simple heuristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qurating-selecting-high-quality-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ControlLM: Crafting Diverse Personalities for Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllm-crafting-diverse-personalities-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This heightens the need to control model behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllm-crafting-diverse-personalities-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visually Dehallucinative Instruction Generation: Know What You Don't Know</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visually-dehallucinative-instruction-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA["When did the emperor Napoleon invented iPhone?"]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visually-dehallucinative-instruction-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Structure Measuring: Introducing PDD, an Automatic Metric for Positional Discourse Coherence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-structure-measuring-introducing-pdd</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent large language models (LLMs) have shown remarkable performance in aligning generated text with user intentions across various tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-structure-measuring-introducing-pdd</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criterion collapse and loss distribution control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/criterion-collapse-and-loss-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we consider the notion of "criterion collapse," in which optimization of one metric implies optimality in another, with a particular focus on conditions for collapse into error probability minimizers under a wide variety of learning criteria, ranging from DRO and OCE risks (CVaR, tilted ERM) to non-monotonic criteria underlying recent ascent-descent algorithms explored in the literature (Flooding, SoftAD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/criterion-collapse-and-loss-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXTRON: Weakly Supervised Multilingual Text Detection through Data Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textron-weakly-supervised-multilingual-text-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to solve this problem, we propose TEXTRON, a Data Programming-based approach, where users can plug various text detection methods into a weak supervision-based learning framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textron-weakly-supervised-multilingual-text-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIAViz: A Browser-based Visualization Tool for Computational Pathology Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiaviz-a-browser-based-visualization-tool-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Throughout the development of a machine learning (ML) model in digital pathology, it is crucial to have flexible, openly available tools to visualize models, from their outputs and predictions to the underlying annotations and images used to train or test a model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiaviz-a-browser-based-visualization-tool-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Decomposition and Quantification for In-Context Learning of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-decomposition-and-quantification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing works have been devoted to quantifying the uncertainty in LLM's response, but they often overlook the complex nature of LLMs and the uniqueness of in-context learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-decomposition-and-quantification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extrapolation-Aware Nonparametric Statistical Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extrapolation-aware-nonparametric-statistical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we extend the nonparametric statistical model to explicitly allow for extrapolation and introduce a class of extrapolation assumptions that can be combined with existing inference techniques to draw extrapolation-aware conclusions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extrapolation-aware-nonparametric-statistical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Arm Identification for Prompt Learning under a Limited Budget</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/best-arm-identification-for-prompt-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this connection, a general framework TRIPLE (besT aRm Identification for Prompt LEarning) is proposed to harness the power of BAI-FB in prompt learning systematically.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/best-arm-identification-for-prompt-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAL: Proxy-Guided Black-Box Attack on Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pal-proxy-guided-black-box-attack-on-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce the Proxy-Guided Attack on LLMs (PAL), the first optimization-based attack on LLMs in a black-box query-only setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pal-proxy-guided-black-box-attack-on-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk-Sensitive Soft Actor-Critic for Robust Deep Reinforcement Learning under Distribution Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-sensitive-soft-actor-critic-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the robustness of deep reinforcement learning algorithms against distribution shifts within contextual multi-stage stochastic combinatorial optimization problems from the operations research domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-sensitive-soft-actor-critic-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Engineering for Scaling Language Models to 128K Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-engineering-for-scaling-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that continual pretraining of the full model on 1B-5B tokens of such data is an effective and affordable strategy for scaling the context length of language models to 128K.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-engineering-for-scaling-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenMathInstruct-1: A 1.8 Million Math Instruction Tuning Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openmathinstruct-1-a-1-8-million-math</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on the recent progress in open-source LLMs, our proposed prompting novelty, and some brute-force scaling, we construct OpenMathInstruct-1, a math instruction tuning dataset with 1. 8M problem-solution pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openmathinstruct-1-a-1-8-million-math</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoEval: Benchmark for Evaluating LLMs and Multi-Modal Models on Geometry Problem-Solving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geoeval-benchmark-for-evaluating-llms-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, their proficiency in tackling geometry math problems, which necessitates an integrated understanding of both textual and visual information, has not been thoroughly evaluated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geoeval-benchmark-for-evaluating-llms-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective Reflection-Tuning: Student-Selected Data Recycling for LLM Instruction-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-reflection-tuning-student-selected</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instruction tuning is critical to large language models (LLMs) for achieving better instruction following and task adaptation capabilities but its success heavily relies on the training data quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-reflection-tuning-student-selected</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Word Tokenization for Sequence Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-word-tokenization-for-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models have proven highly successful at modelling a variety of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-word-tokenization-for-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Quantum Compression for Higgs Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guided-quantum-compression-for-higgs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To ameliorate this issue, we design an architecture that unifies the preprocessing and quantum classification algorithms into a single trainable model: the guided quantum compression model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guided-quantum-compression-for-higgs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOv8-AM: YOLOv8 with Attention Mechanisms for Pediatric Wrist Fracture Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov8-am-yolov8-with-attention-mechanisms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we respectively employ four attention modules, Convolutional Block Attention Module (CBAM), Global Attention Mechanism (GAM), Efficient Channel Attention (ECA), and Shuffle Attention (SA), to design the improved models and train them on GRAZPEDWRI-DX dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov8-am-yolov8-with-attention-mechanisms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prediction of Activated Sludge Settling Characteristics from Microscopy Images with Deep Convolutional Neural Networks and Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-of-activated-sludge-settling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Activated sludge settling characteristics, for example, are affected by microbial community composition, varying by changes in operating conditions and influent characteristics of wastewater treatment plants (WWTPs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-of-activated-sludge-settling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Sharpness in Grokking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-sharpness-in-grokking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks sometimes exhibit grokking, a phenomenon where perfect or near-perfect performance is achieved on a validation set well after the same performance has been obtained on the corresponding training set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-sharpness-in-grokking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Portrait Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-portrait-quality-assessment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated and robust portrait quality assessment (PQA) is of paramount importance in high-impact applications such as smartphone photography.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-portrait-quality-assessment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Vocabulary Segmentation with Unpaired Mask-Text Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-segmentation-with-unpaired</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With this unpaired mask-text supervision, we propose a new weakly-supervised open-vocabulary segmentation framework (Uni-OVSeg) that leverages confident pairs of mask predictions and entities in text descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-segmentation-with-unpaired</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-modality transrectal ultrasound vudei classification for identification of clinically significant prostate cancer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modality-transrectal-ultrasound-vudei</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the aim of effectively identifying prostate cancer, we propose a framework for the classification of clinically significant prostate cancer (csPCa) from multi-modality TRUS videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modality-transrectal-ultrasound-vudei</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEL: Efficient Multi-Task Evolutionary Learning for High-Dimensional Feature Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mel-efficient-multi-task-evolutionary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating information sharing between different feature selection tasks, MEL achieves enhanced learning ability and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mel-efficient-multi-task-evolutionary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Negative Transfer on Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-negative-transfer-on-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate this, we bring a new insight: for semantically similar graphs, although structural differences lead to significant distribution shift in node embeddings, their impact on subgraph embeddings could be marginal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-negative-transfer-on-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exact, Fast and Expressive Poisson Point Processes via Squared Neural Families</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-fast-and-expressive-poisson-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Maximum likelihood and maximum a posteriori estimates in a reparameterisation of the final layer of the intensity function can be obtained by solving a (strongly) convex optimisation problem using projected gradient descent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-fast-and-expressive-poisson-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AQA-Bench: An Interactive Benchmark for Evaluating LLMs' Sequential Reasoning Ability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aqa-bench-an-interactive-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces AQA-Bench, a novel benchmark to assess the sequential reasoning capabilities of large language models (LLMs) in algorithmic contexts, such as depth-first search (DFS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aqa-bench-an-interactive-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
