<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 21:09:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Atari-5: Distilling the Arcade Learning Environment down to Five Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atari-5-distilling-the-arcade-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Arcade Learning Environment (ALE) has become an essential benchmark for assessing the performance of reinforcement learning algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atari-5-distilling-the-arcade-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Adversarial Inverse Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-adversarial-inverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop a novel HIL algorithm based on Adversarial Inverse Reinforcement Learning and adapt it with the Expectation-Maximization algorithm in order to directly recover a hierarchical policy from the unannotated demonstrations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-adversarial-inverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAPX: Generalized Autoregressive Paraphrase-Identification X</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gapx-generalized-autoregressive-paraphrase</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Paraphrase Identification is a fundamental task in Natural Language Processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gapx-generalized-autoregressive-paraphrase</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A kernel-based quantum random forest for improved classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-kernel-based-quantum-random-forest-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emergence of Quantum Machine Learning (QML) to enhance traditional classical learning methods has seen various limitations to its realisation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-kernel-based-quantum-random-forest-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamical systems' based neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamical-systems-based-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The structure of the neural network is then inferred from the properties of the ODE vector field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamical-systems-based-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISFL: Trustworthy Federated Learning for Non-i.i.d. Data with Local Importance Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isfl-trustworthy-federated-learning-for-non-i</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, ISFL is the first non-i. i. d.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isfl-trustworthy-federated-learning-for-non-i</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Video-independent Eye Contact Segmentation from In-the-Wild Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-video-independent-eye-contact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address the task of one-way eye contact detection for videos in the wild.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-video-independent-eye-contact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLM-130B: An Open Bilingual Pre-trained Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glm-130b-an-open-bilingual-pre-trained-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce GLM-130B, a bilingual (English and Chinese) pre-trained language model with 130 billion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glm-130b-an-open-bilingual-pre-trained-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAtt: A Manifold Attention Network for EEG Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matt-a-manifold-attention-network-for-eeg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognition of electroencephalographic (EEG) signals highly affect the efficiency of non-invasive brain-computer interfaces (BCIs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matt-a-manifold-attention-network-for-eeg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Your First Choice: To Address Cold Start Problem in Vision Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-your-first-choice-to-address-cold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we uncover a striking contradiction to this promise: active learning fails to select data as efficiently as random selection at the first few choices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-your-first-choice-to-address-cold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Graph Contrastive Learning from the Perspective of Graph Spectrum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-graph-contrastive-learning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then we theoretically prove that GCL is able to learn the invariance information by contrastive invariance theorem, together with our GAME rule, for the first time, we uncover that the learned representations by GCL essentially encode the low-frequency information, which explains why GCL works.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-graph-contrastive-learning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Particle clustering in turbulence: Prediction of spatial and statistical properties with deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/particle-clustering-in-turbulence-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The simulation data is used to train a U-Net deep learning model to predict gridded three-dimensional representations of the particle density and velocity fields, given as input the corresponding fluid fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/particle-clustering-in-turbulence-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporally Consistent Video Transformer for Long-Term Video Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporally-consistent-video-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Temporally Consistent Video Transformer (TECO), a vector-quantized latent dynamics video prediction model that learns compressed representations to efficiently condition on long videos of hundreds of frames during both training and generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporally-consistent-video-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centralized Feature Pyramid for Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centralized-feature-pyramid-for-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, in this paper, we propose a Centralized Feature Pyramid (CFP) for object detection, which is based on a globally explicit centralized feature regulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centralized-feature-pyramid-for-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CW-ERM: Improving Autonomous Driving Planning with Closed-loop Weighted Empirical Risk Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cw-erm-improving-autonomous-driving-planning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The imitation learning of self-driving vehicle policies through behavioral cloning is often carried out in an open-loop fashion, ignoring the effect of actions to future states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cw-erm-improving-autonomous-driving-planning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Effective Knowledge Transfer for Few-shot Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-effective-knowledge-transfer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the high-shot regime, we propose to use the knowledge learned from ImageNet as guidance for the feature learning in the fine-tuning stage, which will implicitly align the distributions of the novel classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-effective-knowledge-transfer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Vendi Score: A Diversity Evaluation Metric for Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-vendi-score-a-diversity-evaluation-metric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This matrix is induced by a user-defined similarity function applied to the sample to be evaluated for diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-vendi-score-a-diversity-evaluation-metric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprint: Image Forgery Detection and Localization using Compression Fingerprints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprint-image-forgery-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an attempt to fight fake news, forgery detection and localization methods were designed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprint-image-forgery-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Image Retrieval via Nearest Neighbor Search on Pre-trained Image Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-image-retrieval-via-nearest-neighbor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extensively tested the proposed NNS approach and compared the performance with state-of-the-art NNS approaches on benchmark datasets and our created medical image datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-image-retrieval-via-nearest-neighbor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Stage Automated Online Network Data Stream Analytics Framework for IIoT Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-stage-automated-online-network-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel Multi-Stage Automated Network Analytics (MSANA) framework for concept drift adaptation in IIoT systems, consisting of dynamic data pre-processing, the proposed Drift-based Dynamic Feature Selection (DD-FS) method, dynamic model learning & selection, and the proposed Window-based Performance Weighted Probability Averaging Ensemble (W-PWPAE) model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-stage-automated-online-network-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Decentralized Bilevel Optimization over Stochastic and Directed Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-decentralized-bilevel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While personalization in distributed learning has been extensively studied, existing approaches employ dedicated algorithms to optimize their specific type of parameters (e. g., client clusters or model interpolation weights), making it difficult to simultaneously optimize different types of parameters to yield better performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-decentralized-bilevel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformalized Fairness via Quantile Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformalized-fairness-via-quantile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fulfill great needs and advocate the significance of quantile fairness, we propose a novel framework to learn a real-valued quantile function under the fairness requirement of Demographic Parity with respect to sensitive attributes, such as race or gender, and thereby derive a reliable fair prediction interval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformalized-fairness-via-quantile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Sentence Textual Similarity with Compositional Phrase Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-sentence-textual-similarity-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Measuring Sentence Textual Similarity (STS) is a classic task that can be applied to many downstream NLP applications such as text generation and retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-sentence-textual-similarity-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>clip2latent: Text driven sampling of a pre-trained StyleGAN using denoising diffusion and CLIP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip2latent-text-driven-sampling-of-a-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new method to efficiently create text-to-image models from a pre-trained CLIP and StyleGAN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip2latent-text-driven-sampling-of-a-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Across Domains and Devices: Style-Driven Source-Free Domain Adaptation in Clustered Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-across-domains-and-devices-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) has recently emerged as a possible way to tackle the domain shift in real-world Semantic Segmentation (SS) without compromising the private nature of the collected data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-across-domains-and-devices-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPS: Conceptual Minimal Pair Sentences for testing Property Knowledge and Inheritance in Pre-trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comps-conceptual-minimal-pair-sentences-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A characteristic feature of human semantic memory is its ability to not only store and retrieve the properties of concepts observed through experience, but to also facilitate the inheritance of properties (can breathe) from superordinate concepts (animal) to their subordinates (dog) -- i. e. demonstrate property inheritance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comps-conceptual-minimal-pair-sentences-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tripletformer for Probabilistic Interpolation of Asynchronous Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tripletformer-for-probabilistic-interpolation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Asynchronous time series are often observed in several applications such as health care, astronomy, and climate science, and pose a significant challenge to the standard deep learning architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tripletformer-for-probabilistic-interpolation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Quadrature for Probability Threshold Robustness of Partially Undefined Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-quadrature-for-probability-threshold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This enables active learning Gaussian process methods to be applied to problems where the performance of the system is sometimes undefined, and we demonstrate this by testing our methodology on synthetic numerical examples for the autonomous driving domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-quadrature-for-probability-threshold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHINE-Mapping: Large-Scale 3D Mapping Using Sparse Hierarchical Implicit Neural Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shine-mapping-large-scale-3d-mapping-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate mapping of large-scale environments is an essential building block of most outdoor autonomous systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shine-mapping-large-scale-3d-mapping-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relational Proxies: Emergent Relationships as Fine-Grained Discriminators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-proxies-emergent-relationships-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-grained categories that largely share the same set of parts cannot be discriminated based on part information alone, as they mostly differ in the way the local parts relate to the overall global structure of the object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-proxies-emergent-relationships-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promising or Elusive? Unsupervised Object Segmentation from Real-world Single Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promising-or-elusive-unsupervised-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We firstly introduce four complexity factors to quantitatively measure the distributions of object- and scene-level biases in appearance and geometry for datasets with human annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promising-or-elusive-unsupervised-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Video Data Sets for Tracking and Retrieval of Out of Distribution Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-video-data-sets-for-tracking-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the SOS data set containing 20 video sequences of street scenes and more than 1000 labeled frames with up to two OOD objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-video-data-sets-for-tracking-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decanus to Legatus: Synthetic training for 2D-3D human pose lifting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decanus-to-legatus-synthetic-training-for-2d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D human pose estimation is a challenging task because of the difficulty to acquire ground-truth data outside of controlled environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decanus-to-legatus-synthetic-training-for-2d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HeartSpot: Privatized and Explainable Data Compression for Cardiomegaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heartspot-privatized-and-explainable-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[HeartSpot priors are ante-hoc explainable and give a human-interpretable image of the preserved spatial features that clearly outlines the heart.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heartspot-privatized-and-explainable-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-stream Fusion for Class Incremental Learning in Pill Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stream-fusion-for-class-incremental</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From this framework, we consider color-specific information of pill images as a guidance stream and devise an approach, namely "Color Guidance with Multi-stream intermediate fusion"(CG-IMIF) for solving CIL pill image classification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stream-fusion-for-class-incremental</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Me Anything: A simple strategy for prompting language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ask-me-anything-a-simple-strategy-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompting is a brittle process wherein small modifications to the prompt can cause large variations in the model predictions, and therefore significant effort is dedicated towards designing a painstakingly "perfect prompt" for a task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ask-me-anything-a-simple-strategy-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitting a Directional Microstructure Model to Diffusion-Relaxation MRI Data with Self-Supervised Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fitting-a-directional-microstructure-model-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we demonstrate self-supervised machine learning model fitting for a directional microstructural model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fitting-a-directional-microstructure-model-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Target Training for Multi-Source Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-target-training-for-multi-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given any existing fully-trained one-step MSDA model, BORT$^2$ turns it to a labeling function to generate pseudo-labels for the target data and trains a target model using pseudo-labeled target data only.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-target-training-for-multi-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Signal Temporal Logic through Neural Network for Interpretable Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-signal-temporal-logic-through-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning techniques using neural networks have achieved promising success for time-series data classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-signal-temporal-logic-through-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Collocate Visual-Linguistic Neural Modules for Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-collocate-visual-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is because the language is only partially observable, for which we need to dynamically collocate the modules during the process of image captioning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-collocate-visual-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Background Bias in Deep Metric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-background-bias-in-deep-metric-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Metric Learning trains a neural network to map input images to a lower-dimensional embedding space such that similar images are closer together than dissimilar images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-background-bias-in-deep-metric-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explanation-by-Example Based on Item Response Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanation-by-example-based-on-item-response</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intelligent systems that use Machine Learning classification algorithms are increasingly common in everyday society.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanation-by-example-based-on-item-response</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monte Carlo Tree Search based Variable Selection for High Dimensional Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-tree-search-based-variable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian optimization (BO) is a class of popular methods for expensive black-box optimization, and has been widely applied to many scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-tree-search-based-variable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISCOVER: Deep identification of symbolic open-form PDEs via enhanced reinforcement-learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discover-deep-identification-of-symbolic-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The working mechanisms of complex natural systems tend to abide by concise and profound partial differential equations (PDEs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discover-deep-identification-of-symbolic-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Label-Deficient Keyword Spotting Using Self-Supervised Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-label-deficient-keyword-spotting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the use of self-supervised pretraining for the smaller KWS models in a label-deficient scenario.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-label-deficient-keyword-spotting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How deep convolutional neural networks lose spatial information with training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-deep-convolutional-neural-networks-lose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we (i) show empirically for various architectures that stability to image diffeomorphisms is achieved by spatial pooling in the first half of the net, and by channel pooling in the second half, (ii) introduce a scale-detection task for a simple model of data where pooling is learned during training, which captures all empirical observations above and (iii) compute in this model how stability to diffeomorphisms and noise scale with depth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-deep-convolutional-neural-networks-lose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Monitoring of User Stress, Heart Rate and Heart Rate Variability on Mobile Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-monitoring-of-user-stress-heart</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The user's pulse wave is then used to determine stress (according to the Baevsky Stress Index), heart rate, and heart rate variability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-monitoring-of-user-stress-heart</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tree Mover's Distance: Bridging Graph Metrics and Stability of Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-mover-s-distance-bridging-graph-metrics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding generalization and robustness of machine learning models fundamentally relies on assuming an appropriate metric on the data space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-mover-s-distance-bridging-graph-metrics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MBW: Multi-view Bootstrapping in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbw-multi-view-bootstrapping-in-the-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our Multi-view Bootstrapping in the Wild (MBW) approach demonstrates impressive results on standard human datasets, as well as tigers, cheetahs, fish, colobus monkeys, chimpanzees, and flamingos from videos captured casually in a zoo.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbw-multi-view-bootstrapping-in-the-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Positive Pair Distillation Considered Harmful: Continual Meta Metric Learning for Lifelong Object Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/positive-pair-distillation-considered-harmful</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lifelong object re-identification incrementally learns from a stream of re-identification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/positive-pair-distillation-considered-harmful</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
