<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 09:15:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>FedCL: Federated Multi-Phase Curriculum Learning to Synchronously Correlate User Heterogeneity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedcl-federated-multi-phase-curriculum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key challenge in FL is to handle the heterogeneity of local data distribution, resulting in a drifted global model, which is hard to converge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedcl-federated-multi-phase-curriculum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redeeming Intrinsic Rewards via Constrained Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redeeming-intrinsic-rewards-via-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such methods can lead to excellent results on hard exploration tasks but can suffer from intrinsic reward bias and underperform when compared to an agent trained using only task rewards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redeeming-intrinsic-rewards-via-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Device and Audio Data to Tag Music with User-Aware Listening Contexts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-device-and-audio-data-to-tag-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Namely, we propose a system which can generate a situational playlist for a user at a certain time 1) by leveraging user-aware music autotaggers, and 2) by automatically inferring the user's situation from stream data (e. g. device, network) and user's general profile information (e. g. age).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-device-and-audio-data-to-tag-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Images are More Memorable to Machines?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-images-are-more-memorable-to-machines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the problem of measuring and predicting how memorable an image is to pattern recognition machines, as a path to explore machine intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-images-are-more-memorable-to-machines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-Augmented Generative Question Answering for Event Argument Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-generative-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a retrieval-augmented generative QA model (R-GQA) for event argument extraction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-generative-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Adversarial Training with Robust Early-Bird Tickets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-adversarial-training-with-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial training is one of the most powerful methods to improve the robustness of pre-trained language models (PLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-adversarial-training-with-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evade the Trap of Mediocrity: Promoting Diversity and Novelty in Text Generation via Concentrating Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evade-the-trap-of-mediocrity-promoting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we dig into the intrinsic mechanism of this problem and found that sparser attention values in Transformer could improve diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evade-the-trap-of-mediocrity-promoting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treatment-RSPN: Recurrent Sum-Product Networks for Sequential Treatment Regimes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treatment-rspn-recurrent-sum-product-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Models developed using our framework benefit from the full range of RSPN capabilities, including the abilities to model the full distribution of the data, to seamlessly handle latent variables, missing values and categorical data, and to efficiently perform marginal and conditional inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treatment-rspn-recurrent-sum-product-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modality Knowledge Distillation Network for Monocular 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modality-knowledge-distillation-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging LiDAR-based detectors or real LiDAR point data to guide monocular 3D detection has brought significant improvement, e. g., Pseudo-LiDAR methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modality-knowledge-distillation-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing the State-of-the-Art for ECG Analysis through Structured State Space Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-the-state-of-the-art-for-ecg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of deep-learning-based ECG analysis has been largely dominated by convolutional architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-the-state-of-the-art-for-ecg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal EHR Federated Learning Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-ehr-federated-learning-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) is the most practical multi-source learning method for electronic healthcare records (EHR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-ehr-federated-learning-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MT4SSL: Boosting Self-Supervised Speech Representation Learning by Integrating Multiple Targets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mt4ssl-boosting-self-supervised-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide a new perspective on self-supervised speech models from how the self-training targets are obtained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mt4ssl-boosting-self-supervised-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Did the Chicken Cross the Road? Rephrasing and Analyzing Ambiguous Questions in VQA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-did-the-chicken-cross-the-road-rephrasing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Resolving ambiguities in questions is key to successfully answering them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-did-the-chicken-cross-the-road-rephrasing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-distillation with Online Diffusion on Batch Manifolds Improves Deep Metric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-distillation-with-online-diffusion-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this type of method normally ignores the crucial knowledge hidden in the data (e. g., intra-class information variation), which is harmful to the generalization of the trained model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-distillation-with-online-diffusion-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PKCAM: Previous Knowledge Channel Attention Module</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pkcam-previous-knowledge-channel-attention-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, attention mechanisms have been explored with ConvNets, both across the spatial and channel dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pkcam-previous-knowledge-channel-attention-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Image Restoration with Blurry and Noisy Pairs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-image-restoration-with-blurry</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By learning in a collaborative manner, the deblurring and denoising tasks in our method can benefit each other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-image-restoration-with-blurry</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Skill Neurons in Pre-trained Transformer-based Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-skill-neurons-in-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we demonstrate the skill neurons are most likely generated in pre-training rather than fine-tuning by showing that the skill neurons found with prompt tuning are also crucial for other fine-tuning methods freezing neuron weights, such as the adapter-based tuning and BitFit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-skill-neurons-in-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering a Variety of Objects in Spatio-Temporal Human-Object Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-a-variety-of-objects-in-spatio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In daily HOIs, humans often interact with a variety of objects, e. g., holding and touching dozens of household items in cleaning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-a-variety-of-objects-in-spatio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Hard Examples also Harder to Explain? A Study with Human and Model-Generated Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-hard-examples-also-harder-to-explain-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that (1) GPT-3 explanations are as grammatical as human explanations regardless of the hardness of the test samples, (2) for easy examples, GPT-3 generates highly supportive explanations but human explanations are more generalizable, and (3) for hard examples, human explanations are significantly better than GPT-3 explanations both in terms of label-supportiveness and generalizability judgements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-hard-examples-also-harder-to-explain-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Line Segments in Motion-blurred Images with Events</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-line-segments-in-motion-blurred</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To robustly detect line segments over motion blurs, we propose to leverage the complementary information of images and events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-line-segments-in-motion-blurred</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent-NeRF for Shape-Guided Generation of 3D Shapes and Textures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-nerf-for-shape-guided-generation-of-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This unique combination of text and shape guidance allows for increased control over the generation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-nerf-for-shape-guided-generation-of-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IFQA: Interpretable Face Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ifqa-interpretable-face-quality-assessment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing face restoration models have relied on general assessment metrics that do not consider the characteristics of facial regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ifqa-interpretable-face-quality-assessment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedleyVox: An Evaluation Dataset for Multiple Singing Voices Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medleyvox-an-evaluation-dataset-for-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an evaluation dataset and provide baseline studies for multiple singing voices separation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medleyvox-an-evaluation-dataset-for-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language models are good pathologists: using attention-based sequence reduction and text-pretrained transformers for efficient WSI classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-are-good-pathologists-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In digital pathology, Whole Slide Image (WSI) analysis is usually formulated as a Multiple Instance Learning (MIL) problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-are-good-pathologists-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CurvPnP: Plug-and-play Blind Image Restoration with Deep Curvature Denoiser</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvpnp-plug-and-play-blind-image-restoration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the development of deep learning-based denoisers, the plug-and-play strategy has achieved great success in image restoration problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvpnp-plug-and-play-blind-image-restoration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGN-Net: Local-Global Normality Network for Video Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgn-net-local-global-normality-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some of them focus on learning local spatiotemporal representations from consecutive frames in video clips to enhance the representation for normal events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgn-net-local-global-normality-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Text-Conditional Discrete Denoising on Vector-Quantized Latent Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-text-conditional-discrete-denoising-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conditional text-to-image generation has seen countless recent improvements in terms of quality, diversity and fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-text-conditional-discrete-denoising-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CabViT: Cross Attention among Blocks for Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cabvit-cross-attention-among-blocks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed CabViT enhances the interactions of tokens across blocks with potentially different semantics, and encourages more information flows to the lower levels, which together improves model performance and model convergence with limited extra cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cabvit-cross-attention-among-blocks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Autoregressive Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-autoregressive-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we demonstrate that a major limitation of regression using a mean-squared error loss is its sensitivity to the scale of its targets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-autoregressive-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calibrated Interpretation: Confidence Estimation in Semantic Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrated-interpretation-confidence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We examine the calibration characteristics of six models across three model families on two common English semantic parsing datasets, finding that many models are reasonably well-calibrated and that there is a trade-off between calibration and performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrated-interpretation-confidence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dealing with missing data using attention and latent space regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dealing-with-missing-data-using-attention-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most practical data science problems encounter missing data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dealing-with-missing-data-using-attention-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVA: Exploring the Limits of Masked Visual Representation Learning at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eva-exploring-the-limits-of-masked-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We launch EVA, a vision-centric foundation model to explore the limits of visual representation at scale using only publicly accessible data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eva-exploring-the-limits-of-masked-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SportsTrack: An Innovative Method for Tracking Athletes in Sports Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sportstrack-an-innovative-method-for-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The SportsMOT competition aims to solve multiple object tracking of athletes in different sports scenes such as basketball or soccer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sportstrack-an-innovative-method-for-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal patterns in insulin needs for Type 1 diabetes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-patterns-in-insulin-needs-for-type-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Type 1 Diabetes (T1D) is a chronic condition where the body produces little or no insulin, a hormone required for the cells to use blood glucose (BG) for energy and to regulate BG levels in the body.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-patterns-in-insulin-needs-for-type-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Analyzing the Role of Image for Visual-enhanced Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-analyzing-the-role-of-image-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal relation extraction is an essential task for knowledge graph construction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-analyzing-the-role-of-image-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAVEN-ERE: A Unified Large-scale Dataset for Event Coreference, Temporal, Causal, and Subevent Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maven-ere-a-unified-large-scale-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It contains 103, 193 event coreference chains, 1, 216, 217 temporal relations, 57, 992 causal relations, and 15, 841 subevent relations, which is larger than existing datasets of all the ERE tasks by at least an order of magnitude.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maven-ere-a-unified-large-scale-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaptKeyBERT: An Attention-Based approach towards Few-Shot \&amp; Zero-Shot Domain Adaptation of KeyBERT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptkeybert-an-attention-based-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Downstream training for keyword extractors is a lengthy process and requires a significant amount of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptkeybert-an-attention-based-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Face Recognition using Unlabeled Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-face-recognition-using-unlabeled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an unsupervised face recognition model based on unlabeled synthetic data (USynthFace).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-face-recognition-using-unlabeled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CST5: Data Augmentation for Code-Switched Semantic Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cst5-data-augmentation-for-code-switched-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To aid further research in this area, we are also releasing (a) Hinglish-TOP, the largest human annotated code-switched semantic parsing dataset to date, containing 10k human annotated Hindi-English (Hinglish) code-switched utterances, and (b) Over 170K CST5 generated code-switched utterances from the TOPv2 dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cst5-data-augmentation-for-code-switched-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaKRec: Collaborative Meta-Knowledge Enhanced Recommender System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metakrec-collaborative-meta-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill this gap, in this paper, we explore the rich, heterogeneous relationship among items and propose a new KG-enhanced recommendation model called Collaborative Meta-Knowledge Enhanced Recommender System (MetaKRec).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metakrec-collaborative-meta-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Evaluation in Medical Datasets Over Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-evaluation-in-medical-datasets-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning models deployed in healthcare systems face data drawn from continually evolving environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-evaluation-in-medical-datasets-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Follow the Clairvoyant: an Imitation Learning Approach to Optimal Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/follow-the-clairvoyant-an-imitation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider control of dynamical systems through the lens of competitive analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/follow-the-clairvoyant-an-imitation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Few-shot Image Classification with Cosine Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-few-shot-image-classification-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed method FS-CT along with the Cosine attention is simple to implement and can be applied for a wide range of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-few-shot-image-classification-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance-based Learning for Knowledge Base Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-based-learning-for-knowledge-base</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new method for knowledge base completion (KBC): instance-based learning (IBL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-based-learning-for-knowledge-base</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Model Classifier Aligns Better with Physician Word Sensitivity than XGBoost on Readmission Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-model-classifier-aligns-better-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We assess the sensitivity score on a set of representative words in the test set using two classifiers trained for hospital readmission classification with similar performance statistics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-model-classifier-aligns-better-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TorchOpt: An Efficient Library for Differentiable Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchopt-an-efficient-library-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TorchOpt further provides a high-performance distributed execution runtime.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchopt-an-efficient-library-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-Dynamics Imitation Learning from Multimodal Demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-dynamics-imitation-learning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing imitation learning works mainly assume that the demonstrator who collects demonstrations shares the same dynamics as the imitator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-dynamics-imitation-learning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FPT: Improving Prompt Tuning Efficiency via Progressive Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fpt-improving-prompt-tuning-efficiency-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by these observations, we propose Fast Prompt Tuning (FPT), which starts by conducting PT using a small-scale partial PLM, and then progressively expands its depth and width until the full-model size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fpt-improving-prompt-tuning-efficiency-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xu at SemEval-2022 Task 4: Pre-BERT Neural Network Methods vs Post-BERT RoBERTa Approach for Patronizing and Condescending Language Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xu-at-semeval-2022-task-4-pre-bert-neural-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes my participation in the SemEval-2022 Task 4: Patronizing and Condescending Language Detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xu-at-semeval-2022-task-4-pre-bert-neural-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Two Graphs: Freezing and Denoising Graph Structures for Multimodal Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tale-of-two-graphs-freezing-and-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this finding, we propose a simple yet effective model, dubbed as FREEDOM, that FREEzes the item-item graph and DenOises the user-item interaction graph simultaneously for Multimodal recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tale-of-two-graphs-freezing-and-denoising</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
