<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 21:07:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Dense and Continuous Optical Flow from an Event Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-dense-and-continuous-optical-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel deep learning-based dense and continuous optical flow estimation framework from a single image with event streams, which facilitates the accurate perception of high-speed motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-dense-and-continuous-optical-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELDA: Using Edges to Have an Edge on Semantic Segmentation Based UDA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elda-using-edges-to-have-an-edge-on-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their effectiveness, using depth as domain invariant information in UDA tasks may lead to multiple issues, such as excessively high extraction costs and difficulties in achieving a reliable prediction quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elda-using-edges-to-have-an-edge-on-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giving Feedback on Interactive Student Programs with Meta-Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/giving-feedback-on-interactive-student</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, teaching and giving feedback on such software is time-consuming -- standard approaches require instructors to manually grade student-implemented interactive programs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/giving-feedback-on-interactive-student</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaMAE: Adaptive Masking for Efficient Spatiotemporal Learning with Masked Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adamae-adaptive-masking-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our adaptive masking strategy samples visible tokens based on the semantic context using an auxiliary sampling network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adamae-adaptive-masking-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Transformer-Based Model for Ego4D Natural Language Queries Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-transformer-based-model-for-ego4d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report describes Badgers@UW-Madison, our submission to the Ego4D Natural Language Queries (NLQ) Challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-transformer-based-model-for-ego4d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Dynamic Image Harmonization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-dynamic-image-harmonization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the dynamic deep networks that adapt the model structures or parameters conditioned on the inputs, we propose a hierarchical dynamic network (HDNet) for efficient image harmonization to adapt the model parameters and features from local to global view for better feature transformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-dynamic-image-harmonization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McNet: Fuse Multiple Cues for Multichannel Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcnet-fuse-multiple-cues-for-multichannel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In multichannel speech enhancement, both spectral and spatial information are vital for discriminating between speech and noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcnet-fuse-multiple-cues-for-multichannel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmented Physics-Informed Neural Networks (APINNs): A gating network-based soft domain decomposition methodology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmented-physics-informed-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also show cases where XPINN is already better than PINN, so APINN can still slightly improve XPINN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmented-physics-informed-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamical Linear Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamical-linear-bandits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, the hidden state evolves according to a linear dynamics, affected by the performed action too.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamical-linear-bandits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galactica: A Large Language Model for Science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galactica-a-large-language-model-for-science-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe these results demonstrate the potential for language models as a new interface for science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galactica-a-large-language-model-for-science-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squeeze flow of micro-droplets: convolutional neural network with trainable and tunable refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/squeeze-flow-of-micro-droplets-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the second part of this paper, we introduce a residual convolutional neural network to solve the corresponding inverse problem: to translate a high-resolution (HR) imprint image with a specific liquid film thickness to a low-resolution (LR) droplet pattern image capable of producing the given imprint image for an appropriate spread time of droplets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/squeeze-flow-of-micro-droplets-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis and Detectability of Offline Data Poisoning Attacks on Linear Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-and-detectability-of-offline-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A recent body of literature has investigated the effect of data poisoning attacks on data-driven control methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-and-detectability-of-offline-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SETAR-Tree: A Novel and Accurate Tree Algorithm for Global Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/setar-tree-a-novel-and-accurate-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, in the forecasting community, general-purpose tree-based regression algorithms (forests, gradient-boosting) have become popular recently due to their ease of use and accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/setar-tree-a-novel-and-accurate-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMILEtrack: SiMIlarity LEarning for Multiple Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smiletrack-similarity-learning-for-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This design strengthens the modeling of object motion and appearance features for data association.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smiletrack-similarity-learning-for-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Measuring the Intrinsic Few-Shot Hardness of Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-measuring-the-intrinsic-few-shot-hardness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While advances in pre-training have led to dramatic improvements in few-shot learning of NLP tasks, there is limited understanding of what drives successful few-shot adaptation in datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-measuring-the-intrinsic-few-shot-hardness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniRel: Unified Representation and Interaction for Joint Relational Triple Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unirel-unified-representation-and-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Relational triple extraction is challenging for its difficulty in capturing rich correlations between entities and relations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unirel-unified-representation-and-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Domain Adaptation Based on the Predictive Uncertainty of Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-based-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised domain adaptation (UDA) aims to improve the prediction performance in the target domain under distribution shifts from the source domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-based-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesion Guided Explainable Few Weak-shot Medical Report Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesion-guided-explainable-few-weak-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a lesion guided explainable few weak-shot medical report generation framework that learns correlation between seen and novel classes through visual and semantic feature alignment, aiming to generate medical reports for diseases not observed in training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesion-guided-explainable-few-weak-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGE: MAsked Generative Encoder to Unify Representation Learning and Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mage-masked-generative-encoder-to-unify</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose MAsked Generative Encoder (MAGE), the first framework to unify SOTA image generation and self-supervised representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mage-masked-generative-encoder-to-unify</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interacting Hand-Object Pose Estimation via Dense Mutual Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interacting-hand-object-pose-estimation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, we propose a novel dense mutual attention mechanism that is able to model fine-grained dependencies between the hand and the object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interacting-hand-object-pose-estimation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative divergent synthesis with generative models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creative-divergent-synthesis-with-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning approaches now achieve impressive generation capabilities in numerous domains such as image, audio or video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creative-divergent-synthesis-with-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neurodevelopmental Phenotype Prediction: A State-of-the-Art Deep Learning Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurodevelopmental-phenotype-prediction-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A major challenge in medical image analysis is the automated detection of biomarkers from neuroimaging data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurodevelopmental-phenotype-prediction-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where a Strong Backbone Meets Strong Features -- ActionFormer for Ego4D Moment Queries Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/where-a-strong-backbone-meets-strong-features</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report describes our submission to the Ego4D Moment Queries Challenge 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/where-a-strong-backbone-meets-strong-features</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaTriplet-RA: Domain Matching via Adaptive Triplet and Reinforced Attention for Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adatriplet-ra-domain-matching-via-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised domain adaption (UDA) is a transfer learning task where the data and annotations of the source domain are available but only have access to the unlabeled target data during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adatriplet-ra-domain-matching-via-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CL2R: Compatible Lifelong Learning Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cl2r-compatible-lifelong-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We identify stationarity as the property that the feature representation is required to hold to achieve compatibility and propose a novel training procedure that encourages local and global stationarity on the learned representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cl2r-compatible-lifelong-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stare at What You See: Masked Image Modeling without Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stare-at-what-you-see-masked-image-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, unlike the low-level features such as pixel values, we argue the features extracted by powerful teacher models already encode rich semantic correlation across regions in an intact image. This raises one question: is reconstruction necessary in Masked Image Modeling (MIM) with a teacher model?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stare-at-what-you-see-masked-image-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABANICCO: A New Color Space for Multi-Label Pixel Classification and Color Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abanicco-a-new-color-space-for-multi-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In any computer vision task involving color images, a necessary step is classifying pixels according to color and segmenting the respective areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abanicco-a-new-color-space-for-multi-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backdoor Attacks on Time Series: A Generative Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backdoor-attacks-on-time-series-a-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that, compared to images, it can be more challenging to achieve the two goals on time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backdoor-attacks-on-time-series-a-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An FNet based Auto Encoder for Long Sequence News Story Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-fnet-based-auto-encoder-for-long-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we design an auto encoder based off of Google's FNet Architecture in order to generate text from a subset of news stories contained in Google's C4 dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-fnet-based-auto-encoder-for-long-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DLKoopman: A deep learning software package for Koopman theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dlkoopman-a-deep-learning-software-package</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present DLKoopman -- a software package for Koopman theory that uses deep learning to learn an encoding of a nonlinear dynamical system into a linear space, while simultaneously learning the linear dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dlkoopman-a-deep-learning-software-package</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visually Grounded VQA by Lattice-based Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visually-grounded-vqa-by-lattice-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Grounding (VG) in Visual Question Answering (VQA) systems describes how well a system manages to tie a question and its answer to relevant image regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visually-grounded-vqa-by-lattice-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring cell-specific lncRNA regulation with single-cell RNA-sequencing data in the developing human neocortex</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-cell-specific-lncrna-regulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, to analyze lncRNA regulation regarding individual cells, we focus on single-cell RNA-sequencing (scRNA-seq) data instead of bulk data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-cell-specific-lncrna-regulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HGV4Risk: Hierarchical Global View-guided Sequence Representation Learning for Risk Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgv4risk-hierarchical-global-view-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, the hierarchical representations at both instance level and channel level can be coordinated by the heterogeneous information aggregation under the guidance of global view.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgv4risk-hierarchical-global-view-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards an objective characterization of an individual's facial movements using Self-Supervised Person-Specific-Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-objective-characterization-of-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose self-supervised Person-Specific Models (PSMs), in which one model per individual can learn to extract an embedding of the facial movements independently of the person's identity and other structural facial characteristics from unlabeled facial video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-objective-characterization-of-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Predictive Control for Signal Temporal Logic Specifications with Time Interval Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-predictive-control-for-signal-temporal-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, instead of applying MPC directly for the entire task horizon, we decompose the STL formula into several sub-formulae with disjoint time horizons, and shrinking horizon MPC is applied for each short-horizon sub-formula iteratively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-predictive-control-for-signal-temporal-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntegratedPIFu: Integrated Pixel Aligned Implicit Function for Single-view Human Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integratedpifu-integrated-pixel-aligned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose IntegratedPIFu, a new pixel aligned implicit model that builds on the foundation set by PIFuHD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integratedpifu-integrated-pixel-aligned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Joint Use of Rehearsal and Knowledge Distillation in Continual Learning for Spoken Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-joint-use-of-rehearsal-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual learning refers to a dynamical framework in which a model or agent receives a stream of non-stationary data over time and must adapt to new data while preserving previously acquired knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-joint-use-of-rehearsal-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Large-scale Generative Models Corrupt Future Datasets?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/will-large-scale-generative-models-corrupt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These trends lead us to a research question: "will such generated images impact the quality of future datasets and the performance of computer vision models positively or negatively?"]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/will-large-scale-generative-models-corrupt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mechanistic Mode Connectivity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mechanistic-mode-connectivity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We define a notion of $\textit{mechanistic similarity}$ and demonstrate that lack of linear connectivity between two minimizers implies the corresponding models use dissimilar mechanisms for making their predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mechanistic-mode-connectivity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPE-Net: Boosting Point Cloud Analysis via Rotation Robustness Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spe-net-boosting-point-cloud-analysis-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel deep architecture tailored for 3D point cloud applications, named as SPE-Net.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spe-net-boosting-point-cloud-analysis-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Temporal Filtering in Video Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-temporal-filtering-in-video-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pre-determined kernel size severely limits the temporal receptive fields and the fixed weights treat each spatial location across frames equally, resulting in sub-optimal solution for long-range temporal modeling in natural scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-temporal-filtering-in-video-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galactica: A Large Language Model for Science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galactica-a-large-language-model-for-science</link>
      <description><![CDATA[And despite not being trained on a general corpus, Galactica outperforms BLOOM and OPT-175B on BIG-bench.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galactica-a-large-language-model-for-science</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control in triphasic rhythmic neural systems: a comparative mechanistic analysis via infinitesimal local timing response curves</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/control-in-triphasic-rhythmic-neural-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we analyze the responses resulting from modulation of a localized input in each of three classes of model neural networks that have been recognized in the literature for their capacity to produce robust three-phase rhythms: coupled fast-slow oscillators, near-heteroclinic oscillators, and threshold-linear networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/control-in-triphasic-rhythmic-neural-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Connected Memories with a Task-oriented Dialog System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-connected-memories-with-a-task-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have seen an increasing trend in the volume of personal media captured by users, thanks to the advent of smartphones and smart glasses, resulting in large media collections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-connected-memories-with-a-task-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling interpretable development-specific gene signatures in the developing human prefrontal cortex with ICGS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-interpretable-development-specific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, to unveil interpretable development-specific gene signatures in human PFC, we propose a novel gene selection method, named Interpretable Causality Gene Selection (ICGS), which adopts a Bayesian Network (BN) to represent causality between multiple gene variables and a development variable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-interpretable-development-specific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Phrase-based Sequence-to-Sequence Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-phrase-based-sequence-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe a neural transducer that maintains the flexibility of standard sequence-to-sequence (seq2seq) models while incorporating hierarchical phrases as a source of inductive bias during training and as explicit constraints during inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-phrase-based-sequence-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Locate-News: Multimodal Focus Location Estimation in News</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-locate-news-multimodal-focus-location</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, a novel dataset called Multimodal Focus Location of News (MM-Locate-News) is introduced.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-locate-news-multimodal-focus-location</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Metaheuristic Approach for Mining Gradual Patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-metaheuristic-approach-for-mining-gradual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we present a systematic study of several meta-heuristic optimization techniques as efficient solutions to the problem of finding gradual patterns using our search space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-metaheuristic-approach-for-mining-gradual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakpoint Transformers for Modeling and Tracking Intermediate Beliefs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breakpoint-transformers-for-modeling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Can we teach natural language understanding models to track their beliefs through intermediate points in text?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breakpoint-transformers-for-modeling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmark and Dataset for Post-OCR text correction in Sanskrit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-and-dataset-for-post-ocr-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Keeping this in mind, we release a multi-domain dataset, from areas as diverse as astronomy, medicine and mathematics, with some of them as old as 18 centuries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-and-dataset-for-post-ocr-text</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
