<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 09:13:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Domain Adaption Harnessing Vision-Language Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaption-harnessing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose a novel method called Cross-Modal Knowledge Distillation (CMKD), leveraging VLP models as teacher models to guide the learning process in the target domain, resulting in state-of-the-art performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaption-harnessing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet sentiment exacerbates intraday overtrading, evidence from A-Share market</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internet-sentiment-exacerbates-intraday</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, the effect of sentiment on overtrading is observed to be more pronounced among individual investors in large-cap stocks compared to small- and mid-cap stocks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internet-sentiment-exacerbates-intraday</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EuSQuAD: Automatically Translated and Aligned SQuAD2.0 for Basque</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eusquad-automatically-translated-and-aligned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The widespread availability of Question Answering (QA) datasets in English has greatly facilitated the advancement of the Natural Language Processing (NLP) field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eusquad-automatically-translated-and-aligned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing the Robustness of Large Language Models through Self-Denoised Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-the-robustness-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although large language models (LLMs) have achieved significant success, their vulnerability to adversarial perturbations, including recent jailbreak attacks, has raised considerable concerns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-the-robustness-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the interpretability of GNN predictions through conformal-based graph sparsification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-interpretability-of-gnn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have achieved state-of-the-art performance in solving graph classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-interpretability-of-gnn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Joint Rain-/Detail-aware Representations to Eliminate Intricate Rains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-joint-rain-detail-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By integrating CoI-M with the rain-/detail-aware Contrastive learning, we develop CoIC, an innovative and potent algorithm tailored for training models on mixed datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-joint-rain-detail-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expected Coordinate Improvement for High-Dimensional Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expected-coordinate-improvement-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The greatest advantage of the proposed ECI-BO (expected coordinate improvement based Bayesian optimization) algorithm over the standard BO algorithm is that the infill selection problem of the proposed algorithm is always a one-dimensional problem thus can be easily solved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expected-coordinate-improvement-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Quadrature Approach for General-Purpose Batch Bayesian Optimization via Probabilistic Lifting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-quadrature-approach-for-general-purpose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parallelisation in Bayesian optimisation is a common strategy but faces several challenges: the need for flexibility in acquisition functions and kernel choices, flexibility dealing with discrete and continuous variables simultaneously, model misspecification, and lastly fast massive parallelisation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-quadrature-approach-for-general-purpose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sketch-guided Image Inpainting with Partial Discrete Diffusion Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sketch-guided-image-inpainting-with-partial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study the task of sketch-guided image inpainting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sketch-guided-image-inpainting-with-partial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Length Generalization of Causal Transformers without Position Encoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/length-generalization-of-causal-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalizing to longer sentences is important for recent Transformer-based language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/length-generalization-of-causal-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AccidentBlip2: Accident Detection With Multi-View MotionBlip2</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accidentblip2-accident-detection-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) have shown outstanding capabilities in many areas of multimodal reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accidentblip2-accident-detection-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Form(s) to Meaning: Probing the Semantic Depths of Language Models Using Multisense Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-form-s-to-meaning-probing-the-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The staggering pace with which the capabilities of large language models (LLMs) are increasing, as measured by a range of commonly used natural language understanding (NLU) benchmarks, raises many questions regarding what "understanding" means for a language model and how it compares to human understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-form-s-to-meaning-probing-the-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models in Targeted Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-in-targeted-sentiment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reasoning capabilities of the fine-tuned Flan-T5 models with THoR achieve at least 5% increment with the base-size model compared to the results of the zero-shot experiment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-in-targeted-sentiment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concept Induction: Analyzing Unstructured Text with High-Level Concepts Using LLooM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-induction-analyzing-unstructured-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data analysts have long sought to turn unstructured text data into meaningful concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-induction-analyzing-unstructured-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MolCRAFT: Structure-Based Drug Design in Continuous Parameter Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molcraft-structure-based-drug-design-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative models for structure-based drug design (SBDD) have shown promising results in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molcraft-structure-based-drug-design-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partial Large Kernel CNNs for Efficient Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-large-kernel-cnns-for-efficient-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, we introduce Partial Large Kernel CNNs for Efficient Super-Resolution (PLKSR), which achieves state-of-the-art performance on four datasets at a scale of $\times$4, with reductions of 68. 1\% in latency and 80. 2\% in maximum GPU memory occupancy compared to SRFormer-light.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-large-kernel-cnns-for-efficient-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraFIQs: Face Image Quality Assessment Using Gradient Magnitudes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grafiqs-face-image-quality-assessment-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose in this work a novel approach to assess the quality of face images based on inspecting the required changes in the pre-trained FR model weights to minimize differences between testing samples and the distribution of the FR training dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grafiqs-face-image-quality-assessment-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Token-level Direct Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-level-direct-preference-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning pre-trained Large Language Models (LLMs) is essential to align them with human values and intentions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-level-direct-preference-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Diverse Criteria On-the-Fly to Improve Point-wise LLM Rankers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-diverse-criteria-on-the-fly-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The most recent pointwise Large Language Model (LLM) rankers have achieved remarkable ranking results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-diverse-criteria-on-the-fly-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeing Motion at Nighttime with an Event Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seeing-motion-at-nighttime-with-an-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a novel nighttime dynamic imaging method with an event camera.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seeing-motion-at-nighttime-with-an-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMNEE: A Large-Scale Document-Level Event Extraction Dataset based on Open-Source Chinese Military News</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmnee-a-large-scale-document-level-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate this problem, we propose CMNEE, a large-scale, document-level open-source Chinese Military News Event Extraction dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmnee-a-large-scale-document-level-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Foundation Model for Partial Differential Equation: Multi-Operator Learning and Extrapolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-foundation-model-for-partial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More importantly, we provide three extrapolation studies to demonstrate that PROSE-PDE can generalize physical features through the robust training of multiple operators and that the proposed model can extrapolate to predict PDE solutions whose models or data were unseen during the training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-foundation-model-for-partial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6Img-to-3D: Few-Image Large-Scale Outdoor Driving Scene Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/6img-to-3d-few-image-large-scale-outdoor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current 3D reconstruction techniques struggle to infer unbounded scenes from a few images faithfully.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/6img-to-3d-few-image-large-scale-outdoor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-Light: Cross-City Traffic Signal Control Using Transformer on Transformer as Meta Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-light-cross-city-traffic-signal-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The effectiveness of traffic light control has been significantly improved by current reinforcement learning-based approaches via better cooperation among multiple traffic lights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-light-cross-city-traffic-signal-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing v0.5 of the AI Safety Benchmark from MLCommons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introducing-v0-5-of-the-ai-safety-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We created a new taxonomy of 13 hazard categories, of which 7 have tests in the v0. 5 benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introducing-v0-5-of-the-ai-safety-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaskCD: A Remote Sensing Change Detection Network Based on Mask Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskcd-a-remote-sensing-change-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Change detection (CD) from remote sensing (RS) images using deep learning has been widely investigated in the literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskcd-a-remote-sensing-change-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not All Voxels Are Equal: Hardness-Aware Semantic Scene Completion with Self-Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-voxels-are-equal-hardness-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the voxels in the boundary region are more challenging to differentiate than those in the interior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-voxels-are-equal-hardness-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Adjusting Evolutionary Algorithms Are Slow on Multimodal Landscapes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-adjusting-evolutionary-algorithms-are</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The one-fifth rule and its generalizations are a classical parameter control mechanism in discrete domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-adjusting-evolutionary-algorithms-are</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Symmetric Regressor for MRI-Based Assessment of Striatal Dopamine Transporter Uptake in Parkinson's Disease</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-symmetric-regressor-for-mri-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dopamine transporter (DAT) imaging is commonly used for monitoring Parkinson's disease (PD), where striatal DAT uptake amount is computed to assess PD severity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-symmetric-regressor-for-mri-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Observation, Analysis, and Solution: Exploring Strong Lightweight Vision Transformers via Masked Image Modeling Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/observation-analysis-and-solution-exploring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we question if the extremely simple ViTs' fine-tuning performance with a small-scale architecture can also benefit from this pre-training paradigm, which is considerably less studied yet in contrast to the well-established lightweight architecture design methodology with sophisticated components introduced.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/observation-analysis-and-solution-exploring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-In-Context: Understanding Point Cloud via In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-in-context-understanding-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the emergence of large-scale models trained on diverse datasets, in-context learning has emerged as a promising paradigm for multitasking, notably in natural language processing and image processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-in-context-understanding-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleBooth: Image Style Editing with Multimodal Instruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylebooth-image-style-editing-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We integrate encoded textual instruction and image exemplar as a unified condition for diffusion model, enabling the editing of original image following multimodal instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylebooth-image-style-editing-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongEmbed: Extending Embedding Models for Long Context Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longembed-extending-embedding-models-for-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores context window extension of existing embedding models, pushing the limit to 32k without requiring additional training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longembed-extending-embedding-models-for-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information theory unifies atomistic machine learning, uncertainty quantification, and materials thermodynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-theory-unifies-atomistic-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An accurate description of information is relevant for a range of problems in atomistic modeling, such as sampling methods, detecting rare events, analyzing datasets, or performing uncertainty quantification (UQ) in machine learning (ML)-driven simulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-theory-unifies-atomistic-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharing Parameter by Conjugation for Knowledge Graph Embeddings in Complex Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharing-parameter-by-conjugation-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A Knowledge Graph (KG) is the directed graphical representation of entities and relations in the real world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharing-parameter-by-conjugation-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Boundaries and Intensities in Offensive and Hate Speech: Unveiling the Complex Spectrum of Social Media Discourse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-boundaries-and-intensities-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prevalence of digital media and evolving sociopolitical dynamics have significantly amplified the dissemination of hateful content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-boundaries-and-intensities-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TriForce: Lossless Acceleration of Long Sequence Generation with Hierarchical Speculative Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triforce-lossless-acceleration-of-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, key-value (KV) cache, which is stored to avoid re-computation, has emerged as a critical bottleneck by growing linearly in size with the sequence length.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triforce-lossless-acceleration-of-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer tricks: Removing weights for skipless transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-tricks-removing-weights-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[He and Hofmann (arXiv:2311. 01906) detailed a skipless transformer without the V and P (post-attention projection) linear layers, which reduces the total number of weights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-tricks-removing-weights-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hypergraph Self-supervised Learning with Sampling-efficient Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypergraph-self-supervised-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning (SSL) provides a promising alternative for representation learning on hypergraphs without costly labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypergraph-self-supervised-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenBezoar: Small, Cost-Effective and Open Models Trained on Mixes of Instruction Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openbezoar-small-cost-effective-and-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluation is done with the LM Eval Harness tasks/metrics as well as on MT-Bench using the "LLM-as-a-judge" framework with Claude 2. 1, with the finding that the final checkpoint, "OpenBezoar-HH-RLHF-DPO", demonstrates superior performance over many models at the 3B parameter scale, even outperforming the top model in one of the categories on the Huggingface Open LLM Leaderboard.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openbezoar-small-cost-effective-and-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving Object Segmentation: All You Need Is SAM (and Flow)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moving-object-segmentation-all-you-need-is</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The objective of this paper is motion segmentation -- discovering and segmenting the moving objects in a video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moving-object-segmentation-all-you-need-is</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-free Knowledge Distillation for Fine-grained Visual Categorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-free-knowledge-distillation-for-fine-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach utilizes an adversarial distillation framework with attention generator, mixed high-order attention distillation, and semantic feature contrast learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-free-knowledge-distillation-for-fine-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The devil is in the object boundary: towards annotation-free instance segmentation using Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-is-in-the-object-boundary-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foundation models, pre-trained on a large amount of data have demonstrated impressive zero-shot capabilities in various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-is-in-the-object-boundary-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Actions and Walking to LLM-Generated Textual Descriptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-actions-and-walking-to-llm-generated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For action recognition, we employ LLMs to generate textual descriptions of actions in the BABEL-60 dataset, facilitating the alignment of motion sequences with linguistic representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-actions-and-walking-to-llm-generated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning language models with human preferences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-language-models-with-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Chapter 3, I investigate the relation between two approaches to finetuning pretrained LMs using feedback given by a scoring function: reinforcement learning from human feedback (RLHF) and distribution matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-language-models-with-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S3R-Net: A Single-Stage Approach to Self-Supervised Shadow Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s3r-net-a-single-stage-approach-to-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present S3R-Net, the Self-Supervised Shadow Removal Network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s3r-net-a-single-stage-approach-to-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Highly Realistic Artistic Style Transfer via Stable Diffusion with Step-aware and Layer-aware Prompt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-highly-realistic-artistic-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above problems, we propose a novel pre-trained diffusion-based artistic style transfer method, called LSAST, which can generate highly realistic artistic stylized images while preserving the content structure of input content images well, without bringing obvious artifacts and disharmonious style patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-highly-realistic-artistic-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Following the Human Thread in Social Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/following-the-human-thread-in-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the first Social Dynamics Adaptation model (SDA) based on the robot's state-action history to infer the social dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/following-the-human-thread-in-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Gender Bias in Turkish Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-gender-bias-in-turkish-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, prior research has primarily focused on the English language, especially in the context of gender bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-gender-bias-in-turkish-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Causal Nature of Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-causal-nature-of-sentiment-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sentiment analysis (SA) aims to identify the sentiment expressed in a text, such as a product review.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-causal-nature-of-sentiment-analysis</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
