<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 21:04:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>From Relevance to Utility: Evidence Retrieval with Feedback for Fact Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-relevance-to-utility-evidence-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that, rather than relevance, for FV we need to focus on the utility that a claim verifier derives from the retrieved evidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-relevance-to-utility-evidence-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulating Users in Interactive Web Table Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-users-in-interactive-web-table</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our multi-perspective evaluation scheme reveals new insights about query strategies, the impact of modalities, and different user types in simulated WTR search sessions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-users-in-interactive-web-table</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Dataset Cartography for Improved Compositional Generalization in Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-dataset-cartography-for-improved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks have revolutionized language modeling and excelled in various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-dataset-cartography-for-improved</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORE: A Few-Shot Company Relation Classification Dataset for Robust Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/core-a-few-shot-company-relation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the performance of state-of-the-art RC models on the CORE dataset, we conduct experiments in the few-shot domain adaptation setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/core-a-few-shot-company-relation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Long Document Topic Segmentation Models With Enhanced Coherence Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-long-document-topic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach improves $F_{1}$ of old SOTA by 3. 42 (73. 74 -> 77. 16) and reduces $P_{k}$ by 1. 11 points (15. 0 -> 13. 89) on WIKI-727K and achieves an average reduction of 0. 83 points on $P_{k}$ on WikiSection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-long-document-topic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating semantic subspaces of Transformer sentence embeddings through linear structural probing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-semantic-subspaces-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The question of what kinds of linguistic information are encoded in different layers of Transformer-based language models is of considerable interest for the NLP community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-semantic-subspaces-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyze Mass Spectrometry data with Artificial Intelligence to assist the understanding of past habitability of Mars and provide insights for future missions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyze-mass-spectrometry-data-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an application of artificial intelligence on mass spectrometry data for detecting habitability potential of ancient Mars.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyze-mass-spectrometry-data-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Siren's Song: Towards Reliable Fact-Conflicting Hallucination Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-siren-s-song-towards-reliable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs), such as ChatGPT/GPT-4, have garnered widespread attention owing to their myriad of practical applications, yet their adoption has been constrained by issues of fact-conflicting hallucinations across web platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-siren-s-song-towards-reliable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Scale Decomposition MLP-Mixer for Time Series Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-scale-decomposition-mlp-mixer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series data, often characterized by unique composition and complex multi-scale temporal variations, requires special consideration of decomposition and multi-scale modeling in its analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-scale-decomposition-mlp-mixer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfoDiffusion: Information Entropy Aware Diffusion Process for Non-Autoregressive Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infodiffusion-information-entropy-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have garnered considerable interest in the field of text generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infodiffusion-information-entropy-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold: A Global and Local-aware Denoising Framework for Commonsense Knowledge Graph Noise Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gold-a-global-and-local-aware-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Commonsense Knowledge Graphs (CSKGs) are crucial for commonsense reasoning, yet constructing them through human annotations can be costly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gold-a-global-and-local-aware-denoising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Bootstrapping for Uncertainty Quantification in Imaging Inverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-bootstrapping-for-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientific imaging problems are often severely ill-posed, and hence have significant intrinsic uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-bootstrapping-for-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Contrastive Learning for Entity Typing over Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-contrastive-learning-for-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge graph entity typing (KGET) aims at inferring plausible types of entities in knowledge graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-contrastive-learning-for-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerated Policy Gradient: On the Nesterov Momentum for Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerated-policy-gradient-on-the-nesterov</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demonstrate the potential of APG in achieving faster global convergence, we formally show that with the true gradient, APG with softmax policy parametrization converges to an optimal policy at a $\tilde{O}(1/t^2)$ rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerated-policy-gradient-on-the-nesterov</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recasting Continual Learning as Sequence Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recasting-continual-learning-as-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[That is, we propose to formulate continual learning as a sequence modeling problem, allowing advanced sequence models to be utilized for continual learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recasting-continual-learning-as-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take the aTrain. Introducing an Interface for the Accessible Transcription of Interviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-the-atrain-introducing-an-interface-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[If an entry-level graphics card is available, the transcription speed increases to 20% of the audio duration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-the-atrain-introducing-an-interface-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Evaluation of Large Language Models on Legal Judgment Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-evaluation-of-large-language-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated great potential for domain-specific applications, such as the law domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-evaluation-of-large-language-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Generate or Not? Safety-Driven Unlearned Diffusion Models Are Still Easy To Generate Unsafe Images ... For Now</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-generate-or-not-safety-driven-unlearned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this uncertainty, we propose an evaluation framework built upon adversarial attacks (also referred to as adversarial prompts), in order to discern the trustworthiness of these safety-driven unlearned DMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-generate-or-not-safety-driven-unlearned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PREM: A Simple Yet Effective Approach for Node-Level Graph Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prem-a-simple-yet-effective-approach-for-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comprising two modules - a pre-processing module and an ego-neighbor matching module - PREM eliminates the necessity for message-passing propagation during training, and employs a simple contrastive loss, leading to considerable reductions in training time and memory usage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prem-a-simple-yet-effective-approach-for-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototype-based HyperAdapter for Sample-Efficient Multi-task Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-based-hyperadapter-for-sample</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parameter-efficient fine-tuning (PEFT) has shown its effectiveness in adapting the pre-trained language models to downstream tasks while only updating a small number of parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-based-hyperadapter-for-sample</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can bin-wise scaling improve consistency and adaptivity of prediction uncertainty for machine learning regression ?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-bin-wise-scaling-improve-consistency-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Binwise Variance Scaling (BVS) has recently been proposed as a post hoc recalibration method for prediction uncertainties of machine learning regression problems that is able of more efficient corrections than uniform variance (or temperature) scaling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-bin-wise-scaling-improve-consistency-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Pronouns: Interpretability Informs Gender Bias Mitigation for Fairer Instruction-Tuned Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tale-of-pronouns-interpretability-informs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In MT, this might lead to misgendered translations, resulting, among other harms, in the perpetuation of stereotypes and prejudices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tale-of-pronouns-interpretability-informs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Transferable Adversarial Image Examples: Attack Categorization, Evaluation Guidelines, and New Insights</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-transferable-adversarial-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transferable adversarial examples raise critical security concerns in real-world, black-box attack scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-transferable-adversarial-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-shot Faithfulness Evaluation for Text Summarization with Foundation Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-faithfulness-evaluation-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite tremendous improvements in natural language generation, summarization models still suffer from the unfaithfulness issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-faithfulness-evaluation-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT-guided Semantics for Zero-shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-guided-semantics-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we enrich word vectors by combining the word embeddings from class names and descriptions generated by ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-guided-semantics-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Generalized Face Anti-Spoofing with Unknown Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalized-face-anti-spoofing-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although face anti-spoofing (FAS) methods have achieved remarkable performance on specific domains or attack types, few studies have focused on the simultaneous presence of domain changes and unknown attacks, which is closer to real application scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalized-face-anti-spoofing-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISAR: A Multimodal Instructional System with Augmented Reality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/misar-a-multimodal-instructional-system-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Augmented reality (AR) requires the seamless integration of visual, auditory, and linguistic channels for optimized human-computer interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/misar-a-multimodal-instructional-system-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perceptual Measurements, Distances and Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perceptual-measurements-distances-and-metrics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we demonstrate the value of measuring the perceptual scale of classical (spatial frequency, orientation) and less classical physical variables (interpolation between textures) by embedding it in recent probabilistic modeling of perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perceptual-measurements-distances-and-metrics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixEdit: Revisiting Data Augmentation and Beyond for Grammatical Error Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixedit-revisiting-data-augmentation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to clarify how data augmentation improves GEC models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixedit-revisiting-data-augmentation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HB-net: Holistic bursting cell cluster integrated network for occluded multi-objects recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hb-net-holistic-bursting-cell-cluster</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although in high-noise settings, standard CNNs exhibit slightly greater robustness when compared to HB-net models, the models that combine the HB framework and EA mechanism achieve a comparable level of accuracy and resilience to ResNet50, despite having only three convolutional layers and approximately $1/30$ of the parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hb-net-holistic-bursting-cell-cluster</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitNet: Scaling 1-bit Transformers for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitnet-scaling-1-bit-transformers-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing size of large language models has posed challenges for deployment and raised concerns about environmental impact due to high energy consumption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitnet-scaling-1-bit-transformers-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMTLab: An Open-Source Platform for Building, Evaluating, and Diagnosing Interactive Machine Translation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imtlab-an-open-source-platform-for-building</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present IMTLab, an open-source end-to-end interactive machine translation (IMT) system platform that enables researchers to quickly build IMT systems with state-of-the-art models, perform an end-to-end evaluation, and diagnose the weakness of systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imtlab-an-open-source-platform-for-building</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Extraction and Distillation from Large-Scale Image-Text Colonoscopy Records Leveraging Large Language and Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-extraction-and-distillation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[EndoKED automates the transformation of raw colonoscopy records into image datasets with pixel-level annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-extraction-and-distillation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEQ: Trainable Equivalent Transformation for Quantization of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teq-trainable-equivalent-transformation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As large language models (LLMs) become more prevalent, there is a growing need for new and improved quantization methods that can meet the computationalast layer demands of these modern architectures while maintaining the accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teq-trainable-equivalent-transformation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FusionU-Net: U-Net with Enhanced Skip Connection for Pathology Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusionu-net-u-net-with-enhanced-skip</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the key designs of U-Net is the use of skip connections between the encoder and decoder, which helps to recover detailed information after upsampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusionu-net-u-net-with-enhanced-skip</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUST&amp;P-SRL: Multi-lingual and Unified Syllabification in Text and Phonetic Domains for Speech Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/must-p-srl-multi-lingual-and-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a methodology for linguistic feature extraction, focusing particularly on automatically syllabifying words in multiple languages, with a design to be compatible with a forced-alignment tool, the Montreal Forced Aligner (MFA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/must-p-srl-multi-lingual-and-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergent Mixture-of-Experts: Can Dense Pre-trained Transformers Benefit from Emergent Modular Structures?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergent-mixture-of-experts-can-dense-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing modular neural networks are generally $\textit{explicit}$ because their modular architectures are pre-defined, and individual modules are expected to implement distinct functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergent-mixture-of-experts-can-dense-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MonoSKD: General Distillation Framework for Monocular 3D Object Detection via Spearman Correlation Coefficient</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monoskd-general-distillation-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monocular 3D object detection is an inherently ill-posed problem, as it is challenging to predict accurate 3D localization from a single image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monoskd-general-distillation-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unanswerable Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unanswerable-visual-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Teaching Visual Question Answering (VQA) models to abstain from unanswerable questions is indispensable for building a trustworthy AI system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unanswerable-visual-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query2Triple: Unified Query Encoding for Answering Diverse Complex Queries over Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query2triple-unified-query-encoding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these methods train KG embeddings and neural set operators concurrently on both simple (one-hop) and complex (multi-hop and logical) queries, which causes performance degradation on simple queries and low training efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query2triple-unified-query-encoding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NICE: Improving Panoptic Narrative Detection and Segmentation with Cascading Collaborative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nice-improving-panoptic-narrative-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce two cascading modules based on the barycenter of the mask, which are Coordinate Guided Aggregation (CGA) and Barycenter Driven Localization (BDL), responsible for segmentation and detection, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nice-improving-panoptic-narrative-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VcT: Visual change Transformer for Remote Sensing Image Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vct-visual-change-transformer-for-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, each pixel of feature map is regarded as a graph node and the graph neural network is proposed to model the structured information for coarse change map prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vct-visual-change-transformer-for-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Attention: Enhancing QKV Calculation in Self-Attention Mechanism with Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-attention-enhancing-qkv-calculation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of deep learning, the self-attention mechanism has substantiated its pivotal role across a myriad of tasks, encompassing natural language processing and computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-attention-enhancing-qkv-calculation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Cognitive Architecture: Incorporating Biases and Multi-Memory Systems for Lifelong Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-cognitive-architecture-incorporating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial neural networks (ANNs) exhibit a narrow scope of expertise on stationary independent data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-cognitive-architecture-incorporating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SODA: Robust Training of Test-Time Data Adaptors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soda-robust-training-of-test-time-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adapting models deployed to test distributions can mitigate the performance degradation caused by distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soda-robust-training-of-test-time-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent-Specific Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-specific-effects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These challenges are particularly prominent in the context of multi-agent sequential decision-making, where the causal effect of an agent's action on the outcome depends on how the other agents respond to that action.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-specific-effects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Contrastive Learning via Distributionally Robust Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-contrastive-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study reveals the inherent tolerance of contrastive learning (CL) towards sampling bias, wherein negative samples may encompass similar semantics (\eg labels).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-contrastive-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenEval: An Object-Focused Framework for Evaluating Text-to-Image Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geneval-an-object-focused-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent breakthroughs in diffusion models, multimodal pretraining, and efficient finetuning have led to an explosion of text-to-image generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geneval-an-object-focused-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TK-KNN: A Balanced Distance-Based Pseudo Labeling Approach for Semi-Supervised Intent Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tk-knn-a-balanced-distance-based-pseudo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the present work, we describe Top-K K-Nearest Neighbor (TK-KNN), which uses a more robust pseudo-labeling approach based on distance in the embedding space while maintaining a balanced set of pseudo-labeled examples across classes through a ranking-based approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tk-knn-a-balanced-distance-based-pseudo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Simple Spectral Clustering in Theory and Practice</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-simple-spectral-clustering-in-theory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spectral clustering is a popular and effective algorithm designed to find $k$ clusters in a graph $G$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-simple-spectral-clustering-in-theory</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
