<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:08:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Quantification of Serial PET/CT Images for Pediatric Hodgkin Lymphoma Patients Using a Longitudinally-Aware Segmentation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-quantification-of-serial-pet-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For baseline segmentation, LAS-Net achieved a mean Dice score of 0. 772.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-quantification-of-serial-pet-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probing the 3D Awareness of Visual Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-the-3d-awareness-of-visual-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given that such models can classify, delineate, and localize objects in 2D, we ask whether they also represent their 3D structure?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-the-3d-awareness-of-visual-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Multi-System Multivariate Interconnection and Divergence Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-multi-system-multivariate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identifying outlier behavior among sensors and subsystems is essential for discovering faults and facilitating diagnostics in large systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-multi-system-multivariate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataset Reset Policy Optimization for RLHF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-reset-policy-optimization-for-rlhf</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the fact that offline preference dataset provides informative states (i. e., data that is preferred by the labelers), our new algorithm, Dataset Reset Policy Optimization (DR-PO), integrates the existing offline preference dataset into the online policy training procedure via dataset reset: it directly resets the policy optimizer to the states in the offline dataset, instead of always starting from the initial state distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-reset-policy-optimization-for-rlhf</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Physical-Digital Facial Attack Detection Via Simulating Spoofing Clues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-physical-digital-facial-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SPSC and SDSC augment live samples into simulated attack samples by simulating spoofing clues of physical and digital attacks, respectively, which significantly improve the capability of the model to detect "unseen" attack types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-physical-digital-facial-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning representations of learning representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-of-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ICLR conference is unique among the top machine learning conferences in that all submitted papers are openly available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-of-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaSagnA: Language-based Segmentation Assistant for Complex Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lasagna-language-based-segmentation-assistant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements have empowered Large Language Models for Vision (vLLMs) to generate detailed perceptual outcomes, including bounding boxes and masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lasagna-language-based-segmentation-assistant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Image Modeling as a Framework for Self-Supervised Learning across Eye Movements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-image-modeling-as-a-framework-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To make sense of their surroundings, intelligent systems must transform complex sensory inputs to structured codes that are reduced to task-relevant information such as object category.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-image-modeling-as-a-framework-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pay Attention to Your Neighbours: Training-Free Open-Vocabulary Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pay-attention-to-your-neighbours-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing approaches often rely on impractical supervised pre-training or access to additional pre-trained networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pay-attention-to-your-neighbours-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-training Small Base LMs with Fewer Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-small-base-lms-with-fewer-tokens</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we show that smaller LMs trained utilizing some of the layers of GPT2-medium (355M) and GPT-2-large (770M) can effectively match the val loss of their bigger counterparts when trained from scratch for the same number of training steps on OpenWebText dataset with 9B tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-small-base-lms-with-fewer-tokens</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Ambiguity from Perspective of Uncertainty Inference and Affinity Diversification for Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-ambiguity-from-perspective-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When activating class objects, we argue that the false activation stems from the bias to the ambiguous regions during the feature extraction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-ambiguity-from-perspective-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoostTrack: boosting the similarity measure and detection confidence for improved multiple object tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosttrack-boosting-the-similarity-measure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To utilize low-detection score bounding boxes in one-stage association, we propose to boost the confidence scores of two groups of detections: the detections we assume to correspond to the existing tracked object, and the detections we assume to correspond to a previously undetected object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosttrack-boosting-the-similarity-measure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathological Primitive Segmentation Based on Visual Foundation Model with Zero-Shot Mask Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathological-primitive-segmentation-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Primitive detection and segmentation in digitized tissue samples are essential for objective and automated diagnosis and prognosis of cancer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathological-primitive-segmentation-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolutionary Preference Sampling for Pareto Set Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-preference-sampling-for-pareto</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, Pareto Set Learning (PSL) has been proposed for learning the entire Pareto set using a neural network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-preference-sampling-for-pareto</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Integration of Semantic and Structural Knowledge in Knowledge Graph Entity Typing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-integration-of-semantic-and-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Knowledge Graph Entity Typing (KGET) task aims to predict missing type annotations for entities in knowledge graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-integration-of-semantic-and-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Language-Level Performance Disparity in mPLMs via Teacher Language Selection and Cross-lingual Self-Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-language-level-performance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we introduce ALSACE to leverage the learned knowledge from the well-performing languages to guide under-performing ones within the same mPLM, eliminating the need for additional labeled multilingual data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-language-level-performance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperbolic Delaunay Geometric Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbolic-delaunay-geometric-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperbolic machine learning is an emerging field aimed at representing data with a hierarchical structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbolic-delaunay-geometric-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Dataset Creation and Fine-Tuning of Transformer Models for Question Answering in Serbian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-dataset-creation-and-fine-tuning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on generating a synthetic question answering (QA) dataset using an adapted Translate-Align-Retrieve method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-dataset-creation-and-fine-tuning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Explanations for Face Forgery Detection via Adversarial Removal of Artifacts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanations-for-face-forgery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We verify the effectiveness of the proposed explanations from two aspects: (1) Counterfactual Trace Visualization: the enhanced forgery images are useful to reveal artifacts by visually contrasting the original images and two different visualization methods; (2) Transferable Adversarial Attacks: the adversarial forgery images generated by attacking the detection model are able to mislead other detection models, implying the removed artifacts are general.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanations-for-face-forgery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large Scale Survey of Motivation in Software Development and Analysis of its Validity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-survey-of-motivation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, improvement analysis shows that an increase in most motivators predicts an increase in general motivation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-survey-of-motivation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Continuous Sign Language Recognition with Adapted Image Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-continuous-sign-language-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, fully fine-tuning the model easily forgets the generic essential knowledge acquired in the pretraining stage and overfits the downstream data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-continuous-sign-language-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoPE: Mixture of Prefix Experts for Zero-Shot Dialogue State Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mope-mixture-of-prefix-experts-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zero-shot dialogue state tracking (DST) transfers knowledge to unseen domains, reducing the cost of annotating new datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mope-mixture-of-prefix-experts-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Interactive LLM Serving with Proxy Model-based Sequence Length Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-interactive-llm-serving-with-proxy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have been driving a new wave of interactive AI applications across numerous domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-interactive-llm-serving-with-proxy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training-free Boost for Open-Vocabulary Object Detection with Confidence Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-free-boost-for-open-vocabulary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, in the region-proposal stage, proposals that contain novel instances showcase lower objectness scores, since they are treated as background proposals during the training phase.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-free-boost-for-open-vocabulary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Visual Question Answering through Question-Driven Image Captions as Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-visual-question-answering-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study explores the impact of incorporating image captioning as an intermediary process within the VQA pipeline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-visual-question-answering-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EventEgo3D: 3D Human Motion Capture from Egocentric Event Streams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eventego3d-3d-human-motion-capture-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response to the existing limitations, this paper 1) introduces a new problem, i. e., 3D human motion capture from an egocentric monocular event camera with a fisheye lens, and 2) proposes the first approach to it called EventEgo3D (EE3D).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eventego3d-3d-human-motion-capture-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-Scale Multi-Domain Recommendation: an Automatic Domain Feature Extraction and Personalized Integration Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-domain-recommendation-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, by personalized integration of domain features from other domains for each user and the innovation in the training mode, the DFEI framework can yield more accurate conversion identification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-domain-recommendation-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Direct May Not Be the Best: An Incremental Evolution View of Pose Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/direct-may-not-be-the-best-an-incremental</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To deal with this challenge, we propose a fine-grained incremental evolution centered pose generation framework, rather than traditional direct one-to-one in a rush.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/direct-may-not-be-the-best-an-incremental</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape Completion in the Dark: Completing Vertebrae Morphology from 3D Ultrasound</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-completion-in-the-dark-completing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Purpose: Ultrasound (US) imaging, while advantageous for its radiation-free nature, is challenging to interpret due to only partially visible organs and a lack of complete 3D information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-completion-in-the-dark-completing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming detection of significant delay changes in public transport systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-detection-of-significant-delay</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The method we propose can be used with different change detectors, such as ADWIN, applied to location data stream shuffled to individual edges of a transport graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-detection-of-significant-delay</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homography Guided Temporal Fusion for Road Line and Marking Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/homography-guided-temporal-fusion-for-road-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reliable segmentation of road lines and markings is critical to autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/homography-guided-temporal-fusion-for-road-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Any2Point: Empowering Any-modality Large Models for Efficient 3D Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/any2point-empowering-any-modality-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The adapter incorporates prior spatial knowledge from the source modality to guide the local feature aggregation of 3D tokens, compelling the semantic adaption of any-modality transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/any2point-empowering-any-modality-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nostra Domina at EvaLatin 2024: Improving Latin Polarity Detection through Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nostra-domina-at-evalatin-2024-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes submissions from the team Nostra Domina to the EvaLatin 2024 shared task of emotion polarity detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nostra-domina-at-evalatin-2024-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NoticIA: A Clickbait Article Summarization Dataset in Spanish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noticia-a-clickbait-article-summarization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present NoticIA, a dataset consisting of 850 Spanish news articles featuring prominent clickbait headlines, each paired with high-quality, single-sentence generative summarizations written by humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noticia-a-clickbait-article-summarization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monte Carlo Tree Search with Boltzmann Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-tree-search-with-boltzmann-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monte-Carlo Tree Search (MCTS) methods, such as Upper Confidence Bound applied to Trees (UCT), are instrumental to automated planning techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-tree-search-with-boltzmann-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eliminating Catastrophic Overfitting Via Abnormal Adversarial Examples Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eliminating-catastrophic-overfitting-via-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we design a novel method, termed Abnormal Adversarial Examples Regularization (AAER), which explicitly regularizes the variation of AAEs to hinder the classifier from becoming distorted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eliminating-catastrophic-overfitting-via-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DGMamba: Domain Generalization via Generalized State Space Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgmamba-domain-generalization-via-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SPR strives to encourage the model to concentrate more on objects rather than context, consisting of two designs: Prior-Free Scanning~(PFS), and Domain Context Interchange~(DCI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgmamba-domain-generalization-via-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curated Datasets and Neural Models for Machine Translation of Informal Registers between Mayan and Spanish Vernaculars</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curated-datasets-and-neural-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Mayan languages comprise a language family with an ancient history, millions of speakers, and immense cultural value, that, nevertheless, remains severely underrepresented in terms of resources and global exposure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curated-datasets-and-neural-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Language Model with Generalized Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-language-model-with-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce the Scalable Language Model (SLM) to overcome these limitations within a more challenging and generalized setting, representing a significant advancement toward practical applications for continual learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-language-model-with-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MindBridge: A Cross-Subject Brain Decoding Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mindbridge-a-cross-subject-brain-decoding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Currently, brain decoding is confined to a per-subject-per-model paradigm, limiting its applicability to the same individual for whom the decoding model is trained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mindbridge-a-cross-subject-brain-decoding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViM-UNet: Vision Mamba for Biomedical Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vim-unet-vision-mamba-for-biomedical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we introduce ViM-UNet, a novel segmentation architecture based on it and compare it to UNet and UNETR for two challenging microscopy instance segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vim-unet-vision-mamba-for-biomedical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring Change Points in High-Dimensional Linear Regression via Approximate Message Passing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-change-points-in-high-dimensional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of localizing change points in high-dimensional linear regression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-change-points-in-high-dimensional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HGRN2: Gated Linear RNNs with State Expansion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgrn2-gated-linear-rnns-with-state-expansion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hierarchically gated linear RNN (HGRN, Qin et al. 2023) has demonstrated competitive training speed and performance in language modeling, while offering efficient inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgrn2-gated-linear-rnns-with-state-expansion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Augmentation-Based Dialectal Adaptation for LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-based-dialectal-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an approach that combines the strengths of different types of language models and leverages data augmentation techniques to improve task performance on three South Slavic dialects: Chakavian, Cherkano, and Torlak.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-based-dialectal-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLoCO: Learning Long Contexts Offline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lloco-learning-long-contexts-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce LLoCO, a technique that combines context compression, retrieval, and parameter-efficient finetuning using LoRA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lloco-learning-long-contexts-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AmpleGCG: Learning a Universal and Transferable Generative Model of Adversarial Suffixes for Jailbreaking Both Open and Closed LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amplegcg-learning-a-universal-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we utilize those successful suffixes as training data to learn a generative model, named AmpleGCG, which captures the distribution of adversarial suffixes given a harmful query and enables the rapid generation of hundreds of suffixes for any harmful queries in seconds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amplegcg-learning-a-universal-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SFSORT: Scene Features-based Simple Online Real-Time Tracker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfsort-scene-features-based-simple-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces SFSORT, the world's fastest multi-object tracking system based on experiments conducted on MOT Challenge datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfsort-scene-features-based-simple-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Aggregation Network for Dichotomous Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-aggregation-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dichotomous Image Segmentation (DIS) has recently emerged towards high-precision object segmentation from high-resolution natural images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-aggregation-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TBSN: Transformer-Based Blind-Spot Network for Self-Supervised Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tbsn-transformer-based-blind-spot-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For channel self-attention, we observe that it may leak the blind-spot information when the channel number is greater than spatial size in the deep layers of multi-scale architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tbsn-transformer-based-blind-spot-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UltraEval: A Lightweight Platform for Flexible and Comprehensive Evaluation for LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultraeval-a-lightweight-platform-for-flexible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of LLMs calls for a lightweight and easy-to-use framework for swift evaluation deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultraeval-a-lightweight-platform-for-flexible</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
