<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 21:06:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Causality Compensated Attention for Contextual Biased Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-compensated-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual attention does not always capture the essential object representation desired for robust predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-compensated-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GANterfactual-RL: Understanding Reinforcement Learning Agents' Strategies through Visual Counterfactual Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ganterfactual-rl-understanding-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, research focusing on counterfactual explanations, specifically for RL agents with visual input, is scarce and does not go beyond identifying defective agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ganterfactual-rl-understanding-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-Driven Representation Learning for Robotics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-driven-representation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we demonstrate that existing representations yield inconsistent results across these tasks: masked autoencoding approaches pick up on low-level spatial features at the cost of high-level semantics, while contrastive learning approaches capture the opposite.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-driven-representation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Membership Inference Attacks against Synthetic Data through Overfitting Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membership-inference-attacks-against-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we argue for a realistic MIA setting that assumes the attacker has some knowledge of the underlying data distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membership-inference-attacks-against-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inducing Neural Collapse in Deep Long-tailed Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inducing-neural-collapse-in-deep-long-tailed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the reasons is that the learned representations (i. e. features) from the imbalanced datasets are less effective than those from balanced datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inducing-neural-collapse-in-deep-long-tailed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieved Sequence Augmentation for Protein Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieved-sequence-augmentation-for-protein</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RSA links query protein sequences to a set of sequences with similar structures or properties in the database and combines these sequences for downstream prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieved-sequence-augmentation-for-protein</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVERED, CollabOratiVE Robot Environment Dataset for 3D Semantic segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covered-collaborative-robot-environment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the importance of semantic understanding for such applications, 3D semantic segmentation of collaborative robot workspaces lacks sufficient research and dedicated datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covered-collaborative-robot-environment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Convolutional Vision Transformer for Semantic Segmentation of Side-Scan Sonar Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-convolutional-vision-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome the lack of CNN-like inductive biases, thereby making ViTs more conducive to applications in low data regimes, we propose a novel feature extraction module to replace the Multi-layer Perceptron (MLP) block within transformer layers and a novel module to extract multiscale patch embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-convolutional-vision-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUX-PLMs: Pre-training Language Models with Data Multiplexing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mux-plms-pre-training-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data multiplexing is a recently proposed method for improving a model's inference efficiency by processing multiple instances simultaneously using an ordered representation mixture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mux-plms-pre-training-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-Phenotype: Discovering Phenotypes of Predictive Temporal Patterns in Disease Progression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-phenotype-discovering-phenotypes-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clustering time-series data in healthcare is crucial for clinical phenotyping to understand patients' disease progression patterns and to design treatment guidelines tailored to homogeneous patient subgroups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-phenotype-discovering-phenotypes-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Massively Multilingual ASR With Auxiliary CTC Objectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-massively-multilingual-asr-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce our work on improving performance on FLEURS, a 102-language open ASR benchmark, by conditioning the entire model on language identity (LID).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-massively-multilingual-asr-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STA: Self-controlled Text Augmentation for Improving Text Classifications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sta-self-controlled-text-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advancements in Machine Learning, many tasks still involve working in low-data regimes which can make solving natural language problems difficult.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sta-self-controlled-text-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaMA: Open and Efficient Foundation Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-open-and-efficient-foundation-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce LLaMA, a collection of foundation language models ranging from 7B to 65B parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-open-and-efficient-foundation-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LightTS: Lightweight Time Series Classification with Adaptive Ensemble Distillation -- Extended Version</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightts-lightweight-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we propose adaptive ensemble distillation that assigns adaptive weights to different base models such that their varying classification capabilities contribute purposefully to the training of the lightweight model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightts-lightweight-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedDBL: Communication and Data Efficient Federated Deep-Broad Learning for Histopathological Tissue Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddbl-communication-and-data-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a universal and lightweight federated learning framework, named Federated Deep-Broad Learning (FedDBL), to achieve superior classification performance with limited training samples and only one-round communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddbl-communication-and-data-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnbiasedNets: A Dataset Diversification Framework for Robustness Bias Alleviation in Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiasednets-a-dataset-diversification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, UnbiasedNets provides a notable improvement over existing works, while even reducing the robustness bias significantly in some cases, as observed by comparing the NNs trained on the diversified and original datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiasednets-a-dataset-diversification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending Against Backdoor Attacks by Layer-wise Feature Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defending-against-backdoor-attacks-by-layer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find out that the feature difference between benign and poisoned samples tends to be maximum at a critical layer, which is not always the one typically used in existing defenses, namely the layer before fully-connected layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defending-against-backdoor-attacks-by-layer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrospective Uncertainties for Deep Models using Vine Copulas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrospective-uncertainties-for-deep-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the major progress of deep models as learning machines, uncertainty estimation remains a major challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrospective-uncertainties-for-deep-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slate-Aware Ranking for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slate-aware-ranking-for-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, the ranking stage is still essential for most applications to provide high-quality candidate set for the re-ranking stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slate-aware-ranking-for-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EvoTorch: Scalable Evolutionary Computation in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evotorch-scalable-evolutionary-computation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evolutionary computation is an important component within various fields such as artificial intelligence research, reinforcement learning, robotics, industrial automation and/or optimization, engineering design, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evotorch-scalable-evolutionary-computation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Unbalanced Sobolev Transport for Measures on a Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-unbalanced-sobolev-transport-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the proposed unbalanced Sobolev transport (UST) admits a closed-form formula for fast computation, and it is also negative definite.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-unbalanced-sobolev-transport-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Laplace Control for Continuous-time Delayed Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-laplace-control-for-continuous-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many real-world offline reinforcement learning (RL) problems involve continuous-time environments with delays.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-laplace-control-for-continuous-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Targeted Accuracy Diagnostic for Variational Approximations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-targeted-accuracy-diagnostic-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Variational Inference (VI) is an attractive alternative to Markov Chain Monte Carlo (MCMC) due to its computational efficiency in the case of large datasets and/or complex models with high-dimensional parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-targeted-accuracy-diagnostic-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Computationally Efficient Responsibility Attribution in Decentralized Partially Observable MDPs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-computationally-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Responsibility attribution is a key concept of accountable multi-agent decision making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-computationally-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provably Efficient Neural Offline Reinforcement Learning via Perturbed Rewards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-efficient-neural-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel offline reinforcement learning (RL) algorithm, namely Value Iteration with Perturbed Rewards (VIPeR) which amalgamates the randomized value function idea with the pessimism principle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-efficient-neural-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SplineCam: Exact Visualization and Characterization of Deep Network Geometry and Decision Boundaries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/splinecam-exact-visualization-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we go one step further by developing the first provably exact method for computing the geometry of a DN's mapping - including its decision boundary - over a specified region of the data space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/splinecam-exact-visualization-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Stable Test-Time Adaptation in Dynamic Wild World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-stable-test-time-adaptation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the unstable reasons and find that the batch norm layer is a crucial factor hindering TTA stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-stable-test-time-adaptation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurvivalGAN: Generating Time-to-Event Data for Survival Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survivalgan-generating-time-to-event-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SurvivalGAN outperforms multiple baselines at generating survival data, and in particular addresses the failure modes as measured by the new metrics, in addition to improving downstream performance of survival models trained on the synthetic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survivalgan-generating-time-to-event-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotion Prediction Oriented method with Multiple Supervisions for Emotion-Cause Pair Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotion-prediction-oriented-method-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Emotion-cause pair extraction (ECPE) task aims to extract all the pairs of emotions and their causes from an unannotated emotion text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotion-prediction-oriented-method-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProofNet: Autoformalizing and Formally Proving Undergraduate-Level Mathematics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proofnet-autoformalizing-and-formally-proving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce ProofNet, a benchmark for autoformalization and formal proving of undergraduate-level mathematics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proofnet-autoformalizing-and-formally-proving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Temporal Reasoning for Evidence-Based Fact-Checking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-temporal-reasoning-for-evidence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings show that the presence of temporal information and the manner in which timelines are constructed greatly influence how fact-checking models determine the relevance and supporting or refuting character of evidence documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-temporal-reasoning-for-evidence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Depth Look at Word Filling Societal Bias Measures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-depth-look-at-word-filling-societal-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many measures of societal bias in language models have been proposed in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-depth-look-at-word-filling-societal-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Data Efficiency of Multi-Objective Quality-Diversity through Gradient Assistance and Crowding Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-data-efficiency-of-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that MOME-PGX is between 4. 3 and 42 times more data-efficient than MOME and doubles the performance of MOME, NSGA-II and SPEA2 in challenging environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-data-efficiency-of-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Membership Inference Attack under Local Differential Privacy in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-membership-inference-attack-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) was originally regarded as a framework for collaborative learning among clients with data privacy protection through a coordinating server.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-membership-inference-attack-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Sentence Similarity Estimation for Unsupervised Extractive Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-sentence-similarity-estimation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised extractive summarization aims to extract salient sentences from a document as the summary without labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-sentence-similarity-estimation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HULAT at SemEval-2023 Task 9: Data augmentation for pre-trained transformers applied to Multilingual Tweet Intimacy Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hulat-at-semeval-2023-task-9-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During the development phase, our best results were obtained by using XLM-T. Data augmentation techniques provide a very slight improvement in the results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hulat-at-semeval-2023-task-9-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MesoGraph: Automatic Profiling of Malignant Mesothelioma Subtypes from Histological Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesograph-automatic-profiling-of-malignant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tissue is represented by a cell graph with both cell-level morphological and regional features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesograph-automatic-profiling-of-malignant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Limitations of Physics-informed Deep Learning: Illustrations Using First Order Hyperbolic Conservation Law-based Traffic Flow Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-limitations-of-physics-informed-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detailed in the case study, we present the contradistinction in PIDL results between learning the traffic flow model (LWR PDE) and its variation with diffusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-limitations-of-physics-informed-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPINDLE: Spinning Raw Text into Lambda Terms with Graph Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spindle-spinning-raw-text-into-lambda-terms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes SPINDLE - an open source Python module implementing an efficient and accurate parser for written Dutch that transforms raw text input to programs for meaning composition, expressed as {\lambda} terms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spindle-spinning-raw-text-into-lambda-terms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Molecular Structures with Intrinsic Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-molecular-structures-with-intrinsic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since its foundations, more than one hundred years ago, the field of structural biology has strived to understand and analyze the properties of molecules and their interactions by studying the structure that they take in 3D space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-molecular-structures-with-intrinsic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Free Diversity-Based Ensemble Selection For One-Shot Federated Learning in Machine Learning Model Market</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-free-diversity-based-ensemble-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emerging availability of trained machine learning models has put forward the novel concept of Machine Learning Model Market in which one can harness the collective intelligence of multiple well-trained models to improve the performance of the resultant model through one-shot federated learning and ensemble learning in a data-free manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-free-diversity-based-ensemble-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Paradigm Analysis of Thai Capital Market Linkages: Bivariate/Vine Copulas, Granger Causality, Network Centrality, and Graph Neural Network/Graph Embedding Approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-paradigm-analysis-of-thai-capital</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analytically thorough understanding of causal, probabilistic, and informational linkages amongst modern, highly-interconnected capital markets is fundamental to the promotion of capital-market innovation, efficiency, and resilience; whereupon innovative, efficient, and resilient capital markets are fundamental to the sustainable economic development of any nation and the robust financial stability of her economy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-paradigm-analysis-of-thai-capital</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving differential equations using physics informed deep learning: a hand-on tutorial with benchmark tests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-differential-equations-using-physics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We revisit the original approach of using deep learning and neural networks to solve differential equations by incorporating the knowledge of the equation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-differential-equations-using-physics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Adaptive Conformal Prediction Using Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-adaptive-conformal-prediction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the use of self-supervision beyond model pretraining and representation learning has been largely unexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-adaptive-conformal-prediction-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Social Media for Early Detection of Depression in COVID-19 Patients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-social-media-for-early-detection-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, We conducted an extensive analysis of this dataset to investigate the characteristic of COVID-19 patients with a higher risk of depression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-social-media-for-early-detection-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Statement Extraction from Press Briefings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-statement-extraction-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results indicate that claim detection can be used to identify statements in press briefings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-statement-extraction-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web-Scale Academic Name Disambiguation: the WhoIsWho Benchmark, Leaderboard, and Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/web-scale-academic-name-disambiguation-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Name disambiguation -- a fundamental problem in online academic systems -- is now facing greater challenges with the increasing growth of research papers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/web-scale-academic-name-disambiguation-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Neural Span-Based Continual Named Entity Recognition Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-span-based-continual-named-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Named Entity Recognition (NER) models capable of Continual Learning (CL) are realistically valuable in areas where entity types continuously increase (e. g., personal assistants).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-span-based-continual-named-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securely implementing and managing neighborhood solar with storage and peer to peer transactive energy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/securely-implementing-and-managing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed infrastructure would (i) increase the resilience of the customers in case the utility grid becomes unavailable, (ii) reduce AC/DC conversion losses since a majority of the DER generation is in DC, and (iii) with the help of BESS, the customers will have a lesser impact on the utility grid in terms of California 'duck curve.']]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/securely-implementing-and-managing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher Intervention: Improving Convergence of Quantization Aware Training for Ultra-Low Precision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teacher-intervention-improving-convergence-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained Transformer models such as BERT have shown great success in a wide range of applications, but at the cost of substantial increases in model complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teacher-intervention-improving-convergence-of</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
