<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 21:06:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Llama 2: Open Foundation and Fine-Tuned Chat Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-2-open-foundation-and-fine-tuned-chat</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop and release Llama 2, a collection of pretrained and fine-tuned large language models (LLMs) ranging in scale from 7 billion to 70 billion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-2-open-foundation-and-fine-tuned-chat</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EGE-UNet: an Efficient Group Enhanced UNet for skin lesion segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ege-unet-an-efficient-group-enhanced-unet-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, to our best knowledge, this is the first model with a parameter count limited to just 50KB.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ege-unet-an-efficient-group-enhanced-unet-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconstructed Convolution Module Based Look-Up Tables for Efficient Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructed-convolution-module-based-look</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enlarge RF with contained LUT sizes, we propose a novel Reconstructed Convolution(RC) module, which decouples channel-wise and spatial calculation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructed-convolution-module-based-look</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SkeletonMAE: Graph-based Masked Autoencoder for Skeleton Sequence Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeletonmae-graph-based-masked-autoencoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, these methods ignore how to utilize the fine-grained dependencies among different skeleton joints to pre-train an efficient skeleton sequence learning model that can generalize well across different datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeletonmae-graph-based-masked-autoencoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Fly Neural Style Smoothing for Risk-Averse Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-fly-neural-style-smoothing-for-risk</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enable risk-averse predictions from a DG classifier, we propose a novel inference procedure, Test-Time Neural Style Smoothing (TT-NSS), that uses a "style-smoothed" version of the DG classifier for prediction at test time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-fly-neural-style-smoothing-for-risk</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not All Steps are Created Equal: Selective Diffusion Distillation for Image Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-steps-are-created-equal-selective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conditional diffusion models have demonstrated impressive performance in image manipulation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-steps-are-created-equal-selective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLLIE: Systematic Construction of Constrained Text Generation Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collie-systematic-construction-of-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text generation under constraints have seen increasing interests in natural language processing, especially with the rapidly improving capabilities of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collie-systematic-construction-of-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Image Harmonization with Generative Model Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-image-harmonization-with-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, in the harmonization process, a human mainly utilizes his long-term prior on harmonious images and makes a composite image close to that prior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-image-harmonization-with-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flow Matching in Latent Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-matching-in-latent-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose to apply flow matching in the latent spaces of pretrained autoencoders, which offers improved computational efficiency and scalability for high-resolution image synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-matching-in-latent-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retentive Network: A Successor to Transformer for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retentive-network-a-successor-to-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose Retentive Network (RetNet) as a foundation architecture for large language models, simultaneously achieving training parallelism, low-cost inference, and good performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retentive-network-a-successor-to-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Point Affiliation in Feature Upsampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-point-affiliation-in-feature-upsampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the notion of point affiliation into feature upsampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-point-affiliation-in-feature-upsampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AltFreezing for More General Video Face Forgery Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/altfreezing-for-more-general-video-face-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to capture both spatial and temporal artifacts in one model for face forgery detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/altfreezing-for-more-general-video-face-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Local Basis Functions for Shape Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-local-basis-functions-for-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantitative and qualitative experiments demonstrate that our method outperforms the state-of-the-art methods in shape completion, detail preservation, generalization to unseen geometries, and computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-local-basis-functions-for-shape</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlashAttention-2: Faster Attention with Better Parallelism and Work Partitioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashattention-2-faster-attention-with-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that the inefficiency is due to suboptimal work partitioning between different thread blocks and warps on the GPU, causing either low-occupancy or unnecessary shared memory reads/writes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashattention-2-faster-attention-with-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Box-DETR: Understanding and Boxing Conditional Spatial Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/box-detr-understanding-and-boxing-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In DAB-DETR, such queries are modulated by the so-called conditional linear projection at each decoder stage, aiming to search for positions of interest such as the four extremities of the box.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/box-detr-understanding-and-boxing-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Video Depth Stabilizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-video-depth-stabilizer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video depth estimation aims to infer temporally consistent depth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-video-depth-stabilizer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributed bundle adjustment with block-based sparse matrix compression for super large scale datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributed-bundle-adjustment-with-block</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from them, we utilize the exact LM algorithm to conduct global bundle adjustment where the formation of the reduced camera system (RCS) is actually parallelized and executed in a distributed way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributed-bundle-adjustment-with-block</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting the Robustness of the Minimum Error Entropy Criterion: A Transfer Learning Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-robustness-of-the-minimum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we revisit the robustness of the minimum error entropy (MEE) criterion, a widely used objective in statistical signal processing to deal with non-Gaussian noises, and investigate its feasibility and usefulness in real-life transfer learning regression tasks, where distributional shifts are common.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-robustness-of-the-minimum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GBT: Two-stage transformer framework for non-stationary time series forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gbt-two-stage-transformer-framework-for-non</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It decouples the prediction process of TSFT into two stages, including Auto-Regression stage and Self-Regression stage to tackle the problem of different statistical properties between input and prediction sequences. Prediction results of Auto-Regression stage serve as a Good Beginning, i. e., a better initialization for inputs of Self-Regression stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gbt-two-stage-transformer-framework-for-non</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Stealthy Backdoor Attacks against Speech Recognition via Elements of Sound</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-stealthy-backdoor-attacks-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by these findings, we propose to exploit elements of sound ($e. g.$, pitch and timbre) to design more stealthy yet effective poison-only backdoor attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-stealthy-backdoor-attacks-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAYEN: Imposition of Hard Convex Constraints on Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rayen-imposition-of-hard-convex-constraints</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents RAYEN, a framework to impose hard convex constraints on the output or latent variable of a neural network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rayen-imposition-of-hard-convex-constraints</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LuckyMera: a Modular AI Framework for Building Hybrid NetHack Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/luckymera-a-modular-ai-framework-for-building</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the last few decades we have witnessed a significant development in Artificial Intelligence (AI) thanks to the availability of a variety of testbeds, mostly based on simulated environments and video games.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/luckymera-a-modular-ai-framework-for-building</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving End-to-End Speech Translation by Imitation-Based Knowledge Distillation with Synthetic Transcripts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-end-to-end-speech-translation-by-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an imitation learning approach where a teacher NMT system corrects the errors of an AST student without relying on manual transcripts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-end-to-end-speech-translation-by-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-range Dependency based Multi-Layer Perceptron for Heterogeneous Information Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-range-dependency-based-multi-layer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, to solve the high-cost problem of leveraging long-range dependencies, LDMLP adopts a search stage to discover effective meta-paths automatically, reducing the exponentially increased number of meta-paths to a constant.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-range-dependency-based-multi-layer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M-FLAG: Medical Vision-Language Pre-training with Frozen Language Models and Latent Space Geometry Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-flag-medical-vision-language-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method, named Medical vision-language pre-training with Frozen language models and Latent spAce Geometry optimization (M-FLAG), leverages a frozen language model for training stability and efficiency and introduces a novel orthogonality loss to harmonize the latent space geometry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-flag-medical-vision-language-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoAD: Automatic Diagnosis through Symptom and Disease Collaborative Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coad-automatic-diagnosis-through-symptom-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic diagnosis (AD), a critical application of AI in healthcare, employs machine learning techniques to assist doctors in gathering patient symptom information for precise disease diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coad-automatic-diagnosis-through-symptom-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShiftNAS: Improving One-shot NAS via Probability Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shiftnas-improving-one-shot-nas-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the problem of uniform sampling, we propose ShiftNAS, a method that can adjust the sampling probability based on the complexity of subnets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shiftnas-improving-one-shot-nas-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Rubik's Cube inspired approach to Clifford synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-rubik-s-cube-inspired-approach-to-clifford</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The problem of decomposing an arbitrary Clifford element into a sequence of Clifford gates is known as Clifford synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-rubik-s-cube-inspired-approach-to-clifford</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kernel-Based Testing for Single-Cell Differential Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernel-based-testing-for-single-cell</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we propose to benefit from the kernel-testing framework to compare the complex cell-wise distributions of molecular features in a non-linear manner based on their kernel embedding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernel-based-testing-for-single-cell</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HeroLT: Benchmarking Heterogeneous Long-Tailed Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/herolt-benchmarking-heterogeneous-long-tailed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this, we develop the most comprehensive (to the best of our knowledge) long-tailed learning benchmark named HeroLT, which integrates 13 state-of-the-art algorithms and 6 evaluation metrics on 14 real-world benchmark datasets across 4 tasks from 3 domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/herolt-benchmarking-heterogeneous-long-tailed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast model inference and training on-board of Satellites</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-model-inference-and-training-on-board-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we demonstrate the reliable use of RaVAEn onboard a satellite, achieving an encoding time of 0. 110s for tiles of a 4. 8x4. 8 km$^2$ area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-model-inference-and-training-on-board-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOPE: High-order Polynomial Expansion of Black-box Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hope-high-order-polynomial-expansion-of-black</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their remarkable performance, deep neural networks remain mostly ``black boxes'', suggesting inexplicability and hindering their wide applications in fields requiring making rational decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hope-high-order-polynomial-expansion-of-black</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Jailbreak: A Benchmark for Evaluating Text Safety and Output Robustness of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-jailbreak-a-benchmark-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a systematic analysis of the safety and robustness of LLMs concerning the position of explicit normal instructions, word replacement (verbs in explicit normal instructions, target groups in malicious instructions, cue words in malicious instructions), and instruction replacement (different explicit normal instructions).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-jailbreak-a-benchmark-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Item Global Residual Value for Fair Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-item-global-residual-value-for-fair</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we call for a shift of attention from modeling user preferences to developing fair exposure mechanisms for items.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-item-global-residual-value-for-fair</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVDFormer: Complementing Point Cloud via Self-view Augmentation and Self-structure Dual-generator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svdformer-complementing-point-cloud-via-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel network, SVDFormer, to tackle two specific challenges in point cloud completion: understanding faithful global shapes from incomplete point clouds and generating high-accuracy local structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svdformer-complementing-point-cloud-via-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Objective Optimization of Performance and Interpretability of Tabular Supervised Machine Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-optimization-of-performance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficient optimization is achieved via augmentation of the search space of the learning algorithm by incorporating feature selection, interaction and monotonicity constraints into the hyperparameter search space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-optimization-of-performance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBMLtoODEjax: efficient simulation and optimization of ODE SBML models in JAX</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sbmltoodejax-efficient-simulation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Developing methods to explore, predict and control the dynamic behavior of biological systems, from protein pathways to complex cellular processes, is an essential frontier of research for bioengineering and biomedicine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sbmltoodejax-efficient-simulation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scale-Aware Modulation Meet Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-aware-modulation-meet-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, SMT with 11. 5M / 2. 4GFLOPs and 32M / 7. 7GFLOPs can achieve 82. 2% and 84. 3% top-1 accuracy on ImageNet-1K, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-aware-modulation-meet-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence for Science in Quantum, Atomistic, and Continuum Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artificial-intelligence-for-science-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advances in artificial intelligence (AI) are fueling a new paradigm of discoveries in natural sciences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artificial-intelligence-for-science-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deficiency-Aware Masked Transformer for Video Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deficiency-aware-masked-transformer-for-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we pretrain a image inpainting model DMT_img serve as a prior for distilling the video model DMT_vid, thereby benefiting the hallucination of deficiency cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deficiency-aware-masked-transformer-for-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Snake Convolution based on Topological Geometric Constraints for Tubular Structure Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-snake-convolution-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we note the specificity of tubular structures and use this knowledge to guide our DSCNet to simultaneously enhance perception in three stages: feature extraction, feature fusion, and loss constraint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-snake-convolution-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-level Interaction for Domain Adaptive Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-level-interaction-for-domain-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To circumvent the costly pixel-wise annotations of real-world images in the semantic segmentation task, the Unsupervised Domain Adaptation (UDA) is explored to firstly train a model with the labeled source data (synthetic images) and then adapt it to the unlabeled target data (real images).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-level-interaction-for-domain-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Householder Projector for Unsupervised Latent Semantics Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/householder-projector-for-unsupervised-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs), especially the recent style-based generators (StyleGANs), have versatile semantics in the structured latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/householder-projector-for-unsupervised-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GastroVision: A Multi-class Endoscopy Image Dataset for Computer Aided Gastrointestinal Disease Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gastrovision-a-multi-class-endoscopy-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Integrating real-time artificial intelligence (AI) systems in clinical practices faces challenges such as scalability and acceptance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gastrovision-a-multi-class-endoscopy-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Emergent Abilities Exist in Quantized Large Language Models: An Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-emergent-abilities-exist-in-quantized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from previous studies focused on overall performance, this work aims to investigate the impact of quantization on \emph{emergent abilities}, which are important characteristics that distinguish LLMs from small language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-emergent-abilities-exist-in-quantized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Flexible Time-to-event Modeling: Optimizing Neural Networks via Rank Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-flexible-time-to-event-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method is a semiparametric approach to AFT modeling that does not impose any distributional assumptions on the survival time distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-flexible-time-to-event-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFLECT-DGNN: Influencer Prediction with Dynamic Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inflect-dgnn-influencer-prediction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the results of various models to demonstrate the importance of capturing graph representation, temporal dependencies, and using a profit-driven methodology for evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inflect-dgnn-influencer-prediction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For One-Shot Decoding: Unsupervised Deep Learning-Based Polar Decoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/for-one-shot-decoding-unsupervised-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an unsupervised deep learning-based decoding scheme that enables one-shot decoding of polar codes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/for-one-shot-decoding-unsupervised-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransNuSeg: A Lightweight Multi-Task Transformer for Nuclei Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transnuseg-a-lightweight-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In conclusion, TransNuSeg confirms the strength of Transformer in the context of nuclei segmentation, which thus can serve as an efficient solution for real clinical practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transnuseg-a-lightweight-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POMDP inference and robust solution via deep reinforcement learning: An application to railway optimal maintenance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pomdp-inference-and-robust-solution-via-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The POMDP with uncertain parameters is then solved via deep RL techniques with the parameter distributions incorporated into the solution via domain randomization, in order to develop solutions that are robust to model uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pomdp-inference-and-robust-solution-via-deep</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
