<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 21:13:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>GUI-explorer: Autonomous Exploration and Mining of Transition-aware Knowledge for GUI Agent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gui-explorer-autonomous-exploration-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GUI automation faces critical challenges in dynamic environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gui-explorer-autonomous-exploration-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sufficient conditions for offline reactivation in recurrent neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sufficient-conditions-for-offline-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During periods of quiescence, such as sleep, neural activity in many brain circuits resembles that observed during periods of task engagement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sufficient-conditions-for-offline-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpatialScore: Towards Unified Evaluation for Multimodal Spatial Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatialscore-towards-unified-evaluation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal large language models (MLLMs) have achieved impressive success in question-answering tasks, yet their capabilities for spatial understanding are less explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatialscore-towards-unified-evaluation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FoMoH: A clinically meaningful foundation model evaluation for structured electronic health records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fomoh-a-clinically-meaningful-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foundation models hold significant promise in healthcare, given their capacity to extract meaningful representations independent of downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fomoh-a-clinically-meaningful-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptTAD: Object-Prompt Enhanced Traffic Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompttad-object-prompt-enhanced-traffic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous frame-level methods are often vulnerable to interference from these dynamic backgrounds and struggle to detect small objects located at a distance or off-center.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompttad-object-prompt-enhanced-traffic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICYM2I: The illusion of multimodal informativeness under missingness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icym2i-the-illusion-of-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal learning is of continued interest in artificial intelligence-based applications, motivated by the potential information gain from combining different types of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icym2i-the-illusion-of-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoNav: Collaborative Cross-Modal Reasoning for Embodied Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conav-collaborative-cross-modal-reasoning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Embodied navigation demands comprehensive scene understanding and precise spatial reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conav-collaborative-cross-modal-reasoning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EquivPruner: Boosting Efficiency and Quality in LLM-Based Search via Action Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivpruner-boosting-efficiency-and-quality-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose EquivPruner, a simple yet effective approach that identifies and prunes semantically equivalent actions during LLM reasoning search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivpruner-boosting-efficiency-and-quality-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINEA: Fast and Accurate Line Detection Using Scalable Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linea-fast-and-accurate-line-detection-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper develops a new transformer-based method that is significantly faster without requiring pretraining the attention mechanism on large datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linea-fast-and-accurate-line-detection-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AppealCase: A Dataset and Benchmark for Civil Case Appeal Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/appealcase-a-dataset-and-benchmark-for-civil</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in LegalAI have primarily focused on individual case judgment analysis, often overlooking the critical appellate process within the judicial system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/appealcase-a-dataset-and-benchmark-for-civil</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forward-only Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forward-only-diffusion-probabilistic-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents a forward-only diffusion (FoD) approach for generative modelling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forward-only-diffusion-probabilistic-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walk&amp;Retrieve: Simple Yet Effective Zero-shot Retrieval-Augmented Generation via Knowledge Graph Walks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/walk-retrieve-simple-yet-effective-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have showcased impressive reasoning abilities, but often suffer from hallucinations or outdated knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/walk-retrieve-simple-yet-effective-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConvSearch-R1: Enhancing Query Reformulation for Conversational Search with Reasoning via Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convsearch-r1-enhancing-query-reformulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational search systems require effective handling of context-dependent queries that often contain ambiguity, omission, and coreference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convsearch-r1-enhancing-query-reformulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are the confidence scores of reviewers consistent with the review content? Evidence from top conference proceedings in AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-the-confidence-scores-of-reviewers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Peer review is vital in academia for evaluating research quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-the-confidence-scores-of-reviewers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructSAM: A Training-Free Framework for Instruction-Oriented Remote Sensing Object Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructsam-a-training-free-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe the contributions of the proposed tasks, benchmark, and effective approach will advance future research in developing versatile object recognition systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructsam-a-training-free-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffProb: Data Pruning for Face Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffprob-data-pruning-for-face-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Face recognition models have made substantial progress due to advances in deep learning and the availability of large-scale datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffprob-data-pruning-for-face-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoding Phone Pairs from MEG Signals Across Speech Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-phone-pairs-from-meg-signals-across</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the neural mechanisms underlying speech production is essential for both advancing cognitive neuroscience theory and developing practical communication technologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-phone-pairs-from-meg-signals-across</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reliable Vertical Federated Learning in 5G Core Network Architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliable-vertical-federated-learning-in-5g</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes a new algorithm to mitigate model generalization loss in Vertical Federated Learning (VFL) operating under client reliability constraints within 5G Core Networks (CNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliable-vertical-federated-learning-in-5g</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keep Security! Benchmarking Security Policy Preservation in Large Language Model Contexts Against Indirect Attacks in Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/keep-security-benchmarking-security-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As Large Language Models (LLMs) are increasingly deployed in sensitive domains such as enterprise and government, ensuring that they adhere to user-defined security policies within context is critical-especially with respect to information non-disclosure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/keep-security-benchmarking-security-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear Convergence of Plug-and-Play Algorithms with Kernel Denoisers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-convergence-of-plug-and-play</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The focus of this work is on the convergence of PnP iterates for linear inverse problems using kernel denoisers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-convergence-of-plug-and-play</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human in the Loop Adaptive Optimization for Improved Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-in-the-loop-adaptive-optimization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series forecasting models often produce systematic, predictable errors even in critical domains such as energy, finance, and healthcare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-in-the-loop-adaptive-optimization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Responsible Diffusion Models via Constraining Text Embeddings within Safe Regions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/responsible-diffusion-models-via-constraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel self-discovery approach to identifying a semantic direction vector in the embedding space to restrict text embedding within a safe region.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/responsible-diffusion-models-via-constraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer of Structural Knowledge from Synthetic Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-of-structural-knowledge-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also introduce a new synthetic language that leads to better transfer to English than the languages used in previous research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-of-structural-knowledge-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alignment Under Pressure: The Case for Informed Adversaries When Evaluating LLM Defenses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignment-under-pressure-the-case-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that, contrary to previous beliefs, effective adversarial suffixes do exist against SOTA alignment-based defenses, that these can be found by existing attack methods when adversaries exploit alignment knowledge, and that even universal suffixes exist.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignment-under-pressure-the-case-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Unit Language Guidance to Advance Speech Modeling in Textless Speech-to-Speech Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-unit-language-guidance-to-advance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the unit language to overcome the two modeling challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-unit-language-guidance-to-advance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Atlas of In-Context Learning: How Attention Heads Shape In-Context Retrieval Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-atlas-of-in-context-learning-how</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models are able to exploit in-context learning to access external knowledge beyond their training data through retrieval-augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-atlas-of-in-context-learning-how</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ThinkRec: Thinking-based recommendation via LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thinkrec-thinking-based-recommendation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, we propose ThinkRec, a thinking-based framework that shifts LLM4Rec from System 1 to System 2 (rational system).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thinkrec-thinking-based-recommendation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Objective Bicycle Occlusion Level Classification using a Deformable Parts-Based Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/objective-bicycle-occlusion-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A novel method of bicycle occlusion level is proposed to objectively quantify the visibility and occlusion level of bicycle semantic parts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/objective-bicycle-occlusion-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPad: Iterative Proposal-centric End-to-End Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ipad-iterative-proposal-centric-end-to-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[End-to-end (E2E) autonomous driving systems offer a promising alternative to traditional modular pipelines by reducing information loss and error accumulation, with significant potential to enhance both mobility and safety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ipad-iterative-proposal-centric-end-to-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Word Level Timestamp Generation for Automatic Speech Recognition and Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/word-level-timestamp-generation-for-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a data-driven approach for enabling word-level timestamp prediction in the Canary model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/word-level-timestamp-generation-for-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: A Benchmark for Testing the Effects of Capture Conditions on Fundamental Vision Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snap-a-benchmark-for-testing-the-effects-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lastly, we conduct an experiment to establish a human baseline for the VQA task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snap-a-benchmark-for-testing-the-effects-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oral Imaging for Malocclusion Issues Assessments: OMNI Dataset, Deep Learning Baselines and Benchmarking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oral-imaging-for-malocclusion-issues</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Malocclusion is a major challenge in orthodontics, and its complex presentation and diverse clinical manifestations make accurate localization and diagnosis particularly important.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oral-imaging-for-malocclusion-issues</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distance Adaptive Beam Search for Provably Accurate Graph-Based Nearest Neighbor Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-adaptive-beam-search-for-provably</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that, as long as the search graph is navigable, our resulting Adaptive Beam Search method is guaranteed to approximately solve the nearest-neighbor problem, establishing a connection between navigability and the performance of graph-based search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-adaptive-beam-search-for-provably</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Explanations with Human Communication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-explanations-with-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these methods generally ignore the communicative context of explanation-the ability of the user to understand the prediction of the model from the explanation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-explanations-with-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soft Thinking: Unlocking the Reasoning Potential of LLMs in Continuous Concept Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soft-thinking-unlocking-the-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Soft Thinking, a training-free method that emulates human-like "soft" reasoning by generating soft, abstract concept tokens in a continuous concept space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soft-thinking-unlocking-the-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn to Reason Efficiently with Adaptive Length-based Reward Shaping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-to-reason-efficiently-with-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Reasoning Models (LRMs) have shown remarkable capabilities in solving complex problems through reinforcement learning (RL), particularly by generating long reasoning traces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-to-reason-efficiently-with-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Ensembling: Insights from Online Optimization and Empirical Bayes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-ensembling-insights-from-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We revisit the classical problem of Bayesian ensembles and address the challenge of learning optimal combinations of Bayesian models in an online, continual learning setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-ensembling-insights-from-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAVA: Hybrid Approach to Value-Alignment through Reward Weighing for Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hava-hybrid-approach-to-value-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many of the norms are written as laws or rules (legal / safety norms) but even more remain unwritten (social norms).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hava-hybrid-approach-to-value-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unreasonable Effectiveness of Entropy Minimization in LLM Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-unreasonable-effectiveness-of-entropy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entropy minimization (EM) trains the model to concentrate even more probability mass on its most confident outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-unreasonable-effectiveness-of-entropy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modular Jump Gaussian Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modular-jump-gaussian-processes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gaussian processes (GPs) furnish accurate nonlinear predictions with well-calibrated uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modular-jump-gaussian-processes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClickSight: Interpreting Student Clickstreams to Reveal Insights on Learning Strategies via LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clicksight-interpreting-student-clickstreams</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ClickSight demonstrates the potential of LLMs to generate theory-driven insights from educational interaction data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clicksight-interpreting-student-clickstreams</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UWSAM: Segment Anything Model Guided Underwater Instance Segmentation and A Large-scale Benchmark Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uwsam-segment-anything-model-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With recent breakthroughs in large-scale modeling, the Segment Anything Model (SAM) has demonstrated significant potential in a variety of visual applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uwsam-segment-anything-model-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laplace Sample Information: Data Informativeness Through a Bayesian Lens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplace-sample-information-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurately estimating the informativeness of individual samples in a dataset is an important objective in deep learning, as it can guide sample selection, which can improve model efficiency and accuracy by removing redundant or potentially harmful samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplace-sample-information-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving Conformal Prediction Under Local Differential Privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-conformal-prediction-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first approach, users do not access the model but instead provide their input features and a perturbed label using a k-ary randomized response.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-conformal-prediction-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Jailbreak: An Open Comprehensive Benchmark for Jailbreaking Large Audio-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-jailbreak-an-open-comprehensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce AJailBench, the first benchmark specifically designed to evaluate jailbreak vulnerabilities in LAMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-jailbreak-an-open-comprehensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring LLM-Generated Feedback for Economics Essays: How Teaching Assistants Evaluate and Envision Its Use</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-llm-generated-feedback-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For a randomly selected set of essays that they had graded, we used our feedback engine to generate feedback and displayed the feedback as in-text comments in a Word document.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-llm-generated-feedback-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Devil is in Fine-tuning and Long-tailed Problems:A New Benchmark for Scene Text Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-is-in-fine-tuning-and-long-tailed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, a \textit{Fine-tuning Gap}, where models leverage \textit{Dataset-Specific Optimization} (DSO) paradigm for one domain at the cost of reduced effectiveness in others, leads to inflated performances on academic benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-is-in-fine-tuning-and-long-tailed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Problem-Solving to Teaching Problem-Solving: Aligning LLMs with Pedagogy using Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-problem-solving-to-teaching-problem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) can transform education, but their optimization for direct question-answering often undermines effective pedagogy which requires strategically withholding answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-problem-solving-to-teaching-problem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stronger ViTs With Octic Equivariance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stronger-vits-with-octic-equivariance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent efforts at scaling computer vision models have established Vision Transformers (ViTs) as the leading architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stronger-vits-with-octic-equivariance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Informed AV Decision-Making: Computational Model of Well-being and Trust in Mobility</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-informed-av-decision-making</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our model captures the well-being of both an AV user and an interacting road user as cognitive states alongside trust.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-informed-av-decision-making</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
