<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:13:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Data-driven Prior Learning for Bayesian Optimisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-prior-learning-for-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We replace this assumption with a weaker one only requiring the shape of the optimisation landscape to be similar, and analyse the recent method Prior Learning for Bayesian Optimisation - PLeBO - in this setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-prior-learning-for-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bursting Spikes: Efficient and High-performance SNNs for Event-based Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bursting-spikes-efficient-and-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advancing event-driven vision through spiking neural networks (SNNs) is crucial to empowering high-speed and efficient perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bursting-spikes-efficient-and-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable and accelerated spherical harmonic and Wigner transforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-and-accelerated-spherical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop novel algorithmic structures for accelerated and differentiable computation of generalised Fourier transforms on the sphere $\mathbb{S}^2$ and rotation group $\text{SO}(3)$, i. e. spherical harmonic and Wigner transforms, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-and-accelerated-spherical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CT-xCOV: a CT-scan based Explainable Framework for COVid-19 diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ct-xcov-a-ct-scan-based-explainable-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lastly, the results of the comparison of XAI techniques show that Grad-Cam gives the best explanations compared to LIME and IG, by achieving a Dice coefficient of 55%, on COVID-19 positive scans, compared to 29% and 24% obtained by IG and LIME respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ct-xcov-a-ct-scan-based-explainable-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmentation-Based Parametric Painting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-based-parametric-painting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel image-to-painting method that facilitates the creation of large-scale, high-fidelity paintings with human-like quality and stylistic variation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-based-parametric-painting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Domain Misinformation Detection via Multi-modal Feature Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-domain-misinformation-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose a framework that simultaneously considers application scenarios of domain generalization (in which the target domain data is unavailable) and domain adaptation (in which unlabeled target domain data is available).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-domain-misinformation-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paragraph-to-Image Generation with Information-Enriched Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paragraph-to-image-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce an information-enriched diffusion model for paragraph-to-image generation task, termed ParaDiffusion, which delves into the transference of the extensive semantic comprehension capabilities of large language models to the task of image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paragraph-to-image-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charting New Territories: Exploring the Geographic and Geospatial Capabilities of Multimodal LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/charting-new-territories-exploring-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal large language models (MLLMs) have shown remarkable capabilities across a broad range of tasks but their knowledge and abilities in the geographic and geospatial domains are yet to be explored, despite potential wide-ranging benefits to navigation, environmental research, urban development, and disaster response.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/charting-new-territories-exploring-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring Latent Class Statistics from Text for Robust Visual Few-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-latent-class-statistics-from-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel approach that leverages text-derived statistics to predict the mean and covariance of the visual feature distribution for each class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-latent-class-statistics-from-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlled Text Generation via Language Model Arithmetic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlled-text-generation-via-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, the framework allows for more precise control of generated text than direct prompting and prior controlled text generation (CTG) techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlled-text-generation-via-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binarized 3D Whole-body Human Mesh Recovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binarized-3d-whole-body-human-mesh-recovery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a Binarized Dual Residual Network (BiDRN), a novel quantization method to estimate the 3D human body, face, and hands parameters efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binarized-3d-whole-body-human-mesh-recovery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRISP: Hybrid Structured Sparsity for Class-aware Model Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crisp-hybrid-structured-sparsity-for-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning pipelines for classification tasks often train a universal model to achieve accuracy across a broad range of classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crisp-hybrid-structured-sparsity-for-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEGIC: Unleashing the Emergent Correspondence for In-Context Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segic-unleashing-the-emergent-correspondence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In-context segmentation aims at segmenting novel images using a few labeled example images, termed as "in-context examples", exploring content similarities between examples and the target.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segic-unleashing-the-emergent-correspondence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Super-Resolution with Text Prompt Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-super-resolution-with-text-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by advancements in multi-modal methods and text prompt image processing, we introduce text prompts to image SR to provide degradation priors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-super-resolution-with-text-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneFormer3D: One Transformer for Unified Point Cloud Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oneformer3d-one-transformer-for-unified-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic, instance, and panoptic segmentation of 3D point clouds have been addressed using task-specific models of distinct design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oneformer3d-one-transformer-for-unified-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetLOV: Enhancing Jet Tree Tagging through Neural Network Learning of Optimal LundNet Variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jetlov-enhancing-jet-tree-tagging-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning has played a pivotal role in advancing physics, with deep learning notably contributing to solving complex classification problems such as jet tagging in the field of jet physics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jetlov-enhancing-jet-tree-tagging-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuromorphic Intermediate Representation: A Unified Instruction Set for Interoperable Brain-Inspired Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuromorphic-intermediate-representation-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite a well-established mathematical foundation for neural dynamics, the implementation details vary greatly across different platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuromorphic-intermediate-representation-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Concept-based Interpretability of Skin Lesion Diagnosis using Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-concept-based-interpretability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concept-based models naturally lend themselves to the development of inherently interpretable skin lesion diagnosis, as medical experts make decisions based on a set of visual patterns of the lesion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-concept-based-interpretability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sliding Window FastEdit: A Framework for Lesion Annotation in Whole-body PET Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliding-window-fastedit-a-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning has revolutionized the accurate segmentation of diseases in medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliding-window-fastedit-a-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Cluster Discrimination for Deep Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-cluster-discrimination-for-deep-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, one-stage methods are developed mainly for representation learning rather than clustering, where various constraints for cluster assignments are designed to avoid collapsing explicitly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-cluster-discrimination-for-deep-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BHGNN-RT: Network embedding for directed heterogeneous graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bhgnn-rt-network-embedding-for-directed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Networks are one of the most valuable data structures for modeling problems in the real world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bhgnn-rt-network-embedding-for-directed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRUITS: Feature Extraction Using Iterated Sums for Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fruits-feature-extraction-using-iterated-sums</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a pipeline for time series classification that extracts features based on the iterated-sums signature (ISS) and then applies a linear classifier.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fruits-feature-extraction-using-iterated-sums</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DP-NMT: Scalable Differentially-Private Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dp-nmt-scalable-differentially-private</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural machine translation (NMT) is a widely popular text generation task, yet there is a considerable research gap in the development of privacy-preserving NMT models, despite significant data privacy concerns for NMT systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dp-nmt-scalable-differentially-private</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLamol: A Dynamic Multi-Conditional Generative Transformer for De Novo Molecular Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llamol-a-dynamic-multi-conditional-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative models have demonstrated substantial promise in Natural Language Processing (NLP) and have found application in designing molecules, as seen in General Pretrained Transformer (GPT) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llamol-a-dynamic-multi-conditional-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Metalearned Neural Circuit for Nonparametric Bayesian Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-metalearned-neural-circuit-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most applications of machine learning to classification assume a closed set of balanced classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-metalearned-neural-circuit-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT Struct Me: Probing GPT Models on Narrative Entity Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-struct-me-probing-gpt-models-on-narrative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By studying the strengths and limitations of these models in the context of information extraction, we offer insights that can guide future improvements and avenues to explore in this field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-struct-me-probing-gpt-models-on-narrative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaTyper: Adaptive Semantic Column Type Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adatyper-adaptive-semantic-column-type</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key source for understanding a table is the semantics of its columns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adatyper-adaptive-semantic-column-type</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Annealing on Graphs for Combinatorial Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-annealing-on-graphs-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several recent unsupervised learning methods use probabilistic approaches to solve combinatorial optimization (CO) problems based on the assumption of statistically independent solution variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-annealing-on-graphs-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Systematic Review of Deep Learning-based Research on Radiology Report Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-review-of-deep-learning-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we firstly cover pivotal RRG approaches based on the task-specific features of radiographs, reports, and the cross-modal relations between them, and then illustrate the benchmark datasets conventionally used for this task with evaluation metrics, subsequently analyze the performance of different approaches and finally offer our summary on the challenges and the trends in future directions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-review-of-deep-learning-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Phrase Debiaser: Debiasing Masked Language Models at a Multi-Token Level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-phrase-debiaser-debiasing-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The social biases and unwelcome stereotypes revealed by pretrained language models are becoming obstacles to their application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-phrase-debiaser-debiasing-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low Latency Instance Segmentation by Continuous Clustering for Rotating LiDAR Sensors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-latency-instance-segmentation-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Obstacle points are clustered to existing instances in real-time and it is checked at a high-frequency which instances are completed and are ready to be published.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-latency-instance-segmentation-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annotation Sensitivity: Training Data Collection Methods Affect Model Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/annotation-sensitivity-training-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the term annotation sensitivity to refer to the impact of annotation data collection methods on the annotations themselves and on downstream model performance and predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/annotation-sensitivity-training-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaFBP: Learning to Learn High-Order Predictor for Personalized Facial Beauty Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metafbp-learning-to-learn-high-order</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a novel MetaFBP framework, in which we devise a universal feature extractor to capture the aesthetic commonality and then optimize to adapt the aesthetic individuality by shifting the decision boundary of the predictor via a meta-learning mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metafbp-learning-to-learn-high-order</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Dynamic Selection and Pricing of Out-of-Home Deliveries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-dynamic-selection-and-pricing-of-out</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We model the sequential decision-making problem of which OOH location to offer against what incentive for each incoming customer, taking into account future customer arrivals and choices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-dynamic-selection-and-pricing-of-out</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jam-ALT: A Formatting-Aware Lyrics Transcription Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jam-alt-a-formatting-aware-lyrics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current automatic lyrics transcription (ALT) benchmarks focus exclusively on word content and ignore the finer nuances of written lyrics including formatting and punctuation, which leads to a potential misalignment with the creative products of musicians and songwriters as well as listeners' experiences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jam-alt-a-formatting-aware-lyrics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPSUR: Accelerating Differentially Private Stochastic Gradient Descent Using Selective Update and Release</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpsur-accelerating-differentially-private</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, this paper proposes DPSUR, a Differentially Private training framework based on Selective Updates and Release, where the gradient from each iteration is evaluated based on a validation test, and only those updates leading to convergence are applied to the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpsur-accelerating-differentially-private</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RankFeat\&amp;RankWeight: Rank-1 Feature/Weight Removal for Out-of-distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankfeat-rankweight-rank-1-feature-weight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This observation motivates us to propose \texttt{RankFeat}, a simple yet effective \emph{post hoc} approach for OOD detection by removing the rank-1 matrix composed of the largest singular value and the associated singular vectors from the high-level feature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankfeat-rankweight-rank-1-feature-weight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating GPT-4's Vision Capabilities on Brazilian University Admission Exams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-gpt-4-s-vision-capabilities-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in language models have showcased human-comparable performance in academic entrance exams.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-gpt-4-s-vision-capabilities-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EIGEN: Expert-Informed Joint Learning Aggregation for High-Fidelity Information Extraction from Document Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigen-expert-informed-joint-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We empirically show that our EIGEN framework can significantly improve the performance of state-of-the-art deep models with the availability of very few labeled data instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigen-expert-informed-joint-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and Robust Jet Tagging at the LHC with Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-robust-jet-tagging-at-the-lhc</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The challenging environment of real-time data processing systems at the Large Hadron Collider (LHC) strictly limits the computational complexity of algorithms that can be deployed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-robust-jet-tagging-at-the-lhc</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HGCLIP: Exploring Vision-Language Models with Graph Representations for Hierarchical Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgclip-exploring-vision-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore constructing the class hierarchy into a graph, with its nodes representing the textual or image features of each category.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgclip-exploring-vision-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dialogue Quality and Emotion Annotations for Customer Support Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialogue-quality-and-emotion-annotations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Task-oriented conversational datasets often lack topic variability and linguistic diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialogue-quality-and-emotion-annotations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient-based bilevel optimization for multi-penalty Ridge regression through matrix differential calculus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-based-bilevel-optimization-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Common regularization algorithms for linear regression, such as LASSO and Ridge regression, rely on a regularization hyperparameter that balances the tradeoff between minimizing the fitting error and the norm of the learned model coefficients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-based-bilevel-optimization-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating and Benchmarking a Synthetic Dataset for Cloud Optical Thickness Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creating-and-benchmarking-a-synthetic-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate the COT data scarcity problem, in this work we propose a novel synthetic dataset for COT estimation, where top-of-atmosphere radiances have been simulated for 12 of the spectral bands of the Multi-Spectral Instrument (MSI) sensor onboard Sentinel-2 platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creating-and-benchmarking-a-synthetic-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the use of publicly available natural videos to learn Dynamic MR image reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-use-of-publicly-available</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Purpose: To develop and assess a deep learning (DL) pipeline to learn dynamic MR image reconstruction from publicly available natural videos (Inter4K).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-use-of-publicly-available</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning of Diffusion Models with Generative Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-of-diffusion-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that our approach significantly improves the continual learning performance of generative replay with only a moderate increase in the computational costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-of-diffusion-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HGCLIP: Exploring Vision-Language Models with Graph Representations for Hierarchical Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgclip-exploring-vision-language-models-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore constructing the class hierarchy into a graph, with its nodes representing the textual or image features of each category.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgclip-exploring-vision-language-models-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter Exchange for Robust Dynamic Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-exchange-for-robust-dynamic-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The parameters of dynamic networks can be decoupled into a static and a dynamic component, which are designed to learn domain-invariant and domain-specific features, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-exchange-for-robust-dynamic-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting the Power of Small Multimodal Reasoning Models to Match Larger Models with Self-Consistency Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-the-power-of-small-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remarkably, we show that even smaller base models, when equipped with our proposed approach, can achieve results comparable to those of larger models, illustrating the potential of our approach in harnessing the power of rationales for improved multimodal reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-the-power-of-small-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Compositional Graph Convolutional Network for Efficient Composite Human Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-compositional-graph-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With potential applications in fields including intelligent surveillance and human-robot interaction, the human motion prediction task has become a hot research topic and also has achieved high success, especially using the recent Graph Convolutional Network (GCN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-compositional-graph-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
