<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 09:11:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>AnthroNet: Conditional Generation of Humans via Anthropometrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anthronet-conditional-generation-of-humans-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel human body model formulated by an extensive set of anthropocentric measurements, which is capable of generating a wide range of human body shapes and poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anthronet-conditional-generation-of-humans-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnthroNet: Conditional Generation of Humans via Anthropometrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anthronet-conditional-generation-of-humans</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel human body model formulated by an extensive set of anthropocentric measurements, which is capable of generating a wide range of human body shapes and poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anthronet-conditional-generation-of-humans</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-Aware 3D Object Localization from Single Calibrated Images: A Study of Basketballs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-3d-object-localization-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurately localizing objects in three dimensions (3D) is crucial for various computer vision applications, such as robotics, autonomous driving, and augmented reality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-3d-object-localization-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ResFields: Residual Neural Fields for Spatiotemporal Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resfields-residual-neural-fields-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural fields, a category of neural networks trained to represent high-frequency signals, have gained significant attention in recent years due to their impressive performance in modeling complex 3D data, especially large neural signed distance (SDFs) or radiance fields (NeRFs) via a single multi-layer perceptron (MLP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resfields-residual-neural-fields-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulating room transfer functions between transducers mounted on audio devices using a modified image source method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-room-transfer-functions-between</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The image source method (ISM) is often used to simulate room acoustics due to its ease of use and computational efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-room-transfer-functions-between</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-preserving Continual Federated Clustering via Adaptive Resonance Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-continual-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the clustering domain, various algorithms with a federated learning framework (i. e., federated clustering) have been actively studied and showed high clustering performance while preserving data privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-continual-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Recharge: UAV Coverage Path Planning through Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-recharge-uav-coverage-path</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Coverage path planning (CPP) is a critical problem in robotics, where the goal is to find an efficient path that covers every point in an area of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-recharge-uav-coverage-path</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-InvestAR: Enhancing Stock Investment Strategies through Annual Report Analysis with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-investar-enhancing-stock-investment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper aims to simplify the process of assessing Annual Reports of all the firms by leveraging the capabilities of Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-investar-enhancing-stock-investment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Large Language Models for Clinical Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-language-models-for-clinical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable adaptability, showcasing their capacity to excel in tasks for which they were not explicitly trained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-language-models-for-clinical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ResFields: Residual Neural Fields for Spatiotemporal Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resfields-residual-neural-fields-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural fields, a category of neural networks trained to represent high-frequency signals, have gained significant attention in recent years due to their impressive performance in modeling complex 3D data, especially large neural signed distance (SDFs) or radiance fields (NeRFs) via a single multi-layer perceptron (MLP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resfields-residual-neural-fields-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symmetric-Reciprocal-Match Method for Vector Network Analyzer Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetric-reciprocal-match-method-for-vector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The method involves using multiple symmetric one-port loads, a two-port reciprocal device, and a matched load.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetric-reciprocal-match-method-for-vector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeisCLIP: A seismology foundation model pre-trained by multi-modal data for multi-purpose seismic feature extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seisclip-a-seismology-foundation-model-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training specific deep learning models for particular tasks is common across various domains within seismology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seisclip-a-seismology-foundation-model-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anatomy-Driven Pathology Detection on Chest X-rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomy-driven-pathology-detection-on-chest-x</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pathology detection and delineation enables the automatic interpretation of medical scans such as chest X-rays while providing a high level of explainability to support radiologists in making informed decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomy-driven-pathology-detection-on-chest-x</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lightweight, Rapid and Efficient Deep Convolutional Network for Chest X-Ray Tuberculosis Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-rapid-and-efficient-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose LightTBNet, a novel lightweight, fast and efficient deep convolutional network specially customized to detect TB from CXR images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-rapid-and-efficient-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Aggregation for Hierarchical Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-aggregation-for-hierarchical-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hierarchical Agglomerative Clustering (HAC) is likely the earliest and most flexible clustering method, because it can be used with many distances, similarities, and various linkage strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-aggregation-for-hierarchical-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SyntheWorld: A Large-Scale Synthetic Dataset for Land Cover Mapping and Building Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syntheworld-a-large-scale-synthetic-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, when it comes to remote sensing image processing, the creation of synthetic datasets becomes challenging due to the demand for larger-scale and more diverse 3D models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syntheworld-a-large-scale-synthetic-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting File Context for Source Code Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-file-context-for-source-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Source code summarization is the task of writing natural language descriptions of source code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-file-context-for-source-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doppelgangers: Learning to Disambiguate Images of Similar Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doppelgangers-learning-to-disambiguate-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our evaluation shows that our method can distinguish illusory matches in difficult cases, and can be integrated into SfM pipelines to produce correct, disambiguated 3D reconstructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doppelgangers-learning-to-disambiguate-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cognitive Architectures for Language Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cognitive-architectures-for-language-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent efforts have incorporated large language models (LLMs) with external resources (e. g., the Internet) or internal control flows (e. g., prompt chaining) for tasks requiring grounding or reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cognitive-architectures-for-language-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReliTalk: Relightable Talking Portrait Generation from a Single Video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relitalk-relightable-talking-portrait</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our key insight is to decompose the portrait's reflectance from implicitly learned audio-driven facial normals and images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relitalk-relightable-talking-portrait</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robustness and Generalizability of Deepfake Detection: A Study with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-and-generalizability-of-deepfake</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise of deepfake images, especially of well-known personalities, poses a serious threat to the dissemination of authentic information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-and-generalizability-of-deepfake</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Adversarial Implications of Variable-Time Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-adversarial-implications-of-variable-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our examination of the timing side-channel vulnerabilities associated with this algorithm, we identified the potential to enhance decision-based attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-adversarial-implications-of-variable-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensorization: Creating and Utilising Multidimensional Datasets for Multiway Analysis and Tensorised Deep Neural Networks -- Python Tutorial and Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensorization-creating-and-utilising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the size and complexity of data continue to increase, the need for efficient and effective analysis methods becomes ever more crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensorization-creating-and-utilising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superclustering by finding statistically significant separable groups of optimal gaussian clusters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superclustering-by-finding-statistically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper presents the algorithm for clustering a dataset by grouping the optimal, from the point of view of the BIC criterion, number of Gaussian clusters into the optimal, from the point of view of their statistical separability, superclusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superclustering-by-finding-statistically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INCEPTNET: Precise And Early Disease Detection Application For Medical Images Analyses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inceptnet-precise-and-early-disease-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a novel deep neural network (DNN), entitled InceptNet, in the scope of medical image processing, for early disease detection and segmentation of medical images in order to enhance precision and performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inceptnet-precise-and-early-disease-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniSA: Unified Generative Framework for Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unisa-unified-generative-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sentiment analysis is a crucial task that aims to understand people’s emotional states and predict emotional categories based on multimodal information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unisa-unified-generative-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniSA: Unified Generative Framework for Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unisa-unified-generative-framework-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sentiment analysis is a crucial task that aims to understand people's emotional states and predict emotional categories based on multimodal information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unisa-unified-generative-framework-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAT++: Spatially Dynamic Vision Transformer with Deformable Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dat-spatially-dynamic-vision-transformer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the one hand, using dense attention in ViT leads to excessive memory and computational cost, and features can be influenced by irrelevant parts that are beyond the region of interests.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dat-spatially-dynamic-vision-transformer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSTTC: A Large-Scale Dataset for Time-to-Contact Estimation in Driving Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsttc-a-large-scale-dataset-for-time-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time-to-Contact (TTC) estimation is a critical task for assessing collision risk and is widely used in various driver assistance and autonomous driving systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsttc-a-large-scale-dataset-for-time-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relay Diffusion: Unifying diffusion process across resolutions for image synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relay-diffusion-unifying-diffusion-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models achieved great success in image synthesis, but still face challenges in high-resolution generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relay-diffusion-unifying-diffusion-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are We Using Autoencoders in a Wrong Way?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-we-using-autoencoders-in-a-wrong-way</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoencoders are certainly among the most studied and used Deep Learning models: the idea behind them is to train a model in order to reconstruct the same input data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-we-using-autoencoders-in-a-wrong-way</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classic algorithms are fair learners: Classification Analysis of natural weather and wildfire occurrences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classic-algorithms-are-fair-learners</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Classic machine learning algorithms have been reviewed and studied mathematically on its performance and properties in detail.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classic-algorithms-are-fair-learners</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeViL: Decoding Vision features into Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/devil-decoding-vision-features-into-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that DeViL generates textual descriptions relevant to the image content on CC3M surpassing previous lightweight captioning models and attribution maps uncovering the learned concepts of the vision backbone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/devil-decoding-vision-features-into-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMEDIAN: Self-Supervised Learning and Knowledge Distillation for Action Spotting using Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comedian-self-supervised-learning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present COMEDIAN, a novel pipeline to initialize spatio-temporal transformers for action spotting, which involves self-supervised learning and knowledge distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comedian-self-supervised-learning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few shot font generation via transferring similarity guided global style and quantization local style</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-font-generation-via-transferring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better capture the local styles, a cross-attention-based style transfer module is adopted to transfer the styles of reference glyphs to the components, where the components are self-learned discrete latent codes through vector quantization without manual definition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-font-generation-via-transferring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLSP: Bootstrapping Language-Speech Pre-training via Behavior Alignment of Continuation Writing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blsp-bootstrapping-language-speech-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One is a cascaded approach where outputs (tokens or states) of a separately trained speech recognition system are used as inputs for LLMs, which limits their potential in modeling alignment between speech and text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blsp-bootstrapping-language-speech-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLSP: Bootstrapping Language-Speech Pre-training via Behavior Alignment of Continuation Writing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blsp-bootstrapping-language-speech-pre-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One is a cascaded approach where outputs (tokens or states) of a separately trained speech recognition system are used as inputs for LLMs, which limits their potential in modeling alignment between speech and text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blsp-bootstrapping-language-speech-pre-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RevColV2: Exploring Disentangled Representations in Masked Image Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revcolv2-exploring-disentangled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such design enables our architecture with the nice property: maintaining disentangled low-level and semantic information at the end of the network in MIM pre-training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revcolv2-exploring-disentangled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ObjectLab: Automated Diagnosis of Mislabeled Images in Object Detection Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/objectlab-automated-diagnosis-of-mislabeled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite powering sensitive systems like autonomous vehicles, object detection remains fairly brittle in part due to annotation errors that plague most real-world training datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/objectlab-automated-diagnosis-of-mislabeled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Recommendations with Pre-Trained Large Language Models for Multimodal Nudging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-recommendations-with-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a method for zero-shot recommendation of multimodal non-stationary content that leverages recent advancements in the field of generative AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-recommendations-with-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastPoseGait: A Toolbox and Benchmark for Efficient Pose-based Gait Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastposegait-a-toolbox-and-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our toolbox supports a set of cutting-edge pose-based gait recognition algorithms and a variety of related benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastposegait-a-toolbox-and-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial: a priori estimation of sample size, effect size, and statistical power for cluster analysis, latent class analysis, and multivariate mixture models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tutorial-a-priori-estimation-of-sample-size</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The table shows the minimum numbers of observations per expected subgroup (sample size) and features (measured variables) to achieve acceptable statistical power, and can be readily used in study design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tutorial-a-priori-estimation-of-sample-size</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTU4DRadLM: 4D Radar-centric Multi-Modal Dataset for Localization and Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntu4dradlm-4d-radar-centric-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[5) Considered both middle-and large-scale outdoor environments , i. e., the 6 trajectories range from 246m to 6. 95km.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntu4dradlm-4d-radar-centric-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretation of High-Dimensional Linear Regression: Effects of Nullspace and Regularization Demonstrated on Battery Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretation-of-high-dimensional-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We developed an optimization formulation to compare regression coefficients and coefficients obtained by physical engineering knowledge to understand which part of the coefficient differences are close to the nullspace.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretation-of-high-dimensional-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-Bind &amp; Point-LLM: Aligning Point Cloud with Multi-modality for 3D Understanding, Generation, and Instruction Following</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-bind-point-llm-aligning-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Point-Bind, a 3D multi-modality model aligning point clouds with 2D image, language, audio, and video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-bind-point-llm-aligning-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SparseSat-NeRF: Dense Depth Supervised Neural Radiance Fields for Sparse Satellite Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsesat-nerf-dense-depth-supervised-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, NeRF and its variants require many views to produce convincing scene's geometries which in earth observation satellite imaging is rare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsesat-nerf-dense-depth-supervised-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Theoretical and Practical Framework for Evaluating Uncertainty Calibration in Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-theoretical-and-practical-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proliferation of Deep Neural Networks has resulted in machine learning systems becoming increasingly more present in various real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-theoretical-and-practical-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Text-based Approach For Link Prediction on Wikipedia Articles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-text-based-approach-for-link-prediction-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper present our work in the DSAA 2023 Challenge about Link Prediction for Wikipedia Articles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-text-based-approach-for-link-prediction-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let the Models Respond: Interpreting Language Model Detoxification Through the Lens of Prompt Dependence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-the-models-respond-interpreting-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to language models' propensity to generate toxic or hateful responses, several techniques were developed to align model generations with users' preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-the-models-respond-interpreting-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patent image retrieval using transformer-based deep metric learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patent-image-retrieval-using-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intellectual property work covers a wide range of areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patent-image-retrieval-using-transformer</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
