<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:10:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the potential of channel interactions for image restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-potential-of-channel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image restoration aims to reconstruct a clear image from a degraded observation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-potential-of-channel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PICNN: A Pathway towards Interpretable Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/picnn-a-pathway-towards-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results have demonstrated that our method PICNN (the combination of standard CNNs with our proposed pathway) exhibits greater interpretability than standard CNNs while achieving higher or comparable discrimination power.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/picnn-a-pathway-towards-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing Guiding Principles for NLP for Healthcare: A Case Study of Maternal Health</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designing-guiding-principles-for-nlp-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conclusion: This set of principles can serve as a resource to practitioners working on maternal health and other healthcare fields to emphasize the importance of technical nuance, historical context, and inclusive design when developing LLMs for use in clinical settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designing-guiding-principles-for-nlp-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brush Your Text: Synthesize Any Scene Text on Images via Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brush-your-text-synthesize-any-scene-text-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, we propose Diff-Text, which is a training-free scene text generation framework for any language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brush-your-text-synthesize-any-scene-text-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical and Incremental Structural Entropy Minimization for Unsupervised Social Event Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-and-incremental-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a trending approach for social event detection, graph neural network (GNN)-based methods enable a fusion of natural language semantics and the complex social network structural information, thus showing SOTA performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-and-incremental-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-DINOiser: Teaching CLIP a few DINO tricks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-dinoiser-teaching-clip-a-few-dino-tricks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose to locally improve dense MaskCLIP features, computed with a simple modification of CLIP's last pooling layer, by integrating localization priors extracted from self-supervised features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-dinoiser-teaching-clip-a-few-dino-tricks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Inference Stability for Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-inference-stability-for-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To minimize that gap, we propose a novel \textit{sequence-aware} loss that aims to reduce the estimation gap to enhance the sampling quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-inference-stability-for-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Dual-Level Graph Self-Supervised Pretraining with Motif Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-dual-level-graph-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While self-supervised graph pretraining techniques have shown promising results in various domains, their application still experiences challenges of limited topology learning, human knowledge dependency, and incompetent multi-level interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-dual-level-graph-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fluctuation-based Adaptive Structured Pruning for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fluctuation-based-adaptive-structured-pruning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retraining-free is important for LLMs' pruning methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fluctuation-based-adaptive-structured-pruning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roll With the Punches: Expansion and Shrinkage of Soft Label Selection for Semi-supervised Fine-Grained Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roll-with-the-punches-expansion-and-shrinkage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While semi-supervised learning (SSL) has yielded promising results, the more realistic SSL scenario remains to be explored, in which the unlabeled data exhibits extremely high recognition difficulty, e. g., fine-grained visual classification in the context of SSL (SS-FGVC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roll-with-the-punches-expansion-and-shrinkage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Arm Identification with Fixed Budget: A Large Deviation Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/best-arm-identification-with-fixed-budget-a-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we present \sred (Continuous Rejects), a truly adaptive algorithm that can reject arms in {\it any} round based on the observed empirical gaps between the rewards of various arms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/best-arm-identification-with-fixed-budget-a-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDD-UNet: Domain Adaptation for Medical Image Segmentation with Theoretical Guarantees, a Proof of Concept</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdd-unet-domain-adaptation-for-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The current state-of-the art techniques for image segmentation are often based on U-Net architectures, a U-shaped encoder-decoder networks with skip connections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdd-unet-domain-adaptation-for-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Frequency-Aware Network for Laparoscopic Image Desmoking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-frequency-aware-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Laparoscopic surgery offers minimally invasive procedures with better patient outcomes, but smoke presence challenges visibility and safety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-frequency-aware-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial AutoMixup</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-automixup</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose AdAutomixup, an adversarial automatic mixup augmentation approach that generates challenging samples to train a robust classifier for image classification, by alternatively optimizing the classifier and the mixup sample generator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-automixup</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MossFormer2: Combining Transformer and RNN-Free Recurrent Network for Enhanced Time-Domain Monaural Speech Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mossformer2-combining-transformer-and-rnn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of applying the recurrent neural networks (RNNs) that use traditional recurrent connections, we present a recurrent module based on a feedforward sequential memory network (FSMN), which is considered "RNN-free" recurrent network due to the ability to capture recurrent patterns without using recurrent connections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mossformer2-combining-transformer-and-rnn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftCTM: Cell detection by soft instance segmentation and consideration of cell-tissue interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softctm-cell-detection-by-soft-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that a "soft", probability-map instance segmentation ground truth leads to best model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softctm-cell-detection-by-soft-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urban Generative Intelligence (UGI): A Foundational Platform for Agents in Embodied City Environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/urban-generative-intelligence-ugi-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Urban environments, characterized by their complex, multi-layered networks encompassing physical, social, economic, and environmental dimensions, face significant challenges in the face of rapid urbanization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/urban-generative-intelligence-ugi-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Detection of Perfect and Partial Input-Dependent Symmetries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-detection-of-perfect-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Group equivariance ensures consistent responses to group transformations of the input, leading to more robust models and enhanced generalization capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-detection-of-perfect-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedDiv: Collaborative Noise Filtering for Federated Learning with Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddiv-collaborative-noise-filtering-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these prior methods do not learn noise filters by exploiting knowledge across all clients, leading to sub-optimal and inferior noise filtering performance and thus damaging training stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddiv-collaborative-noise-filtering-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Prototypes: Semantic Anchor Regularization for Better Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-prototypes-semantic-anchor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By pulling the learned features to these semantic anchors, several advantages can be attained: 1) the intra-class compactness and naturally inter-class separability, 2) induced bias or errors from feature learning can be avoided, and 3) robustness to the long-tailed problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-prototypes-semantic-anchor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Learning Expectation Maximization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/big-learning-expectation-maximization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mixture models serve as one fundamental tool with versatile applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/big-learning-expectation-maximization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse is Enough in Fine-tuning Pre-trained Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-is-enough-in-fine-tuning-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the prevalence of pre-training-fine-tuning paradigm, how to efficiently adapt the pre-trained model to the downstream tasks has been an intriguing issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-is-enough-in-fine-tuning-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FontDiffuser: One-Shot Font Generation via Denoising Diffusion with Multi-Scale Content Aggregation and Style Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fontdiffuser-one-shot-font-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic font generation is an imitation task, which aims to create a font library that mimics the style of reference images while preserving the content from source images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fontdiffuser-one-shot-font-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VITA: 'Carefully Chosen and Weighted Less' Is Better in Medication Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vita-carefully-chosen-and-weighted-less-is</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While there exist a number of recommender systems designed for this problem, we point out that they are challenged in accurately capturing the relation (spec., the degree of relevance) between the current and each of the past visits for the patient when obtaining her current health status, which is the basis for recommending medications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vita-carefully-chosen-and-weighted-less-is</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synergistic Anchored Contrastive Pre-training for Few-Shot Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synergistic-anchored-contrastive-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our framework involves a symmetrical contrastive objective that encompasses both sentence-anchored and label-anchored contrastive losses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synergistic-anchored-contrastive-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exact ASP Counting with Compact Encodings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-asp-counting-with-compact-encodings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, there has been growing interest in problems beyond satisfiability, such as model counting, in the context of ASP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-asp-counting-with-compact-encodings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I-CEE: Tailoring Explanations of Image Classifications Models to User Expertise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-cee-tailoring-explanations-of-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Informed by existing work, I-CEE explains the decisions of image classification models by providing the user with an informative subset of training data (i. e., example images), corresponding local explanations, and model decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-cee-tailoring-explanations-of-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Balanced Alignment: Modal-Enhanced Semantic Modeling for Video Moment Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-balanced-alignment-modal-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Modal-Enhanced Semantic Modeling (MESM), a novel framework for more balanced alignment through enhancing features at two levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-balanced-alignment-modal-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expressive Forecasting of 3D Whole-body Human Motions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressive-forecasting-of-3d-whole-body-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human motion forecasting, with the goal of estimating future human behavior over a period of time, is a fundamental task in many real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressive-forecasting-of-3d-whole-body-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COOPER: Coordinating Specialized Agents towards a Complex Dialogue Goal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooper-coordinating-specialized-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, there has been a growing interest in exploring dialogues with more complex goals, such as negotiation, persuasion, and emotional support, which go beyond traditional service-focused dialogue systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooper-coordinating-specialized-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SegRefiner: Towards Model-Agnostic Segmentation Refinement with Discrete Diffusion Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segrefiner-towards-model-agnostic-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a model-agnostic solution called SegRefiner, which offers a novel perspective on this problem by interpreting segmentation refinement as a data generation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segrefiner-towards-model-agnostic-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MELO: Enhancing Model Editing with Neuron-Indexed Dynamic LoRA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melo-enhancing-model-editing-with-neuron</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown great success in various Natural Language Processing (NLP) tasks, whist they still need updates after deployment to fix errors or keep pace with the changing knowledge in the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melo-enhancing-model-editing-with-neuron</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bypassing the Safety Training of Open-Source LLMs with Priming Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bypassing-the-safety-training-of-open-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the recent surge in popularity of LLMs has come an ever-increasing need for LLM safety training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bypassing-the-safety-training-of-open-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Fairness in Graphs: A GNN Architecture Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chasing-fairness-in-graphs-a-gnn-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we aim to achieve fairness via a new GNN architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chasing-fairness-in-graphs-a-gnn-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relation-Aware Question Answering for Heterogeneous Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relation-aware-question-answering-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we construct a \textbf{dual relation graph} where each node denotes a relation in the original KG (\textbf{primal entity graph}) and edges are constructed between relations sharing same head or tail entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relation-aware-question-answering-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avoiding Data Contamination in Language Model Evaluation: Dynamic Test Construction with Latest Materials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avoiding-data-contamination-in-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data contamination in evaluation is getting increasingly prevalent with the emerge of language models pre-trained on super large, automatically-crawled corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avoiding-data-contamination-in-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulating Intermediate 3D Features for Vision-Centric Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regulating-intermediate-3d-features-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To resolve this problem, we propose to regulate intermediate dense 3D features with the help of volume rendering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regulating-intermediate-3d-features-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models Play StarCraft II: Benchmarks and A Chain of Summarization Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-play-starcraft-ii</link>
      <description><![CDATA[StarCraft II is a challenging benchmark for AI agents due to the necessity of both precise micro level operations and strategic macro awareness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-play-starcraft-ii</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XLand-MiniGrid: Scalable Meta-Reinforcement Learning Environments in JAX</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xland-minigrid-scalable-meta-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present XLand-MiniGrid, a suite of tools and grid-world environments for meta-reinforcement learning research inspired by the diversity and depth of XLand and the simplicity and minimalism of MiniGrid.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xland-minigrid-scalable-meta-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M-BEV: Masked BEV Perception for Robust Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-bev-masked-bev-perception-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It mimics various missing cases by randomly masking features of different camera views, then leverages the original features of these views as self-supervision, and reconstructs the masked ones with the distinct spatio-temporal context across views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-bev-masked-bev-perception-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Graph Error Detection with Contrastive Confidence Adaption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graph-error-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge graphs (KGs) often contain various errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graph-error-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object-Aware Domain Generalization for Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-aware-domain-generalization-for-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these problems, we propose an object-aware domain generalization (OA-DG) method for single-domain generalization in object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-aware-domain-generalization-for-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Model Meets New Normals: Test-time Adaptation for Unsupervised Time-series Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-model-meets-new-normals-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time-series anomaly detection deals with the problem of detecting anomalous timesteps by learning normality from the sequence of observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-model-meets-new-normals-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LHManip: A Dataset for Long-Horizon Language-Grounded Manipulation Tasks in Cluttered Tabletop Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lhmanip-a-dataset-for-long-horizon-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instructing a robot to complete an everyday task within our homes has been a long-standing challenge for robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lhmanip-a-dataset-for-long-horizon-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dual-way Enhanced Framework from Text Matching Point of View for Multimodal Entity Linking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dual-way-enhanced-framework-from-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal Entity Linking (MEL) aims at linking ambiguous mentions with multimodal information to entity in Knowledge Graph (KG) such as Wikipedia, which plays a key role in many applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dual-way-enhanced-framework-from-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shapley-PC: Constraint-based Causal Structure Learning with Shapley Values</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapley-pc-constraint-based-causal-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal Structure Learning (CSL), amounting to extracting causal relations among the variables in a dataset, is widely perceived as an important step towards robust and transparent models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapley-pc-constraint-based-causal-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eliciting Kemeny Rankings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eliciting-kemeny-rankings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, if all agents' preferences are strict rankings over the alternatives, we provide means to prune confidence intervals and thereby guide a more efficient elicitation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eliciting-kemeny-rankings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent-based Learning of Materials Datasets from Scientific Literature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-based-learning-of-materials-datasets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach simplifies compilation of machine learning-ready datasets for various materials discovery applications, and significantly ease the accessibility of advanced natural language processing tools for novice users in natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-based-learning-of-materials-datasets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poker Hand History File Format Specification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poker-hand-history-file-format-specification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the Poker Hand History (PHH) file format, designed to standardize the recording of poker hands across different game variants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poker-hand-history-file-format-specification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Financial Literacy via Semi-supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-financial-literacy-via-semi-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the SMOGN-COREG model for semi-supervised regression, applying SMOGN to deal with unbalanced datasets and a nonparametric multi-learner co-regression (COREG) algorithm for labeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-financial-literacy-via-semi-1</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
