<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 09:12:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Video Super-Resolution via Implicit Resampling-based Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-video-super-resolution-via-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that bilinear interpolation inherently attenuates high-frequency information while an MLP-based coordinate network can approximate more frequencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-video-super-resolution-via-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Self-training Framework for Fine-grained Scene Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-self-training-framework-for-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce a Self-Training framework for SGG (ST-SGG) that assigns pseudo-labels for unannotated triplets based on which the SGG models are trained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-self-training-framework-for-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divide and not forget: Ensemble of selectively trained experts in Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divide-and-not-forget-ensemble-of-selectively</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Class-incremental learning is becoming more popular as it helps models widen their applicability while not forgetting what they already know.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divide-and-not-forget-ensemble-of-selectively</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Learning from Graphs with Heterophily: Progress and Future</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-learning-from-graphs-with-heterophily</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graphs are structured data that models complex relations between real-world entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-learning-from-graphs-with-heterophily</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Neural Code Completion Models Size up the Situation: Attaining Cheaper and Faster Completion through Dynamic Model Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-neural-code-completion-models-size-up</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These findings motivate our exploration of dynamic inference in code completion and inspire us to enhance it with a decision-making mechanism that stops the generation of incorrect code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-neural-code-completion-models-size-up</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Image-Text Matching with Adaptive Feature Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-image-text-matching-with-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image-text matching aims to find matched cross-modal pairs accurately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-image-text-matching-with-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparative Study on the Performance of Categorical Variable Encoders in Classification and Regression Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-study-on-the-performance-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study broadly classifies machine learning models into three categories: 1) ATI models that implicitly perform affine transformations on inputs, such as multi-layer perceptron neural network; 2) Tree-based models that are based on decision trees, such as random forest; and 3) the rest, such as kNN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-study-on-the-performance-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Automated Quality Assessment Network for Interactive Building Segmentation in High-Resolution Remote Sensing Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-automated-quality-assessment-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this research, we introduce the enhanced automated quality assessment network (IBS-AQSNet), an innovative solution for assessing the quality of interactive building segmentation within high-resolution remote sensing imagery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-automated-quality-assessment-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sub2Full: split spectrum to boost OCT despeckling without clean data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sub2full-split-spectrum-to-boost-oct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optical coherence tomography (OCT) suffers from speckle noise, causing the deterioration of image quality, especially in high-resolution modalities like visible light OCT (vis-OCT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sub2full-split-spectrum-to-boost-oct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep spatial context: when attention-based models meet spatial regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-spatial-context-when-attention-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The DSCon allows for a quantitative measure of the spatial context's role using three Spatial Context Measures: $SCM_{features}$, $SCM_{targets}$, $SCM_{residuals}$ to distinguish whether the spatial context is observable within the features of neighboring regions, their target values (attention scores) or residuals, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-spatial-context-when-attention-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Reasoning with Probabilistic Graphical Models for Analyzing Socioecological Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-reasoning-with-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal and counterfactual reasoning are emerging directions in data science that allow us to reason about hypothetical scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-reasoning-with-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R-Judge: Benchmarking Safety Risk Awareness for LLM Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-judge-benchmarking-safety-risk-awareness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce R-Judge, a benchmark crafted to evaluate the proficiency of LLMs in judging safety risks given agent interaction records.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-judge-benchmarking-safety-risk-awareness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Viral Rumors and Vulnerable Users for Infodemic Surveillance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-viral-rumors-and-vulnerable-users</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel approach to predict viral rumors and vulnerable users using a unified graph neural network model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-viral-rumors-and-vulnerable-users</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chem-FINESE: Validating Fine-Grained Few-shot Entity Extraction through Text Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chem-finese-validating-fine-grained-few-shot-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-grained few-shot entity extraction in the chemical domain faces two unique challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chem-finese-validating-fine-grained-few-shot-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EfficientRec an unlimited user-item scale recommendation system based on clustering and users interaction embedding profile</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficientrec-an-unlimited-user-item-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The businesses are constantly growing users and products, causing the number of users and items to continuously increase over time, to very large numbers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficientrec-an-unlimited-user-item-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Prompting Elicits Conditional Reasoning Abilities in Text+Code LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/code-prompting-elicits-conditional-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a chain of prompts that transforms a natural language problem into code and prompts the LLM with the generated code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/code-prompting-elicits-conditional-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMG-Seg: Is One Model Good Enough For All Segmentation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omg-seg-is-one-model-good-enough-for-all</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address various segmentation tasks, each traditionally tackled by distinct or partially unified models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omg-seg-is-one-model-good-enough-for-all</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance Brownian Bridge as Texts for Open-vocabulary Video Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-brownian-bridge-as-texts-for-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mold instance queries to follow Brownian bridge and accomplish alignment with class texts, we design Bridge-Text Alignment (BTA) to learn discriminative bridge-level representations of instances via contrastive objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-brownian-bridge-as-texts-for-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Source Code Clone Detection Using Unsupervised Similarity Measures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/source-code-clone-detection-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assessing similarity in source code has gained significant attention in recent years due to its importance in software engineering tasks such as clone detection and code search and recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/source-code-clone-detection-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PPNet: A Novel Neural Network Structure for End-to-End Near-Optimal Path Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppnet-a-novel-neural-network-structure-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results show PPNet can find a near-optimal solution in 15. 3ms, which is much shorter than the state-of-the-art path planners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppnet-a-novel-neural-network-structure-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicitly Disentangled Representations in Object-Centric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicitly-disentangled-representations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extracting structured representations from raw visual data is an important and long-standing challenge in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicitly-disentangled-representations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Interleaved: Interleaved Image-Text Generative Modeling via Multi-modal Feature Synchronizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-interleaved-interleaved-image-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Developing generative models for interleaved image-text data has both research and practical value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-interleaved-interleaved-image-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPCL: Cross-Modal Prototypical Contrastive Learning for Weakly Supervised Text-based Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cpcl-cross-modal-prototypical-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly supervised text-based person re-identification (TPRe-ID) seeks to retrieve images of a target person using textual descriptions, without relying on identity annotations and is more challenging and practical.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cpcl-cross-modal-prototypical-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Question-Answer Cross Language Image Matching for Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/question-answer-cross-language-image-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Class Activation Map (CAM) has emerged as a popular tool for weakly supervised semantic segmentation (WSSS), allowing the localization of object regions in an image using only image-level labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/question-answer-cross-language-image-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infinite-Horizon Graph Filters: Leveraging Power Series to Enhance Sparse Information Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infinite-horizon-graph-filters-leveraging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have shown considerable effectiveness in a variety of graph learning tasks, particularly those based on the message-passing approach in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infinite-horizon-graph-filters-leveraging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Compression Techniques in Biometrics Applications: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-compression-techniques-in-biometrics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of deep learning algorithms has extensively empowered humanity's task automatization capacity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-compression-techniques-in-biometrics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All in How You Ask for It: Simple Black-Box Method for Jailbreak Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-in-how-you-ask-for-it-simple-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) like ChatGPT face `jailbreak' challenges, where safeguards are bypassed to produce ethically harmful prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-in-how-you-ask-for-it-simple-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooperative Edge Caching Based on Elastic Federated and Multi-Agent Deep Reinforcement Learning in Next-Generation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-edge-caching-based-on-elastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we propose a multi-agent deep reinforcement learning (MADRL) based algorithm to decide where the predicted popular contents are collaboratively cached among SBSs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-edge-caching-based-on-elastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Explain Transformers by Illuminating Important Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-explain-transformers-by-illuminating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based models excel in various natural language processing (NLP) tasks, attracting countless efforts to explain their inner workings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-explain-transformers-by-illuminating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Latent Diffusion Approach for Panoptic Segmentation and Mask Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-latent-diffusion-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Panoptic and instance segmentation networks are often trained with specialized object detection modules, complex loss functions, and ad-hoc post-processing steps to handle the permutation-invariance of the instance masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-latent-diffusion-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enabling Efficient Equivariant Operations in the Fourier Basis via Gaunt Tensor Products</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-efficient-equivariant-operations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We mathematically connect the commonly used Clebsch-Gordan coefficients to the Gaunt coefficients, which are integrals of products of three spherical harmonics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-efficient-equivariant-operations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SkyEyeGPT: Unifying Remote Sensing Vision-Language Tasks via Instruction Tuning with Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skyeyegpt-unifying-remote-sensing-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, after projecting RS visual features to the language domain via an alignment layer, they are fed jointly with task-specific instructions into an LLM-based RS decoder to predict answers for RS open-ended tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skyeyegpt-unifying-remote-sensing-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAP-SAM: Towards Real-Time All-Purpose Segment Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rap-sam-towards-real-time-all-purpose-segment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segment Anything Model (SAM) is one remarkable model that can achieve generalized segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rap-sam-towards-real-time-all-purpose-segment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMamba: Visual State Space Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vmamba-visual-state-space-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) and Vision Transformers (ViTs) stand as the two most popular foundation models for visual representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vmamba-visual-state-space-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Manga Whisperer: Automatically Generating Transcriptions for Comics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-manga-whisperer-automatically-generating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the past few decades, Japanese comics, commonly referred to as Manga, have transcended both cultural and linguistic boundaries to become a true worldwide sensation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-manga-whisperer-automatically-generating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme-ingful Analysis: Enhanced Understanding of Cyberbullying in Memes Through Multimodal Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meme-ingful-analysis-enhanced-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A Contrastive Language-Image Pretraining (CLIP) projection-based multimodal shared-private multitask approach has been proposed for visual and textual explanation of a meme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meme-ingful-analysis-enhanced-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Land Cover Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/land-cover-image-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Land Cover (LC) image classification has become increasingly significant in understanding environmental changes, urban planning, and disaster management.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/land-cover-image-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event-Based Visual Odometry on Non-Holonomic Ground Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-based-visual-odometry-on-non-holonomic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the promise of superior performance under challenging conditions, event-based motion estimation remains a hard problem owing to the difficulty of extracting and tracking stable features from event streams.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-based-visual-odometry-on-non-holonomic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging State and History Representations: Understanding Self-Predictive RL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-state-and-history-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These findings culminate in a set of practical guidelines for RL practitioners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-state-and-history-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P$^2$OT: Progressive Partial Optimal Transport for Deep Imbalanced Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p-2-ot-progressive-partial-optimal-transport</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep clustering, which learns representation and semantic clustering without labels information, poses a great challenge for deep learning-based approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p-2-ot-progressive-partial-optimal-transport</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idempotence and Perceptual Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idempotence-and-perceptual-image-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we find that theoretically: 1) Conditional generative model-based perceptual codec satisfies idempotence; 2) Unconditional generative model with idempotence constraint is equivalent to conditional generative codec.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idempotence-and-perceptual-image-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedLoGe: Joint Local and Generic Federated Learning under Long-tailed Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedloge-joint-local-and-generic-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Long-Tailed Learning (Fed-LT), a paradigm wherein data collected from decentralized local clients manifests a globally prevalent long-tailed distribution, has garnered considerable attention in recent times.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedloge-joint-local-and-generic-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Hierarchical Interactions for Protein Surface Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-hierarchical-interactions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a principled framework based on deep learning techniques, namely Hierarchical Chemical and Geometric Feature Interaction Network (HCGNet), for protein surface analysis by bridging chemical and geometric features with hierarchical interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-hierarchical-interactions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trapped in texture bias? A large scale comparison of deep instance segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trapped-in-texture-bias-a-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In summary we evaluate 68 models on 61 versions of MS COCO for a total of 4148 evaluations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trapped-in-texture-bias-a-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PixelDINO: Semi-Supervised Semantic Segmentation for Detecting Permafrost Disturbances</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixeldino-semi-supervised-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve model generalization across the Arctic without the need for additional labelled data, we present a semi-supervised learning approach to train semantic segmentation models to detect RTS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixeldino-semi-supervised-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEL: A Continual Learning Model for Disease Outbreak Prediction by Leveraging Domain Adaptation via Elastic Weight Consolidation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cel-a-continual-learning-model-for-disease</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This model aims to mitigate the catastrophic forgetting phenomenon in a domain incremental setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cel-a-continual-learning-model-for-disease</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoCrafter2: Overcoming Data Limitations for High-Quality Video Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videocrafter2-overcoming-data-limitations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this stronger coupling, we shift the distribution to higher quality without motion degradation by finetuning spatial modules with high-quality images, resulting in a generic high-quality video model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videocrafter2-overcoming-data-limitations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating distribution shift in machine learning-augmented hybrid simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-distribution-shift-in-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of distribution shift generally arising in machine-learning augmented hybrid simulation, where parts of simulation algorithms are replaced by data-driven surrogates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-distribution-shift-in-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autonomous Catheterization with Open-source Simulator and Expert Trajectory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autonomous-catheterization-with-open-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Endovascular robots have been actively developed in both academia and industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autonomous-catheterization-with-open-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asynchronous Local-SGD Training for Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asynchronous-local-sgd-training-for-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Local stochastic gradient descent (Local-SGD), also referred to as federated averaging, is an approach to distributed optimization where each device performs more than one SGD update per communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asynchronous-local-sgd-training-for-language</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
