<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 21:06:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SED: A Simple Encoder-Decoder for Open-Vocabulary Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sed-a-simple-encoder-decoder-for-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a simple encoder-decoder, named SED, for open-vocabulary semantic segmentation, which comprises a hierarchical encoder-based cost map generation and a gradual fusion decoder with category early rejection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sed-a-simple-encoder-decoder-for-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Increasing Coverage and Precision of Textual Information in Multilingual Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/increasing-coverage-and-precision-of-textual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work in Natural Language Processing and Computer Vision has been using textual information -- e. g., entity names and descriptions -- available in knowledge graphs to ground neural models to high-quality structured data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/increasing-coverage-and-precision-of-textual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUnE: Dataset for Unified Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dune-dataset-for-unified-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we broaden the scope of the editing problem to include an array of editing cases such as debiasing and rectifying reasoning errors and define an edit as any natural language expression that solicits a change in the model's outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dune-dataset-for-unified-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boot and Switch: Alternating Distillation for Zero-Shot Dense Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boot-and-switch-alternating-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results demonstrate that our unsupervised $\texttt{ABEL}$ model outperforms both leading supervised and unsupervised retrievers on the BEIR benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boot-and-switch-alternating-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Generation for Post-OCR correction of Cyrillic handwriting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-generation-for-post-ocr-correction-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply a Handwritten Text Recognition (HTR) model to this dataset to identify OCR errors, forming the basis for our POC model training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-generation-for-post-ocr-correction-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should We Learn Most Likely Functions or Parameters?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/should-we-learn-most-likely-functions-or</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, the most likely parameters under the parameter posterior do not generally correspond to the most likely function induced by the parameter posterior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/should-we-learn-most-likely-functions-or</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSIN: Self-Supervised Learning for Rainfall Spatial Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssin-self-supervised-learning-for-rainfall</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the Cloze task and BERT, we fully consider the characteristics of spatial interpolation and design the SpaFormer model based on the Transformer architecture as the core of SSIN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssin-self-supervised-learning-for-rainfall</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Battleship Approach to the Low Resource Entity Matching Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-battleship-approach-to-the-low-resource</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entity matching, a core data integration problem, is the task of deciding whether two data tuples refer to the same real-world entity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-battleship-approach-to-the-low-resource</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OccWorld: Learning a 3D Occupancy World Model for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occworld-learning-a-3d-occupancy-world-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore a new framework of learning a world model, OccWorld, in the 3D Occupancy space to simultaneously predict the movement of the ego car and the evolution of the surrounding scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occworld-learning-a-3d-occupancy-world-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpotServe: Serving Generative Large Language Models on Preemptible Instances</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spotserve-serving-generative-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper aims to reduce the monetary cost for serving LLMs by leveraging preemptible GPU instances on modern clouds, which offer accesses to spare GPUs at a much cheaper price than regular instances but may be preempted by the cloud at any time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spotserve-serving-generative-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utilizing Explainability Techniques for Reinforcement Learning Model Assurance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilizing-explainability-techniques-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Explainable Reinforcement Learning (XRL) can provide transparency into the decision-making process of a Deep Reinforcement Learning (DRL) model and increase user trust and adoption in real-world use cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilizing-explainability-techniques-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLIME: General, Stable and Local LIME Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glime-general-stable-and-local-lime</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, LIME's sampling neighborhood is non-local and biased towards the reference, resulting in poor local fidelity and sensitivity to reference choice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glime-general-stable-and-local-lime</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Dataset Distillation via Minimax Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-dataset-distillation-via-minimax</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Observing that key factors for constructing an effective surrogate dataset are representativeness and diversity, we design additional minimax criteria in the generative training to enhance these facets for the generated images of diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-dataset-distillation-via-minimax</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaesarNeRF: Calibrated Semantic Representation for Few-shot Generalizable Neural Rendering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caesarnerf-calibrated-semantic-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CaesarNeRF explicitly models pose differences of reference views to combine scene-level semantic representations, providing a calibrated holistic understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caesarnerf-calibrated-semantic-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DreamCreature: Crafting Photorealistic Virtual Creatures from Imagination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamcreature-crafting-photorealistic-virtual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce a novel task, Virtual Creatures Generation: Given a set of unlabeled images of the target concepts (e. g., 200 bird species), we aim to train a T2I model capable of creating new, hybrid concepts within diverse backgrounds and contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamcreature-crafting-photorealistic-virtual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Event Detection in Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-event-detection-in-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our previously published work, we introduced a supervised deep learning method for event detection in multivariate time series data, employing regression instead of binary classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-event-detection-in-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Autoencoders for Feature Exploration and Malignancy Prediction of Lung Lesions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-autoencoders-for-feature-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Proposed models were trained on lesions extracted from 3D CT scans in the LIDC-IDRI public dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-autoencoders-for-feature-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Vulnerability of Federated Learning: A Learning Algorithm Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-vulnerability-of-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this survey paper, our research indicates that the to-learn data, the learning gradients, and the learned model at different stages all can be manipulated to initiate malicious attacks that range from undermining model performance, reconstructing private local data, and to inserting backdoors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-vulnerability-of-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Quantitative Approach to Understand Self-Supervised Models as Cross-lingual Feature Extractors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-quantitative-approach-to-understand-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a positive correlation between PSR scores and ASR performance, suggesting that phonetic information extracted by monolingual SSL models can be used for downstream tasks in cross-lingual settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-quantitative-approach-to-understand-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Side4Video: Spatial-Temporal Side Network for Memory-Efficient Image-to-Video Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/side4video-spatial-temporal-side-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel Spatial-Temporal Side Network for memory-efficient fine-tuning large image models to video understanding, named Side4Video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/side4video-spatial-temporal-side-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFIN: Universal Feature Interaction Network for Multi-Domain Click-Through Rate Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufin-universal-feature-interaction-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above issue, we propose the Universal Feature Interaction Network (UFIN) approach for CTR prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufin-universal-feature-interaction-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniRepLKNet: A Universal Perception Large-Kernel ConvNet for Audio, Video, Point Cloud, Time-Series and Image Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unireplknet-a-universal-perception-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[1) We propose four architectural guidelines for designing large-kernel ConvNets, the core of which is to exploit the essential characteristics of large kernels that distinguish them from small kernels - they can see wide without going deep.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unireplknet-a-universal-perception-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDITRON-70B: Scaling Medical Pretraining for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meditron-70b-scaling-medical-pretraining-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) can potentially democratize access to medical knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meditron-70b-scaling-medical-pretraining-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tell2Design: A Dataset for Language-Guided Floor Plan Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tell2design-a-dataset-for-language-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We make multiple contributions to initiate research on this task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tell2design-a-dataset-for-language-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVRDA: A Web-based Dataset Annotation Tool for Slice-to-Volume Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svrda-a-web-based-dataset-annotation-tool-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conclusions: SVRDA can facilitate collaborative annotation of benchmark datasets while being potentially applicable to other pipelines incorporating slice-to-volume registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svrda-a-web-based-dataset-annotation-tool-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Many Unicorns Are in This Image? A Safety Evaluation Benchmark for Vision LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-many-unicorns-are-in-this-image-a-safety</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from prior studies, we shift our focus from evaluating standard performance to introducing a comprehensive safety evaluation suite, covering both out-of-distribution (OOD) generalization and adversarial robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-many-unicorns-are-in-this-image-a-safety</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Diffusion Models with Text-Encoder Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-diffusion-models-with-text-encoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While fine-tuning the U-Net can partially improve performance, it remains suffering from the suboptimal text encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-diffusion-models-with-text-encoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-6D: Segment Anything Model Meets Zero-Shot 6D Object Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-6d-segment-anything-model-meets-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zero-shot 6D object pose estimation involves the detection of novel objects with their 6D poses in cluttered scenes, presenting significant challenges for model generalizability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-6d-segment-anything-model-meets-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only Positive Cases: 5-fold High-order Attention Interaction Model for Skin Segmentation Derived Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/only-positive-cases-5-fold-high-order</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a multiple high-order attention interaction model (MHA-UNet) for use in a highly explainable skin lesion segmentation task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/only-positive-cases-5-fold-high-order</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving Data Sharing in Agriculture: Enforcing Policy Rules for Secure and Confidential Data Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-data-sharing-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Big Data can provide the farming community with valuable insights and improve efficiency, there is significant concern regarding the security of this data as well as the privacy of the participants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-data-sharing-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VeryFL: A Verify Federated Learning Framework Embedded with Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/veryfl-a-verify-federated-learning-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These mechanism on blockchain shows an underlying support of blockchain for federated learning to provide a verifiable training, aggregation and incentive distribution procedure and thus we named this framework VeryFL (A Verify Federated Learninig Framework Embedded with Blockchain).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/veryfl-a-verify-federated-learning-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noisy Self-Training with Synthetic Queries for Dense Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisy-self-training-with-synthetic-queries</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although existing neural retrieval models reveal promising results when training data is abundant and the performance keeps improving as training data increases, collecting high-quality annotated data is prohibitively costly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisy-self-training-with-synthetic-queries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning for Wildfire Mitigation in Simulated Disaster Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-for-wildfire</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Climate change has resulted in a year over year increase in adverse weather and weather conditions which contribute to increasingly severe fire seasons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-for-wildfire</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-informed neural networks for transformed geometries and manifolds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-neural-networks-for-14</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel method for integrating geometric transformations within PINNs to robustly accommodate geometric variations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-neural-networks-for-14</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YUAN 2.0: A Large Language Model with Localized Filtering-based Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yuan-2-0-a-large-language-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, the Localized Filtering-based Attention (LFA) is introduced to incorporate prior knowledge of local dependencies of natural language into Attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yuan-2-0-a-large-language-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Pixels to Titles: Video Game Identification by Screenshots using Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-pixels-to-titles-video-game</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates video game identification through single screenshots, utilizing five convolutional neural network (CNN) architectures (MobileNet, DenseNet, EfficientNetB0, EfficientNetB2, and EfficientNetB3) across 22 home console systems, spanning from Atari 2600 to PlayStation 5.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-pixels-to-titles-video-game</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Transport Aggregation for Visual Place Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-aggregation-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of Visual Place Recognition (VPR) aims to match a query image against references from an extensive database of images from different places, relying solely on visual cues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-aggregation-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViT-Lens-2: Gateway to Omni-modal Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vit-lens-2-gateway-to-omni-modal-intelligence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present ViT-Lens-2 that facilitates efficient omni-modal representation learning by perceiving novel modalities with a pretrained ViT and aligning them to a pre-defined space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vit-lens-2-gateway-to-omni-modal-intelligence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-Bench: A Comprehensive Benchmark and Toolkit for Evaluating Video-based Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-bench-a-comprehensive-benchmark-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video-based large language models (Video-LLMs) have been recently introduced, targeting both fundamental improvements in perception and comprehension, and a diverse range of user inquiries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-bench-a-comprehensive-benchmark-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XLB: Distributed Multi-GPU Lattice Boltzmann Simulation Framework for Differentiable Scientific Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xlb-distributed-multi-gpu-lattice-boltzmann</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The lattice Boltzmann method (LBM) has emerged as a prominent technique for solving fluid dynamics problems due to its algorithmic potential for computational scalability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xlb-distributed-multi-gpu-lattice-boltzmann</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensitivity-Based Layer Insertion for Residual and Feedforward Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensitivity-based-layer-insertion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The training of neural networks requires tedious and often manual tuning of the network architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensitivity-based-layer-insertion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experimental Analysis of Large-scale Learnable Vector Storage Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/experimental-analysis-of-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learnable embedding vector is one of the most important applications in machine learning, and is widely used in various database-related domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/experimental-analysis-of-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A precise symbolic emulator of the linear matter power spectrum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-precise-symbolic-emulator-of-the-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We obtain an analytic approximation to the linear power spectrum with a root mean squared fractional error of 0. 2% between $k = 9\times10^{-3} - 9 \, h{\rm \, Mpc^{-1}}$ and across a wide range of cosmological parameters, and we provide physical interpretations for various terms in the expression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-precise-symbolic-emulator-of-the-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERT Goes Off-Topic: Investigating the Domain Transfer Challenge using Genre Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bert-goes-off-topic-investigating-the-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While performance of many text classification tasks has been recently improved due to Pre-trained Language Models (PLMs), in this paper we show that they still suffer from a performance gap when the underlying distribution of topics changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bert-goes-off-topic-investigating-the-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffSLVA: Harnessing Diffusion Models for Sign Language Video Anonymization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffslva-harnessing-diffusion-models-for-sign</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While signers have expressed interest, for a variety of applications, in sign language video anonymization that would effectively preserve linguistic content, attempts to develop such technology have had limited success, given the complexity of hand movements and facial expressions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffslva-harnessing-diffusion-models-for-sign</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animatable Gaussians: Learning Pose-dependent Gaussian Maps for High-fidelity Human Avatar Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animatable-gaussians-learning-pose-dependent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, our method can create lifelike avatars with dynamic, realistic and generalized appearances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animatable-gaussians-learning-pose-dependent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Measurement of Vascular Calcification in Femoral Endarterectomy Patients Using Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-measurement-of-vascular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, manual analysis of CTA images is time-consuming and tedious.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-measurement-of-vascular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Perceptual Quality in Video Super-Resolution through Temporally-Consistent Detail Synthesis using Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-perceptual-quality-in-video-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the effectiveness of StableVSR in enhancing the perceptual quality of upscaled videos compared to existing state-of-the-art methods for VSR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-perceptual-quality-in-video-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A deep learning approach for marine snow synthesis and removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-approach-for-marine-snow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Marine snow, the floating particles in underwater images, severely degrades the visibility and performance of human and machine vision systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-approach-for-marine-snow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT4Vis: What Can GPT-4 Do for Zero-shot Visual Recognition?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt4vis-what-can-gpt-4-do-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study centers on the evaluation of GPT-4's linguistic and visual capabilities in zero-shot visual recognition tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt4vis-what-can-gpt-4-do-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
