<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 09:11:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Large Multilingual Models Pivot Zero-Shot Multimodal Learning across Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-multilingual-models-pivot-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building a competitive counterpart in other languages is highly challenging due to the low-resource nature of non-English multimodal data (i. e., lack of large-scale, high-quality image-text data).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-multilingual-models-pivot-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Data Perturbation and Model Stabilization for Semi-supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-data-perturbation-and-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Studies on semi-supervised medical image segmentation (SSMIS) have seen fast progress recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-data-perturbation-and-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head-Tail Cooperative Learning Network for Unbiased Scene Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/head-tail-cooperative-learning-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose a self-supervised learning approach to enhance the prediction ability of the tail-prefer feature representation branch by constraining tail-prefer predicate features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/head-tail-cooperative-learning-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MolGrapher: Graph-based Visual Recognition of Chemical Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molgrapher-graph-based-visual-recognition-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we introduce a large-scale benchmark of annotated real molecule images, USPTO-30K, to spur research on this critical topic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molgrapher-graph-based-visual-recognition-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DR-Tune: Improving Fine-tuning of Pretrained Visual Models by Distribution Regularization with Semantic Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dr-tune-improving-fine-tuning-of-pretrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, to alleviate the interference by semantic drift, we develop the semantic calibration (SC) module to align the global shape and class centers of the pretrained and downstream feature distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dr-tune-improving-fine-tuning-of-pretrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modal Multi-Task (3MT) Road Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-multi-task-3mt-road-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The inference times obtained in all experiments are very promising for real-time experiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-multi-task-3mt-road-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMIT: Source-Free Adaptation of Uni-Modal Models to Multi-Modal Targets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/summit-source-free-adaptation-of-uni-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we relax both of these assumptions by addressing the problem of adapting a set of models trained independently on uni-modal data to a target domain consisting of unlabeled multi-modal data, without having access to the original source dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/summit-source-free-adaptation-of-uni-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instruction Position Matters in Sequence Generation with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-position-matters-in-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are capable of performing conditional sequence generation tasks, such as translation or summarization, through instruction fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-position-matters-in-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CgT-GAN: CLIP-guided Text GAN for Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cgt-gan-clip-guided-text-gan-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, we use adversarial training to teach CgT-GAN to mimic the phrases of an external text corpus and CLIP-based reward to provide semantic guidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cgt-gan-clip-guided-text-gan-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverse Policies Converge in Reward-free Markov Decision Processe</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-policies-converge-in-reward-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under such a framework, we also propose a provably efficient diversity reinforcement learning algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-policies-converge-in-reward-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Value of Assistance for Mobile Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/value-of-assistance-for-mobile-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In some settings, it may be possible to perform assistive actions that reduce uncertainty about a robot's location.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/value-of-assistance-for-mobile-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Privacy-Supporting Fall Detection via Deep Unsupervised RGB2Depth Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-privacy-supporting-fall-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a privacy-supporting solution that makes the RGB-trained model applicable in depth domain and utilizes depth data at test time for fall detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-privacy-supporting-fall-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt2Model: Generating Deployable Models from Natural Language Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt2model-generating-deployable-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Prompt2Model, a general-purpose method that takes a natural language task description like the prompts provided to LLMs, and uses it to train a special-purpose model that is conducive to deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt2model-generating-deployable-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OFVL-MS: Once for Visual Localization across Multiple Indoor Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ofvl-ms-once-for-visual-localization-across</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we seek to predict camera poses across scenes with a multi-task learning manner, where we view the localization of each scene as a new task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ofvl-ms-once-for-visual-localization-across</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Framework for 3D Point Cloud Visual Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-framework-for-3d-point-cloud-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This elegant design enables 3DRefTR to achieve both well-performing 3DRES and 3DREC capacities with only a 6% additional latency compared to the original 3DREC model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-framework-for-3d-point-cloud-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion-to-Matching: A Mixed Paradigm for 3D Single Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-to-matching-a-mixed-paradigm-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D single object tracking with LiDAR points is an important task in the computer vision field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-to-matching-a-mixed-paradigm-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SILT: Shadow-aware Iterative Label Tuning for Learning to Detect Shadows from Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/silt-shadow-aware-iterative-label-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing shadow detection datasets often contain missing or mislabeled shadows, which can hinder the performance of deep learning models trained directly on such data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/silt-shadow-aware-iterative-label-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IncreLoRA: Incremental Parameter Allocation Method for Parameter-Efficient Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/increlora-incremental-parameter-allocation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach is different from the pruning method as it is not limited by the initial number of training parameters, and each parameter matrix has a higher rank upper bound for the same training overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/increlora-incremental-parameter-allocation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPPNet: A Single-Point Prompt Network for Nuclei Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sppnet-a-single-point-prompt-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to the segment anything model, SPPNet shows roughly 20 times faster inference, with 1/70 parameters and computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sppnet-a-single-point-prompt-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LKPNR: LLM and KG for Personalized News Recommendation Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lkpnr-llm-and-kg-for-personalized-news</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional methods are usually difficult to grasp the complex semantic information in news texts, resulting in unsatisfactory recommendation results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lkpnr-llm-and-kg-for-personalized-news</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>${\rm E}(3)$-Equivariant Actor-Critic Methods for Cooperative Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rm-e-3-equivariant-actor-critic-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identification and analysis of symmetrical patterns in the natural world have led to significant discoveries across various scientific fields, such as the formulation of gravitational laws in physics and advancements in the study of chemical structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rm-e-3-equivariant-actor-critic-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LFS-GAN: Lifelong Few-Shot Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lfs-gan-lifelong-few-shot-image-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Surprisingly, we find that our LFS-GAN even outperforms the existing few-shot GANs in the few-shot image generation task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lfs-gan-lifelong-few-shot-image-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlexKBQA: A Flexible LLM-Powered Framework for Few-Shot Knowledge Base Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexkbqa-a-flexible-llm-powered-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge base question answering (KBQA) is a critical yet challenging task due to the vast number of entities within knowledge bases and the diversity of natural language questions posed by users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexkbqa-a-flexible-llm-powered-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-driven decision-focused surrogate modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-decision-focused-surrogate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the concept of decision-focused surrogate modeling for solving computationally challenging nonlinear optimization problems in real-time settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-decision-focused-surrogate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Objective Optimization for Sparse Deep Neural Network Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-optimization-for-sparse-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a Multi-Objective Optimization algorithm using a modified Weighted Chebyshev scalarization for training Deep Neural Networks (DNNs) with respect to several tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-optimization-for-sparse-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing Selection Bias in Computerized Adaptive Testing: A User-Wise Aggregate Influence Function Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-selection-bias-in-computerized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Indeed, when naively training the diagnostic model using CAT response data, we observe that item profiles deviate significantly from the ground-truth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-selection-bias-in-computerized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic landslide susceptibility mapping over recent three decades to uncover variations in landslide causes in subtropical urban mountainous areas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-landslide-susceptibility-mapping-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The chosen study area is Lantau Island, Hong Kong, where we conducted a comprehensive dynamic LSA spanning from 1992 to 2019.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-landslide-susceptibility-mapping-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMRec: Benchmarking Large Language Models on Recommendation Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmrec-benchmarking-large-language-models-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The benchmark results indicate that LLMs displayed only moderate proficiency in accuracy-based tasks such as sequential and direct recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmrec-benchmarking-large-language-models-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development and external validation of a lung cancer risk estimation tool using gradient-boosting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/development-and-external-validation-of-a-lung</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a machine learning (ML) tool trained on data from the PLCO Cancer Screening Trial and validated on the NLST to estimate the likelihood of lung cancer occurrence within five years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/development-and-external-validation-of-a-lung</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ULDP-FL: Federated Learning with Across Silo User-Level Differential Privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uldp-fl-federated-learning-with-across-silo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we present ULDP-FL, a novel FL framework designed to guarantee user-level DP in cross-silo FL where a single user's data may belong to multiple silos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uldp-fl-federated-learning-with-across-silo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Language Models Can Perform Many Tasks with Scaling and Instruction-Finetuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-language-models-can-perform-many</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then reprogram pretrained masked language models into diffusion language models via diffusive adaptation, wherein task-specific finetuning and instruction finetuning are explored to unlock their versatility in solving general language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-language-models-can-perform-many</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Change Detection for the Romanian Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-change-detection-for-the-romanian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic semantic change methods try to identify the changes that appear over time in the meaning of words by analyzing their usage in diachronic corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-change-detection-for-the-romanian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topical-Chat: Towards Knowledge-Grounded Open-Domain Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topical-chat-towards-knowledge-grounded-open-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Topical-Chat, a knowledge-grounded human-human conversation dataset where the underlying knowledge spans 8 broad topics and conversation partners don't have explicitly defined roles, to help further research in open-domain conversational AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topical-chat-towards-knowledge-grounded-open-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Reward Modulation for Pretraining Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-reward-modulation-for-pretraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using learned reward functions (LRFs) as a means to solve sparse-reward reinforcement learning (RL) tasks has yielded some steady progress in task-complexity through the years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-reward-modulation-for-pretraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masking Strategies for Background Bias Removal in Computer Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masking-strategies-for-background-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Models for fine-grained image classification tasks, where the difference between some classes can be extremely subtle and the number of samples per class tends to be low, are particularly prone to picking up background-related biases and demand robust methods to handle potential examples with out-of-distribution (OOD) backgrounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masking-strategies-for-background-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeamlessM4T-Massively Multilingual &amp; Multimodal Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seamlessm4t-massively-multilingual-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To build this, we used 1 million hours of open speech audio data to learn self-supervised speech representations with w2v-BERT 2. 0.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seamlessm4t-massively-multilingual-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Target-Grounded Graph-Aware Transformer for Aerial Vision-and-Dialog Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-grounded-graph-aware-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report details the method of the winning entry of the AVDN Challenge in ICCV 2023.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-grounded-graph-aware-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Generalization via Rationale Invariance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalization-via-rationale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose treating the element-wise contributions to the final results as the rationale for making a decision and representing the rationale for each sample as a matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalization-via-rationale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Dynamic Range Imaging of Dynamic Scenes with Saturation Compensation but without Explicit Motion Compensation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dynamic-range-imaging-of-dynamic-scenes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For HDR imaging, some methods capture multiple low dynamic range (LDR) images with altering exposures to aggregate more information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dynamic-range-imaging-of-dynamic-scenes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting column-generation-based matheuristic for learning classification trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-column-generation-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach improves scalability and can work with large datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-column-generation-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expecting The Unexpected: Towards Broad Out-Of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expecting-the-unexpected-towards-broad-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings reveal that while these methods excel in detecting unknown classes, their performance is inconsistent when encountering other types of distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expecting-the-unexpected-towards-broad-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Open Vocabulary Enhanced Safe-landing with Intelligence (DOVESEI)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-open-vocabulary-enhanced-safe-landing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work targets what we consider to be the foundational step for urban airborne robots, a safe landing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-open-vocabulary-enhanced-safe-landing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensor Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensor-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tensors, as high dimensional extensions of vectors, are considered as natural representations of high dimensional data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensor-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Authorship Representation Learning Capture Stylistic Features?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-authorship-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatically disentangling an author's style from the content of their writing is a longstanding and possibly insurmountable problem in computational linguistics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-authorship-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development of a Novel Quantum Pre-processing Filter to Improve Image Classification Accuracy of Neural Network Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/development-of-a-novel-quantum-pre-processing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel quantum pre-processing filter (QPF) to improve the image classification accuracy of neural network (NN) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/development-of-a-novel-quantum-pre-processing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SONAR: Sentence-Level Multimodal and Language-Agnostic Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentence-level-multimodal-and-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our single text encoder, covering 200 languages, substantially outperforms existing sentence embeddings such as LASER3 and LabSE on the xsim and xsim++ multilingual similarity search tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentence-level-multimodal-and-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Much Temporal Long-Term Context is Needed for Action Segmentation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-much-temporal-long-term-context-is-needed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we try to answer how much long-term temporal context is required for temporal action segmentation by introducing a transformer-based model that leverages sparse attention to capture the full context of a video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-much-temporal-long-term-context-is-needed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Knot Prediction in Wood Logs with Longitudinal Feature Propagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-knot-prediction-in-wood-logs-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we address the task of predicting the location of inner defects from the outer shape of the logs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-knot-prediction-in-wood-logs-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Large Language Models on Graphs: Performance Insights and Comparative Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-large-language-models-on-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, the application of LLMs to graph data remains under-explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-large-language-models-on-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Framework for Multi-mode Spatial-Temporal Data Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-framework-for-multi-mode-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatial-temporal data modeling aims to mine the underlying spatial relationships and temporal dependencies of objects in a system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-framework-for-multi-mode-spatial</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
