<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 21:08:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Task Benchmark for Korean Legal Language Understanding and Judgement Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-task-benchmark-for-korean-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we present the first large-scale benchmark of Korean legal AI datasets, LBox Open, that consists of one legal corpus, two classification tasks, two legal judgement prediction (LJP) tasks, and one summarization task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-task-benchmark-for-korean-legal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Foggy Scene Understanding via Self Spatial-Temporal Label Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-foggy-scene-understanding-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, based on the two discoveries of local spatial similarity and adjacent temporal correspondence of the sequential image data, we propose a novel Target-Domain driven pseudo label Diffusion (TDo-Dif) scheme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-foggy-scene-understanding-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactively Learning Preference Constraints in Linear Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactively-learning-preference-constraints</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide an instance-dependent lower bound for constrained linear best-arm identification and show that ACOL's sample complexity matches the lower bound in the worst-case.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactively-learning-preference-constraints</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refining neural network predictions using background knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refining-neural-network-predictions-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using a new algorithm, we combine refinement functions to find refined predictions for logical formulas of any complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refining-neural-network-predictions-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask to Know More: Generating Counterfactual Explanations for Fake Claims</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ask-to-know-more-generating-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose elucidating fact checking predictions using counterfactual explanations to help people understand why a specific piece of news was identified as fake.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ask-to-know-more-generating-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed integer linear optimization formulations for learning optimal binary classification trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-integer-linear-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An optimal binary classification tree can be obtained by solving a biobjective optimization problem that seeks to (i) maximize the number of correctly classified datapoints and (ii) minimize the number of branching vertices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-integer-linear-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-optimal-transport</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the use of amortized optimization to predict optimal transport (OT) maps from the input measures, which we call Meta OT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-optimal-transport</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Template: Topology-aware Reconstruction and Disentangled Generation of 3D Meshes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-template-topology-aware-reconstruction-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel framework called DTNet for 3D mesh reconstruction and generation via Disentangled Topology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-template-topology-aware-reconstruction-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffeomorphic Counterfactuals with Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffeomorphic-counterfactuals-with-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterfactuals can explain classification decisions of neural networks in a human interpretable way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffeomorphic-counterfactuals-with-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Borrowing or Codeswitching? Annotating for Finer-Grained Distinctions in Language Mixing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/borrowing-or-codeswitching-annotating-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new corpus of Twitter data annotated for codeswitching and borrowing between Spanish and English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/borrowing-or-codeswitching-annotating-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Counterfactual Environment Model Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-counterfactual-environment-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the target policies can be various and unknown in policy learning, we propose an adversarial CQRM objective in which the model learns on counterfactual data queried by adversarial policies, and finally derive a tractable solution GALILEO.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-counterfactual-environment-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RuCoCo: a new Russian corpus with coreference annotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rucoco-a-new-russian-corpus-with-coreference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new corpus with coreference annotation, Russian Coreference Corpus (RuCoCo).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rucoco-a-new-russian-corpus-with-coreference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merak: A Efficient Distributed DNN Training Framework with Automated 3D Parallelism for Giant Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merak-a-efficient-distributed-dnn-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These features make it necessary to apply 3D parallelism, which integrates data parallelism, pipeline model parallelism and tensor model parallelism, to achieve high training efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merak-a-efficient-distributed-dnn-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Referring Image Matting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/referring-image-matting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image matting refers to extracting the accurate foregrounds in the image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/referring-image-matting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Space of Deep Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-space-of-deep-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we show that it is possible to use representation learning to learn a fixed-size, low-dimensional embedding space of trained deep models and that such space can be explored by interpolation or optimization to attain ready-to-use models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-space-of-deep-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Deep Gaussian Markov Random Fields for General Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-deep-gaussian-markov-random-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a flexible GMRF model for general graphs built on the multi-layer structure of Deep GMRFs, originally proposed for lattice graphs only.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-deep-gaussian-markov-random-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Conditional Model Extrapolation for Streaming Data under Class-Prior Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-conditional-model-extrapolation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce LIMES, a new method for learning with non-stationary streaming data, inspired by the recent success of meta-learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-conditional-model-extrapolation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Prompt Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-prompt-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The size of vision models has grown exponentially over the last few years, especially after the emergence of Vision Transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-prompt-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure-consistent Restoration Network for Cataract Fundus Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-consistent-restoration-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, to circumvent the strict deployment requirement, a structure-consistent restoration network (SCR-Net) for cataract fundus images is developed from synthesized data that shares an identical structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-consistent-restoration-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analytical Composition of Differential Privacy via the Edgeworth Accountant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analytical-composition-of-differential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many modern machine learning algorithms are composed of simple private algorithms; thus, an increasingly important problem is to efficiently compute the overall privacy loss under composition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analytical-composition-of-differential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-Actor: Text-Driven Recommendation and Stylization for Animating Human Meshes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-actor-text-driven-recommendation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CLIP-Actor animates a 3D human mesh to conform to a text prompt by recommending a motion sequence and learning mesh style attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-actor-text-driven-recommendation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xplique: A Deep Learning Explainability Toolbox</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xplique-a-deep-learning-explainability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today's most advanced machine-learning models are hardly scrutable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xplique-a-deep-learning-explainability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering bias in the PlantVillage dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-bias-in-the-plantvillage-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We report our investigation on the use of the popular PlantVillage dataset for training deep learning based plant disease detection models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-bias-in-the-plantvillage-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlearning Protected User Attributes in Recommendations with Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlearning-protected-user-attributes-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct experiments on the MovieLens-1M and LFM-2b-DemoBias datasets, and evaluate the effectiveness of the bias mitigation method based on the inability of external attackers in revealing the users' gender information from the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlearning-protected-user-attributes-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Spatiotemporal Representation Learning for Longitudinally-consistent Neuroimage Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-spatiotemporal-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent self-supervised advances in medical computer vision exploit global and local anatomical self-similarity for pretraining prior to downstream tasks such as segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-spatiotemporal-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STIP: A SpatioTemporal Information-Preserving and Perception-Augmented Model for High-Resolution Video Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stip-a-spatiotemporal-information-preserving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve the information loss problem, the proposed model aims to preserve the spatiotemporal information for videos during the feature extraction and the state transitions, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stip-a-spatiotemporal-information-preserving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Layer-wise Image Vectorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-layer-wise-image-vectorization-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image rasterization is a mature technique in computer graphics, while image vectorization, the reverse path of rasterization, remains a major challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-layer-wise-image-vectorization-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distillation Decision Tree</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-decision-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With well-known advantages in interpretation, decision tree is a competitive candidate of the transparent model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-decision-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BigVGAN: A Universal Neural Vocoder with Large-Scale Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bigvgan-a-universal-neural-vocoder-with-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent progress in generative adversarial network(GAN)-based vocoders, where the model generates raw waveform conditioned on mel spectrogram, it is still challenging to synthesize high-fidelity audio for numerous speakers across varied recording environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bigvgan-a-universal-neural-vocoder-with-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiSparse: Disentangled Sparsification for Multitask Model Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disparse-disentangled-sparsification-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyzed the pruning masks generated with DiSparse and observed strikingly similar sparse network architecture identified by each task even before the training starts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disparse-disentangled-sparsification-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Entropy Search For Maximally-Informed Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-entropy-search-for-maximally-informed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a light-weight approach with superior results, JES provides a new go-to acquisition function for Bayesian optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-entropy-search-for-maximally-informed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study on Disentanglement of Negative-free Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-disentanglement-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the proposed metric, we benchmark the disentanglement property of negative-free contrastive learning for the first time, on both popular synthetic datasets and a real-world dataset CelebA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-disentanglement-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimVP: Simpler yet Better Video Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simvp-simpler-yet-better-video-prediction-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From CNN, RNN, to ViT, we have witnessed remarkable advancements in video prediction, incorporating auxiliary inputs, elaborate neural architectures, and sophisticated training strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simvp-simpler-yet-better-video-prediction-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Fair Meta-learned Recommender System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-fair-meta-learned-recommender</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core idea is to learn global shared meta-initialization parameters for all users and rapidly adapt them into local parameters for each user respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-fair-meta-learned-recommender</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoINR: Learning Video Implicit Neural Representation for Continuous Space-Time Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videoinr-learning-video-implicit-neural-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The learned implicit neural representation can be decoded to videos of arbitrary spatial resolution and frame rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videoinr-learning-video-implicit-neural-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Challenges and Opportunities in Offline Reinforcement Learning from Visual Observations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenges-and-opportunities-in-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Offline reinforcement learning has shown great promise in leveraging large pre-collected datasets for policy learning, allowing agents to forgo often-expensive online data collection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenges-and-opportunities-in-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Two-Ball Esllberg Paradox: Experimental Evidence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-ball-esllberg-paradox-experimental</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct an incentivized experiment on a nationally representative US sample (N=708) to test how people prefer to avoid ambiguity even when the ambiguity improves the probability of receiving a fixed price.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-ball-esllberg-paradox-experimental</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to generalize Dispatching rules on the Job Shop Scheduling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generalize-dispatching-rules-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current models on the JSP do not focus on generalization, although, as we show in this work, this is key to learning better heuristics on the problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generalize-dispatching-rules-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neo-GNNs: Neighborhood Overlap-aware Graph Neural Networks for Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neo-gnns-neighborhood-overlap-aware-graph-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have been widely applied to various fields for learning over graph-structured data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neo-gnns-neighborhood-overlap-aware-graph-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Relational Intervention Approach for Unsupervised Dynamics Generalization in Model-Based Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-relational-intervention-approach-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, because environments are not labelled, the extracted information inevitably contains redundant information unrelated to the dynamics in transition segments and thus fails to maintain a crucial property of $Z$: $Z$ should be similar in the same environment and dissimilar in different ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-relational-intervention-approach-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointNeXt: Revisiting PointNet++ with Improved Training and Scaling Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointnext-revisiting-pointnet-with-improved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we revisit the classical PointNet++ through a systematic study of model training and scaling strategies, and offer two major contributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointnext-revisiting-pointnet-with-improved</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Spectral Representation of Kernel Stein Discrepancy with Application to Goodness-of-Fit Tests for Measures on Infinite Dimensional Hilbert Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-spectral-representation-of-kernel-stein</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is often employed in the scenario where a user has a collection of samples from a candidate probability measure and wishes to compare them against a specified target probability measure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-spectral-representation-of-kernel-stein</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Identification for Austronesian Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-identification-for-austronesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper provides language identification models for low- and under-resourced languages in the Pacific region with a focus on previously unavailable Austronesian languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-identification-for-austronesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VITA: Video Instance Segmentation via Object Token Association</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vita-video-instance-segmentation-via-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we use an image object detector as a means of distilling object-specific contexts into object tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vita-video-instance-segmentation-via-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and Robust 2D-to-BEV Representation Learning via Geometry-guided Kernel Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-robust-2d-to-bev-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GKT leverages the geometric priors to guide the transformer to focus on discriminative regions and unfolds kernel features to generate BEV representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-robust-2d-to-bev-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Attention Multi-Layer Perceptron</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-attention-multi-layer-perceptron-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) have achieved great success in many graph-based applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-attention-multi-layer-perceptron-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGConv: Adaptive Graph Convolution on 3D Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agconv-adaptive-graph-convolution-on-3d-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Adaptive Graph Convolution (AGConv) for wide applications of point cloud analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agconv-adaptive-graph-convolution-on-3d-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Dictionary Learning by End-To-End Training of Iterative Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-dictionary-learning-by-end-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparsity-based methods have a long history in the field of signal processing and have been successfully applied to various image reconstruction problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-dictionary-learning-by-end-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Critical Review on the Use (and Misuse) of Differential Privacy in Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-critical-review-on-the-use-and-misuse-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We review the use of differential privacy (DP) for privacy protection in machine learning (ML).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-critical-review-on-the-use-and-misuse-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SwinCheX: Multi-label classification on chest X-ray images with transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swinchex-multi-label-classification-on-chest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model has been tested with several number of MLP layers for the head setting, each achieves a competitive AUC score on all classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swinchex-multi-label-classification-on-chest</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
