<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 21:08:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Text2Playlist: Generating Personalized Playlists from Text on Deezer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2playlist-generating-personalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The streaming service Deezer heavily relies on the search to help users navigate through its extensive music catalog.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2playlist-generating-personalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halal or Not: Knowledge Graph Completion for Predicting Cultural Appropriateness of Daily Products</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/halal-or-not-knowledge-graph-completion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then propose a pre-trained relational graph attention network model with residual connections to learn the structural relation between entities in the knowledge graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/halal-or-not-knowledge-graph-completion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affordably Fine-tuned LLMs Provide Better Answers to Course-specific MCQs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affordably-fine-tuned-llms-provide-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In education, the capability of generating human-like text of Large Language Models (LLMs) inspired work on how they can increase the efficiency of learning and teaching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affordably-fine-tuned-llms-provide-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Attention-Guided Deep Learning Approach for Classifying 39 Skin Lesion Types</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attention-guided-deep-learning-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using this dataset, the performance of five state-of-the-art deep learning models -- MobileNetV2, Xception, InceptionV3, EfficientNetB1, and Vision Transformer - is rigorously evaluated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attention-guided-deep-learning-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConSim: Measuring Concept-Based Explanations' Effectiveness with Automated Simulatability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consim-measuring-concept-based-explanations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an evaluation framework for measuring concept explanations via automated simulatability: a simulator's ability to predict the explained model's outputs based on the provided explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consim-measuring-concept-based-explanations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LlamaV-o1: Rethinking Step-by-step Visual Reasoning in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llamav-o1-rethinking-step-by-step-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The benchmark presents a diverse set of challenges with eight different categories ranging from complex visual perception to scientific reasoning with over 4k reasoning steps in total, enabling robust evaluation of LLMs' abilities to perform accurate and interpretable visual reasoning across multiple steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llamav-o1-rethinking-step-by-step-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeltaGNN: Graph Neural Network with Information Flow Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deltagnn-graph-neural-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) are popular deep learning models designed to process graph-structured data through recursive neighborhood aggregations in the message passing process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deltagnn-graph-neural-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Partial Cycle-Consistency for Multi-View Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-partial-cycle-consistency-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Matching objects across partially overlapping camera views is crucial in multi-camera systems and requires a view-invariant feature extraction network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-partial-cycle-consistency-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data driven discovery of human mobility models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-discovery-of-human-mobility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, for decades new mathematical formulas to model mobility phenomena have been scarce and usually discovered by analogy to physical processes, such as the gravity model and the radiation model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-discovery-of-human-mobility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Financial Statements Database: A firm-level collection of the universe of financial statements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/russian-financial-statements-database-a-firm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Russian Financial Statements Database (RFSD) is an open, harmonized collection of annual unconsolidated financial statements of the universe of Russian firms in 2011-2023.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/russian-financial-statements-database-a-firm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From discrete-time policies to continuous-time diffusion samplers: Asymptotic equivalences and faster training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-discrete-time-policies-to-continuous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of training neural stochastic differential equations, or diffusion models, to sample from a Boltzmann distribution without access to target samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-discrete-time-policies-to-continuous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Reversible Consistency Learning for Cross-modal Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-reversible-consistency-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, RSC employs a Modality-invariant Representation Recasting mechanism (MRR) to recast the potential modality-invariant representations from sample semantic labels by the generalized inverse matrix of the prior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-reversible-consistency-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StructSR: Refuse Spurious Details in Real-World Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structsr-refuse-spurious-details-in-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion-based models have shown great promise in real-world image super-resolution (Real-ISR), but often generate content with structural errors and spurious texture details due to the empirical priors and illusions of these models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structsr-refuse-spurious-details-in-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAMER: A Test-Time Adaptive MoE-Driven Framework for EHR Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tamer-a-test-time-adaptive-moe-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose TAMER, a Test-time Adaptive MoE-driven framework for EHR Representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tamer-a-test-time-adaptive-moe-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valley2: Exploring Multimodal Models with Scalable Vision-Language Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valley2-exploring-multimodal-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, vision-language models have made remarkable progress, demonstrating outstanding capabilities in various tasks such as image captioning and video understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valley2-exploring-multimodal-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evidential Deep Learning for Uncertainty Quantification and Out-of-Distribution Detection in Jet Identification using Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evidential-deep-learning-for-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These studies illustrate a methodological approach to interpreting EDL in jet classification models, providing new insights on how EDL quantifies uncertainty and detects out-of-distribution data which may lead to improved EDL methods for DL models applied to classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evidential-deep-learning-for-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>kANNolo: Sweet and Smooth Approximate k-Nearest Neighbors Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kannolo-sweet-and-smooth-approximate-k</link>
      <description><![CDATA[kANNolo is the first ANN library that supports dense and sparse vector representations made available on top of different similarity measures, e. g., euclidean distance and inner product.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kannolo-sweet-and-smooth-approximate-k</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Backdoor Stealthiness in Model Parameter Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-backdoor-stealthiness-in-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To answer this question, we examine 12 common backdoor attacks that focus on input-space or feature-space stealthiness and 17 diverse representative defenses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-backdoor-stealthiness-in-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Enzyme Function Prediction via Residue-Level Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-enzyme-function-prediction-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It uses a set of learnable functional queries to adaptatively extract different local representations from the sequence of residue-level features for predicting different EC numbers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-enzyme-function-prediction-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poetry in Pixels: Prompt Tuning for Poem Image Generation via Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poetry-in-pixels-prompt-tuning-for-poem-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging this dataset alongside PoemSum, we conducted both quantitative and qualitative evaluations of image generation using our PoemToPixel framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poetry-in-pixels-prompt-tuning-for-poem-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Impact of Human Feedback via Influence Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-impact-of-human-feedback-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By quantifying the impact of human feedback on reward models, we believe that influence functions can enhance feedback interpretability and contribute to scalable oversight in RLHF, helping labelers provide more accurate and consistent feedback.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-impact-of-human-feedback-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alignment without Over-optimization: Training-Free Solution for Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignment-without-over-optimization-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models excel in generative tasks, but aligning them with specific objectives while maintaining their versatility remains challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignment-without-over-optimization-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TB-Bench: Training and Testing Multi-Modal AI for Understanding Spatio-Temporal Traffic Behaviors from Dashcam Images/Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tb-bench-training-and-testing-multi-modal-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, this study represents a step forward by introducing a comprehensive benchmark, high-quality datasets, and baselines, thus supporting the gradual integration of MLLMs into the perception, prediction, and planning stages of AD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tb-bench-training-and-testing-multi-modal-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Neighbor-based Approach to Pitch Ownership Models in Soccer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neighbor-based-approach-to-pitch-ownership</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pitch ownership models allow many types of analysis in soccer and provide valuable assistance to tactical analysts in understanding the game's dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neighbor-based-approach-to-pitch-ownership</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELENA: Epigenetic Learning through Evolved Neural Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elena-epigenetic-learning-through-evolved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the success of metaheuristic algorithms in solving complex network optimization problems, they often struggle with adaptation, especially in dynamic or high-dimensional search spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elena-epigenetic-learning-through-evolved</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Averaged Adam accelerates stochastic optimization in the training of deep neural network approximations for partial differential equation and optimal control problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/averaged-adam-accelerates-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning methods - usually consisting of a class of deep neural networks (DNNs) trained by a stochastic gradient descent (SGD) optimization method - are nowadays omnipresent in data-driven learning problems as well as in scientific computing tasks such as optimal control (OC) and partial differential equation (PDE) problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/averaged-adam-accelerates-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Federated Bayesian Causal Inference and Its Application in Advanced Manufacturing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-federated-bayesian-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal inference has recently gained notable attention across various fields like biology, healthcare, and environmental science, especially within explainable artificial intelligence (xAI) systems, for uncovering the causal relationships among multiple variables and outcomes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-federated-bayesian-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pose-independent 3D Anthropometry from Sparse Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-independent-3d-anthropometry-from-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that our method achieves comparable results to competing methods that use dense geometry in the standard A-pose, but has the capability of estimating the body measurements from any pose using sparse landmarks only.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-independent-3d-anthropometry-from-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HFMF: Hierarchical Fusion Meets Multi-Stream Models for Deepfake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hfmf-hierarchical-fusion-meets-multi-stream</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first component of our approach integrates vision Transformers and convolutional nets through a hierarchical feature fusion mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hfmf-hierarchical-fusion-meets-multi-stream</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Tune a Multilingual Encoder Model for Germanic Languages: A Study of PEFT, Full Fine-Tuning, and Language Adapters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-tune-a-multilingual-encoder-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the optimal use of the multilingual encoder model mDeBERTa for tasks in three Germanic languages -- German, Swedish, and Icelandic -- representing varying levels of presence and likely data quality in mDeBERTas pre-training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-tune-a-multilingual-encoder-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExPO: Explainable Phonetic Trait-Oriented Network for Speaker Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expo-explainable-phonetic-trait-oriented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we investigate phonetic traits from within-speaker and between-speaker variation perspectives to determine which trait is most effective for speaker verification, marking an important step towards explainable speaker verification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expo-explainable-phonetic-trait-oriented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to generate feasible graphs using graph grammars</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generate-feasible-graphs-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Currently, a large class of generative approaches for graphs, such as methods based on artificial neural networks, is based on message passing schemes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generate-feasible-graphs-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multimodal Dataset for Enhancing Industrial Task Monitoring and Engagement Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multimodal-dataset-for-enhancing-industrial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting and interpreting operator actions, engagement, and object interactions in dynamic industrial workflows remains a significant challenge in human-robot collaboration research, especially within complex, real-world environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multimodal-dataset-for-enhancing-industrial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-class guided Transformer for Zero-Shot Attribute Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-class-guided-transformer-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose Super-class guided transFormer (SugaFormer), a novel framework that leverages super-classes to enhance scalability and generalizability for zero-shot attribute classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-class-guided-transformer-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Unsupervised Graph Few-shot Learning via Set Functions and Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-unsupervised-graph-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph few-shot learning has garnered significant attention for its ability to rapidly adapt to downstream tasks with limited labeled data, sparking considerable interest among researchers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-unsupervised-graph-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merging Feed-Forward Sublayers for Compressed Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merging-feed-forward-sublayers-for-compressed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With our method, we demonstrate performance comparable to the original models while combining more than a third of model feed-forward sublayers, and demonstrate improved performance over a strong layer-pruning baseline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merging-feed-forward-sublayers-for-compressed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervision policies can shape long-term risk management in general-purpose AI models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervision-policies-can-shape-long-term-risk</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid proliferation and deployment of General-Purpose AI (GPAI) models, including large language models (LLMs), present unprecedented challenges for AI supervisory entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervision-policies-can-shape-long-term-risk</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIGHT: A globally distributed multimodal building damage assessment dataset with very-high-resolution for all-weather disaster response</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bright-a-globally-distributed-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a BDA dataset using veRy-hIGH-resoluTion optical and SAR imagery (BRIGHT) to support AI-based all-weather disaster response.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bright-a-globally-distributed-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orthogonal projection-based regularization for efficient model augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orthogonal-projection-based-regularization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep-learning-based nonlinear system identification has shown the ability to produce reliable and highly accurate models in practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orthogonal-projection-based-regularization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TakuNet: an Energy-Efficient CNN for Real-Time Inference on Embedded UAV systems in Emergency Response Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/takunet-an-energy-efficient-cnn-for-real-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing efficient neural networks for embedded devices is a critical challenge, particularly in applications requiring real-time performance, such as aerial imaging with drones and UAVs for emergency responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/takunet-an-energy-efficient-cnn-for-real-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>rmlnomogram: An R package to construct an explainable nomogram for any machine learning algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmlnomogram-an-r-package-to-construct-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conclusions: Our R package and web application could construct nomogram with model explainability of any ML algorithms using a fair number of predictors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmlnomogram-an-r-package-to-construct-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Language Model Learning on Text Data Without User Identifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-language-model-learning-on-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many practical natural language applications, user data are highly sensitive, requiring anonymous uploads of text data from mobile devices to the cloud without user identifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-language-model-learning-on-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing Domain Shift via Imbalance-Aware Domain Adaptation in Embryo Development Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-domain-shift-via-imbalance-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning models in medical imaging face dual challenges: domain shift, where models perform poorly when deployed in settings different from their training environment, and class imbalance, where certain disease conditions are naturally underrepresented.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-domain-shift-via-imbalance-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battling the Non-stationarity in Time Series Forecasting via Test-time Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/battling-the-non-stationarity-in-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Neural Networks have spearheaded remarkable advancements in time series forecasting (TSF), one of the major tasks in time series modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/battling-the-non-stationarity-in-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search-o1: Agentic Search-Enhanced Large Reasoning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/search-o1-agentic-search-enhanced-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we introduce \textbf{Search-o1}, a framework that enhances LRMs with an agentic retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) mechanism and a Reason-in-Documents module for refining retrieved documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/search-o1-agentic-search-enhanced-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GAN is dead; long live the GAN! A Modern GAN Baseline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-gan-is-dead-long-live-the-gan-a-modern</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a widely-spread claim that GANs are difficult to train, and GAN architectures in the literature are littered with empirical tricks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-gan-is-dead-long-live-the-gan-a-modern</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$DPF^*$: improved Depth Potential Function for scale-invariant sulcal depth estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpf-improved-depth-potential-function-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The shape of human brain is complex and highly variable, with interactions between brain size, cortical folding, and age well-documented in the literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpf-improved-depth-potential-function-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning In-Distribution Representations for Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-in-distribution-representations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that FIRM surpasses other contrastive methods in standard benchmarks, significantly enhancing anomaly detection compared to both traditional and supervised contrastive learning objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-in-distribution-representations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compression with Global Guidance: Towards Training-free High-Resolution MLLMs Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compression-with-global-guidance-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal large language models (MLLMs) have attracted considerable attention due to their exceptional performance in visual content understanding and reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compression-with-global-guidance-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparison Study: Glacier Calving Front Delineation in Synthetic Aperture Radar Images With Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-study-glacier-calving-front</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Calving front position variation of marine-terminating glaciers is an indicator of ice mass loss and a crucial parameter in numerical glacier models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-study-glacier-calving-front</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
