<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 21:07:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Post-Processing of Audio Event Detectors Using Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-post-processing-of-audio-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply post-processing to the class probability distribution outputs of audio event classification models and employ reinforcement learning to jointly discover the optimal parameters for various stages of a post-processing stack, such as the classification thresholds and the kernel sizes of median filtering algorithms used to smooth out model predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-post-processing-of-audio-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniCausal: Unified Benchmark and Model for Causal Text Mining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unicausal-unified-benchmark-and-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we proposed UniCausal, a unified benchmark for causal text mining across three tasks: Causal Sequence Classification, Cause-Effect Span Detection and Causal Pair Classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unicausal-unified-benchmark-and-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafting Monocular Cues and Velocity Guidance for Self-Supervised Multi-Frame Depth Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crafting-monocular-cues-and-velocity-guidance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, multi-frame depth estimation methods improve the depth accuracy thanks to the success of Multi-View Stereo (MVS), which directly makes use of geometric constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crafting-monocular-cues-and-velocity-guidance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold Diffusion: Inverting Arbitrary Image Transforms Without Noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cold-diffusion-inverting-arbitrary-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that the generative behavior of diffusion models is not strongly dependent on the choice of image degradation, and in fact an entire family of generative models can be constructed by varying this choice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cold-diffusion-inverting-arbitrary-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UKP-SQuARE v2 Explainability and Adversarial Attacks for Trustworthy QA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ukp-square-v2-explainability-and-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce SQuARE v2, the new version of SQuARE, to provide an explainability infrastructure for comparing models based on methods such as saliency maps and graph-based explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ukp-square-v2-explainability-and-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ginex: SSD-enabled Billion-scale Graph Neural Network Training on a Single Machine via Provably Optimal In-memory Caching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ginex-ssd-enabled-billion-scale-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we propose Ginex, the first SSD-based GNN training system that can process billion-scale graph datasets on a single machine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ginex-ssd-enabled-billion-scale-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-based Time Series Imputation and Forecasting with Structured State Space Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-time-series-imputation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The imputation of missing values represents a significant obstacle for many real-world data analysis pipelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-time-series-imputation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyMIC: A deep learning toolkit for annotation-efficient medical image segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pymic-a-deep-learning-toolkit-for-annotation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim to develop a new deep learning toolkit to support annotation-efficient learning for medical image segmentation, which can accelerate and simply the development of deep learning models with limited annotation budget, e. g., learning from partial, sparse or noisy annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pymic-a-deep-learning-toolkit-for-annotation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverse Video Captioning by Adaptive Spatio-temporal Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-video-captioning-by-adaptive-spatio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To generate proper captions for videos, the inference needs to identify relevant concepts and pay attention to the spatial relationships between them as well as to the temporal development in the clip.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-video-captioning-by-adaptive-spatio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAFARI: Versatile and Efficient Evaluations for Robustness of Interpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safari-versatile-and-efficient-evaluations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interpretability of Deep Learning (DL) models is arguably the barrier in front of trustworthy AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safari-versatile-and-efficient-evaluations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Unsupervised Short- and Long-Term Mask Representation for Multivariate Time Series Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-unsupervised-short-and-long-term-mask</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Anomaly detection of multivariate time series is meaningful for system behavior monitoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-unsupervised-short-and-long-term-mask</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dialogue Policies for Confusion Mitigation in Situated HRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialogue-policies-for-confusion-mitigation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Confusion is a mental state triggered by cognitive disequilibrium that can occur in many types of task-oriented interaction, including Human-Robot Interaction (HRI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialogue-policies-for-confusion-mitigation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expressing Multivariate Time Series as Graphs with Time Series Attention Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressing-multivariate-time-series-as-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further visualize the embedded dynamic graphs to illustrate the graph representation power of TSAT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressing-multivariate-time-series-as-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curbing Task Interference using Representation Similarity-Guided Multi-Task Feature Sharing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curbing-task-interference-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, increased sharing exposes more parameters to task interference which likely hinders both generalization and robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curbing-task-interference-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Temporal Graph Attention Network for Skeleton-Based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-temporal-graph-attention-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In such conditions, short-term dependencies are few formally considered, which are critical for classifying similar actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-temporal-graph-attention-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAuLT: Augmenting the Vision-and-Language Transformer with the Propagation of Deep Language Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vault-augmenting-the-vision-and-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[VAuLT is an extension of the popular Vision-and-Language Transformer (ViLT), and improves performance on vision-and-language tasks that involve more complex text inputs than image captions while having minimal impact on training and inference efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vault-augmenting-the-vision-and-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadows Aren't So Dangerous After All: A Fast and Robust Defense Against Shadow-Based Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadows-aren-t-so-dangerous-after-all-a-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust classification is essential in tasks like autonomous vehicle sign recognition, where the downsides of misclassification can be grave.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadows-aren-t-so-dangerous-after-all-a-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musika! Fast Infinite Waveform Music Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musika-fast-infinite-waveform-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We release the source code and pretrained autoencoder weights at github. com/marcoppasini/musika, such that a GAN can be trained on a new music domain with a single GPU in a matter of hours.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musika-fast-infinite-waveform-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFLA: Gaussian Receptive Field based Label Assignment for Tiny Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rfla-gaussian-receptive-field-based-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, instead of assigning samples with IoU or center sampling strategy, a new Receptive Field Distance (RFD) is proposed to directly measure the similarity between the Gaussian receptive field and ground truth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rfla-gaussian-receptive-field-based-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-distribution Detection via Frequency-regularized Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-via-frequency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, generative models are shown to overly rely on the background information to estimate the likelihood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-via-frequency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reproducibility Report: Contrastive Learning of Socially-aware Motion Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducibility-report-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The following paper is a reproducibility report for "Social NCE: Contrastive Learning of Socially-aware Motion Representations" {\cite{liu2020snce}} published in ICCV 2021 as part of the ML Reproducibility Challenge 2021.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducibility-report-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Session Contexts for Next-Item Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-session-contexts-for-next-item</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Session-based recommender systems capture the short-term interest of a user within a session.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-session-contexts-for-next-item</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Monte Carlo a bad sampling strategy for learning smooth functions in high dimensions?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-monte-carlo-a-bad-sampling-strategy-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that there is a least-squares scheme based on $m$ MC samples whose error decays algebraically fast in $m/\log(m)$, with a rate that is the same as that of the best $n$-term polynomial approximation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-monte-carlo-a-bad-sampling-strategy-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Visual Perception by Dispersible Points Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-visual-perception-by-dispersible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The method, called UniHead, views different visual perception tasks as the dispersible points learning via the transformer encoder architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-visual-perception-by-dispersible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restoration of User Videos Shared on Social Media</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/restoration-of-user-videos-shared-on-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new general video restoration framework for the restoration of user videos shared on social media platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/restoration-of-user-videos-shared-on-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine learning algorithms for three-dimensional mean-curvature computation in the level-set method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-algorithms-for-three</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a data-driven mean-curvature solver for the level-set method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-algorithms-for-three</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Challenges and opportunities in applying Neural Temporal Point Processes to large scale industry data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenges-and-opportunities-in-applying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we identify open research opportunities in applying Neural Temporal Point Process (NTPP) models to industry scale customer behavior data by carefully reproducing NTPP models published up to date on known literature benchmarks as well as applying NTPP models to a novel, real world consumer behavior dataset that is twice as large as the largest publicly available NTPP benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenges-and-opportunities-in-applying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Pursuit Control based on Gaussian Processes with Switched Motion Trajectories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-pursuit-control-based-on-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper considers a scenario of pursuing a moving target that may switch behaviors due to external factors in a dynamic environment by motion estimation using visual sensors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-pursuit-control-based-on-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L3: Accelerator-Friendly Lossless Image Format for High-Resolution, High-Throughput DNN Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l3-accelerator-friendly-lossless-image-format</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The decoding process of L3 is effectively parallelized on the accelerator, thus minimizing CPU intervention for data preparation during DNN training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l3-accelerator-friendly-lossless-image-format</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Two-stream Convolutional Network for Musculoskeletal and Neurological Disorders Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-stream-convolutional-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, we propose a solution that explicitly takes both individual joint features and inter-joint features as input, relieving the system from the need of discovering more complicated features from small data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-stream-convolutional-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Up-Sampling for Asynchronous Events</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-up-sampling-for-asynchronous-events</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main idea of our algorithm is to generate up-sampling events on the event motion trajectory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-up-sampling-for-asynchronous-events</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quality issues in Machine Learning Software Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quality-issues-in-machine-learning-software</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This empirical study aims to identify a catalog of bad-practices related to poor quality in MLSSs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quality-issues-in-machine-learning-software</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Re-Ranking with a Corpus Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-re-ranking-with-a-corpus-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Search systems often employ a re-ranking pipeline, wherein documents (or passages) from an initial pool of candidates are assigned new ranking scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-re-ranking-with-a-corpus-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Spatial-Frequency Transformer for Visual Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-spatial-frequency-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To handle these issues, in this paper, we propose a unified Spatial-Frequency Transformer that models the Gaussian spatial Prior and High-frequency emphasis Attention (GPHA) simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-spatial-frequency-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Two-Way Selection Preference for Person-Job Fit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-two-way-selection-preference-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To model the two-way selection preference from the dual-perspective of job seekers and employers, we incorporate two different nodes for each candidate (or job) and characterize both successful matching and failed matching via a unified dual-perspective interaction graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-two-way-selection-preference-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mere Contrastive Learning for Cross-Domain Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mere-contrastive-learning-for-cross-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-domain sentiment analysis aims to predict the sentiment of texts in the target domain using the model trained on the source domain to cope with the scarcity of labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mere-contrastive-learning-for-cross-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Sentiment and Common Sense for Zero-shot Stance Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-sentiment-and-common-sense-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, ablation studies prove the significance of each module in our model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-sentiment-and-common-sense-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KuaiRand: An Unbiased Sequential Recommendation Dataset with Randomly Exposed Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kuairand-an-unbiased-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate model learning, we further collect rich features of users and items as well as users' behavior history.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kuairand-an-unbiased-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Algorithmic Framework for Distributed Adaptive Signal and Feature Fusion Problems -- Part I: Algorithm Derivation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-algorithmic-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper focuses on the algorithm derivation of the DASF framework along with simulations demonstrating its performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-algorithmic-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Representation Learning for the Automatic Indexing of Sound Effects Libraries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-learning-for-the-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Labeling and maintaining a commercial sound effects library is a time-consuming task exacerbated by databases that continually grow in size and undergo taxonomy updates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-learning-for-the-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transcending XAI Algorithm Boundaries through End-User-Inspired Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transcending-xai-algorithm-boundaries-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using the explanation forms, we then conduct a user study with 32 layperson participants in the context of achieving different explanation goals (such as verifying AI decisions, and improving user's predicted outcomes) in four critical tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transcending-xai-algorithm-boundaries-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind the Gap in Distilling StyleGANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-the-gap-in-distilling-stylegans</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further enhance the semantic consistency between the teacher and student model, we present a latent-direction-based distillation loss that preserves the semantic relations in latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-the-gap-in-distilling-stylegans</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCNNV-19: Uma rede neural convolucional profunda para detecção de COVID-19 em tomografias computadorizadas torácicas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcnnv-19-uma-rede-neural-convolucional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This technical report proposes the use of a deep convolutional neural network as a preliminary diagnostic method in the analysis of chest computed tomography images from patients with symptoms of Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome (SARS) and suspected COVID-19 disease, especially on occasions when the delay of the RT-PCR result and the absence of urgent care could result in serious temporary, long-term, or permanent health damage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcnnv-19-uma-rede-neural-convolucional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConMatch: Semi-Supervised Learning with Confidence-Guided Consistency Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conmatch-semi-supervised-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel semi-supervised learning framework that intelligently leverages the consistency regularization between the model's predictions from two strongly-augmented views of an image, weighted by a confidence of pseudo-label, dubbed ConMatch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conmatch-semi-supervised-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient data-driven gap filling of satellite image time series using deep neural networks with partial convolutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-data-driven-gap-filling-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on previous work in computer vision on image inpainting, this paper shows how three-dimensional spatiotemporal partial convolutions can be used as layers in neural networks to fill gaps in satellite image time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-data-driven-gap-filling-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSportradar-v1: Computer Vision Dataset for Sports Understanding with High Quality Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepsportradar-v1-computer-vision-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the recent development of Deep Learning applied to Computer Vision, sport video understanding has gained a lot of attention, providing much richer information for both sport consumers and leagues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepsportradar-v1-computer-vision-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer Encoder for Social Science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-encoder-for-social-science</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a compact pretrained deep neural network, Transformer Encoder for Social Science (TESS), explicitly designed to tackle text processing tasks in social science research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-encoder-for-social-science</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Lecture Presentations Dataset: Understanding Multimodality in Educational Slides</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-lecture-presentations-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a step toward developing AI to aid in student learning as intelligent teacher assistants, we introduce the Multimodal Lecture Presentations dataset as a large-scale benchmark testing the capabilities of machine learning models in multimodal understanding of educational content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-lecture-presentations-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Incomplete Multi-view Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-incomplete-multi-view-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in practical applications, such as disease diagnosis, multimedia analysis, and recommendation system, it is common to observe that not all views of samples are available in many cases, which leads to the failure of the conventional multi-view clustering methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-incomplete-multi-view-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Position-aware Structure Learning for Graph Topology-imbalance by Relieving Under-reaching and Over-squashing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-aware-structure-learning-for-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topology-imbalance is a graph-specific imbalance problem caused by the uneven topology positions of labeled nodes, which significantly damages the performance of GNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-aware-structure-learning-for-graph</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
