<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 21:06:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic bSDD: Improving the GraphQL, JSON and RDF Representations of buildingSmart Data Dictionary</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-bsdd-improving-the-graphql-json-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The buildingSmart Data Dictionary (bSDD) is an important shared resource in the Architecture, Engineering, Construction, and Operations (AECO) domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-bsdd-improving-the-graphql-json-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ladder Fine-tuning approach for SAM integrating complementary network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ladder-fine-tuning-approach-for-sam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Currently, ongoing research focuses on exploring the effective utilization of these generalized models for specific domains, such as medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ladder-fine-tuning-approach-for-sam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftGPT: Learn Goal-oriented Soft Object Manipulation Skills by Generative Pre-trained Heterogeneous Graph Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softgpt-learn-goal-oriented-soft-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Soft object manipulation tasks in domestic scenes pose a significant challenge for existing robotic skill learning techniques due to their complex dynamics and variable shape characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softgpt-learn-goal-oriented-soft-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Word Models to World Models: Translating from Natural Language to the Probabilistic Language of Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-word-models-to-world-models-translating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose \textit{rational meaning construction}, a computational framework for language-informed thinking that combines neural models of language with probabilistic models for rational inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-word-models-to-world-models-translating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Semantic Segmentation: Strong Adversarial Attacks and Fast Training of Robust Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-semantic-segmentation-strong</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While a large amount of work has focused on designing adversarial attacks against image classifiers, only a few methods exist to attack semantic segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-semantic-segmentation-strong</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifying and Extracting Rare Disease Phenotypes with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-and-extracting-rare-disease</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite this, ChatGPT achieved similar or higher accuracy for certain entities (i. e., rare diseases and signs) in the one-shot setting (F1 of 0. 776 and 0. 725).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-and-extracting-rare-disease</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Solution of Portfolio Optimization Problems via Dimension Reduction and Sparsification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-solution-of-portfolio-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The size reduction is based on predictions from machine learning techniques and the solution to a linear programming problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-solution-of-portfolio-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating SNN Training with Stochastic Parallelizable Spiking Neurons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-snn-training-with-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the Stochastic Parallelizable Spiking Neuron (SPSN) to overcome the sequential training limitation of LIF neurons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-snn-training-with-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class-Incremental Learning based on Label Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-incremental-learning-based-on-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the great success of pre-trained language models, it is still a challenge to use these models for continual learning, especially for the class-incremental learning (CIL) setting due to catastrophic forgetting (CF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-incremental-learning-based-on-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AugDMC: Data Augmentation Guided Deep Multiple Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augdmc-data-augmentation-guided-deep-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thereafter, multiple clusterings based on different aspects of the data can be obtained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augdmc-data-augmentation-guided-deep-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affine Correspondences between Multi-Camera Systems for Relative Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affine-correspondences-between-multi-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel method to compute the relative pose of multi-camera systems using two affine correspondences (ACs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affine-correspondences-between-multi-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squeeze, Recover and Relabel: Dataset Condensation at ImageNet Scale From A New Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/squeeze-recover-and-relabel-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new dataset condensation framework termed Squeeze, Recover and Relabel (SRe$^2$L) that decouples the bilevel optimization of model and synthetic data during training, to handle varying scales of datasets, model architectures and image resolutions for effective dataset condensation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/squeeze-recover-and-relabel-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimalist and High-Quality Panoramic Imaging with PSF-aware Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimalist-and-high-quality-panoramic-imaging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Panoramic Computational Imaging Engine (PCIE) to address minimalist and high-quality panoramic imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimalist-and-high-quality-panoramic-imaging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-Resolution of BVOC Emission Maps Via Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolution-of-bvoc-emission-maps-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our work, we aim at super-resolving low resolution emission maps derived from satellite observations by leveraging the information of emission maps obtained through numerical simulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolution-of-bvoc-emission-maps-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Mixing for Writer Retrieval and Identification on Papyri Fragments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-mixing-for-writer-retrieval-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a deep-learning-based approach to writer retrieval and identification for papyri, with a focus on identifying fragments associated with a specific writer and those corresponding to the same image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-mixing-for-writer-retrieval-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Discrimination Report Card</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-discrimination-report-card</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop an Empirical Bayes grading scheme that balances the informativeness of the assigned grades against the expected frequency of ranking errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-discrimination-report-card</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Mixed Offline Reinforcement Learning Datasets via Trajectory Weighting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-mixed-offline-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This re-weighted sampling strategy may be combined with any offline RL algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-mixed-offline-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Bernstein Change Detector for High-Dimensional Data Streams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-bernstein-change-detector-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In high-dimensional data, change detectors should not only be able to identify when changes happen, but also in which subspace they occur.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-bernstein-change-detector-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Exploring Node-feature and Graph-structure Diversities for Node Drop Graph Pooling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-exploring-node-feature-and-graph-structure-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A pooling operation is essential for effective graph-level representation learning, where the node drop pooling has become one mainstream graph pooling technology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-exploring-node-feature-and-graph-structure-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond OOD State Actions: Supported Cross-Domain Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-ood-state-actions-supported-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Offline reinforcement learning (RL) aims to learn a policy using only pre-collected and fixed data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-ood-state-actions-supported-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XAI-TRIS: Non-linear benchmarks to quantify ML explanation performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xai-tris-non-linear-benchmarks-to-quantify-ml</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of 'explainable' artificial intelligence (XAI) has produced highly cited methods that seek to make the decisions of complex machine learning (ML) methods 'understandable' to humans, for example by attributing 'importance' scores to input features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xai-tris-non-linear-benchmarks-to-quantify-ml</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyKoopman: A Python Package for Data-Driven Approximation of the Koopman Operator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pykoopman-a-python-package-for-data-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PyKoopman is a Python package for the data-driven approximation of the Koopman operator associated with a dynamical system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pykoopman-a-python-package-for-data-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Interactive Interface for Novel Class Discovery in Tabular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-interactive-interface-for-novel-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This task is difficult and can often only be performed by a domain expert.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-interactive-interface-for-novel-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OptIForest: Optimal Isolation Forest for Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optiforest-optimal-isolation-forest-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on a series of benchmarking datasets for comparative and ablation studies demonstrate that our approach can efficiently and robustly achieve better detection performance in general than the state-of-the-arts including the deep learning based methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optiforest-optimal-isolation-forest-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MFCCGAN: A Novel MFCC-Based Speech Synthesizer Using Adversarial Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mfccgan-a-novel-mfcc-based-speech-synthesizer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluated the model based on a popular intrusive objective speech intelligibility measure (STOI) and quality (NISQA score).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mfccgan-a-novel-mfcc-based-speech-synthesizer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't be so Monotone: Relaxing Stochastic Line Search in Over-Parameterized Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-be-so-monotone-relaxing-stochastic-line</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works have shown that line search methods can speed up Stochastic Gradient Descent (SGD) and Adam in modern over-parameterized settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-be-so-monotone-relaxing-stochastic-line</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Representations for Relation Prediction in Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-representations-for-relation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose SEEK, a novel approach for explainable representations to support relation prediction in knowledge graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-representations-for-relation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Scale-Up ExpansionIoU and Deep Features Association for Multi-Object Tracking in Sports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-scale-up-expansioniou-and-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to this reason, we proposed a novel online and robust multi-object tracking approach, named Iterative Scale-Up ExpansionIoU and Deep Features for multi-object tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-scale-up-expansioniou-and-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Knowledge Switching for Pancreas Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-knowledge-switching-for-pancreas</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pancreas segmentation is challenging due to the small proportion and highly changeable anatomical structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-knowledge-switching-for-pancreas</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highly accurate and efficient deep learning paradigm for full-atom protein loop modeling with KarmaLoop</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/highly-accurate-and-efficient-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Protein loop modeling is the most challenging yet highly non-trivial task in protein structure prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/highly-accurate-and-efficient-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1st Place Solution to MultiEarth 2023 Challenge on Multimodal SAR-to-EO Image Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1st-place-solution-to-multiearth-2023</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Multimodal Learning for Earth and Environment Workshop (MultiEarth 2023) aims to harness the substantial amount of remote sensing data gathered over extensive periods for the monitoring and analysis of Earth's ecosystems'health.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1st-place-solution-to-multiearth-2023</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StrainNet: Predicting crystal structure elastic properties using SE(3)-equivariant graph neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strainnet-predicting-crystal-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurately predicting the elastic properties of crystalline solids is vital for computational materials science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strainnet-predicting-crystal-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptIR: Prompting for All-in-One Blind Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptir-prompting-for-all-in-one-blind-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a prompt-based learning approach, PromptIR, for All-In-One image restoration that can effectively restore images from various types and levels of degradation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptir-prompting-for-all-in-one-blind-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the use of the Gram matrix for multivariate functional principal components analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-of-the-gram-matrix-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dimension reduction is crucial in functional data analysis (FDA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-of-the-gram-matrix-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Discrimination in Insurance with Wasserstein Barycenters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-discrimination-in-insurance-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given that such discrimination can often be attributed to historical data biases, an elimination or at least mitigation is desirable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-discrimination-in-insurance-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xSIM++: An Improved Proxy to Bitext Mining Performance for Low-Resource Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xsim-an-improved-proxy-to-bitext-mining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In comparison to xSIM, we show that xSIM++ is better correlated with the downstream BLEU scores of translation systems trained on mined bitexts, providing a reliable proxy of bitext mining performance without needing to run expensive bitext mining pipelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xsim-an-improved-proxy-to-bitext-mining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitted Value Iteration Methods for Bicausal Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fitted-value-iteration-methods-for-bicausal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a fitted value iteration (FVI) method to compute bicausal optimal transport (OT) where couplings have an adapted structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fitted-value-iteration-methods-for-bicausal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling Global Narratives: A Multilingual Twitter Dataset of News Media on the Russo-Ukrainian Conflict</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-global-narratives-a-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ongoing Russo-Ukrainian conflict has been a subject of intense media coverage worldwide.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-global-narratives-a-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Robust and Multilingual Automatic Evaluation Metrics for Open-Domain Dialogue Systems at DSTC 11 Track 4</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overview-of-robust-and-multilingual-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advent and fast development of neural networks have revolutionized the research on dialogue systems and subsequently have triggered various challenges regarding their automatic evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overview-of-robust-and-multilingual-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HypeRS: Building a Hypergraph-driven ensemble Recommender System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypers-building-a-hypergraph-driven-ensemble</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel ensemble recommender system that combines predictions made by different models into a unified hypergraph ranking framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypers-building-a-hypergraph-driven-ensemble</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evading Forensic Classifiers with Attribute-Conditioned Adversarial Faces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evading-forensic-classifiers-with-attribute-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While these forensic models can detect whether a face image is synthetic or real with high accuracy, they are also vulnerable to adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evading-forensic-classifiers-with-attribute-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying lottery tickets under label noise: accuracy, calibration, and complexity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-lottery-tickets-under-label-noise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pruning deep neural networks is a widely used strategy to alleviate the computational burden in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-lottery-tickets-under-label-noise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Heterophily Aware Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-heterophily-aware-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, urban graphs usually can be observed to possess a unique spatial heterophily property; that is, the dissimilarity of neighbors at different spatial distances can exhibit great diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-heterophily-aware-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding human mobility patterns in Chicago: an analysis of taxi data using clustering techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-human-mobility-patterns-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This analysis will provide a sense of which neighborhoods individuals are using taxis to travel between, suggesting regions to focus new public transit development efforts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-human-mobility-patterns-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3HAN: A Deep Neural Network for Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3han-a-deep-neural-network-for-fake-news</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid spread of fake news is a serious problem calling for AI solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3han-a-deep-neural-network-for-fake-news</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving and Generating NPR Sunday Puzzles with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-and-generating-npr-sunday-puzzles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore the ability of large language models to solve and generate puzzles from the NPR Sunday Puzzle game show using PUZZLEQA, a dataset comprising 15 years of on-air puzzles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-and-generating-npr-sunday-puzzles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Conditional Instrumental Variable Representation for Causal Effect Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-conditional-instrumental-variable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the fundamental challenges in causal inference is to estimate the causal effect of a treatment on its outcome of interest from observational data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-conditional-instrumental-variable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Hierarchical Approach to exploiting Multiple Datasets from TalkBank</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hierarchical-approach-to-exploiting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TalkBank is an online database that facilitates the sharing of linguistics research data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hierarchical-approach-to-exploiting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Neural Simulation-Based Inference Over Event Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-neural-simulation-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When analyzing real-world data it is common to work with event ensembles, which comprise sets of observations that collectively constrain the parameters of an underlying model of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-neural-simulation-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Molecular Discovery with Natural Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-molecular-discovery-with-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Natural language is expected to be a key medium for various human-machine interactions in the era of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-molecular-discovery-with-natural</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
