<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 09:16:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Optimization of Oblivious Decision Tree Ensembles Evaluation for CPU</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-of-oblivious-decision-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We increase performance by 20-40% using AVX2 instructions without quality impact.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-of-oblivious-decision-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Vision-Language Models with Less Bimodal Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-vision-language-models-with-less</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We experiment with a high-performing vision-language model, and analyze the effect of bimodal supervision on three vision-language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-vision-language-models-with-less</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONDAQA: A Contrastive Reading Comprehension Dataset for Reasoning about Negation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/condaqa-a-contrastive-reading-comprehension</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also have workers make three kinds of edits to the passage -- paraphrasing the negated statement, changing the scope of the negation, and reversing the negation -- resulting in clusters of question-answer pairs that are difficult for models to answer with spurious shortcuts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/condaqa-a-contrastive-reading-comprehension</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can maker-taker fees prevent algorithmic cooperation in market making?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-maker-taker-fees-prevent-algorithmic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a semi-realistic market simulator, independent reinforcement learning algorithms may facilitate market makers to maintain wide spreads even without communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-maker-taker-fees-prevent-algorithmic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Deduction with Incomplete Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-deduction-with-incomplete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A growing body of work studies how to answer a question or verify a claim by generating a natural language "proof": a chain of deductive inferences yielding the answer based on a set of premises.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-deduction-with-incomplete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GMF: General Multimodal Fusion Framework for Correspondence Outlier Rejection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gmf-general-multimodal-fusion-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose General Multimodal Fusion (GMF) to learn to reject the correspondence outliers by leveraging both the structure and texture information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gmf-general-multimodal-fusion-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Position-Aware Subgraph Neural Networks with Data-Efficient Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-aware-subgraph-neural-networks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[2) Prevailing graph augmentation methods for GEL, including rule-based, sample-based, adaptive, and automated methods, are not suitable for augmenting subgraphs because a subgraph contains fewer nodes but richer information such as position, neighbor, and structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-aware-subgraph-neural-networks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency Cam: Imaging Periodic Signals in Real-Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-cam-imaging-periodic-signals-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discuss the important design parameters for fullsensor frequency imaging and present Frequency Cam, an open-source implementation as a ROS node that can run on a single core of a laptop CPU at more than 50 million events per second.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-cam-imaging-periodic-signals-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Imbalanced Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-imbalanced-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated Machine Learning has grown very successful in automating the time-consuming, iterative tasks of machine learning model development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-imbalanced-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapter-Based Extension of Multi-Speaker Text-to-Speech Model for New Speakers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapter-based-extension-of-multi-speaker-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the proposed approach, a few small adapter modules are added to the original network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapter-based-extension-of-multi-speaker-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech-text based multi-modal training with bidirectional attention for improved speech recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-text-based-multi-modal-training-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To let the state-of-the-art end-to-end ASR model enjoy data efficiency, as well as much more unpaired text data by multi-modal training, one needs to address two problems: 1) the synchronicity of feature sampling rates between speech and language (aka text data); 2) the homogeneity of the learned representations from two encoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-text-based-multi-modal-training-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Variational Autoencoders with Density Gap-based Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-variational-autoencoders-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are effective ways proposed to prevent posterior collapse in VAEs, but we observe that they in essence make trade-offs between posterior collapse and hole problem, i. e., mismatch between the aggregated posterior distribution and the prior distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-variational-autoencoders-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amplifying Membership Exposure via Data Poisoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amplifying-membership-exposure-via-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the third type of exploitation of data poisoning - increasing the risks of privacy leakage of benign training samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amplifying-membership-exposure-via-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Training with Complementary Labels: On the Benefit of Gradually Informative Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-training-with-complementary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial training (AT) with imperfect supervision is significant but receives limited attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-training-with-complementary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E2E Refined Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e2e-refined-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the well-known MR-to-text E2E dataset has been used by many researchers, its MR-text pairs include many deletion/insertion/substitution errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e2e-refined-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Task-Aware Effective Brain Connectivity for fMRI Analysis with Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-task-aware-effective-brain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better adapt GNNs for fMRI analysis, we propose TBDS, an end-to-end framework based on \underline{T}ask-aware \underline{B}rain connectivity \underline{D}AG (short for Directed Acyclic Graph) \underline{S}tructure generation for fMRI analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-task-aware-effective-brain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rating Triggers for Collateral-Inclusive XVA via Machine Learning and SDEs on Lie Groups</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rating-triggers-for-collateral-inclusive-xva</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we model the rating process of an entity by using a geometrical approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rating-triggers-for-collateral-inclusive-xva</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Composite Feature Selection using Deep Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composite-feature-selection-using-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To do so, we define predictive groups in terms of linear and non-linear interactions between features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composite-feature-selection-using-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARE: Causality Reasoning for Empathetic Responses by Conditional Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/care-causality-reasoning-for-empathetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent approaches to empathetic response generation incorporate emotion causalities to enhance comprehension of both the user's feelings and experiences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/care-causality-reasoning-for-empathetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Perturbation Attack on Differentiable No-Reference Image- and Video-Quality Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-perturbation-attack-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Indeed, if an attack can confuse the metric, an attacker can easily increase quality scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-perturbation-attack-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T5lephone: Bridging Speech and Text Self-supervised Models for Spoken Language Understanding via Phoneme level T5</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t5lephone-bridging-speech-and-text-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Spoken language understanding (SLU), a natural solution is concatenating pre-trained speech models (e. g. HuBERT) and pretrained language models (PLM, e. g. T5).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t5lephone-bridging-speech-and-text-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Graph Neural Network Inference at Large Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-graph-neural-network-inference-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) have demonstrated excellent performance in a wide range of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-graph-neural-network-inference-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SADT: Combining Sharpness-Aware Minimization with Self-Distillation for Improved Model Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sadt-combining-sharpness-aware-minimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods for improving deep neural network training times and model generalizability consist of various data augmentation, regularization, and optimization approaches, which tend to be sensitive to hyperparameter settings and make reproducibility more challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sadt-combining-sharpness-aware-minimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Only Training for Image Captioning using Noise-Injected CLIP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-only-training-for-image-captioning-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the task of image-captioning using only the CLIP model and additional text data at training time, and no additional captioned images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-only-training-for-image-captioning-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretability in the Wild: a Circuit for Indirect Object Identification in GPT-2 small</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretability-in-the-wild-a-circuit-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Research in mechanistic interpretability seeks to explain behaviors of machine learning models in terms of their internal components.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretability-in-the-wild-a-circuit-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and parallel decoding for transducer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-parallel-decoding-for-transducer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a constrained version of transducer loss to learn strictly monotonic alignments between the sequences; we also improve the standard greedy search and beam search algorithms by limiting the number of symbols that can be emitted per time step in transducer decoding, making it more efficient to decode in parallel with batches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-parallel-decoding-for-transducer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Close Look into the Calibration of Pre-trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-close-look-into-the-calibration-of-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the first question, we conduct fine-grained control experiments to study the dynamic change in PLMs' calibration performance in training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-close-look-into-the-calibration-of-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Pre-Training with Speech and Bilingual Text for Direct Speech to Speech Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-pre-training-with-speech-and-bilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, direct S2ST suffers from the data scarcity problem because the corpora from speech of the source language to speech of the target language are very rare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-pre-training-with-speech-and-bilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large scale traffic forecasting with gradient boosting, Traffic4cast 2022 challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-traffic-forecasting-with-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate traffic forecasting is of the utmost importance for optimal travel planning and for efficient city mobility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-traffic-forecasting-with-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARRIS: Hybrid Ranking and Regression Forests for Algorithm Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harris-hybrid-ranking-and-regression-forests</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is well known that different algorithms perform differently well on an instance of an algorithmic problem, motivating algorithm selection (AS): Given an instance of an algorithmic problem, which is the most suitable algorithm to solve it?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harris-hybrid-ranking-and-regression-forests</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Hierarchical Metrical Structure Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-hierarchical-metrical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel method to model hierarchical metrical structures for both symbolic music and audio signals in a self-supervised manner with minimal domain knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-hierarchical-metrical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Optimize Permutation Flow Shop Scheduling via Graph-based Imitation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-optimize-permutation-flow-shop</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to the state-of-the-art reinforcement learning method, our model's network parameters are reduced to only 37\% of theirs, and the solution gap of our model towards the expert solutions decreases from 6. 8\% to 1. 3\% on average.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-optimize-permutation-flow-shop</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L-GreCo: An Efficient and General Framework for Layerwise-Adaptive Gradient Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l-greco-an-efficient-and-general-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data-parallel distributed training of deep neural networks (DNN) has gained very widespread adoption, but can still experience communication bottlenecks due to gradient transmission.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l-greco-an-efficient-and-general-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Charge Prediction Models Learn Legal Theory?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-charge-prediction-models-learn-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The charge prediction task aims to predict the charge for a case given its fact description.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-charge-prediction-models-learn-legal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reduce Catastrophic Forgetting of Dense Retrieval Training with Teleportation Negatives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduce-catastrophic-forgetting-of-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the instability in the standard dense retrieval training, which iterates between model training and hard negative selection using the being-trained model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduce-catastrophic-forgetting-of-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent-Time Attention for Sparse Rewards Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-time-attention-for-sparse-rewards-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse and delayed rewards pose a challenge to single agent reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-time-attention-for-sparse-rewards-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Open MatSci ML Toolkit: A Flexible Framework for Machine Learning in Materials Science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-open-matsci-ml-toolkit-a-flexible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Open MatSci ML Toolkit: a flexible, self-contained, and scalable Python-based framework to apply deep learning models and methods on scientific data with a specific focus on materials science and the OpenCatalyst Dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-open-matsci-ml-toolkit-a-flexible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensemble transport smoothing -- Part 2: nonlinear updates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-transport-smoothing-part-2-nonlinear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Smoothing is a specialized form of Bayesian inference for state-space models that characterizes the posterior distribution of a collection of states given an associated sequence of observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-transport-smoothing-part-2-nonlinear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delay-penalized transducer for low-latency streaming ASR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delay-penalized-transducer-for-low-latency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In streaming automatic speech recognition (ASR), it is desirable to reduce latency as much as possible while having minimum impact on recognition accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delay-penalized-transducer-for-low-latency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensemble transport smoothing -- Part 1: unified framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-transport-smoothing-part-1-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A companion paper explores the implementation of nonlinear ensemble transport smoothers in greater depth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-transport-smoothing-part-1-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CausalBench: A Large-scale Benchmark for Network Inference from Single-cell Perturbation Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalbench-a-large-scale-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CausalBench introduces several biologically meaningful performance metrics and operates on two large, curated and openly available benchmark data sets for evaluating methods on the inference of gene regulatory networks from single-cell data generated under perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalbench-a-large-scale-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Text Classification with Self-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-text-classification-with-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in large pretrained language models have increased attention to zero-shot text classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-text-classification-with-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Temporal Generalization of Pre-trained Language Models with Lexical Semantic Change</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-temporal-generalization-of-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods mainly perform continual training to mitigate such a misalignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-temporal-generalization-of-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Optimal Transport Framework for Universal Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-optimal-transport-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, UniOT is the first method with the capability to automatically discover and recognize private categories in the target domain for UniDA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-optimal-transport-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiaCorrect: End-to-end error correction for speaker diarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diacorrect-end-to-end-error-correction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, speaker diarization has attracted widespread attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diacorrect-end-to-end-error-correction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPTQ: Accurate Post-Training Quantization for Generative Pre-trained Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gptq-accurate-post-training-quantization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative Pre-trained Transformer (GPT) models set themselves apart through breakthrough performance across complex language modelling tasks, but also by their extremely high computational and storage costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gptq-accurate-post-training-quantization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotional Brain State Classification on fMRI Data Using Deep Residual and Convolutional Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotional-brain-state-classification-on-fmri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then developed two distinct Convolution-based approaches to decode emotional brain states using only spatial information from single, minimally pre-processed (slice timing and realignment) fMRI volumes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotional-brain-state-classification-on-fmri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Emotion Embeddings to Transfer Knowledge Between Emotions, Languages, and Annotation Formats</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-emotion-embeddings-to-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study how we can build a single model that can transition between these different configurations by leveraging multilingual models and Demux, a transformer-based model whose input includes the emotions of interest, enabling us to dynamically change the emotions predicted by the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-emotion-embeddings-to-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 Ways to Bake a Cookie: Mapping the Landscape of Procedural Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/50-ways-to-bake-a-cookie-mapping-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The web is full of guidance on a wide variety of tasks, from changing the oil in your car to baking an apple pie.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/50-ways-to-bake-a-cookie-mapping-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Selection of the Optimal Strategy to Improve Precision and Power in Randomized Trials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-selection-of-the-optimal-strategy-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Benkeser et al. demonstrate how adjustment for baseline covariates in randomized trials can meaningfully improve precision for a variety of outcome types, including binary, ordinal, and time-to-event.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-selection-of-the-optimal-strategy-to</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
