<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 09:13:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Explainable Motion Prediction using Heterogeneous Graph Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explainable-motion-prediction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we aim to improve the explainability of motion prediction systems by using different approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explainable-motion-prediction-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconciling a Centroid-Hypothesis Conflict in Source-Free Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconciling-a-centroid-hypothesis-conflict-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose to reconcile this conflict by aligning the entropy minimization objective with that of the pseudo labels' cross entropy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconciling-a-centroid-hypothesis-conflict-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intervening With Confidence: Conformal Prescriptive Monitoring of Business Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intervening-with-confidence-conformal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prescriptive process monitoring methods seek to improve the performance of a process by selectively triggering interventions at runtime (e. g., offering a discount to a customer) to increase the probability of a desired case outcome (e. g., a customer making a purchase).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intervening-with-confidence-conformal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truthful Meta-Explanations for Local Interpretability of Machine Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truthful-meta-explanations-for-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, the demand for a selection tool, a meta-explanation technique based on a high-quality evaluation metric, is apparent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truthful-meta-explanations-for-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIAR: Harmony of Data-Centric and Model-Centric for Multi-Modality Microscopy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mediar-harmony-of-data-centric-and-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cell segmentation is a fundamental task for computational biology analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mediar-harmony-of-data-centric-and-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZegCLIP: Towards Adapting CLIP for Zero-shot Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zegclip-towards-adapting-clip-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, CLIP has been applied to pixel-level zero-shot learning tasks via a two-stage scheme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zegclip-towards-adapting-clip-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Matters: Investigating the Role of Supervision in Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-matters-investigating-the-role-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare ViTs trained through different methods of supervision, and show that they learn a diverse range of behaviors in terms of their attention, representations, and downstream performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-matters-investigating-the-role-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Latent Knowledge in Language Models Without Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-latent-knowledge-in-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing techniques for training language models can be misaligned with the truth: if we train models with imitation learning, they may reproduce errors that humans make; if we train them to generate text that humans rate highly, they may output errors that human evaluators can't detect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-latent-knowledge-in-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness and Explainability: Bridging the Gap Towards Fair Model Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-and-explainability-bridging-the-gap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although research efforts have been devoted to measuring and mitigating bias, they mainly study bias from the result-oriented perspective while neglecting the bias encoded in the decision-making procedure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-and-explainability-bridging-the-gap</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLeaD: Improving GANs with A Generator-Leading Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glead-improving-gans-with-a-generator-leading</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative adversarial network (GAN) is formulated as a two-player game between a generator (G) and a discriminator (D), where D is asked to differentiate whether an image comes from real data or is produced by G. Under such a formulation, D plays as the rule maker and hence tends to dominate the competition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glead-improving-gans-with-a-generator-leading</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Specifying Behavior Preference with Tiered Reward Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/specifying-behavior-preference-with-tiered</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, we propose an environment-independent tiered reward structure and show it is guaranteed to induce policies that are Pareto-optimal according to our preference relation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/specifying-behavior-preference-with-tiered</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIDER &amp; CLOSER: Mixture of Short-channel Distillers for Zero-shot Cross-lingual Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wider-closer-mixture-of-short-channel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, a mixture of short-channel distillers (MSD) method is proposed to fully interact the rich hierarchical information in the teacher model and to transfer knowledge to the student model sufficiently and efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wider-closer-mixture-of-short-channel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimVTP: Simple Video Text Pre-training with Masked Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simvtp-simple-video-text-pre-training-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents SimVTP: a Simple Video-Text Pretraining framework via masked autoencoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simvtp-simple-video-text-pre-training-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Generative Approach for Script Event Prediction via Contrastive Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generative-approach-for-script-event-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, the pretrained language models adopted by current works ignore event-level knowledge, resulting in an inability to capture the correlations between events well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generative-approach-for-script-event-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic Rising Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-rising-bandits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper is in the field of stochastic Multi-Armed Bandits (MABs), i. e., those sequential selection techniques able to learn online using only the feedback given by the chosen option (a. k. a.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-rising-bandits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slimmable Pruned Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slimmable-pruned-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Slimmable Neural Networks (S-Net) is a novel network which enabled to select one of the predefined proportions of channels (sub-network) dynamically depending on the current computational resource availability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slimmable-pruned-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Continuous Depth Representation via Geometric Spatial Aggregator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-continuous-depth-representation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Depth map super-resolution (DSR) has been a fundamental task for 3D computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-continuous-depth-representation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-SDF: Text-to-Shape via Voxelized Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-sdf-text-to-shape-via-voxelized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous approaches lack flexibility in both 3D data representation and shape generation, thereby failing to generate highly diversified 3D shapes conforming to the given text descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-sdf-text-to-shape-via-voxelized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FacT: Factor-Tuning for Lightweight Adaptation on Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fact-factor-tuning-for-lightweight-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work has explored the potential to adapt a pre-trained vision transformer (ViT) by updating only a few parameters so as to improve storage efficiency, called parameter-efficient transfer learning (PETL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fact-factor-tuning-for-lightweight-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-aware Message Broadcasting for Efficient Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-message-broadcasting-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this way, our message broadcasting encourages the group tokens to learn more informative and diverse information for effective domain alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-message-broadcasting-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABN: Anti-Blur Neural Networks for Multi-Stage Deformable Image Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abn-anti-blur-neural-networks-for-multi-stage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research on deformable image registration is mainly focused on improving the registration accuracy using multi-stage alignment methods, where the source image is repeatedly deformed in stages by a same neural network until it is well-aligned with the target image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abn-anti-blur-neural-networks-for-multi-stage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Testing of Computer Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-testing-of-computer-vision-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision models often fail systematically on groups of data that share common semantic characteristics (e. g., rare objects or unusual scenes), but identifying these failure modes is a challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-testing-of-computer-vision-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Next Boundary Detection for Instance Segmentation of Tree Rings in Microscopy Images of Shrub Cross Sections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-next-boundary-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze the problem of detecting tree rings in microscopy images of shrub cross sections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-next-boundary-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Document-Level Abstractive Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/document-level-abstractive-summarization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of automatic text summarization produces a concise and fluent text summary while preserving key information and overall meaning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/document-level-abstractive-summarization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Tractogram Filtering using Geometric Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-tractogram-filtering-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A tractogram is a virtual representation of the brain white matter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-tractogram-filtering-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZeroKBC: A Comprehensive Benchmark for Zero-Shot Knowledge Base Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zerokbc-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, there has been limited research on the zero-shot KBC settings, where we need to deal with unseen entities and relations that emerge in a constantly growing knowledge base.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zerokbc-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERNet: Unsupervised Collective Extraction and Registration in Neuroimaging Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ernet-unsupervised-collective-extraction-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our code and data can be found at https://github. com/ERNetERNet/ERNet]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ernet-unsupervised-collective-extraction-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternVideo: General Video Foundation Models via Generative and Discriminative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internvideo-general-video-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, InternVideo efficiently explores masked video modeling and video-language contrastive learning as the pretraining objectives, and selectively coordinates video representations of these two complementary frameworks in a learnable manner to boost various video applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internvideo-general-video-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dist-PU: Positive-Unlabeled Learning from a Label Distribution Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dist-pu-positive-unlabeled-learning-from-a-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Positive-Unlabeled (PU) learning tries to learn binary classifiers from a few labeled positive examples with many unlabeled ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dist-pu-positive-unlabeled-learning-from-a-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards human-compatible autonomous car: A study of non-verbal Turing test in automated driving with affective transition modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-human-compatible-autonomous-car-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Participants rode in autonomous cars (driven by either human or AI drivers) as a passenger and judged whether the driver was human or AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-human-compatible-autonomous-car-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loss Adapted Plasticity in Deep Neural Networks to Learn from Data with Unreliable Sources</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loss-adapted-plasticity-in-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When data is streaming from multiple sources, conventional training methods update model weights often assuming the same level of reliability for each source; that is: a model does not consider data quality of each source during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loss-adapted-plasticity-in-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking AutoML algorithms on a collection of binary problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-automl-algorithms-on-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated machine learning (AutoML) algorithms have grown in popularity due to their high performance and flexibility to adapt to different problems and data sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-automl-algorithms-on-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switching to Discriminative Image Captioning by Relieving a Bottleneck of Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/switching-to-discriminative-image-captioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Discriminativeness is a desirable feature of image captions: captions should describe the characteristic details of input images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/switching-to-discriminative-image-captioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniGeo: Unifying Geometry Logical Reasoning via Reformulating Mathematical Expression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unigeo-unifying-geometry-logical-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Naturally, we also present a unified multi-task Geometric Transformer framework, Geoformer, to tackle calculation and proving problems simultaneously in the form of sequence generation, which finally shows the reasoning ability can be improved on both two tasks by unifying formulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unigeo-unifying-geometry-logical-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FretNet: Continuous-Valued Pitch Contour Streaming for Polyphonic Guitar Tablature Transcription</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fretnet-continuous-valued-pitch-contour</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a GTT formulation that estimates continuous-valued pitch contours, grouping them according to their string and fret of origin.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fretnet-continuous-valued-pitch-contour</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Data Heterogeneity in Federated Learning with Class Prototypes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-data-heterogeneity-in-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose FedNH, a novel method that improves the local models' performance for both personalization and generalization by combining the uniformity and semantics of class prototypes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-data-heterogeneity-in-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposal of a Score Based Approach to Sampling Using Monte Carlo Estimation of Score and Oracle Access to Target Density</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proposal-of-a-score-based-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Score based approaches to sampling have shown much success as a generative algorithm to produce new samples from a target density given a pool of initial samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proposal-of-a-score-based-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust convex biclustering with a tuning-free method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-convex-biclustering-with-a-tuning-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose a tuning-free method for automatically selecting the optimal robustification parameter with high efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-convex-biclustering-with-a-tuning-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Baseline for Weather Forecasting Using Spatiotemporal Context Aggregation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-baseline-for-weather-forecasting-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional weather forecasting relies on domain expertise and computationally intensive numerical simulation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-baseline-for-weather-forecasting-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSDA3D: Semi-supervised Domain Adaptation for 3D Object Detection from Point Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssda3d-semi-supervised-domain-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these UDA solutions just yield unsatisfactory 3D detection results when there is a severe domain shift, e. g., from Waymo (64-beam) to nuScenes (32-beam).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssda3d-semi-supervised-domain-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Conditional Diffusion Networks for Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-conditional-diffusion-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rich semantics are further regarded as semantic prior to trigger the learning of Diffusion Transformer, which produces the output sentence in a diffusion process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-conditional-diffusion-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Union-set Multi-source Model Adaptation for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/union-set-multi-source-model-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model adaptation is proposed as a new domain adaptation problem which requires access to a pre-trained model instead of data for the source domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/union-set-multi-source-model-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-Bridged Causal Interaction Network for Causal Emotion Entailment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-bridged-causal-interaction-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, social-interaction CSK serves as emotion-level bridge (E-bridge) and action-level bridge (A-bridge) to connect candidate utterances with the target one, which provides explicit causal clues for the Emotional Interaction module and Actional Interaction module to reason the target emotion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-bridged-causal-interaction-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Point Cloud Segmentation with Noisy Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-point-cloud-segmentation-with-noisy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To handle boundary-level label noise, we also propose a variant ``PNAL-boundary " with a progressive boundary label cleaning strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-point-cloud-segmentation-with-noisy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PØDA: Prompt-driven Zero-shot Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poda-prompt-driven-zero-shot-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain adaptation has been vastly investigated in computer vision but still requires access to target images at train time, which might be intractable in some conditions, especially for long-tail samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poda-prompt-driven-zero-shot-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IncepFormer: Efficient Inception Transformer with Pyramid Pooling for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incepformer-efficient-inception-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation usually benefits from global contexts, fine localisation information, multi-scale features, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incepformer-efficient-inception-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffusionInst: Diffusion Model for Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusioninst-diffusion-model-for-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes DiffusionInst, a novel framework that represents instances as instance-aware filters and formulates instance segmentation as a noise-to-filter denoising process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusioninst-diffusion-model-for-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a more efficient computation of individual attribute and policy contribution for post-hoc explanation of cooperative multi-agent systems using Myerson values</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-more-efficient-computation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A quantitative assessment of the global importance of an agent in a team is as valuable as gold for strategists, decision-makers, and sports coaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-more-efficient-computation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-resolution Probabilistic Rain Prediction from Satellite Data Using 3D U-Nets and EarthFormers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolution-probabilistic-rain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further improve the model performance, multi-model ensemble and threshold optimization were used to produce the final probabilistic rain prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolution-probabilistic-rain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Machine Translation with Contrastive Translation Memories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-machine-translation-with-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-augmented Neural Machine Translation models have been successful in many translation scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-machine-translation-with-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
