<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 09:14:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-Encoding Morph-Tokens for Multimodal LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-encoding-morph-tokens-for-multimodal-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For multimodal LLMs, the synergy of visual comprehension (textual output) and generation (visual output) presents an ongoing challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-encoding-morph-tokens-for-multimodal-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe-Eval: A hard evaluation suite for measuring progress of multimodal language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vibe-eval-a-hard-evaluation-suite-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Vibe-Eval: a new open benchmark and framework for evaluating multimodal chat models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vibe-eval-a-hard-evaluation-suite-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Context Flows for Learning Generalizable Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-context-flows-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Ordinary Differential Equations typically struggle to generalize to new dynamical behaviors created by parameter changes in the underlying system, even when the dynamics are close to previously seen behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-context-flows-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Learning for Real-World Super-Resolution from Dual and Multiple Zoomed Observations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-for-real-world-super-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we further take multiple zoomed observations to explore self-supervised RefSR, and present a progressive fusion scheme for the effective utilization of reference images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-for-real-world-super-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Pre-trained Teacher: Towards Robust Feature Discrepancy for Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-pre-trained-teacher-towards-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of knowledge distillation mainly relies on how to keep the feature discrepancy between the teacher and student model, in which it assumes that: (1) the teacher model can jointly represent two different distributions for the normal and abnormal patterns, while (2) the student model can only reconstruct the normal distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-pre-trained-teacher-towards-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the test-time zero-shot generalization of vision-language models: Do we really need prompt learning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-test-time-zero-shot-generalization-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, our method does not rely on ad hoc rules (e. g., confidence threshold) used in some previous test-time augmentation techniques to filter the augmented views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-test-time-zero-shot-generalization-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Attention Based Pipeline for Identifying Pre-Cancer Lesions in Head and Neck Clinical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attention-based-pipeline-for-identifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Early detection of cancer can help improve patient prognosis by early intervention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attention-based-pipeline-for-identifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probablistic Restoration with Adaptive Noise Sampling for 3D Human Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probablistic-restoration-with-adaptive-noise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The accuracy and robustness of 3D human pose estimation (HPE) are limited by 2D pose detection errors and 2D to 3D ill-posed challenges, which have drawn great attention to Multi-Hypothesis HPE research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probablistic-restoration-with-adaptive-noise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularized Q-learning through Robust Averaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularized-q-learning-through-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new Q-learning variant, called 2RA Q-learning, that addresses some weaknesses of existing Q-learning methods in a principled manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularized-q-learning-through-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stabilizing Backpropagation Through Time to Learn Complex Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stabilizing-backpropagation-through-time-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Of all the vector fields surrounding the minima of recurrent learning setups, the gradient field with its exploding and vanishing updates appears a poor choice for optimization, offering little beyond efficient computability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stabilizing-backpropagation-through-time-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOPICAL: TOPIC Pages AutomagicaLly</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topical-topic-pages-automagically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topic pages aggregate useful information about an entity or concept into a single succinct and accessible article.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topical-topic-pages-automagically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SFFNet: A Wavelet-Based Spatial and Frequency Domain Fusion Network for Remote Sensing Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sffnet-a-wavelet-based-spatial-and-frequency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to fully utilize spatial information for segmentation and address the challenge of handling areas with significant grayscale variations in remote sensing segmentation, we propose the SFFNet (Spatial and Frequency Domain Fusion Network) framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sffnet-a-wavelet-based-spatial-and-frequency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Detection of Source Code Clones via an Ensemble of Unsupervised Similarity Measures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advanced-detection-of-source-code-clones-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The capability of accurately determining code similarity is crucial in many tasks related to software development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advanced-detection-of-source-code-clones-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinySeg: Model Optimizing Framework for Image Segmentation on Tiny Embedded Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyseg-model-optimizing-framework-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work implements TinySeg on top of the existing tiny machine learning framework and demonstrates that TinySeg can reduce the peak memory usage of an image segmentation model by 39. 3% for tiny embedded systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyseg-model-optimizing-framework-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Micro Gesture Recognition for Emotion Understanding via Context-aware Visual-Text Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-micro-gesture-recognition-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, instead of using handcrafted prompts for visual-text contrastive learning, we propose a novel module called Adaptive prompting to generate context-aware prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-micro-gesture-recognition-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Concept Alignment in Vision-Language Concept Bottleneck Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-concept-alignment-in-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concept Bottleneck Models (CBM) map the input image to a high-level human-understandable concept space and then make class predictions based on these concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-concept-alignment-in-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-level projection with exponential parallel speedup; Application to sparse auto-encoders neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-projection-with-exponential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new bi-level projection method for which we show that the time complexity for the $\ell_{1,\infty}$ norm is only $\mathcal{O}\big(n m \big)$ for a matrix in $\mathbb{R}^{n\times m}$, and $\mathcal{O}\big(n + m \big)$ with full parallel power.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-projection-with-exponential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlotGAT: Slot-based Message Passing for Heterogeneous Graph Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slotgat-slot-based-message-passing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We identify a potential semantic mixing issue in existing message passing processes, where the representations of the neighbors of a node $v$ are forced to be transformed to the feature space of $v$ for aggregation, though the neighbors are in different types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slotgat-slot-based-message-passing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVMoE: Multi-Task Vehicle Routing Solver with Mixture-of-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvmoe-multi-task-vehicle-routing-solver-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to develop a unified neural solver that can cope with a range of VRP variants simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvmoe-multi-task-vehicle-routing-solver-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Problem Solving in Large Language and Vision Models -- What Would it Take?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creative-problem-solving-in-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we discuss approaches for integrating Computational Creativity (CC) with research in large language and vision models (LLVMs) to address a key limitation of these models, i. e., creative problem solving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creative-problem-solving-in-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Torch2Chip: An End-to-end Customizable Deep Neural Network Compression and Deployment Toolkit for Prototype Hardware Accelerator Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torch2chip-an-end-to-end-customizable-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The limited degree of freedom in the current toolkit and the under-explored customization hinder the prototype ASIC or FPGA-based accelerator design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torch2chip-an-end-to-end-customizable-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLAID SHIRTTT for Large-Scale Streaming Dense Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plaid-shirttt-for-large-scale-streaming-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PLAID, an efficient implementation of the ColBERT late interaction bi-encoder using pretrained language models for ranking, consistently achieves state-of-the-art performance in monolingual, cross-language, and multilingual retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plaid-shirttt-for-large-scale-streaming-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Fairness in Multilingual Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-fairness-in-multilingual-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also evaluate real MLIR systems on two publicly available benchmarks and show that the PEER scores align with prior analytical findings on MLIR fairness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-fairness-in-multilingual-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UQA: Corpus for Urdu Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uqa-corpus-for-urdu-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces UQA, a novel dataset for question answering and text comprehension in Urdu, a low-resource language with over 70 million native speakers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uqa-corpus-for-urdu-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning Models in Speech Recognition: Measuring GPU Energy Consumption, Impact of Noise and Model Quantization for Edge Deployment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-models-in-speech-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By analyzing WER and transcription speed across models using FP32, FP16, and INT8 quantization on clean and noisy datasets, we highlight the crucial trade-offs between accuracy, speeds, quantization, energy efficiency, and memory needs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-models-in-speech-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1-Diffractor: Efficient and Utility-Preserving Text Obfuscation Leveraging Word-Level Metric Differential Privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1-diffractor-efficient-and-utility-preserving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The study of privacy-preserving Natural Language Processing (NLP) has gained rising attention in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1-diffractor-efficient-and-utility-preserving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Procedural Generation for Learning Autonomous Peg-in-Hole Assembly in Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-procedural-generation-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the adaptability of our agents to novel scenarios and assembly sequences while emphasizing the potential of leveraging advanced simulation techniques for robot learning in space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-procedural-generation-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynFlowNet: Towards Molecule Design with Guaranteed Synthesis Pathways</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synflownet-towards-molecule-design-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent breakthroughs in generative modelling have led to a number of works proposing molecular generation models for drug discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synflownet-towards-molecule-design-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A probabilistic estimation of remaining useful life from censored time-to-event data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-estimation-of-remaining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work encourages the inclusion of censored data in predictive maintenance models and highlights the unique advantages that survival analysis offers when it comes to probabilistic RUL estimation and early fault detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-estimation-of-remaining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Representations for Speech, Music, and Acoustic Events</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-representations-for-speech-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Limited diversity in standardized benchmarks for evaluating audio representation learning (ARL) methods may hinder systematic comparison of current methods' capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-representations-for-speech-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeMo-Aligner: Scalable Toolkit for Efficient Model Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nemo-aligner-scalable-toolkit-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, building efficient tools to perform alignment can be challenging, especially for the largest and most competent LLMs which often contain tens or hundreds of billions of parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nemo-aligner-scalable-toolkit-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Question Translation Training in Multilingual Reasoning: Broadened Scope and Deepened Insights</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-power-of-question-translation-training-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore how broadly this method can be applied by examining its effects in reasoning with executable code and reasoning with common sense.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-power-of-question-translation-training-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spider: A Unified Framework for Context-dependent Concept Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spider-a-unified-framework-for-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from the context-independent (CI) concepts such as human, car, and airplane, context-dependent (CD) concepts require higher visual understanding ability, such as camouflaged object and medical lesion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spider-a-unified-framework-for-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LocInv: Localization-aware Inversion for Text-Guided Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locinv-localization-aware-inversion-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale Text-to-Image (T2I) diffusion models demonstrate significant generation capabilities based on textual prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locinv-localization-aware-inversion-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lying Graph Convolution: Learning to Lie for Node Classification Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lying-graph-convolution-learning-to-lie-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Lying-GCN, a new DGN inspired by opinion dynamics that can adaptively work in both the heterophilic and the homophilic setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lying-graph-convolution-learning-to-lie-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Relevance Feedback and Convergence of Adaptive Re-Ranking: University of Glasgow Terrier Team at TREC DL 2023</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-relevance-feedback-and-convergence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In re-ranking, we investigate operating points of adaptive re-ranking with different first stages to find the point in graph traversal where the first stage no longer has an effect on the performance of the overall retrieval pipeline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-relevance-feedback-and-convergence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topics in the Study of the Pragmatic Functions of Phonetic Reduction in Dialog</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topics-in-the-study-of-the-pragmatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reduced articulatory precision is common in speech, but for dialog its acoustic properties and pragmatic functions have been little studied.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topics-in-the-study-of-the-pragmatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lipschitz constant estimation for general neural network architectures using control tools</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lipschitz-constant-estimation-for-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper is devoted to the estimation of the Lipschitz constant of neural networks using semidefinite programming.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lipschitz-constant-estimation-for-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A text-based, generative deep learning model for soil reflectance spectrum simulation in the VIS-NIR (400-2499 nm) bands</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-text-based-generative-deep-learning-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, a fully data-driven soil optics generative model (SOGM) for simulation of soil reflectance spectra based on soil property inputs was developed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-text-based-generative-deep-learning-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balance Reward and Safety Optimization for Safe Reinforcement Learning: A Perspective of Gradient Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balance-reward-and-safety-optimization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ensuring the safety of Reinforcement Learning (RL) is crucial for its deployment in real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balance-reward-and-safety-optimization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster Learned Sparse Retrieval with Block-Max Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-learned-sparse-retrieval-with-block</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learned sparse retrieval systems aim to combine the effectiveness of contextualized language models with the scalability of conventional data structures such as inverted indexes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-learned-sparse-retrieval-with-block</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distillation for Multilingual Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-for-multilingual-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work in cross-language information retrieval (CLIR), where queries and documents are in different languages, has shown the benefit of the Translate-Distill framework that trains a cross-language neural dual-encoder model using translation and distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-for-multilingual-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATO: Stable Text-to-Motion Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sato-stable-text-to-motion-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a methodology for constructing an SATO that satisfies the stability of attention and prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sato-stable-text-to-motion-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RaffeSDG: Random Frequency Filtering enabled Single-source Domain Generalization for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raffesdg-random-frequency-filtering-enabled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle domain shifts in data-scarce medical scenarios, we propose a Random frequency filtering enabled Single-source Domain Generalization algorithm (RaffeSDG), which promises robust out-of-domain inference with segmentation models trained on a single-source domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raffesdg-random-frequency-filtering-enabled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Online Ensembles of Basis Expansions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-online-ensembles-of-basis-expansions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Practical Bayesian learning often requires (1) online inference, (2) dynamic models, and (3) ensembling over multiple different models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-online-ensembles-of-basis-expansions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATOM: Attention Mixer for Efficient Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atom-attention-mixer-for-efficient-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges in dataset distillation, we propose the ATtentiOn Mixer (ATOM) module to efficiently distill large datasets using a mixture of channel and spatial-wise attention in the feature matching process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atom-attention-mixer-for-efficient-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiniGPT-3D: Efficiently Aligning 3D Point Clouds with Large Language Models using 2D Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minigpt-3d-efficiently-aligning-3d-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, MiniGPT-3D gains an 8. 12 increase on GPT-4 evaluation score for the challenging object captioning task compared to ShapeLLM-13B, while the latter costs 160 total GPU-hours on 8 A800.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minigpt-3d-efficiently-aligning-3d-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Activity-Driven Music Listening with PACE</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-activity-driven-music-listening-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the topic of listening context is widely studied in the literature of music recommender systems, the integration of regular user behavior is often omitted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-activity-driven-music-listening-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imagine2touch: Predictive Tactile Sensing for Robotic Manipulation using Efficient Low-Dimensional Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagine2touch-predictive-tactile-sensing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We train Imagine2touch on two out of those shapes and validate it on the ood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagine2touch-predictive-tactile-sensing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Convergence in Bayesian Few-Shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-convergence-in-bayesian-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian few-shot classification has been a focal point in the field of few-shot learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-convergence-in-bayesian-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
