<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 09:24:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>LifelongPR: Lifelong knowledge fusion for point cloud place recognition based on replay and prompt learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelongpr-lifelong-knowledge-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Point cloud place recognition (PCPR) plays a crucial role in photogrammetry and robotics applications such as autonomous driving, intelligent transportation, and augmented reality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelongpr-lifelong-knowledge-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REST: Stress Testing Large Reasoning Models by Asking Multiple Problems at Once</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rest-stress-testing-large-reasoning-models-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent Large Reasoning Models (LRMs) have achieved remarkable progress on task-specific benchmarks, yet their evaluation methods remain constrained by isolated problem-solving paradigms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rest-stress-testing-large-reasoning-models-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Robustness and Generalization Against Word Substitution Attacks in NLP via the Growth Bound Matrix Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-robustness-and-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite advancements in Natural Language Processing (NLP), models remain vulnerable to adversarial attacks, such as synonym substitutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-robustness-and-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Visual Semantic Constrained AI-Generated Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-visual-semantic-constrained-ai-generated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach integrates key capabilities from multiple models and tackles the aforementioned challenges by introducing two core modules: the Text-assisted Semantic Alignment Module (TSAM), which leverages Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) to bridge the semantic gap by generating an image description and comparing it against the original prompt for a refined consistency check, and the Frequency-domain Fine-Grained Degradation Perception Module (FFDPM), which draws inspiration from Human Visual System (HVS) properties by employing frequency domain analysis combined with perceptual sensitivity weighting to better quantify subtle visual distortions and enhance the capture of fine-grained visual quality details in images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-visual-semantic-constrained-ai-generated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VoTranhAbyssCoreMicro and PoliticalCore: A Unified Framework for Simulating Complex Economic and Political Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/votranhabysscoremicro-and-politicalcore-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The VoTranhAbyssCoreMicro framework, integrated with the PoliticalCore mod- ule, provides a robust platform for simulating complex economic and political dy- namics with a validated accuracy of 90% across multiple tested economies and polit- ical scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/votranhabysscoremicro-and-politicalcore-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Enhanced Pediatric Pneumonia Detection: A CNN-Based Approach Using Data Augmentation and Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-enhanced-pediatric-pneumonia-detection-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study presents a machine learning-based Pediatric Chest Pneumonia Classification System to assist healthcare professionals in diagnosing pneumonia from chest X-ray images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-enhanced-pediatric-pneumonia-detection-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PanoDiff-SR: Synthesizing Dental Panoramic Radiographs using Diffusion and Super-resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panodiff-sr-synthesizing-dental-panoramic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inception scores were 2. 55, 2. 30, 2. 90 and 2. 98 for real HR, synthetic HR, real LR and synthetic LR images, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panodiff-sr-synthesizing-dental-panoramic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car Object Counting and Position Estimation via Extension of the CLIP-EBC Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/car-object-counting-and-position-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the applicability of the CLIP-EBC framework, originally designed for crowd counting, to car object counting using the CARPK dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/car-object-counting-and-position-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Objectomaly: Objectness-Aware Refinement for OoD Segmentation with Structural Consistency and Boundary Precision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/objectomaly-objectness-aware-refinement-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-Distribution (OoD) segmentation is critical for safety-sensitive applications like autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/objectomaly-objectness-aware-refinement-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCOOTER: A Human Evaluation Framework for Unrestricted Adversarial Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scooter-a-human-evaluation-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This issue necessitates a unified framework that supports and streamlines such an assessment for evaluating and comparing unrestricted attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scooter-a-human-evaluation-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNN-CNN: An Efficient Hybrid Model of Convolutional and Graph Neural Networks for Text Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnn-cnn-an-efficient-hybrid-model-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time, cost, and energy efficiency are critical considerations in Deep-Learning (DL), particularly when processing long texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnn-cnn-an-efficient-hybrid-model-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PacGDC: Label-Efficient Generalizable Depth Completion with Projection Ambiguity and Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pacgdc-label-efficient-generalizable-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents PacGDC, a label-efficient technique that enhances data diversity with minimal annotation effort for generalizable depth completion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pacgdc-label-efficient-generalizable-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMO: A Lightweight Sharpness-Aware Approach for Multi-Task Optimization with Joint Global-Local Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samo-a-lightweight-sharpness-aware-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sharpness-aware minimization (SAM) minimizes task loss while simultaneously reducing the sharpness of the loss landscape.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samo-a-lightweight-sharpness-aware-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Query-based Transformer for Continual Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-query-based-transformer-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these, we conduct an in-depth investigation of the built-in objectness and find that highly aggregated image features provide a shortcut for queries to generate masks through simple feature alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-query-based-transformer-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Interpretable Time Series Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-interpretable-time-series-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the distillation of time series reasoning capabilities into small, instruction-tuned language models as a step toward building interpretable time series foundation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-interpretable-time-series-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Planning &amp; Control System with Language Agents for Autonomous Scientific Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-planning-control-system-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a multi-agent system for automation of scientific research tasks, cmbagent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-planning-control-system-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MS-DPPs: Multi-Source Determinantal Point Processes for Contextual Diversity Refinement of Composite Attributes in Text to Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ms-dpps-multi-source-determinantal-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this task, we propose Multi-Source DPPs, a simple yet strong baseline that extends the Determinantal Point Process (DPP) to multi-sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ms-dpps-multi-source-determinantal-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoFE-Time: Mixture of Frequency Domain Experts for Time-Series Forecasting Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mofe-time-mixture-of-frequency-domain-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although existing models achieve some success, they rarely both model time and frequency characteristics in a pretraining-finetuning paradigm leading to suboptimal performance in predictions of complex time series, which requires both modeling periodicity and prior pattern knowledge of signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mofe-time-mixture-of-frequency-domain-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InvestAlign: Overcoming Data Scarcity in Aligning Large Language Models with Investor Decision-Making Processes under Herd Behavior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investalign-overcoming-data-scarcity-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose InvestAlign, a novel framework that constructs high-quality SFT datasets by leveraging theoretical solutions to similar and simple optimal investment problems rather than complex scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investalign-overcoming-data-scarcity-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UQLM: A Python Package for Uncertainty Quantification in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uqlm-a-python-package-for-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hallucinations, defined as instances where Large Language Models (LLMs) generate false or misleading content, pose a significant challenge that impacts the safety and trust of downstream applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uqlm-a-python-package-for-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Graph Structure via Adapted Flux Balance Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-graph-structure-via-adapted-flux</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many dynamic processes such as telecommunication and transport networks can be described through discrete time series of graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-graph-structure-via-adapted-flux</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Diversity All You Need for Scalable Robotic Manipulation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-diversity-all-you-need-for-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data scaling has driven remarkable success in foundation models for Natural Language Processing (NLP) and Computer Vision (CV), yet the principles of effective data scaling in robotic manipulation remain insufficiently understood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-diversity-all-you-need-for-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Neuron Labelling Enables Generative Steering and Interpretability in Protein Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-neuron-labelling-enables-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Protein language models (PLMs) encode rich biological information, yet their internal neuron representations are poorly understood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-neuron-labelling-enables-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eegFloss: A Python package for refining sleep EEG recordings using machine learning models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eegfloss-a-python-package-for-refining-sleep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By addressing a fundamental challenge faced by most sleep studies, eegFloss can enhance the precision and rigor of their analysis as well as the accuracy and reliability of their outcomes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eegfloss-a-python-package-for-refining-sleep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PaddleOCR 3.0 Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paddleocr-3-0-technical-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This technical report introduces PaddleOCR 3. 0, an Apache-licensed open-source toolkit for OCR and document parsing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paddleocr-3-0-technical-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SE(3)-Equivariant Diffusion Policy in Spherical Fourier Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/se-3-equivariant-diffusion-policy-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose Spherical Diffusion Policy (SDP), an SE(3) equivariant diffusion policy that adapts trajectories according to 3D transformations of the scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/se-3-equivariant-diffusion-policy-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Transformers: Modular Composition and Layer-wise Expansion on a Frozen Substrate</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/growing-transformers-modular-composition-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prevailing paradigm for scaling large language models (LLMs) involves monolithic, end-to-end training, a resource-intensive process that lacks flexibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/growing-transformers-modular-composition-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skywork-R1V3 Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skywork-r1v3-technical-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The strong performance of Skywork-R1V3 primarily stems from our elaborate post-training RL framework, which effectively activates and enhances the model's reasoning ability, without the need for additional continue pre-training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skywork-r1v3-technical-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-Guided Backdoor Defense through Entropy-Based Poisoned Dataset Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-guided-backdoor-defense-through-entropy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CGD utilizes a publicly accessible CLIP model to identify inputs that are likely to be clean or poisoned.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-guided-backdoor-defense-through-entropy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Driven Cytomorphology Image Synthesis for Medical Diagnostics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-driven-cytomorphology-image-synthesis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When training a ResNet classifier, accuracy increased from 27. 3\% to 78. 4\% (+51. 1\%) by adding 5000 synthetic images per class to a small and highly imbalanced real dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-driven-cytomorphology-image-synthesis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differential Attention for Multimodal Crisis Event Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-attention-for-multimodal-crisis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further refine multimodal fusion, we employ Guided Cross Attention (Guided CA) and combine it with the Differential Attention mechanism to enhance feature alignment by emphasizing critical information while filtering out irrelevant content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-attention-for-multimodal-crisis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergent Semantics Beyond Token Embeddings: Transformer LMs with Frozen Visual Unicode Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergent-semantics-beyond-token-embeddings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We attribute this to "representational interference" in conventional models, where the embedding layer is burdened with learning both structural and semantic features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergent-semantics-beyond-token-embeddings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating Object Physical Properties from RGB-D Vision and Depth Robot Sensors Using Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-object-physical-properties-from-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This synthetic data is used to train an image generation model for estimating dense depth maps, which we then use to augment an existing dataset of images paired with mass values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-object-physical-properties-from-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>any4: Learned 4-bit Numeric Representation for LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/any4-learned-4-bit-numeric-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present any4, a learned 4-bit weight quantization solution for large language models (LLMs) providing arbitrary numeric representations without requiring pre-processing of weights or activations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/any4-learned-4-bit-numeric-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Extended SONICOM HRTF Dataset and Spatial Audio Metrics Toolbox</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-extended-sonicom-hrtf-dataset-and-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Headphone-based spatial audio uses head-related transfer functions (HRTFs) to simulate real-world acoustic environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-extended-sonicom-hrtf-dataset-and-spatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EduCoder: An Open-Source Annotation System for Education Transcript Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/educoder-an-open-source-annotation-system-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce EduCoder, a domain-specialized tool designed to support utterance-level annotation of educational dialogue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/educoder-an-open-source-annotation-system-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VERITAS: Verification and Explanation of Realness in Images for Transparency in AI Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/veritas-verification-and-explanation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The widespread and rapid adoption of AI-generated content, created by models such as Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) and Diffusion Models, has revolutionized the digital media landscape by allowing efficient and creative content generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/veritas-verification-and-explanation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Robust Stereo Matching in the Wild with Selective Mixture-of-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-stereo-matching-in-the-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose SMoEStereo, a novel framework that adapts VFMs for stereo matching through a tailored, scene-specific fusion of Low-Rank Adaptation (LoRA) and Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) modules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-stereo-matching-in-the-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SV-DRR: High-Fidelity Novel View X-Ray Synthesis Using Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sv-drr-high-fidelity-novel-view-x-ray</link>
      <description><![CDATA[X-ray imaging is a rapid and cost-effective tool for visualizing internal human anatomy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sv-drr-high-fidelity-novel-view-x-ray</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DreamVLA: A Vision-Language-Action Model Dreamed with Comprehensive World Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamvla-a-vision-language-action-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing methods are limited to challenging image-based forecasting, which suffers from redundant information and lacks comprehensive and critical world knowledge, including dynamic, spatial and semantic information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamvla-a-vision-language-action-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOTE: Vision-Language-Action Optimization with Trajectory Ensemble Voting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vote-vision-language-action-optimization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose VOTE, an efficient and general framework for the optimization and acceleration of VLA models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vote-vision-language-action-optimization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Remote Physiological Signal Measurement under Dynamic Lighting Conditions at Night: Dataset, Experiment, and Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-remote-physiological-signal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we present and release a large-scale rPPG dataset collected under dynamic lighting conditions at night, named DLCN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-remote-physiological-signal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FA: Forced Prompt Learning of Vision-Language Models for Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fa-forced-prompt-learning-of-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, instead of delving into the intricate OOD-related knowledge, we propose an innovative CLIP-based framework based on Forced prompt leArning (FA), designed to make full use of the In-Distribution (ID) knowledge and ultimately boost the effectiveness of OOD detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fa-forced-prompt-learning-of-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoSiA: Efficient High-Rank Fine-Tuning via Subnet Localization and Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/losia-efficient-high-rank-fine-tuning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also present LoSiA-Pro, a faster implementation of LoSiA, which reduces the training latency by about $27\%$ compared to LoRA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/losia-efficient-high-rank-fine-tuning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MambaFusion: Height-Fidelity Dense Global Fusion for Multi-modal 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambafusion-height-fidelity-dense-global</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the first work demonstrating that a pure Mamba block can achieve efficient Dense Global Fusion, meanwhile guaranteeing top performance for camera-LiDAR multi-modal 3D object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambafusion-height-fidelity-dense-global</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVNet: Hyperspectral Remote Sensing Image Classification Based on Hybrid Mamba-Transformer Vision Backbone Architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvnet-hyperspectral-remote-sensing-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperspectral image (HSI) classification faces challenges such as high-dimensional data, limited training samples, and spectral redundancy, which often lead to overfitting and insufficient generalization capability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvnet-hyperspectral-remote-sensing-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PresentAgent: Multimodal Agent for Presentation Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/presentagent-multimodal-agent-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present PresentAgent, a multimodal agent that transforms long-form documents into narrated presentation videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/presentagent-multimodal-agent-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Continual Learning with Prior Compensation for Human Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-continual-learning-with-prior-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on four HMP benchmark datasets demonstrate the effectiveness and flexibility of TCL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-continual-learning-with-prior-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Collaborative Attention Network for Link Prediction in Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-collaborative-attention-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge graphs offer a structured representation of real-world entities and their relationships, enabling a wide range of applications from information retrieval to automated reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-collaborative-attention-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic Human Motion Prediction with Memory of Action Transition and Action Characteristic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-human-motion-prediction-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The STAB stores the action transition information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-human-motion-prediction-with-1</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
