<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 09:12:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Feature-compatible Progressive Learning for Video Copy Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-compatible-progressive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video Copy Detection (VCD) has been developed to identify instances of unauthorized or duplicated video content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-compatible-progressive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CKBP v2: An Expert-Annotated Evaluation Set for Commonsense Knowledge Base Population</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ckbp-v2-an-expert-annotated-evaluation-set</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Populating Commonsense Knowledge Bases (CSKB) is an important yet hard task in NLP, as it tackles knowledge from external sources with unseen events and entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ckbp-v2-an-expert-annotated-evaluation-set</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Program with Natural Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-program-with-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we further propose the Learning to Program (LP) method to ask LLMs themselves to learn natural language programs from the training dataset of complex tasks and then use the learned program to guide inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-program-with-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PED-ANOVA: Efficiently Quantifying Hyperparameter Importance in Arbitrary Subspaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ped-anova-efficiently-quantifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent rise in popularity of Hyperparameter Optimization (HPO) for deep learning has highlighted the role that good hyperparameter (HP) space design can play in training strong models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ped-anova-efficiently-quantifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Cellular Coverage from Real Network Configurations using GNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-cellular-coverage-from-real-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cellular coverage quality estimation has been a critical task for self-organized networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-cellular-coverage-from-real-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angle based dynamic learning rate for gradient descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/angle-based-dynamic-learning-rate-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our work, we propose a novel yet simple approach to obtain an adaptive learning rate for gradient-based descent methods on classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/angle-based-dynamic-learning-rate-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularizing Second-Order Influences for Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-second-order-influences-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual learning aims to learn on non-stationary data streams without catastrophically forgetting previous knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-second-order-influences-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards replacing precipitation ensemble predictions systems using machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-replacing-precipitation-ensemble</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the feasibility of generating realistic precipitation ensemble members on unseen higher resolutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-replacing-precipitation-ensemble</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Bottleneck Concepts in Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-bottleneck-concepts-in-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using some image classification tasks as our testbed, we demonstrate BotCL's potential to rebuild neural networks for better interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-bottleneck-concepts-in-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Open Intent Classification with K-center Contrastive Learning and Adjustable Decision Boundary</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-open-intent-classification-with-k</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce novel K-center contrastive learning and adjustable decision boundary learning (CLAB) to improve the effectiveness of open intent classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-open-intent-classification-with-k</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt-Learning for Cross-Lingual Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-learning-for-cross-lingual-relation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on WMT17-EnZh XRE also show the effectiveness of our Prompt-XRE against other competitive baselines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-learning-for-cross-lingual-relation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A geometry-aware deep network for depth estimation in monocular endoscopy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-geometry-aware-deep-network-for-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we introduce a gradient loss to penalize edge fluctuations ambiguous around stepped edge structures and a normal loss to explicitly express the sensitivity to frequently small structures, and propose a geometric consistency loss to spreads the spatial information across the sample grids to constrain the global geometric anatomy structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-geometry-aware-deep-network-for-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noisy Universal Domain Adaptation via Divergence Optimization for Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisy-universal-domain-adaptation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To transfer the knowledge learned from a labeled source domain to an unlabeled target domain, many studies have worked on universal domain adaptation (UniDA), where there is no constraint on the label sets of the source domain and target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisy-universal-domain-adaptation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety Assessment of Chinese Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-assessment-of-chinese-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further promote the safe deployment of LLMs, we develop a Chinese LLM safety assessment benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-assessment-of-chinese-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omni Aggregation Networks for Lightweight Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omni-aggregation-networks-for-lightweight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While lightweight ViT framework has made tremendous progress in image super-resolution, its uni-dimensional self-attention modeling, as well as homogeneous aggregation scheme, limit its effective receptive field (ERF) to include more comprehensive interactions from both spatial and channel dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omni-aggregation-networks-for-lightweight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Implicit Neural Representations in Low-Level Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-implicit-neural-representations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implicit Neural Representation (INR) has been emerging in computer vision in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-implicit-neural-representations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Censoring chemical data to mitigate dual use risk</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/censoring-chemical-data-to-mitigate-dual-use</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dual use of machine learning applications, where models can be used for both beneficial and malicious purposes, presents a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/censoring-chemical-data-to-mitigate-dual-use</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Manipulating Tokenization Aid Cross-Lingual Transfer? A Study on POS Tagging for Non-Standardized Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-manipulating-tokenization-aid-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This can for instance be observed when finetuning PLMs on one language and evaluating them on data in a closely related language variety with no standardized orthography.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-manipulating-tokenization-aid-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image-text Retrieval via preserving main Semantics of Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-text-retrieval-via-preserving-main</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, this paper presents a semantic optimization approach, implemented as a Visual Semantic Loss (VSL), to assist the model in focusing on an image's main content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-text-retrieval-via-preserving-main</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StoManager1: Automated, High-throughput Tool to Measure Leaf Stomata Using Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stomanager1-automated-high-throughput-tool-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stomatal characteristics of leaves are crucial for plant physiological performance and ecological functioning in regulating global water and carbon cycling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stomanager1-automated-high-throughput-tool-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road Genome: A Topology Reasoning Benchmark for Scene Understanding in Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/road-genome-a-topology-reasoning-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By introducing Road Genome (OpenLane-V2), we intend to shift the community's attention and take a step further beyond perception - to the task of topology reasoning for scene structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/road-genome-a-topology-reasoning-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTIRE 2023 Challenge on Light Field Image Super-Resolution: Dataset, Methods and Results</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntire-2023-challenge-on-light-field-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we summarize the first NTIRE challenge on light field (LF) image super-resolution (SR), which aims at super-resolving LF images under the standard bicubic degradation with a magnification factor of 4.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntire-2023-challenge-on-light-field-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certified Adversarial Robustness Within Multiple Perturbation Bounds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certified-adversarial-robustness-within</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further propose a novel \textit{training noise distribution} along with a \textit{regularized training scheme} to improve the certification within both $\ell_1$ and $\ell_2$ perturbation norms simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certified-adversarial-robustness-within</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Temporal Modeling with Learnable Alignment for Video Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-temporal-modeling-with-learnable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While modeling temporal information within straight through tube is widely adopted in literature, we find that simple frame alignment already provides enough essence without temporal attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-temporal-modeling-with-learnable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix: Democratizing ChatGPT across Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phoenix-democratizing-chatgpt-across</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents our efforts to democratize ChatGPT across language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phoenix-democratizing-chatgpt-across</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Neural Networks with Knapsack Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/securing-neural-networks-with-knapsack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The second way to accelerate Secure Inference is based on cutting the number of bit comparisons required for a secure ReLU operation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/securing-neural-networks-with-knapsack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Dynamic Bayesian Networks for Predicting Acute Kidney Injury Before Onset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-dynamic-bayesian-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Ranking Approaches for Unknown Structures (RAUS), an automated framework to systematically inform variable ordering and learn networks end-to-end.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-dynamic-bayesian-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Deep Reinforcement Learning Scheduling via Weight Anchoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-deep-reinforcement-learning-scheduling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Questions remain on the robustness of data-driven learning methods when crossing the gap from simulation to reality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-deep-reinforcement-learning-scheduling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Diffusion for Multi-Modal Face Generation and Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-diffusion-for-multi-modal-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Collaborative Diffusion, where pre-trained uni-modal diffusion models collaborate to achieve multi-modal face generation and editing without re-training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-diffusion-for-multi-modal-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Tuning: A Little Help to Make Masked Autoencoders Forget</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-tuning-a-little-help-to-make</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study how to combine the efficiency and scalability of MIM with the ability of ID to perform downstream classification in the absence of large amounts of labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-tuning-a-little-help-to-make</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Offline Metric for the Debiasedness of Click Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-offline-metric-for-the-debiasedness-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that debiasedness is a necessary condition for recovering unbiased and consistent relevance scores and for the invariance of click prediction under covariate shift.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-offline-metric-for-the-debiasedness-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolving Constrained Reinforcement Learning Policy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolving-constrained-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evolutionary algorithms have been used to evolve a population of actors to generate diverse experiences for training reinforcement learning agents, which helps to tackle the temporal credit assignment problem and improves the exploration efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolving-constrained-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MasakhaNEWS: News Topic Classification for African languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masakhanews-news-topic-classification-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we explore several alternatives to full fine-tuning of language models that are better suited for zero-shot and few-shot learning such as cross-lingual parameter-efficient fine-tuning (like MAD-X), pattern exploiting training (PET), prompting language models (like ChatGPT), and prompt-free sentence transformer fine-tuning (SetFit and Cohere Embedding API).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masakhanews-news-topic-classification-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive-Hint Prompting Improves Reasoning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-hint-prompting-improves-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of Large Language Models (LLMs) in reasoning tasks depends heavily on prompt design, with Chain-of-Thought (CoT) and self-consistency being critical methods that enhance this ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-hint-prompting-improves-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMT: All-Pairs Multi-Field Transforms for Efficient Frame Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amt-all-pairs-multi-field-transforms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is based on two essential designs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amt-all-pairs-multi-field-transforms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Semantic Segmentation with Semantic Boundaries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-semantic-segmentation-with-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the recent development in improving semantic segmentation by incorporating boundaries as auxiliary tasks, we propose a multi-task framework that uses semantic boundary detection (SBD) as an auxiliary task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-semantic-segmentation-with-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Carbon Storage Operations for Long-Term Safety</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-carbon-storage-operations-for-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we address these issues by modeling the decision-making process for carbon storage operations as a partially observable Markov decision process (POMDP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-carbon-storage-operations-for-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information Geometrically Generalized Covariate Shift Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-geometrically-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, the phenomenon that the marginal distribution of the data changes is called covariate shift, one of the most important research topics in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-geometrically-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models Enable Simple Systems for Generating Structured Views of Heterogeneous Data Lakes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-enable-simple-systems-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Code synthesis is cheap, but far less accurate than directly processing each document with the LLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-enable-simple-systems-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big-Little Adaptive Neural Networks on Low-Power Near-Subthreshold Processors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/big-little-adaptive-neural-networks-on-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the energy savings that near-subthreshold processors can obtain in edge AI applications and proposes strategies to improve them while maintaining the accuracy of the application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/big-little-adaptive-neural-networks-on-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling keywords and their positions in text generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-keywords-and-their-positions-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we tackle a novel task of controlling not only keywords but also the position of each keyword in the text generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-keywords-and-their-positions-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPMQA: Multimodal Question Answering on Product Manuals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpmqa-multimodal-question-answering-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Taking into account the length of product manuals and the fact that a question is always related to a small number of pages, MPMQA can be naturally split into two subtasks: retrieving most related pages and then generating multimodal answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpmqa-multimodal-question-answering-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Corpora for Germanic Low-Resource Languages and Dialects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-corpora-for-germanic-low-resource</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we instead focus on low-resource languages and in particular non-standardized low-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-corpora-for-germanic-low-resource</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approximate non-linear model predictive control with safety-augmented neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximate-non-linear-model-predictive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method requires a single evaluation of the NN and forward integration of the input sequence online, which is fast to compute on resource-constrained systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximate-non-linear-model-predictive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TieFake: Title-Text Similarity and Emotion-Aware Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiefake-title-text-similarity-and-emotion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose a scale-dot product attention mechanism to capture the similarity between title features and textual features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiefake-title-text-similarity-and-emotion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>https://arxiv.org/abs/2304.09797</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/https-arxiv-org-abs-2304-09797</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of Large Language Models (LLMs) in reasoning tasks depends heavily on prompt design, with Chain-of-Thought (CoT) and self-consistency being critical methods that enhance this ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/https-arxiv-org-abs-2304-09797</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-coherent data-driven forecasting model for a combined cycle power plant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-coherent-data-driven-forecasting-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the transformation of energy models to align with machine learning requirements as a promising tool for optimizing the operation of combined cycle power plants (CCPPs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-coherent-data-driven-forecasting-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Resource Scheduling with High Priority Users using Deep Deterministic Policy Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-resource-scheduling-with-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advances in mobile communication capabilities open the door for closer integration of pre-hospital and in-hospital care processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-resource-scheduling-with-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Neuron Representations with Concept Vectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-neuron-representations-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mechanistic interpretability aims to understand how models store representations by breaking down neural networks into interpretable units.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-neuron-representations-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Density-Insensitive Unsupervised Domain Adaption on 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/density-insensitive-unsupervised-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, few works attempt to tackle the domain gap in objects, but still fail to adapt to the gap of varying beam-densities between two domains, which is critical to mitigate the characteristic differences of the LiDAR collectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/density-insensitive-unsupervised-domain</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
