<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 21:06:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rethink DARTS Search Space and Renovate a New Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethink-darts-search-space-and-renovate-a-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DARTS search space (DSS) has become a canonical benchmark for NAS whereas some emerging works pointed out the issue of narrow accuracy range and claimed it would hurt the method ranking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethink-darts-search-space-and-renovate-a-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficiently Learning the Graph for Semi-supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiently-learning-the-graph-for-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further show how to approximately learn the best graphs from the sparse families efficiently using the conjugate gradient method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiently-learning-the-graph-for-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Copilot: Bridging Billions of Data and Humans with Autonomous Workflow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-copilot-bridging-billions-of-data-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Various industries such as finance, meteorology, and energy generate vast amounts of heterogeneous data every day.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-copilot-bridging-billions-of-data-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Quantization-aware Training with Adaptive Coreset Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-quantization-aware-training-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared with previous coreset selection methods, our method significantly improves QAT performance with different dataset fractions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-quantization-aware-training-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Transformer Overconfidence via Lipschitz Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-transformer-overconfidence-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though Transformers have achieved promising results in many computer vision tasks, they tend to be over-confident in predictions, as the standard Dot Product Self-Attention (DPSA) can barely preserve distance for the unbounded input domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-transformer-overconfidence-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NF4 Isn't Information Theoretically Optimal (and that's Good)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nf4-isn-t-information-theoretically-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This note shares some simple calculations and experiments related to absmax-based blockwise quantization, as used in Dettmers et al., 2023.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nf4-isn-t-information-theoretically-optimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Plug and Play: Posterior Sampling for Inverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-plug-and-play-posterior-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Generative Plug-and-Play (GPnP), a generalization of PnP to sample from the posterior distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-plug-and-play-posterior-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volume-DROID: A Real-Time Implementation of Volumetric Mapping with DROID-SLAM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volume-droid-a-real-time-implementation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Volume-DROID takes camera images (monocular or stereo) or frames from a video as input and combines DROID-SLAM, point cloud registration, an off-the-shelf semantic segmentation network, and Convolutional Bayesian Kernel Inference (ConvBKI) to generate a 3D semantic map of the environment and provide accurate localization for the robot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volume-droid-a-real-time-implementation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECAP: Retrieval-Enhanced Context-Aware Prefix Encoder for Personalized Dialogue Response Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recap-retrieval-enhanced-context-aware-prefix</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Endowing chatbots with a consistent persona is essential to an engaging conversation, yet it remains an unresolved challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recap-retrieval-enhanced-context-aware-prefix</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Constrained Bidding via Minimax Regret Optimization with Causality-Aware Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-constrained-bidding-via-minimax</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this regard, we explore the problem of constrained bidding in adversarial bidding environments, which assumes no knowledge about the adversarial factors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-constrained-bidding-via-minimax</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear Classifier: An Often-Forgotten Baseline for Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-classifier-an-often-forgotten-baseline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale pre-trained language models such as BERT are popular solutions for text classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-classifier-an-often-forgotten-baseline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmenting Language Models with Long-Term Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-language-models-with-long-term</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such a decoupled memory design can easily cache and update long-term past contexts for memory retrieval without suffering from memory staleness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-language-models-with-long-term</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Forward Gradient Match Backpropagation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-forward-gradient-match-backpropagation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Forward Gradients - the idea of using directional derivatives in forward differentiation mode - have recently been shown to be utilizable for neural network training while avoiding problems generally associated with backpropagation gradient computation, such as locking and memorization requirements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-forward-gradient-match-backpropagation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tuning Legged Locomotion Controllers via Safe Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tuning-legged-locomotion-controllers-via-safe</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a data-driven strategy to simplify the deployment of model-based controllers in legged robotic hardware platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tuning-legged-locomotion-controllers-via-safe</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global and Local Semantic Completion Learning for Vision-Language Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-and-local-semantic-completion-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, in this paper, we propose a novel Global and Local Semantic Completion Learning (GLSCL) task to facilitate global-local alignment and local-local alignment simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-and-local-semantic-completion-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transcendental Idealism of Planner: Evaluating Perception from Planning Perspective for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transcendental-idealism-of-planner-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating the performance of perception modules in autonomous driving is one of the most critical tasks in developing the complex intelligent system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transcendental-idealism-of-planner-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waffling around for Performance: Visual Classification with Random Words and Broad Concepts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/waffling-around-for-performance-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study this behavior in detail and propose \texttt{Waffle}CLIP, a framework for zero-shot visual classification which achieves similar performance gains on a large number of visual classification tasks by simply replacing LLM-generated descriptors with random character and word descriptors \textbf{without} querying external models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/waffling-around-for-performance-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVABLE: Exploring Long-Tailed Classification of Software Vulnerability Types</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/livable-exploring-long-tailed-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(2) adaptive re-weighting module, which adjusts the learning weights for different types according to the training epochs and numbers of associated samples by a novel training loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/livable-exploring-long-tailed-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Do Annotator Demographics Matter? Measuring the Influence of Annotator Demographics with the POPQUORN Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-do-annotator-demographics-matter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, our work shows that backgrounds not previously considered in NLP (e. g., education), are meaningful and should be considered.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-do-annotator-demographics-matter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaskedFusion360: Reconstruct LiDAR Data by Querying Camera Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskedfusion360-reconstruct-lidar-data-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In self-driving applications, LiDAR data provides accurate information about distances in 3D but lacks the semantic richness of camera data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskedfusion360-reconstruct-lidar-data-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>detrex: Benchmarking Detection Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detrex-benchmarking-detection-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we develop a unified, highly modular, and lightweight codebase called detrex, which supports a majority of the mainstream DETR-based instance recognition algorithms, covering various fundamental tasks, including object detection, segmentation, and pose estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detrex-benchmarking-detection-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Devil is in the Details: On the Pitfalls of Event Extraction Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-is-in-the-details-on-the-pitfalls-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we check the reliability of EE evaluations and identify three major pitfalls: (1) The data preprocessing discrepancy makes the evaluation results on the same dataset not directly comparable, but the data preprocessing details are not widely noted and specified in papers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-is-in-the-details-on-the-pitfalls-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Multilingual Sentence Representations with Cross-lingual Consistency Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-multilingual-sentence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multilingual sentence representations are the foundation for similarity-based bitext mining, which is crucial for scaling multilingual neural machine translation (NMT) system to more languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-multilingual-sentence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient Ascent Post-training Enhances Language Model Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-ascent-post-training-enhances</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we empirically show that updating pretrained LMs (350M, 1. 3B, 2. 7B) with just a few steps of Gradient Ascent Post-training (GAP) on random, unlabeled text corpora enhances its zero-shot generalization capabilities across diverse NLP tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-ascent-post-training-enhances</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniPoll: A Unified Social Media Poll Generation Framework via Multi-Objective Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unipoll-a-unified-social-media-poll</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Social media platforms are essential outlets for expressing opinions, providing a valuable resource for capturing public viewpoints via text analytics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unipoll-a-unified-social-media-poll</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LTCR: Long-Text Chinese Rumor Detection Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ltcr-long-text-chinese-rumor-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Long-Text Chinese Rumor detection dataset we developed is focusing on the identification of misleading information in the context of rumor verification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ltcr-long-text-chinese-rumor-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Language Corrections for Teaching Physical Control Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-language-corrections-for-teaching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AI assistance continues to help advance applications in education, from language learning to intelligent tutoring systems, yet current methods for providing students feedback are still quite limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-language-corrections-for-teaching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Effect of Masking Strategies on Knowledge Retention by Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-masking-strategies-on-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To foster reproducibility, the code, as well as the data used in this paper, are openly available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-masking-strategies-on-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly-Supervised Scientific Document Classification via Retrieval-Augmented Multi-Stage Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-scientific-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose a weakly-supervised approach for scientific document classification using label names only.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-scientific-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-precision interpolation of stellar atmospheres with a deep neural network using a 1D convolutional auto encoder for feature extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-precision-interpolation-of-stellar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the widespread availability of grids of models for stellar atmospheres, it is necessary to recover intermediate atmospheric models by means of accurate techniques that go beyond simple linear interpolation and capture the intricacies of the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-precision-interpolation-of-stellar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using a neural network approach to accelerate disequilibrium chemistry calculations in exoplanet atmospheres</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-a-neural-network-approach-to-accelerate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that in 90% of the cases, the fully trained model is able to predict the evolved mixing ratios of the species in the hot-Jupiter atmosphere simulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-a-neural-network-approach-to-accelerate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Neural Network Training Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-neural-network-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to address these challenges, we introduce a new, competitive, time-to-result benchmark using multiple workloads running on fixed hardware, the AlgoPerf: Training Algorithms benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-neural-network-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recurrent Attention Networks for Long-text Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrent-attention-networks-for-long-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Revisiting the self-attention mechanism and the recurrent structure, this paper proposes a novel long-document encoding model, Recurrent Attention Network (RAN), to enable the recurrent operation of self-attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrent-attention-networks-for-long-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coupled Attention Networks for Multivariate Time Series Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coupled-attention-networks-for-multivariate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a coupled attention-based neural network framework (CAN) for anomaly detection in multivariate time series data featuring dynamic variable relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coupled-attention-networks-for-multivariate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Forecasts for Heterogeneous Time Series by "Averaging", with Application to Food Demand Forecast</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-forecasts-for-heterogeneous-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A common forecasting setting in real world applications considers a set of possibly heterogeneous time series of the same domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-forecasts-for-heterogeneous-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Hessian's Connection to the Decision Boundary</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-hessian-s-connection-to-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this finding, we provide a new and straightforward approach to studying the complexity of a high-dimensional decision boundary; show that this connection naturally inspires a new generalization measure; and finally, we develop a novel margin estimation technique which, in combination with the generalization measure, precisely identifies minima with simple wide-margin boundaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-hessian-s-connection-to-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Vision Fails: Text Attacks Against ViT and OCR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-vision-fails-text-attacks-against-vit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While text-based machine learning models that operate on visual inputs of rendered text have become robust against a wide range of existing attacks, we show that they are still vulnerable to visual adversarial examples encoded as text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-vision-fails-text-attacks-against-vit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unprocessing Seven Years of Algorithmic Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unprocessing-seven-years-of-algorithmic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unprocessing allows for a direct comparison of methods using different underlying models and levels of relaxation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unprocessing-seven-years-of-algorithmic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precise and Generalized Robustness Certification for Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precise-and-generalized-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We identify two key properties, independence and continuity, that convert the latent space into a precise and analysis-friendly input space representation for certification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precise-and-generalized-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating the Uncertainty in Emotion Attributes using Deep Evidential Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-the-uncertainty-in-emotion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In automatic emotion recognition (AER), labels assigned by different human annotators to the same utterance are often inconsistent due to the inherent complexity of emotion and the subjectivity of perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-the-uncertainty-in-emotion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Source Test-Time Adaptation as Dueling Bandits for Extractive Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-test-time-adaptation-as-dueling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study multi-source test-time model adaptation from user feedback, where K distinct models are established for adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-test-time-adaptation-as-dueling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransMRSR: Transformer-based Self-Distilled Generative Prior for Brain MRI Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transmrsr-transformer-based-self-distilled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We perform a generative task to encapsulate diverse priors into a generative network (GAN), which is the decoder sub-module of the deep non-local feature capture part, in the first stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transmrsr-transformer-based-self-distilled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$E(2)$-Equivariant Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-2-equivariant-vision-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we design a Group Equivariant Vision Transformer (GE-ViT) via a novel, effective positional encoding operator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-2-equivariant-vision-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2-D SSM: A General Spatial Layer for Visual Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2-d-ssm-a-general-spatial-layer-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, vision transformers equipped with our layer exhibit effective performance even without positional encoding]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2-d-ssm-a-general-spatial-layer-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mimicking the Thinking Process for Emotion Recognition in Conversation with Prompts and Paraphrasing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimicking-the-thinking-process-for-emotion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is a challenging task since the recognition of the emotion in one utterance involves many complex factors, such as the conversational context, the speaker's background, and the subtle difference between emotion labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimicking-the-thinking-process-for-emotion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Importance Sparsification for Sinkhorn Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/importance-sparsification-for-sinkhorn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sinkhorn algorithm has been used pervasively to approximate the solution to optimal transport (OT) and unbalanced optimal transport (UOT) problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/importance-sparsification-for-sinkhorn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Robust and Consistent Time Series Representations: A Dilated Inception-Based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-and-consistent-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representation learning for time series has been an important research area for decades.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-and-consistent-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REACT2023: the first Multi-modal Multiple Appropriate Facial Reaction Generation Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/react2023-the-first-multi-modal-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Multi-modal Multiple Appropriate Facial Reaction Generation Challenge (REACT2023) is the first competition event focused on evaluating multimedia processing and machine learning techniques for generating human-appropriate facial reactions in various dyadic interaction scenarios, with all participants competing strictly under the same conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/react2023-the-first-multi-modal-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast, Distribution-free Predictive Inference for Neural Networks with Coverage Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-distribution-free-predictive-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel, computationally-efficient algorithm for predictive inference (PI) that requires no distributional assumptions on the data and can be computed faster than existing bootstrap-type methods for neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-distribution-free-predictive-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VPUFormer: Visual Prompt Unified Transformer for Interactive Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vpuformer-visual-prompt-unified-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we design a Prompt-unified Encoder (PuE) by using Gaussian mapping to generate a unified one-dimensional vector for click, box, and scribble prompts, which well captures users' intentions as well as provides a denser representation of user prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vpuformer-visual-prompt-unified-transformer</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
