<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 21:07:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>TiZero: Mastering Multi-Agent Football with Curriculum Learning and Self-Play</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tizero-mastering-multi-agent-football-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-agent football poses an unsolved challenge in AI research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tizero-mastering-multi-agent-football-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Teacher: Semi-Supervised Object Detection for YOLOv5</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-teacher-semi-supervised-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Pseudo Label Assigner prevents the occurrence of bias caused by a large number of low-quality pseudo labels that may interfere with the Dense Detector during the student-teacher mutual learning mechanism, and the Epoch Adaptor utilizes domain and distribution adaptation to allow Dense Detector to learn globally distributed consistent features, making the training independent of the proportion of labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-teacher-semi-supervised-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frameworks for SNNs: a Review of Data Science-oriented Software and an Expansion of SpykeTorch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frameworks-for-snns-a-review-of-data-science</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Developing effective learning systems for Machine Learning (ML) applications in the Neuromorphic (NM) field requires extensive experimentation and simulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frameworks-for-snns-a-review-of-data-science</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tri-Perspective View for Vision-Based 3D Semantic Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tri-perspective-view-for-vision-based-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To lift image features to the 3D TPV space, we further propose a transformer-based TPV encoder (TPVFormer) to obtain the TPV features effectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tri-perspective-view-for-vision-based-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCONNA: A Stochastic Computing Based Optical Accelerator for Ultra-Fast, Energy-Efficient Inference of Integer-Quantized CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sconna-a-stochastic-computing-based-optical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To leverage the innate precision flexibility of stochastic computing, we invent an MRR-based optical stochastic multiplier (OSM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sconna-a-stochastic-computing-based-optical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Summarization Data to Help Text Simplification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-summarization-data-to-help-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the major problems with text simplification is the lack of high-quality data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-summarization-data-to-help-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical Cross-system Shilling Attacks with Limited Access to Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-cross-system-shilling-attacks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the idea of Cross-system Attack, we design a Practical Cross-system Shilling Attack (PC-Attack) framework that requires little information about the victim RS model and the target RS data for conducting attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-cross-system-shilling-attacks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOWOv2: A Stronger yet Efficient Multi-level Detection Framework for Real-time Spatio-temporal Action Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yowov2-a-stronger-yet-efficient-multi-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing a real-time framework for the spatio-temporal action detection task is still a challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yowov2-a-stronger-yet-efficient-multi-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPISODE: Episodic Gradient Clipping with Periodic Resampled Corrections for Federated Learning with Heterogeneous Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/episode-episodic-gradient-clipping-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we design EPISODE, the very first algorithm to solve FL problems with heterogeneous data in the nonconvex and relaxed smoothness setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/episode-episodic-gradient-clipping-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting long-term collective animal behavior with deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-long-term-collective-animal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces a deep learning model for social interactions in the fish species Hemigrammus rhodostomus, and compares its results to experiments and to the results of a state-of-the-art analytical model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-long-term-collective-animal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetic Micro-Programs for Automated Software Testing with Large Path Coverage</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2302-07646</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ongoing progress in computational intelligence (CI) has led to an increased desire to apply CI techniques for the purpose of improving software engineering processes, particularly software testing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2302-07646</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Multi-source Active Learning for Natural Language Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-multi-source-active-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that four popular active learning schemes fail to outperform random selection when applied to unlabelled pools comprised of multiple data sources on the task of natural language inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-multi-source-active-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightsolver challenges a leading deep learning solver for Max-2-SAT problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightsolver-challenges-a-leading-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Maximum 2-satisfiability (MAX-2-SAT) is a type of combinatorial decision problem that is known to be NP-hard.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightsolver-challenges-a-leading-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Complex Event Scenarios via Simple Entity-focused Questions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-complex-event-scenarios-via-simple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event scenarios are often complex and involve multiple event sequences connected through different entity participants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-complex-event-scenarios-via-simple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have become the de facto models of choice in machine learning, typically leading to impressive performance on many applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>simpleKT: A Simple But Tough-to-Beat Baseline for Knowledge Tracing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplekt-a-simple-but-tough-to-beat-baseline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge tracing (KT) is the problem of predicting students' future performance based on their historical interactions with intelligent tutoring systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplekt-a-simple-but-tough-to-beat-baseline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EspalomaCharge: Machine learning-enabled ultra-fast partial charge assignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/espalomacharge-machine-learning-enabled-ultra</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our hybrid approach couples a graph neural network to a streamlined charge equilibration approach in order to predict molecule-specific atomic electronegativity and hardness parameters, followed by analytical determination of optimal charge-equilibrated parameters that preserves total molecular charge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/espalomacharge-machine-learning-enabled-ultra</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative State Value Estimation for Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conservative-state-value-estimation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Conservative State Value Estimation (CSVE), a new approach that learns conservative V-function via directly imposing penalty on OOD states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conservative-state-value-estimation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Value Decomposition with Greedy Marginal Contribution Computation for Cooperative Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-value-decomposition-with-greedy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first illustrate that the proposed value decomposition can consider the complicated interactions among agents and is feasible to learn in large-scale scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-value-decomposition-with-greedy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SwitchPrompt: Learning Domain-Specific Gated Soft Prompts for Classification in Low-Resource Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/switchprompt-learning-domain-specific-gated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompting pre-trained language models leads to promising results across natural language processing tasks but is less effective when applied in low-resource domains, due to the domain gap between the pre-training data and the downstream task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/switchprompt-learning-domain-specific-gated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UKnow: A Unified Knowledge Protocol for Common-Sense Reasoning and Vision-Language Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uknow-a-unified-knowledge-protocol-for-common</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents a unified knowledge protocol, called UKnow, which facilitates knowledge-based studies from the perspective of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uknow-a-unified-knowledge-protocol-for-common</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A modern look at the relationship between sharpness and generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modern-look-at-the-relationship-between</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, we observe that sharpness does not correlate well with generalization but rather with some training parameters like the learning rate that can be positively or negatively correlated with generalization depending on the setup.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modern-look-at-the-relationship-between</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Guidance for Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-guidance-for-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Typical diffusion models are trained to accept a particular form of conditioning, most commonly text, and cannot be conditioned on other modalities without retraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-guidance-for-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard-aware Instance Adaptive Self-training for Unsupervised Cross-domain Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-aware-instance-adaptive-self-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The divergence between labeled training data and unlabeled testing data is a significant challenge for recent deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-aware-instance-adaptive-self-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team DETR: Guide Queries as a Professional Team in Detection Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/team-detr-guide-queries-as-a-professional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent proposed DETR variants have made tremendous progress in various scenarios due to their streamlined processes and remarkable performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/team-detr-guide-queries-as-a-professional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffFashion: Reference-based Fashion Design with Structure-aware Transfer by Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difffashion-reference-based-fashion-design</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We focus on a new fashion design task, where we aim to transfer a reference appearance image onto a clothing image while preserving the structure of the clothing image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difffashion-reference-based-fashion-design</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Anomaly Detection for Software Systems via Semi-supervised Cross-modal Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-anomaly-detection-for-software-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study demonstrates that logs and metrics can manifest system anomalies collaboratively and complementarily, and neither of them only is sufficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-anomaly-detection-for-software-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lero: A Learning-to-Rank Query Optimizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lero-a-learning-to-rank-query-optimizer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a learning to rank query optimizer, called Lero, which builds on top of the native query optimizer and continuously learns to improve query optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lero-a-learning-to-rank-query-optimizer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Transport for Change Detection on LiDAR Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-for-change-detection-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the DEM's interpolation step causes an information loss related to the height of the objects, affecting the detection capability of building changes, where the high resolution of LiDAR point clouds in the third dimension would be the most beneficial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-for-change-detection-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distinguishability Calibration to In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinguishability-calibration-to-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When using prompt-based learning for text classification, the goal is to use a pre-trained language model (PLM) to predict a missing token in a pre-defined template given an input text, which can be mapped to a class label.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinguishability-calibration-to-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Poisoned Water Detection Method Using Smartphone Embedded Wi-Fi Technology and Machine Learning Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-poisoned-water-detection-method-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Wi-Fi access points (WAPs) signal is acquired via equivalent smartphone-embedded Wi-Fi chipsets, and then Channel-State-Information CSI measures are extracted and converted into feature vectors to be used as input for machine learning classification algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-poisoned-water-detection-method-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Hardware-Efficient Long Convolutions for Sequence Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-hardware-efficient-long-convolutions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that a key requirement to achieving high performance is keeping the convolution kernels smooth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-hardware-efficient-long-convolutions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symbolic Discovery of Optimization Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-discovery-of-optimization-algorithms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a method to formulate algorithm discovery as program search, and apply it to discover optimization algorithms for deep neural network training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-discovery-of-optimization-algorithms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can GPT-3 Perform Statutory Reasoning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-gpt-3-perform-statutory-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By also posing the same questions when the synthetic statutes are written in sentence form, we find that some of GPT-3's poor performance results from difficulty in parsing the typical structure of statutes, containing subsections and paragraphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-gpt-3-perform-statutory-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threatening Patch Attacks on Object Detection in Optical Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/threatening-patch-attacks-on-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advanced Patch Attacks (PAs) on object detection in natural images have pointed out the great safety vulnerability in methods based on deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/threatening-patch-attacks-on-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlabeled Imperfect Demonstrations in Adversarial Imitation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlabeled-imperfect-demonstrations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The trajectories of an initial agent policy could be closer to those non-optimal expert demonstrations, but within the framework of adversarial imitation learning, agent policy will be optimized to cheat the discriminator and produce trajectories that are similar to those optimal expert demonstrations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlabeled-imperfect-demonstrations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Bayesian Neural Networks via Resolution of Singularities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-bayesian-neural-networks-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we advocate for the importance of singular learning theory (SLT) as it pertains to the theory and practice of variational inference in Bayesian neural networks (BNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-bayesian-neural-networks-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Noisy Crowd Labels with Logics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-noisy-crowd-labels-with-logics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the integration of symbolic logic knowledge into deep neural networks for learning from noisy crowd labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-noisy-crowd-labels-with-logics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reliability Assurance for Deep Neural Network Architectures Against Numerical Defects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliability-assurance-for-deep-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To assure high reliability against numerical defects, in this paper, we propose the RANUM approach including novel techniques for three reliability assurance tasks: detection of potential numerical defects, confirmation of potential-defect feasibility, and suggestion of defect fixes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliability-assurance-for-deep-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIGER: Temporal Interaction Graph Embedding with Restarts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiger-temporal-interaction-graph-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to the entangled temporal and structural dependencies, existing methods have to process the sequence of events chronologically and consecutively to ensure node representations are up-to-date.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiger-temporal-interaction-graph-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AbLit: A Resource for Analyzing and Generating Abridged Versions of English Literature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ablit-a-resource-for-analyzing-and-generating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dataset captures passage-level alignments between the original and abridged texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ablit-a-resource-for-analyzing-and-generating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Scale Multi-Lingual Multi-Modal Summarization Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-lingual-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Significant developments in techniques such as encoder-decoder models have enabled us to represent information comprising multiple modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-lingual-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Shot Federated Conformal Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-federated-conformal-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a conformal prediction method to construct prediction sets in a oneshot federated learning setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-federated-conformal-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Noise Filtering with Dynamic Sparse Training in Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-noise-filtering-with-dynamic-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tomorrow's robots will need to distinguish useful information from noise when performing different tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-noise-filtering-with-dynamic-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Circuits That Know What They Don't Know</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-circuits-that-know-what-they</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to neural networks, they are often assumed to be well-calibrated and robust to out-of-distribution (OOD) data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-circuits-that-know-what-they</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raising the Cost of Malicious AI-Powered Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raising-the-cost-of-malicious-ai-powered</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an approach to mitigating the risks of malicious image editing posed by large diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raising-the-cost-of-malicious-ai-powered</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Can't Discourse Parsing Generalize? A Thorough Investigation of the Impact of Data Diversity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-can-t-discourse-parsing-generalize-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our knowledge, this study is the first to fully evaluate cross-corpus RST parsing generalizability on complete trees, examine between-genre degradation within an RST corpus, and investigate the impact of genre diversity in training data composition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-can-t-discourse-parsing-generalize-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sum of Its Parts: Visual Part Segmentation for Inertial Parameter Identification of Manipulated Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-sum-of-its-parts-visual-part-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To operate safely and efficiently alongside human workers, collaborative robots (cobots) require the ability to quickly understand the dynamics of manipulated objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-sum-of-its-parts-visual-part-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataset Distillation with Convexified Implicit Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-distillation-with-convexified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new dataset distillation algorithm using reparameterization and convexification of implicit gradients (RCIG), that substantially improves the state-of-the-art.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-distillation-with-convexified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge from Large-Scale Protein Contact Prediction Models Can Be Transferred to the Data-Scarce RNA Contact Prediction Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-from-large-scale-protein-contact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings indicate that the learned structural patterns of proteins can be transferred to RNAs, opening up potential new avenues for research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-from-large-scale-protein-contact</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
