<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 21:06:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>OccNeRF: Self-Supervised Multi-Camera Occupancy Prediction with Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occnerf-self-supervised-multi-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, for semantic occupancy prediction, we design several strategies to polish the prompts and filter the outputs of a pretrained open-vocabulary 2D segmentation model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occnerf-self-supervised-multi-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent Attention: On the Integration of Softmax and Linear Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-attention-on-the-integration-of-softmax</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the Agent Attention, denoted as a quadruple $(Q, A, K, V)$, introduces an additional set of agent tokens $A$ into the conventional attention module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-attention-on-the-integration-of-softmax</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Depth Completion from a Stereo Matching Perspective for Cross-domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-depth-completion-from-a-stereo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a new framework for depth completion robust against domain-shifting issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-depth-completion-from-a-stereo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VL-GPT: A Generative Pre-trained Transformer for Vision and Language Understanding and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vl-gpt-a-generative-pre-trained-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In combination with the existing text tokenizer and detokenizer, this framework allows for the encoding of interleaved image-text data into a multimodal sequence, which can subsequently be fed into the transformer model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vl-gpt-a-generative-pre-trained-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's do the time-warp-attend: Learning topological invariants of dynamical systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-s-do-the-time-warp-attend-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method provides valuable insights into the qualitative, long-term behavior of a wide range of dynamical systems, and can detect bifurcations or catastrophic transitions in large-scale physical and biological systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-s-do-the-time-warp-attend-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using eye tracking to investigate what native Chinese speakers notice about linguistic landscape images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-eye-tracking-to-investigate-what-native</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper uses eye tracking technology to study the actual fixation of the linguistic landscape and finds that in the two dimensions of fixation time and fixation times, the fixation of native Chinese speakers to the linguistic landscape is higher than that of the general landscape.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-eye-tracking-to-investigate-what-native</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single and Multi-Objective Benchmark Problems Focusing on Human-Powered Aircraft Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-and-multi-objective-benchmark-problems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel set of benchmark problems aimed at advancing research in both single and multi-objective optimization, with a specific focus on the design of human-powered aircraft (HPA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-and-multi-objective-benchmark-problems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aleth-NeRF: Illumination Adaptive NeRF with Concealing Field Assumption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aleth-nerf-illumination-adaptive-nerf-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The standard Neural Radiance Fields (NeRF) paradigm employs a viewer-centered methodology, entangling the aspects of illumination and material reflectance into emission solely from 3D points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aleth-nerf-illumination-adaptive-nerf-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-Driven Modulation of Neural Networks with Attention Mechanism for Next Activity Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-driven-modulation-of-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predictive Process Monitoring (PPM) aims at leveraging historic process execution data to predict how ongoing executions will continue up to their completion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-driven-modulation-of-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's Next? Predicting Hamiltonian Dynamics from Discrete Observations of a Vector Field</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-s-next-predicting-hamiltonian-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present several methods for predicting the dynamics of Hamiltonian systems from discrete observations of their vector field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-s-next-predicting-hamiltonian-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataset Distillation via Adversarial Prediction Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-distillation-via-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This ensures the memory efficiency of our method and provides a flexible tradeoff between time and memory budgets, allowing us to distil ImageNet-1K using a minimum of only 6. 5GB of GPU memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-distillation-via-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-guided Federated Learning on Heterogeneous and Long-Tailed Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-guided-federated-learning-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For server-side learning, in order to mitigate the heterogeneity and class-distribution imbalance, we generate federated features to retrain the server model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-guided-federated-learning-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiPFT: Binary Pre-trained Foundation Transformer with Low-rank Estimation of Binarization Residual Polynomials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bipft-binary-pre-trained-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we first analyze the binarization error in self-attention operations and derive the polynomials of binarization error.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bipft-binary-pre-trained-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIT-UAS: A Wildland-fire Infrared Thermal Dataset to Detect Crew Assets From Aerial Views</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wit-uas-a-wildland-fire-infrared-thermal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Wildland-fire Infrared Thermal (WIT-UAS) dataset for long-wave infrared sensing of crew and vehicle assets amidst prescribed wildland fire environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wit-uas-a-wildland-fire-infrared-thermal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UCMCTrack: Multi-Object Tracking with Uniform Camera Motion Compensation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ucmctrack-multi-object-tracking-with-uniform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response to this, we introduce UCMCTrack, a novel motion model-based tracker robust to camera movements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ucmctrack-multi-object-tracking-with-uniform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incomplete Contrastive Multi-View Clustering with High-Confidence Guiding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incomplete-contrastive-multi-view-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we proposed a novel Incomplete Contrastive Multi-View Clustering method with high-confidence guiding (ICMVC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incomplete-contrastive-multi-view-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast sampling from constrained spaces using the Metropolis-adjusted Mirror Langevin Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-sampling-from-constrained-spaces-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This algorithm adds an accept-reject filter to the Markov chain induced by a single step of the mirror Langevin algorithm (Zhang et al., 2020), which is a basic discretisation of the mirror Langevin dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-sampling-from-constrained-spaces-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VSFormer: Visual-Spatial Fusion Transformer for Correspondence Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vsformer-visual-spatial-fusion-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Correspondence pruning aims to find correct matches (inliers) from an initial set of putative correspondences, which is a fundamental task for many applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vsformer-visual-spatial-fusion-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissecting vocabulary biases datasets through statistical testing and automated data augmentation for artifact mitigation in Natural Language Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dissecting-vocabulary-biases-datasets-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we focus on investigating dataset artifacts and developing strategies to address these issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dissecting-vocabulary-biases-datasets-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting value-expressive text posts in Russian social media</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-value-expressive-text-posts-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aimed to find a model that can accurately detect value-expressive posts in Russian social media VKontakte.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-value-expressive-text-posts-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMBHelper: A Neural Approach to Reduce Search Space for Graph Combinatorial Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combhelper-a-neural-approach-to-reduce-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combinatorial Optimization (CO) problems over graphs appear routinely in many applications such as in optimizing traffic, viral marketing in social networks, and matching for job allocation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combhelper-a-neural-approach-to-reduce-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detection and Defense of Unlearnable Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-and-defense-of-unlearnable-examples</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detectability of unlearnable examples with simple networks motivates us to design a novel defense method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-and-defense-of-unlearnable-examples</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust and Expressive Whole-body Human Pose and Shape Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-and-expressive-whole-body-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Whole-body pose and shape estimation aims to jointly predict different behaviors (e. g., pose, hand gesture, facial expression) of the entire human body from a monocular image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-and-expressive-whole-body-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Uncertain Feature Self-reinforcement for Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-uncertain-feature-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon this, we introduce a complementary self-enhancement method that constrains the semantic consistency between these confident regions and an augmented image with the same class labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-uncertain-feature-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PANDA: Architecture-Level Power Evaluation by Unifying Analytical and Machine Learning Solutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panda-architecture-level-power-evaluation-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the formulation, we propose PANDA, an innovative architecture-level solution that combines the advantages of analytical and ML power models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panda-architecture-level-power-evaluation-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Rewards in Multi-Agent Deep Reinforcement Learning for Autonomous Mobility on Demand Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-rewards-in-multi-agent-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study vehicle dispatching in autonomous mobility on demand (AMoD) systems, where a central operator assigns vehicles to customer requests or rejects these with the aim of maximizing its total profit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-rewards-in-multi-agent-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EAT: Towards Long-Tailed Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eat-towards-long-tailed-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main difficulty lies in distinguishing OOD data from samples belonging to the tail classes, as the ability of a classifier to detect OOD instances is not strongly correlated with its accuracy on the in-distribution classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eat-towards-long-tailed-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Complex Mathematical Reasoning via Large Language Model based MathAgent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-complex-mathematical-reasoning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) face challenges in solving complex mathematical problems that require comprehensive capacities to parse the statements, associate domain knowledge, perform compound logical reasoning, and integrate the intermediate rationales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-complex-mathematical-reasoning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weighted Ensemble Models Are Strong Continual Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-ensemble-models-are-strong-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose an improved variant of CoMA, named Continual Fisher-weighted Model Averaging (or CoFiMA), that selectively weighs each parameter in the weight ensemble by leveraging the Fisher information of the weights of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-ensemble-models-are-strong-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CattleEyeView: A Multi-task Top-down View Cattle Dataset for Smarter Precision Livestock Farming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cattleeyeview-a-multi-task-top-down-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cattle farming is one of the important and profitable agricultural industries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cattleeyeview-a-multi-task-top-down-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Polar Representation: An Extreme-Adaptive Model for Long-Term Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-polar-representation-an-extreme</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the hydrology field, time series forecasting is crucial for efficient water resource management, improving flood and drought control and increasing the safety and quality of life for the general population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-polar-representation-an-extreme</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factorization Vision Transformer: Modeling Long Range Dependency with Local Window Cost</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factorization-vision-transformer-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accordingly, we propose a novel factorization self-attention mechanism (FaSA) that enjoys both the advantages of local window cost and long-range dependency modeling capability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factorization-vision-transformer-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoom in on the Plant: Fine-grained Analysis of Leaf, Stem and Vein Instances</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zoom-in-on-the-plant-fine-grained-analysis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robot perception is far from what humans are capable of.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zoom-in-on-the-plant-fine-grained-analysis-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaxK-GNN: Towards Theoretical Speed Limits for Accelerating Graph Neural Networks Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maxk-gnn-towards-theoretical-speed-limits-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present MaxK-GNN, an advanced high-performance GPU training system integrating algorithm and system innovation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maxk-gnn-towards-theoretical-speed-limits-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning a Low-Rank Feature Representation: Achieving Better Trade-Off between Stability and Plasticity in Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-low-rank-feature-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach optimizes network parameters in the null space of the past tasks' feature representation matrix to guarantee the stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-low-rank-feature-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CT-MVSNet: Efficient Multi-View Stereo with Cross-scale Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ct-mvsnet-efficient-multi-view-stereo-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent deep multi-view stereo (MVS) methods have widely incorporated transformers into cascade network for high-resolution depth estimation, achieving impressive results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ct-mvsnet-efficient-multi-view-stereo-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Amplification by Iteration for ADMM with (Strongly) Convex Objective Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-amplification-by-iteration-for-admm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our main result is that the privacy guarantee for the gradient ADMM variant can be amplified proportionally to the number of iterations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-amplification-by-iteration-for-admm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greedy Shapley Client Selection for Communication-Efficient Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/greedy-shapley-client-selection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The standard client selection algorithms for Federated Learning (FL) are often unbiased and involve uniform random sampling of clients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/greedy-shapley-client-selection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZeroQuant(4+2): Redefining LLMs Quantization with a New FP6-Centric Strategy for Diverse Generative Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zeroquant-4-2-redefining-llms-quantization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With our design, FP6 can become a promising solution to the current 4-bit quantization methods used in LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zeroquant-4-2-redefining-llms-quantization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Conditional Controlling for Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-conditional-controlling-for-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a new simple yet practical task setting: local control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-conditional-controlling-for-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair Clustering: A Causal Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-clustering-a-causal-perspective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach enables the specification of the causal fairness metrics that should be minimised.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-clustering-a-causal-perspective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polyper: Boundary Sensitive Polyp Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyper-boundary-sensitive-polyp-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new boundary sensitive framework for polyp segmentation, called Polyper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyper-boundary-sensitive-polyp-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformalised data synthesis with statistical quality guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformalised-data-synthesis-with-statistical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the proliferation of ever more complicated Deep Learning architectures, data synthesis is a highly promising technique to address the demand of data-hungry models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformalised-data-synthesis-with-statistical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NestE: Modeling Nested Relational Structures for Knowledge Graph Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neste-modeling-nested-relational-structures</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NestE represents each atomic fact as a $1\times3$ matrix, and each nested relation is modeled as a $3\times3$ matrix that rotates the $1\times3$ atomic fact matrix through matrix multiplication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neste-modeling-nested-relational-structures</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Model-based Feature Knowledge Distillation for Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-model-based-feature-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing this gap, our paper introduces an innovative knowledge distillation framework, with the generative model for training a lightweight student model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-model-based-feature-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks with Diverse Spectral Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-with-diverse-spectral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spectral Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have achieved tremendous success in graph machine learning, with polynomial filters applied for graph convolutions, where all nodes share the identical filter weights to mine their local contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-with-diverse-spectral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient Informed Proximal Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-informed-proximal-policy-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel policy learning method that integrates analytical gradients from differentiable environments with the Proximal Policy Optimization (PPO) algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-informed-proximal-policy-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DriveMLM: Aligning Multi-Modal Large Language Models with Behavioral Planning States for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivemlm-aligning-multi-modal-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we delve into the potential of large language models (LLMs) in autonomous driving (AD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivemlm-aligning-multi-modal-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achelous++: Power-Oriented Water-Surface Panoptic Perception Framework on Edge Devices based on Vision-Radar Fusion and Pruning of Heterogeneous Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achelous-power-oriented-water-surface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Urban water-surface robust perception serves as the foundation for intelligent monitoring of aquatic environments and the autonomous navigation and operation of unmanned vessels, especially in the context of waterway safety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achelous-power-oriented-water-surface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Picture is Worth More Than 77 Text Tokens: Evaluating CLIP-Style Models on Dense Captions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-picture-is-worth-more-than-77-text-tokens</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Curation methods for massive vision-language datasets trade off between dataset size and quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-picture-is-worth-more-than-77-text-tokens</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
