<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 21:08:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>RealViformer: Investigating Attention for Real-World Video Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realviformer-investigating-attention-for-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, channel attention leads to feature redundancy, as evidenced by the higher covariance among output channels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realviformer-investigating-attention-for-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLAudio Listens to the Sound of the Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glaudio-listens-to-the-sound-of-the-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose GLAudio: Graph Learning on Audio representation of the node features and the connectivity structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glaudio-listens-to-the-sound-of-the-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompted Aspect Key Point Analysis for Quantitative Review Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompted-aspect-key-point-analysis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A majority of KPA studies for reviews adopt supervised learning to extract short sentences as KPs before matching KPs to review comments for quantification of KP prevalence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompted-aspect-key-point-analysis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Token-level Correlation-guided Compression for Efficient Multimodal Document Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-level-correlation-guided-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, we present a token-level sampling method that efficiently captures the most informative tokens by delving into the correlation between the [CLS] token and patch tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-level-correlation-guided-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAG-QA Arena: Evaluating Domain Robustness for Long-form Retrieval Augmented Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rag-qa-arena-evaluating-domain-robustness-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Question answering based on retrieval augmented generation (RAG-QA) is an important research topic in NLP and has a wide range of real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rag-qa-arena-evaluating-domain-robustness-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETSCL: An Evidence Theory-Based Supervised Contrastive Learning Framework for Multi-modal Glaucoma Grading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/etscl-an-evidence-theory-based-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, existing methods overlook the uncertainty estimation of different modalities, leading to unreliable predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/etscl-an-evidence-theory-based-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Reliability of Self-Explanations in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-reliability-of-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the reliability of explanations generated by large language models (LLMs) when prompted to explain their previous output.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-reliability-of-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Audio Open</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-audio-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open generative models are vitally important for the community, allowing for fine-tunes and serving as baselines when presenting new models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-audio-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mono-ViFI: A Unified Learning Framework for Self-supervised Single- and Multi-frame Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mono-vifi-a-unified-learning-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The single- and multi-frame models can share weights, making our framework compact and memory-efficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mono-vifi-a-unified-learning-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Frequency Enhancement Network for Single Image Deraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-frequency-enhancement-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We employ convolutions of different scales to adaptively decompose image frequency bands, introduce a feature enhancement module to boost the features of different frequency components and present a novel interaction module for interchanging and merging information from various frequency branches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-frequency-enhancement-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MC-PanDA: Mask Confidence for Panoptic Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mc-panda-mask-confidence-for-panoptic-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous state of the art addresses this problem with cross-task consistency, careful system-level optimization and heuristic improvement of teacher predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mc-panda-mask-confidence-for-panoptic-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Post hoc Portfolio Management Financial Policy of a Deep Reinforcement Learning agent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-post-hoc-portfolio-management</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By executing our methodology, we can interpret in prediction time the actions of the agent to assess whether they follow the requisites of an investment policy or to assess the risk of following the agent suggestions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-post-hoc-portfolio-management</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECCO: Can We Improve Model-Generated Code Efficiency Without Sacrificing Functional Correctness?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecco-can-we-improve-model-generated-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although large language models (LLMs) have been largely successful in generating functionally correct programs, conditioning models to produce efficient solutions while ensuring correctness remains a challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecco-can-we-improve-model-generated-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch-based Intuitive Multimodal Prototypes Network (PIMPNet) for Alzheimer's Disease classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-based-intuitive-multimodal-prototypes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present PIMPNet, the first interpretable multimodal model for 3D images and demographics applied to the binary classification of AD from 3D sMRI and patient's age.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-based-intuitive-multimodal-prototypes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>System-1.x: Learning to Balance Fast and Slow Planning with Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/system-1-x-learning-to-balance-fast-and-slow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose the System-1. x Planner, a controllable planning framework with LLMs that is capable of generating hybrid plans and balancing between the two planning modes based on the difficulty of the problem at hand.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/system-1-x-learning-to-balance-fast-and-slow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieving Well-Informed Decision-Making in Drug Discovery: A Comprehensive Calibration Study using Neural Network-Based Structure-Activity Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-well-informed-decision-making-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we show that combining post hoc calibration method with well-performing uncertainty quantification approaches can boost model accuracy and calibration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-well-informed-decision-making-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cardinality of Identifying Code Sets for Soccer Ball Graph with Application to Remote Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-cardinality-of-identifying-code-sets-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of satellite monitoring of the earth, we can assume that the surface of the earth is divided into a set of regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-cardinality-of-identifying-code-sets-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L^2CL: Embarrassingly Simple Layer-to-Layer Contrastive Learning for Graph Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l-2cl-embarrassingly-simple-layer-to-layer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Surprisingly, we find that L2CL, using only one-hop contrastive learning paradigm, is able to capture intrinsic semantic structures and improve the quality of node representation, leading to a simple yet effective architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l-2cl-embarrassingly-simple-layer-to-layer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Improved Method for Class-specific Keyword Extraction: A Case Study in the German Business Registry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-improved-method-for-class-specific-keyword</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of $\textit{keyword extraction}$ is often an important initial step in unsupervised information extraction, forming the basis for tasks such as topic modeling or document classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-improved-method-for-class-specific-keyword</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLAssist: Simple Tools for Automating Literature Review Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llassist-simple-tools-for-automating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces LLAssist, an open-source tool designed to streamline literature reviews in academic research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llassist-simple-tools-for-automating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmark for Gaussian Splatting Compression and Quality Assessment Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, based on GGSC, we create a GS Quality Assessment dataset (GSQA) with 120 samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TTT: A Temporal Refinement Heuristic for Tenuously Tractable Discrete Time Reachability Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ttt-a-temporal-refinement-heuristic-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we introduce an automatic framework for performing temporal refinement and we demonstrate the effectiveness of this technique on computing approximate reachable sets for nonlinear systems with neural network control policies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ttt-a-temporal-refinement-heuristic-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Group Robustness is in the Details: Revisiting Finetuning under Spurious Correlations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-group-robustness-is-in-the-details</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern machine learning models are prone to over-reliance on spurious correlations, which can often lead to poor performance on minority groups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-group-robustness-is-in-the-details</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indoor Air Quality Dataset with Activities of Daily Living in Low to Middle-income Communities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indoor-air-quality-dataset-with-activities-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, indoor air pollution has posed a significant threat to our society, claiming over 3. 2 million lives annually.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indoor-air-quality-dataset-with-activities-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataset Distillation by Automatic Training Trajectories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-distillation-by-automatic-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dataset Distillation is used to create a concise, yet informative, synthetic dataset that can replace the original dataset for training purposes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-distillation-by-automatic-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PolyFormer: Scalable Node-wise Filters via Polynomial Graph Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyformer-scalable-node-wise-filters-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, many current methods focus on employing shared polynomial coefficients for all nodes, i. e., learning node-unified filters, which limits the filters' flexibility for node-level tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyformer-scalable-node-wise-filters-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Underwater Gesture Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-underwater-gesture-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we advocate the need for zero-shot underwater gesture recognition (ZSUGR), where the objective is to train a model with visual samples of gestures from a few ``seen'' classes only and transfer the gained knowledge at test time to recognize semantically-similar unseen gesture classes as well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-underwater-gesture-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Preparation Pays Off: New Classifier Pre-tuning for Class Incremental Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-preparation-pays-off-new-classifier-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new classifier pre-tuning~(NeST) method applied before the formal training process, learning a transformation from old classifiers to generate new classifiers for initialization rather than directly tuning the parameters of new classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-preparation-pays-off-new-classifier-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reexamining Racial Disparities in Automatic Speech Recognition Performance: The Role of Confounding by Provenance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reexamining-racial-disparities-in-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic speech recognition (ASR) models trained on large amounts of audio data are now widely used to convert speech to written text in a variety of applications from video captioning to automated assistants used in healthcare and other domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reexamining-racial-disparities-in-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Text Generation in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-text-generation-in-the-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, it is still challenging to render high-quality text images in real-world scenarios, as three critical criteria should be satisfied: (1) Fidelity: the generated text images should be photo-realistic and the contents are expected to be the same as specified in the given conditions; (2) Reasonability: the regions and contents of the generated text should cohere with the scene; (3) Utility: the generated text images can facilitate related tasks (e. g., text detection and recognition).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-text-generation-in-the-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Panoptic Perception: Towards Multi-modal Incremental Interpretation of Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-panoptic-perception-towards-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Continual Panoptic Perception (CPP), a unified continual learning model that leverages multi-task joint learning covering pixel-level classification, instance-level segmentation and image-level perception for universal interpretation in remote sensing images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-panoptic-perception-towards-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Kernel Distillation Network for Efficient Single Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-kernel-distillation-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficient and lightweight single-image super-resolution (SISR) has achieved remarkable performance in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-kernel-distillation-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving GBDT Performance on Imbalanced Datasets: An Empirical Study of Class-Balanced Loss Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-gbdt-performance-on-imbalanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Class imbalance remains a significant challenge in machine learning, particularly for tabular data classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-gbdt-performance-on-imbalanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Privacy Protection Mask Against Unauthorized Facial Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-privacy-protection-mask-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we incorporate a perceptibility optimization to preserve the visual quality of the protected facial images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-privacy-protection-mask-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Inference with Complex Treatments: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-inference-with-complex-treatments-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal inference plays an important role in explanatory analysis and decision making across various fields like statistics, marketing, health care, and education.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-inference-with-complex-treatments-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Attention-based Representation Distillation Baseline for Multi-Label Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attention-based-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It relies on a knowledge transfer technique that seeks to align the representations of the student network -- which trains continuously and is subject to forgetting -- with the teacher ones, which is pretrained and kept frozen.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attention-based-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Classification of News Subjects in Broadcast News: Application to a Gender Bias Representation Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-classification-of-news-subjects-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using the generated LLM annotations, we explore the finetuning of a specialized smaller classification model, to reduce the computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-classification-of-news-subjects-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internal Consistency and Self-Feedback in Large Language Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internal-consistency-and-self-feedback-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we summarize a theoretical framework, termed Internal Consistency, which offers unified explanations for phenomena such as the lack of reasoning and the presence of hallucinations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internal-consistency-and-self-feedback-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Study of Deep Reinforcement Learning Models: DQN vs PPO vs A2C</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-deep-reinforcement-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study conducts a comparative analysis of three advanced Deep Reinforcement Learning models: Deep Q-Networks (DQN), Proximal Policy Optimization (PPO), and Advantage Actor-Critic (A2C), within the BreakOut Atari game environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-deep-reinforcement-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Byzantine-tolerant distributed learning of finite mixture models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/byzantine-tolerant-distributed-learning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes two split-and-conquer (SC) learning estimators for finite mixture models that are tolerant to Byzantine failures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/byzantine-tolerant-distributed-learning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longhorn: State Space Models are Amortized Online Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longhorn-state-space-models-are-amortized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore SSM design through the lens of online learning, conceptualizing SSMs as meta-modules for specific online learning problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longhorn-state-space-models-are-amortized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaGAT: Topology-Aware Graph Attention Network For Multi-modal Retinal Image Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tagat-topology-aware-graph-attention-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of medical image fusion, integrating information from various modalities is crucial for improving diagnostics and treatment planning, especially in retinal health, where the important features exhibit differently in different imaging modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tagat-topology-aware-graph-attention-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed-precision Neural Networks on RISC-V Cores: ISA extensions for Multi-Pumped Soft SIMD Operations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-precision-neural-networks-on-risc-v</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At hardware level, we firstly expand the ALU unit within our proof-of-concept micro-architecture to support configurable fine grained mixed-precision arithmetic operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-precision-neural-networks-on-risc-v</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucketed Ranking-based Losses for Efficient Training of Object Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bucketed-ranking-based-losses-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, they require pairwise comparisons among $P$ positive and $N$ negative predictions, introducing a time complexity of $\mathcal{O}(PN)$, which is prohibitive since $N$ is often large (e. g., $10^8$ in ATSS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bucketed-ranking-based-losses-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6DoF Head Pose Estimation through Explicit Bidirectional Interaction with Face Geometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/6dof-head-pose-estimation-through-explicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study addresses the nuanced challenge of estimating head translations within the context of six-degrees-of-freedom (6DoF) head pose estimation, placing emphasis on this aspect over the more commonly studied head rotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/6dof-head-pose-estimation-through-explicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complementary Learning for Real-World Model Failure Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complementary-learning-for-real-world-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In real-world autonomous driving, deep learning models can experience performance degradation due to distributional shifts between the training data and the driving conditions encountered.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complementary-learning-for-real-world-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlacidDreamer: Advancing Harmony in Text-to-3D Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/placiddreamer-advancing-harmony-in-text-to-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous methods utilize end-to-end 3D generation models to initialize 3D Gaussians, multi-view diffusion models to enforce multi-view consistency, and text-to-image diffusion models to refine details with score distillation algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/placiddreamer-advancing-harmony-in-text-to-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Effect of Training Schedules on Morphological Robustness and Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-training-schedules-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we define various training schedules to specify how these variations are introduced during an evolutionary learning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-training-schedules-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Visual Content Refinement in Low-Shot CLIP Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-visual-content-refinement-in-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these adaptation methods are usually operated on the global view of an input image, and thus biased perception of partial local details of the image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-visual-content-refinement-in-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurvReLU: Inherently Interpretable Survival Analysis via Deep ReLU Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survrelu-inherently-interpretable-survival</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, deep survival models using neural networks have dominated due to their representational power and state-of-the-art performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survrelu-inherently-interpretable-survival</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
