<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 21:07:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Intrinsic Manifolds of Radiological Images and their Role in Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-intrinsic-manifolds-of-radiological</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These results give a more principled underpinning for the intuition that radiological images can be more challenging to apply deep learning to than natural image datasets common to machine learning research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-intrinsic-manifolds-of-radiological</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOv7: Trainable bag-of-freebies sets new state-of-the-art for real-time object detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov7-trainable-bag-of-freebies-sets-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[YOLOv7 surpasses all known object detectors in both speed and accuracy in the range from 5 FPS to 160 FPS and has the highest accuracy 56. 8% AP among all known real-time object detectors with 30 FPS or higher on GPU V100.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov7-trainable-bag-of-freebies-sets-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Histopathology DatasetGAN: Synthesizing Large-Resolution Histopathology Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histopathology-datasetgan-synthesizing-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning (SSL) methods are enabling an increasing number of deep learning models to be trained on image datasets in domains where labels are difficult to obtain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histopathology-datasetgan-synthesizing-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Domain Adaptation through Shape Modeling for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-through-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous methods proposed Variational Autoencoder (VAE) based models to learn the distribution of shape for a particular organ and used it to automatically evaluate the quality of a segmentation prediction by fitting it into the learned shape distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-through-shape</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Pay Attention to the Noise: Learning Self-supervised Representations of Light Curves with a Denoising Time Series Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-pay-attention-to-the-noise-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Astrophysical light curves are particularly challenging data objects due to the intensity and variety of noise contaminating them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-pay-attention-to-the-noise-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAMa: Cross-view Video Geo-localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gama-cross-view-video-geo-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are no existing datasets for this problem, therefore we propose GAMa dataset, a large-scale dataset with ground videos and corresponding aerial images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gama-cross-view-video-geo-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCT-Net: Domain-Calibrated Translation for Portrait Stylization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dct-net-domain-calibrated-translation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces DCT-Net, a novel image translation architecture for few-shot portrait stylization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dct-net-domain-calibrated-translation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tractable Dendritic RNNs for Reconstructing Nonlinear Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tractable-dendritic-rnns-for-reconstructing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many scientific disciplines, we are interested in inferring the nonlinear dynamical system underlying a set of observed time series, a challenging task in the face of chaotic behavior and noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tractable-dendritic-rnns-for-reconstructing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch-wise Deep Metric Learning for Unsupervised Low-Dose CT Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-wise-deep-metric-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The acquisition conditions for low-dose and high-dose CT images are usually different, so that the shifts in the CT numbers often occur.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-wise-deep-metric-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Value of Gazetteer in Chinese Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-value-of-gazetteer-in-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gazetteer is widely used in Chinese named entity recognition (NER) to enhance span boundary detection and type classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-value-of-gazetteer-in-chinese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAST-VQA: Efficient End-to-end Video Quality Assessment with Fragment Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-vqa-efficient-end-to-end-video-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consisting of fragments and FANet, the proposed FrAgment Sample Transformer for VQA (FAST-VQA) enables efficient end-to-end deep VQA and learns effective video-quality-related representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-vqa-efficient-end-to-end-video-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional Distribution Function Estimation Using Neural Networks for Censored and Uncensored Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-distribution-function-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most work in neural networks focuses on estimating the conditional mean of a continuous response variable given a set of covariates. In this article, we consider estimating the conditional distribution function using neural networks for both censored and uncensored data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-distribution-function-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is the U-Net Directional-Relationship Aware?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-the-u-net-directional-relationship-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CNNs are often assumed to be capable of using contextual information about distinct objects (such as their directional relations) inside their receptive field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-the-u-net-directional-relationship-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network Pruning via Feature Shift Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-pruning-via-feature-shift</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel Feature Shift Minimization (FSM) method to compress CNN models, which evaluates the feature shift by converging the information of both features and filters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-pruning-via-feature-shift</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Learning System for Motion Planning of Free-Float Dual-Arm Space Manipulator towards Non-Cooperative Object</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-learning-system-for-motion-planning-of-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Module I realizes the multi-target trajectory planning for two end-effectors within a large target space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-learning-system-for-motion-planning-of-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Relighting of Real Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-relighting-of-real-scenes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the task of local relighting, which changes a photograph of a scene by switching on and off the light sources that are visible within the image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-relighting-of-real-scenes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chairs Can be Stood on: Overcoming Object Bias in Human-Object Interaction Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chairs-can-be-stood-on-overcoming-object-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To quantitatively study the object bias problem, we advocate a new protocol for evaluating model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chairs-can-be-stood-on-overcoming-object-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Counterfactual Image Manipulation via CLIP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-counterfactual-image-manipulation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we design a simple yet effective scheme that explicitly maps CLIP embeddings (of target text) to the latent space and fuses them with latent codes for effective latent code optimization and accurate editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-counterfactual-image-manipulation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifying and Mitigating Flaws of Deep Perceptual Similarity Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-and-mitigating-flaws-of-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work investigates the most common DPS metric, where deep features are compared by spatial position, along with metrics comparing the averaged and sorted deep features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-and-mitigating-flaws-of-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GFNet: Geometric Flow Network for 3D Point Cloud Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gfnet-geometric-flow-network-for-3d-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, recent projection-based methods for point cloud semantic segmentation usually utilize a vanilla late fusion strategy for the predictions of different views, failing to explore the complementary information from a geometric perspective during the representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gfnet-geometric-flow-network-for-3d-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Light-weight spatio-temporal graphs for segmentation and ejection fraction prediction in cardiac ultrasound</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/light-weight-spatio-temporal-graphs-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, segmentations of the left ventricle can be used to derive ventricular volume, ejection fraction (EF) and other relevant measurements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/light-weight-spatio-temporal-graphs-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Language Left Behind: Scaling Human-Centered Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-language-left-behind-scaling-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driven by the goal of eradicating language barriers on a global scale, machine translation has solidified itself as a key focus of artificial intelligence research today.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-language-left-behind-scaling-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strong Heuristics for Named Entity Linking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strong-heuristics-for-named-entity-linking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Named entity linking (NEL) in news is a challenging endeavour due to the frequency of unseen and emerging entities, which necessitates the use of unsupervised or zero-shot methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strong-heuristics-for-named-entity-linking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-area Target Individual Detection with Free Drawing on Video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-area-target-individual-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper has provided a novel design idea and some implementation methods to make a real time detection of multi-areas with multiple detecting areas that are generated by the real time drawing on the screen display of the video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-area-target-individual-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3DG-STFM: 3D Geometric Guided Student-Teacher Feature Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dg-stfm-3d-geometric-guided-student-teacher</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, 3DG-STFM is the first student-teacher learning method for the local feature matching task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dg-stfm-3d-geometric-guided-student-teacher</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Adaptive Video Segmentation via Temporal Pseudo Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-video-segmentation-via-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we design cross-frame pseudo labelling to provide pseudo supervision from previous video frames while learning from the augmented current video frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-video-segmentation-via-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compositional Generalization in Grounded Language Learning via Induced Model Sparsity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-generalization-in-grounded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide a study of how induced model sparsity can help achieve compositional generalization and better sample efficiency in grounded language learning problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-generalization-in-grounded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeRL: Mastering Code Generation through Pretrained Models and Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coderl-mastering-code-generation-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the limitations, we propose "CodeRL", a new framework for program synthesis tasks through pretrained LMs and deep reinforcement learning (RL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coderl-mastering-code-generation-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Array Camera Image Fusion using Physics-Aware Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/array-camera-image-fusion-using-physics-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate a physics-aware transformer for feature-based data fusion from cameras with diverse resolution, color spaces, focal planes, focal lengths, and exposure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/array-camera-image-fusion-using-physics-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guiding Machine Perception with Psychophysics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-machine-perception-with-psychophysics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[{G}{ustav} Fechner's 1860 delineation of psychophysics, the measurement of sensation in relation to its stimulus, is widely considered to be the advent of modern psychological science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-machine-perception-with-psychophysics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSFormer: One-Stage Camouflaged Instance Segmentation with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/osformer-one-stage-camouflaged-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present OSFormer, the first one-stage transformer framework for camouflaged instance segmentation (CIS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/osformer-one-stage-camouflaged-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pretraining on Interactions for Learning Grounded Affordance Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pretraining-on-interactions-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lexical semantics and cognitive science point to affordances (i. e. the actions that objects support) as critical for understanding and representing nouns and verbs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pretraining-on-interactions-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiPOCO: Bi-Directional Trajectory Prediction with Pose Constraints for Pedestrian Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bipoco-bi-directional-trajectory-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present BiPOCO, a Bi-directional trajectory predictor with POse COnstraints, for detecting anomalous activities of pedestrians in videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bipoco-bi-directional-trajectory-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Trajectory Prediction for Pedestrian Video Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-trajectory-prediction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video anomaly detection is a core problem in vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-trajectory-prediction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCHOS: Stochastic Opportunistic Maintenance Scheduling For Offshore Wind Farms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochos-stochastic-opportunistic-maintenance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the promising outlook, the numerous economic and environmental benefits of offshore wind energy are still compromised by its high operations and maintenance (O&M) expenditures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochos-stochastic-opportunistic-maintenance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Learning a Real-Time Tabular AutoML Method For Small Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-a-real-time-tabular-automl</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our AutoML method is meta-learned using the Transformer-based Prior-Data Fitted Network (PFN) architecture and approximates Bayesian inference with a prior that is based on assumptions of simplicity and causal structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-a-real-time-tabular-automl</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Spatial-Temporal Information Fusion for LiDAR-Based 3D Moving Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-spatial-temporal-information-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also use a point refinement module via 3D sparse convolution to fuse the information from both LiDAR range image and point cloud representations and reduce the artifacts on the borders of the objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-spatial-temporal-information-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Covariance Conditioning of the SVD Meta-layer by Orthogonality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-covariance-conditioning-of-the-svd</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inserting an SVD meta-layer into neural networks is prone to make the covariance ill-conditioned, which could harm the model in the training stability and generalization abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-covariance-conditioning-of-the-svd</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReMix: A General and Efficient Framework for Multiple Instance Learning based Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remix-a-general-and-efficient-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate ReMix on two public datasets with two state-of-the-art MIL methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remix-a-general-and-efficient-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Meta-Learning Framework for Dynamic Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-meta-learning-framework-for-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transfer learning refers to the transfer of knowledge or information from a relevant source task to a target task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-meta-learning-framework-for-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Game Levels of Diverse Behaviour Engagement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-game-levels-of-diverse-behaviour</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years, there has been growing interests in experience-driven procedural level generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-game-levels-of-diverse-behaviour</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuralPassthrough: Learned Real-Time View Synthesis for VR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralpassthrough-learned-real-time-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Virtual reality (VR) headsets provide an immersive, stereoscopic visual experience, but at the cost of blocking users from directly observing their physical environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralpassthrough-learned-real-time-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The StarCraft Multi-Agent Challenges+ : Learning of Multi-Stage Tasks and Environmental Factors without Precise Reward Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-starcraft-multi-agent-challenges-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This challenge, on the other hand, is interested in the exploration capability of MARL algorithms to efficiently learn implicit multi-stage tasks and environmental factors as well as micro-control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-starcraft-multi-agent-challenges-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-modal Robustness Analysis Against Language and Visual Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-robustness-analysis-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we perform the first extensive robustness study of such models against various real-world perturbations focusing on video and language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-robustness-analysis-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vector Quantisation for Robust Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vector-quantisation-for-robust-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The reliability of segmentation models in the medical domain depends on the model's robustness to perturbations in the input space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vector-quantisation-for-robust-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRoA: A Probabilistic Robustness Assessment against Functional Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proa-a-probabilistic-robustness-assessment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments demonstrate the effectiveness and flexibility of PRoA in terms of evaluating the probabilistic robustness against a broad range of functional perturbations, and PRoA can scale well to various large-scale deep neural networks compared to existing state-of-the-art baselines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proa-a-probabilistic-robustness-assessment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Features Based Adaptive Augmentation for Graph Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/features-based-adaptive-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-Supervised learning aims to eliminate the need for expensive annotation in graph representation learning, where graph contrastive learning (GCL) is trained with the self-supervision signals containing data-data pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/features-based-adaptive-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoF: Post-Training of Feature Extractor for Improving Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pof-post-training-of-feature-extractor-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We developed a training algorithm called PoF: Post-Training of Feature Extractor that updates the feature extractor part of an already-trained deep model to search a flatter minimum.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pof-post-training-of-feature-extractor-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and Improving Group Normalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-improving-group</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Various normalization layers have been proposed to help the training of neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-improving-group</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AvatarCap: Animatable Avatar Conditioned Monocular Human Volumetric Capture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avatarcap-animatable-avatar-conditioned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then given a monocular RGB video of this subject, our method integrates information from both the image observation and the avatar prior, and accordingly recon-structs high-fidelity 3D textured models with dynamic details regardless of the visibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avatarcap-animatable-avatar-conditioned</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
