<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 21:05:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>IUST at ClimateActivism 2024: Towards Optimal Stance Detection: A Systematic Study of Architectural Choices and Data Cleaning Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iust-at-climateactivism-2024-towards-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents a systematic search of various model architecture configurations and data cleaning methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iust-at-climateactivism-2024-towards-optimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Model Ensemble Approach with LLM for Chinese Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-model-ensemble-approach-with-llm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic medical text categorization can assist doctors in efficiently managing patient information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-model-ensemble-approach-with-llm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recovering Latent Confounders from High-dimensional Proxy Variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recovering-latent-confounders-from-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting latent confounders from proxy variables is an essential problem in causal effect estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recovering-latent-confounders-from-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reactor Optimization Benchmark by Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reactor-optimization-benchmark-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neutronic calculations for reactors are a daunting task when using Monte Carlo (MC) methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reactor-optimization-benchmark-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pensieve: Retrospect-then-Compare Mitigates Visual Hallucination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pensieve-retrospect-then-compare-mitigates</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal Large Language Models (MLLMs) demonstrate remarkable success across various vision-language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pensieve-retrospect-then-compare-mitigates</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Segmentation Ability to Multi-modal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-segmentation-ability-to-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal large language models (MLLMs) can understand image-language prompts and demonstrate impressive reasoning ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-segmentation-ability-to-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact Assessment of Missing Data in Model Predictions for Earth Observation Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-assessment-of-missing-data-in-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we assess the impact of missing temporal and static EO sources in trained models across four datasets with classification and regression tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-assessment-of-missing-data-in-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OA-CNNs: Omni-Adaptive Sparse CNNs for 3D Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oa-cnns-omni-adaptive-sparse-cnns-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This exploration led to the creation of Omni-Adaptive 3D CNNs (OA-CNNs), a family of networks that integrates a lightweight module to greatly enhance the adaptivity of sparse CNNs at minimal computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oa-cnns-omni-adaptive-sparse-cnns-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spanning Multi-Asset Payoffs With ReLUs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spanning-multi-asset-payoffs-with-relus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a distributional formulation of the spanning problem of a multi-asset payoff by vanilla basket options.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spanning-multi-asset-payoffs-with-relus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lightweight Attention-based Deep Network via Multi-Scale Feature Fusion for Multi-View Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-attention-based-deep-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, the PWFS block employs a feature selection mechanism that discards less meaningful features prior to the fusion process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-attention-based-deep-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplified Diffusion Schrödinger Bridge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplified-diffusion-schrodinger-bridge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel theoretical simplification of the Diffusion Schr\"odinger Bridge (DSB) that facilitates its unification with Score-based Generative Models (SGMs), addressing the limitations of DSB in complex data generation and enabling faster convergence and enhanced performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplified-diffusion-schrodinger-bridge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-Rex2: Towards Generic Object Detection via Text-Visual Prompt Synergy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-rex2-towards-generic-object-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizing the complementary strengths and weaknesses of both text and visual prompts, we introduce T-Rex2 that synergizes both prompts within a single model through contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-rex2-towards-generic-object-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>covSTATIS: a multi-table technique for network neuroscience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covstatis-a-multi-table-technique-for-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Similarity analyses between multiple correlation or covariance tables constitute the cornerstone of network neuroscience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covstatis-a-multi-table-technique-for-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Enhanced Data-free Approach for Federated Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-enhanced-data-free-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this field, Data-Free Knowledge Transfer (DFKT) plays a crucial role in addressing catastrophic forgetting and data privacy problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-enhanced-data-free-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Vocabulary Attention Maps with Token Optimization for Semantic Segmentation in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-attention-maps-with-token</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach limits the generation of segmentation masks derived from word tokens not contained in the text prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-attention-maps-with-token</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAC: Hash-grid Assisted Context for 3D Gaussian Splatting Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hac-hash-grid-assisted-context-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) has emerged as a promising framework for novel view synthesis, boasting rapid rendering speed with high fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hac-hash-grid-assisted-context-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View-decoupled Transformer for Person Re-identification under Aerial-ground Camera Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/view-decoupled-transformer-for-person-re</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on two datasets show that VDT is a feasible and effective solution for AGPReID, surpassing the previous method on mAP/Rank1 by up to 5. 0%/2. 7% on CARGO and 3. 7%/5. 2% on AG-ReID, keeping the same magnitude of computational complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/view-decoupled-transformer-for-person-re</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiFactDiff: A Large, Realistic, and Temporally Adaptable Dataset for Atomic Factual Knowledge Update in Causal Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikifactdiff-a-large-realistic-and-temporally</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To study this task, we present WikiFactDiff, a dataset that describes the evolution of factual knowledge between two dates as a collection of simple facts divided into three categories: new, obsolete, and static.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikifactdiff-a-large-realistic-and-temporally</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DomainLab: A modular Python package for domain generalization in deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domainlab-a-modular-python-package-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DomainLab is a modular Python package for training user specified neural networks with composable regularization loss terms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domainlab-a-modular-python-package-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-Enhanced Recommendation with User-Centric Subgraph Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-enhanced-recommendation-with-user</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommendation systems, as widely implemented nowadays on various platforms, recommend relevant items to users based on their preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-enhanced-recommendation-with-user</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSALM: Pixelwise SegmentAtion with Large Multi-Modal Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psalm-pixelwise-segmentation-with-large-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PSALM is a powerful extension of the Large Multi-modal Model (LMM) to address the segmentation task challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psalm-pixelwise-segmentation-with-large-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperGALE: ASD Classification via Hypergraph Gated Attention with Learnable Hyperedges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypergale-asd-classification-via-hypergraph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autism Spectrum Disorder (ASD) is a neurodevelopmental condition characterized by varied social cognitive challenges and repetitive behavioral patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypergale-asd-classification-via-hypergraph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HETAL: Efficient Privacy-preserving Transfer Learning with Homomorphic Encryption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hetal-efficient-privacy-preserving-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although numerous previous studies proposed to use homomorphic encryption to resolve the data privacy issue in transfer learning in the machine learning as a service setting, most of them only focused on encrypted inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hetal-efficient-privacy-preserving-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRM: Large Gaussian Reconstruction Model for Efficient 3D Reconstruction and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grm-large-gaussian-reconstruction-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce GRM, a large-scale reconstructor capable of recovering a 3D asset from sparse-view images in around 0. 1s.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grm-large-gaussian-reconstruction-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Historical Image Retrieval with Compositional Cues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-historical-image-retrieval-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In analyzing vast amounts of digitally stored historical image data, existing content-based retrieval methods often overlook significant non-semantic information, limiting their effectiveness for flexible exploration across varied themes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-historical-image-retrieval-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loop Improvement: An Efficient Approach for Extracting Shared Features from Heterogeneous Data without Central Server</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loop-improvement-an-efficient-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LI integrates a loop topology with layer-wise and end-to-end training, compatible with various neural network models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loop-improvement-an-efficient-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Framework for Model Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-framework-for-model-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With EMMET, we present a closed form solution for the equality-constrained version of the preservation-memorization objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-framework-for-model-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Static and Dynamic Network: Efficient Temporal Filtering for Video Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-static-and-dynamic-network-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the activity-silent and persistent activity mechanisms in human visual perception biology, we design a Unified Static and Dynamic Network (UniSDNet), to learn the semantic association between the video and text/audio queries in a cross-modal environment for efficient video grounding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-static-and-dynamic-network-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobra: Extending Mamba to Multi-Modal Large Language Model for Efficient Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cobra-extending-mamba-to-multi-modal-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the application of multimodal large language models (MLLM) in various fields has achieved remarkable success.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cobra-extending-mamba-to-multi-modal-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Chinese Commonsense Reasoning of LLMs: From Chinese-Specifics to Reasoning-Memorization Correlations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-chinese-commonsense-reasoning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce CHARM, the first benchmark for comprehensively and in-depth evaluating the commonsense reasoning ability of large language models (LLMs) in Chinese, which covers both globally known and Chinese-specific commonsense.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-chinese-commonsense-reasoning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftPatch: Unsupervised Anomaly Detection with Noisy Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softpatch-unsupervised-anomaly-detection-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Noise discriminators are utilized to generate outlier scores for patch-level noise elimination before coreset construction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softpatch-unsupervised-anomaly-detection-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVSplat: Efficient 3D Gaussian Splatting from Sparse Multi-View Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvsplat-efficient-3d-gaussian-splatting-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose MVSplat, an efficient feed-forward 3D Gaussian Splatting model learned from sparse multi-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvsplat-efficient-3d-gaussian-splatting-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A reinforcement learning guided hybrid evolutionary algorithm for the latency location routing problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reinforcement-learning-guided-hybrid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The latency location routing problem integrates the facility location problem and the multi-depot cumulative capacitated vehicle routing problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reinforcement-learning-guided-hybrid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning for Trajectory Data Management and Mining: A Survey and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-trajectory-data-management</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a comprehensive review of the development and recent advances in deep learning for trajectory computing (DL4Traj).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-trajectory-data-management</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetic Programming for Explainable Manifold Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genetic-programming-for-explainable-manifold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental analysis demonstrates that GP-EMaL is able to match the performance of the existing approach in most cases, while using simpler, smaller, and more interpretable tree structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genetic-programming-for-explainable-manifold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Concept Trustworthiness in Concept Bottleneck Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-concept-trustworthiness-in-concept</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concept Bottleneck Models (CBMs), which break down the reasoning process into the input-to-concept mapping and the concept-to-label prediction, have garnered significant attention due to their remarkable interpretability achieved by the interpretable concept bottleneck.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-concept-trustworthiness-in-concept</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less but Better: Enabling Generalized Zero-shot Learning Towards Unseen Domains by Intrinsic Learning from Redundant LLM Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-but-better-enabling-generalized-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from existing GZSL methods which alleviate DSP by generating features of unseen classes with semantics, CDGZSL needs to construct a common feature space across domains and acquire the corresponding intrinsic semantics shared among domains to transfer from seen to unseen domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-but-better-enabling-generalized-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Image Classification Accuracy through Complementary Intra-Class and Inter-Class Mixup</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-image-classification-accuracy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, our integrated solution seamlessly combines our intra-class mixup method with an existing mixup approach such as MixUp or Manifold MixUp.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-image-classification-accuracy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaIR: Adaptive All-in-One Image Restoration via Frequency Mining and Modulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adair-adaptive-all-in-one-image-restoration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach is motivated by the observation that different degradation types impact the image content on different frequency subbands, thereby requiring different treatments for each restoration task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adair-adaptive-all-in-one-image-restoration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine-learning invariant foliations in forced systems for reduced order modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-invariant-foliations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We identify reduced order models (ROM) of forced systems from data using invariant foliations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-invariant-foliations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Models with Ensembled Structure-Based Anomaly Scoring for Unsupervised Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-with-ensembled-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that this ensembling strategy can enhance the performance of DMs and mitigate the sensitivity to different kernel sizes across varying pathologies, highlighting its promise for brain MRI anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-with-ensembled-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMIDR: Teaching Large Language Model to Interpret Multimodal Misinformation via Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmidr-teaching-large-language-model-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic detection of multimodal misinformation has gained a widespread attention recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmidr-teaching-large-language-model-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpikingResformer: Bridging ResNet and Vision Transformer in Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spikingresformer-bridging-resnet-and-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on DSSA, we propose a novel spiking Vision Transformer architecture called SpikingResformer, which combines the ResNet-based multi-stage architecture with our proposed DSSA to improve both performance and energy efficiency while reducing parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spikingresformer-bridging-resnet-and-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Ranking Loss for Recommendation with Sparse User Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-ranking-loss-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we uncover a new challenge associated with BCE loss in scenarios with sparse positive feedback, such as CTR prediction: the gradient vanishing for negative samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-ranking-loss-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Repository for Long Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-repository-for-long-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a Language Repository (LangRepo) for LLMs, that maintains concise and structured information as an interpretable (i. e., all-textual) representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-repository-for-long-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Elements of Differentiable Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-elements-of-differentiable-programming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence has recently experienced remarkable advances, fueled by large models, vast datasets, accelerated hardware, and, last but not least, the transformative power of differentiable programming.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-elements-of-differentiable-programming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Learning for Cross-dataset Isolated Sign Language Recognition in Under-Resourced Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-cross-dataset-isolated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sign language recognition (SLR) has recently achieved a breakthrough in performance thanks to deep neural networks trained on large annotated sign datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-cross-dataset-isolated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAmBLA: A Framework for Evaluating the Reliability of LLMs as Assistants in the Biomedical Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rambla-a-framework-for-evaluating-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) increasingly support applications in a wide range of domains, some with potential high societal impact such as biomedicine, yet their reliability in realistic use cases is under-researched.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rambla-a-framework-for-evaluating-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising Diffusion Models for 3D Healthy Brain Tissue Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-models-for-3d-healthy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monitoring diseases that affect the brain's structural integrity requires automated analysis of magnetic resonance (MR) images, e. g., for the evaluation of volumetric changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-models-for-3d-healthy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CombiNeRF: A Combination of Regularization Techniques for Few-Shot Neural Radiance Field View Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combinerf-a-combination-of-regularization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When dealing with few-shot settings, i. e. with a small set of input views, the training could overfit those views, leading to artifacts and geometric and chromatic inconsistencies in the resulting rendering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combinerf-a-combination-of-regularization</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
