<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 21:08:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Attention-Guided Residual U-Net with SE Connection and ASPP for Watershed-Based Cell Segmentation in Microscopy Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-guided-residual-u-net-with-se</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose a novel framework called RA-SE-ASPP-Net, which incorporates Residual Blocks, Attention Mechanism, Squeeze-and-Excitation connection, and Atrous Spatial Pyramid Pooling to achieve precise and robust cell segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-guided-residual-u-net-with-se</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Generative Models Unveil Patterns in Medical Images Through Vision-Language Conditioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-generative-models-unveil-patterns-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep generative models have significantly advanced medical imaging analysis by enhancing dataset size and quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-generative-models-unveil-patterns-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Graph Quantized Tokenizers for Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-graph-quantized-tokenizers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers serve as the backbone architectures of Foundational Models, where a domain-specific tokenizer helps them adapt to various domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-graph-quantized-tokenizers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLM-Grounder: A VLM Agent for Zero-Shot 3D Visual Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlm-grounder-a-vlm-agent-for-zero-shot-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D visual grounding is crucial for robots, requiring integration of natural language and 3D scene understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlm-grounder-a-vlm-agent-for-zero-shot-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking Inward: Language Models Can Learn About Themselves by Introspection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-inward-language-models-can-learn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study introspection by finetuning LLMs to predict properties of their own behavior in hypothetical scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-inward-language-models-can-learn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Disparate Benefits of Deep Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-disparate-benefits-of-deep-ensembles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we identify the per-group difference in predictive diversity of ensemble members as the potential cause of the disparate benefits effect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-disparate-benefits-of-deep-ensembles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Capabilities of Masked Generative Models for Image Synthesis via Self-Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-capabilities-of-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key factor in the performance of continuous diffusion models stems from the guidance methods, which enhance the sample quality at the expense of diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-capabilities-of-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Function Placement in Virtual Networks: An Online Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-function-placement-in-virtual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a model for the virtual function placement problem and several novel algorithms using ideas based on multi-armed bandits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-function-placement-in-virtual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Use of Audio to Improve Dialogue Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-of-audio-to-improve-dialogue</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the significant progress of speech technologies, spoken goal-oriented dialogue systems are becoming increasingly popular.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-of-audio-to-improve-dialogue</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EH-MAM: Easy-to-Hard Masked Acoustic Modeling for Self-Supervised Speech Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eh-mam-easy-to-hard-masked-acoustic-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present EH-MAM (Easy-to-Hard adaptive Masked Acoustic Modeling), a novel self-supervised learning approach for speech representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eh-mam-easy-to-hard-masked-acoustic-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Prompt-leveraged Weakly Supervised Cancer Segmentation based on Segment Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-prompt-leveraged-weakly-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demonstrate the superiority of the proposed method, experimental studies are conducted on histopathological breast cancer datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-prompt-leveraged-weakly-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Evolved Universal Transformer Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-evolved-universal-transformer-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior methods propose to offset the escalating costs of modern foundation models by dropping specific parts of their contexts with hand-designed rules, while attempting to preserve their original performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-evolved-universal-transformer-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Free-Form Decision-Making Inconsistency of Language Models in Military Crisis Simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-free-form-decision-making</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that inconsistency due to semantically equivalent prompt variations can exceed response inconsistency from temperature sampling for most studied models across different levels of ablations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-free-form-decision-making</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research on Travel Route Planing Problems Based on Greedy Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/research-on-travel-route-planing-problems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The greedy algorithm based route planning problem is a method of finding the optimal or near optimal route between a given starting and ending point.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/research-on-travel-route-planing-problems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novelty-based Sample Reuse for Continuous Robotics Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novelty-based-sample-reuse-for-continuous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In reinforcement learning, agents collect state information and rewards through environmental interactions, essential for policy refinement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novelty-based-sample-reuse-for-continuous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Janus: Decoupling Visual Encoding for Unified Multimodal Understanding and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/janus-decoupling-visual-encoding-for-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Janus, an autoregressive framework that unifies multimodal understanding and generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/janus-decoupling-visual-encoding-for-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Design Space of Visual Context Representation in Video MLLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-design-space-of-visual-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we explore the scaling effects in frame selection and token selection respectively, and fit the corresponding function curve by conducting extensive empirical experiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-design-space-of-visual-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pose-Based Sign Language Appearance Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-based-sign-language-appearance-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a method for transferring the signer's appearance in sign language skeletal poses while preserving the sign content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-based-sign-language-appearance-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Little Human Data Goes A Long Way</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-little-human-data-goes-a-long-way</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Faced with an expensive human annotation process, creators of NLP systems increasingly turn to synthetic data generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-little-human-data-goes-a-long-way</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D-FINE: Redefine Regression Task in DETRs as Fine-grained Distribution Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-fine-redefine-regression-task-in-detrs-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When pretrained on Objects365, D-FINE-L / X attains 57. 1% / 59. 3% AP, surpassing all existing real-time detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-fine-redefine-regression-task-in-detrs-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Efficient Representations of Neutrino Telescope Events</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-efficient-representations-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neutrino telescopes detect rare interactions of particles produced in some of the most extreme environments in the Universe.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-efficient-representations-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MotionBank: A Large-scale Video Motion Benchmark with Disentangled Rule-based Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motionbank-a-large-scale-video-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ultimate goal of LMM is to serve as a foundation model for versatile motion-related tasks, e. g., human motion generation, with interpretability and generalizability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motionbank-a-large-scale-video-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All models are wrong, some are useful: Model Selection with Limited Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-models-are-wrong-some-are-useful-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the multitude of pretrained models available thanks to the advancements in large-scale supervised and self-supervised learning, choosing the right model is becoming increasingly pivotal in the machine learning lifecycle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-models-are-wrong-some-are-useful-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMOPT: Learning to Define and Solve General Optimization Problems from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmopt-learning-to-define-and-solve-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Namely, the accuracy of most current LLM-based methods and the generality of optimization problem types that they can model are still limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmopt-learning-to-define-and-solve-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BenTo: Benchmark Task Reduction with In-Context Transferability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bento-benchmark-task-reduction-with-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating large language models (LLMs) is costly: it requires the generation and examination of LLM outputs on a large-scale benchmark of various tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bento-benchmark-task-reduction-with-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Dataset Distillation via Label Inconsistency Elimination and Learning Pattern Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-dataset-distillation-via-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the final evaluation, our M-DATM achieved accuracies of 0. 4061 and 0. 1831 on the CIFAR-100 and Tiny ImageNet datasets, ranking 1st in the Fixed Images Per Class (IPC) Track.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-dataset-distillation-via-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can MLLMs Understand the Deep Implication Behind Chinese Images?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-mllms-understand-the-deep-implication</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill the gap, we introduce the **C**hinese **I**mage **I**mplication understanding **Bench**mark, **CII-Bench**, which aims to assess the higher-order perception and understanding capabilities of MLLMs for Chinese images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-mllms-understand-the-deep-implication</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-style conversion for semantic segmentation of lesions in fundus images by adversarial attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-style-conversion-for-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach enables training a segmentation model with diverse databases while controlling and leveraging annotation styles for improved retinopathy diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-style-conversion-for-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Kernel Thinning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-kernel-thinning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we generalize the KT algorithm to speed up supervised learning problems involving kernel methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-kernel-thinning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Human-in-the-Loop Fairness-Aware Model Selection Framework for Complex Fairness Objective Landscapes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-human-in-the-loop-fairness-aware-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this socio-technical and empirical study, we frame fairness as a many-objective (MaO) problem by treating fairness metrics as conflicting objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-human-in-the-loop-fairness-aware-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Imperceptibility of Stable Diffusion-based Adversarial Examples Generation with Momentum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-imperceptibility-of-stable-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel framework, Stable Diffusion-based Momentum Integrated Adversarial Examples (SD-MIAE), for generating adversarial examples that can effectively mislead neural network classifiers while maintaining visual imperceptibility and preserving the semantic similarity to the original class label.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-imperceptibility-of-stable-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCUP: A Controllable Synthetic Data Generation Pipeline for Pretraining Cloth-Changing Person Re-Identification Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccup-a-controllable-synthetic-data-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cloth-changing person re-identification (CC-ReID), also known as Long-Term Person Re-Identification (LT-ReID) is a critical and challenging research topic in computer vision that has recently garnered significant attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccup-a-controllable-synthetic-data-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIRAGE-Bench: Automatic Multilingual Benchmark Arena for Retrieval-Augmented Generation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mirage-bench-automatic-multilingual-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our work, we benchmark 19 diverse multilingual-focused LLMs, and achieve a high correlation (Kendall Tau ($\tau$) = 0. 909) using our surrogate judge learned using heuristic features with pairwise evaluations and between GPT-4o as a teacher on the MIRAGE-Bench leaderboard using the Bradley-Terry framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mirage-bench-automatic-multilingual-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balancing Label Quantity and Quality for Scalable Elicitation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-label-quantity-and-quality-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scalable oversight studies methods of training and evaluating AI systems in domains where human judgement is unreliable or expensive, such as scientific research and software engineering in complex codebases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-label-quantity-and-quality-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SiamSeg: Self-Training with Contrastive Learning for Unsupervised Domain Adaptation in Remote Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siamseg-self-training-with-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation of remote sensing (RS) images is a challenging task with significant potential across various applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siamseg-self-training-with-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimLayerKV: A Simple Framework for Layer-Level KV Cache Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simlayerkv-a-simple-framework-for-layer-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate this issue, we present SimLayerKV, a simple yet effective method that reduces inter-layer KV cache redundancies by selectively dropping cache in identified lazy layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simlayerkv-a-simple-framework-for-layer-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Defenses Against Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-defenses-against-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models excel at performing inference over text to extract information, summarize information, or generate additional text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-defenses-against-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLaMP 2: Multimodal Music Information Retrieval Across 101 Languages Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clamp-2-multimodal-music-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Challenges in managing linguistic diversity and integrating various musical modalities are faced by current music information retrieval systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clamp-2-multimodal-music-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAG-DDR: Optimizing Retrieval-Augmented Generation Using Differentiable Data Rewards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rag-ddr-optimizing-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments on various knowledge-intensive tasks demonstrate that DDR significantly outperforms the SFT method, particularly for LLMs with smaller-scale parameters that depend more on the retrieved knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rag-ddr-optimizing-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help Me Identify: Is an LLM+VQA System All We Need to Identify Visual Concepts?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/help-me-identify-is-an-llm-vqa-system-all-we</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An ability to learn about new objects from a small amount of visual data and produce convincing linguistic justification about the presence/absence of certain concepts (that collectively compose the object) in novel scenarios is an important characteristic of human cognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/help-me-identify-is-an-llm-vqa-system-all-we</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance of Gaussian Mixture Model Classifiers on Embedded Feature Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-of-gaussian-mixture-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our first contribution is to investigate GMM based classification performance taking advantage of the embedded spaces CLIP and ImageBind.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-of-gaussian-mixture-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DepthSplat: Connecting Gaussian Splatting and Depth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depthsplat-connecting-gaussian-splatting-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gaussian splatting and single/multi-view depth estimation are typically studied in isolation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depthsplat-connecting-gaussian-splatting-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remember, Retrieve and Generate: Understanding Infinite Visual Concepts as Your Personalized Assistant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remember-retrieve-and-generate-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further improve generation quality and alignment with user-specific information, we design a pipeline for data collection and create a specialized dataset for personalized training of MLLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remember-retrieve-and-generate-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-DiffuB: A Contextualized Sequence-to-Sequence Text Diffusion Model with Meta-Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-diffub-a-contextualized-sequence-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The diffusion model, a new generative modeling paradigm, has achieved significant success in generating images, audio, video, and text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-diffub-a-contextualized-sequence-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORSO: Accelerating Reward Design via Online Reward Selection and Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orso-accelerating-reward-design-via-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reward shaping is a critical component in reinforcement learning (RL), particularly for complex tasks where sparse rewards can hinder learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orso-accelerating-reward-design-via-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniDrive: Towards Universal Driving Perception Across Camera Configurations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidrive-towards-universal-driving-perception</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further propose a virtual configuration optimization method by minimizing the expected projection error between original cameras and virtual cameras.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidrive-towards-universal-driving-perception</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORCHID: A Chinese Debate Corpus for Target-Independent Stance Detection and Argumentative Dialogue Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orchid-a-chinese-debate-corpus-for-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dialogue agents have been receiving increasing attention for years, and this trend has been further boosted by the recent progress of large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orchid-a-chinese-debate-corpus-for-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>aiXcoder-7B: A Lightweight and Effective Large Language Model for Code Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aixcoder-7b-a-lightweight-and-effective-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a lightweight and effective LLM for code completion named aiXcoder-7B.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aixcoder-7b-a-lightweight-and-effective-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Gen: A Cast of Media Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/movie-gen-a-cast-of-media-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our models set a new state-of-the-art on multiple tasks: text-to-video synthesis, video personalization, video editing, video-to-audio generation, and text-to-audio generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/movie-gen-a-cast-of-media-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUMA: Empowering Unified MLLM with Multi-granular Visual Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puma-empowering-unified-mllm-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work represents a significant step towards a truly unified MLLM capable of adapting to the granularity demands of various visual tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puma-empowering-unified-mllm-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
