<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 21:08:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing MMDiT-Based Text-to-Image Models for Similar Subject Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-mmdit-based-text-to-image-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant improvements, we observe that semantic ambiguity persists when generating multiple similar subjects, as the guidance provided by overlap loss is not explicit enough.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-mmdit-based-text-to-image-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveying the space of descriptions of a composite system with machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surveying-the-space-of-descriptions-of-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By integrating machine learning into a fine-grained information theoretic analysis of composite random variables, our framework opens a new avenues for probing the structure of real-world complex systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surveying-the-space-of-descriptions-of-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning with Fairness Guarantees using Lorenz Dominance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-multi-objective-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning (MORL) aims to learn a set of policies that optimize trade-offs between multiple, often conflicting objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-multi-objective-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulating Tabular Datasets through LLMs to Rapidly Explore Hypotheses about Real-World Entities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-tabular-datasets-through-llms-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Do horror writers have worse childhoods than other writers?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-tabular-datasets-through-llms-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Draft Model Knows When to Stop: A Self-Verification Length Policy for Speculative Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/draft-model-knows-when-to-stop-a-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speculative Decoding (SD) has become an important technique in accelerating the inference speed of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/draft-model-knows-when-to-stop-a-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimeMarker: A Versatile Video-LLM for Long and Short Video Understanding with Superior Temporal Localization Ability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timemarker-a-versatile-video-llm-for-long-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rapid development of large language models (LLMs) has significantly advanced multimodal large language models (LMMs), particularly in vision-language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timemarker-a-versatile-video-llm-for-long-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Blind All-in-One Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-blind-all-in-one-image-restoration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Blind all-in-one image restoration models aim to recover a high-quality image from an input degraded with unknown distortions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-blind-all-in-one-image-restoration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Noise Token Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-noise-token-pruning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the present work we present Training Noise Token (TNT) Pruning for vision transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-noise-token-pruning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLS: Geometry-aware 3D Language Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gls-geometry-aware-3d-language-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, 3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) has achieved significant performance on indoor surface reconstruction and open-vocabulary segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gls-geometry-aware-3d-language-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Multispectral Object Detection: A Bag of Tricks and Comprehensive Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-multispectral-object-detection-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multispectral object detection, utilizing RGB and TIR (thermal infrared) modalities, is widely recognized as a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-multispectral-object-detection-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatRex: Taming Multimodal LLM for Joint Perception and Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatrex-taming-multimodal-llm-for-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From the data perspective, we build a fully automated data engine and construct the Rexverse-2M dataset which possesses multiple granularities to support the joint training of perception and understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatrex-taming-multimodal-llm-for-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating and Improving the Robustness of Security Attack Detectors Generated by LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-and-improving-the-robustness-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are increasingly used in software development to generate functions, such as attack detectors, that implement security requirements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-and-improving-the-robustness-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Mamba Distillation for Low-resolution Fine-grained Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-mamba-distillation-for-low-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-resolution fine-grained image classification has recently made significant progress, largely thanks to the super-resolution techniques and knowledge distillation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-mamba-distillation-for-low-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Knowledge Concepts to Whole Slide Images for Precise Histopathology Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-knowledge-concepts-to-whole-slide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the large size and lack of fine-grained annotation, Whole Slide Images (WSIs) analysis is commonly approached as a Multiple Instance Learning (MIL) problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-knowledge-concepts-to-whole-slide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Fourier-embedded Network for Bi-modal Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fourier-embedded-network-for-bi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of deep learning provides a significant improvement of salient object detection combining both RGB and thermal images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fourier-embedded-network-for-bi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Surface Priors for Editable Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-surface-priors-for-editable-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike other methods, our pipeline allows modifications applied to the extracted mesh to be propagated to the proxy representation, from which we recover the updated parameters of the Gaussians.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-surface-priors-for-editable-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Neural Networks Do Work with Pre-Defined Filters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-do-work-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel class of Convolutional Neural Networks called Pre-defined Filter Convolutional Neural Networks (PFCNNs), where all nxn convolution kernels with n>1 are pre-defined and constant during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-do-work-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RL for Mitigating Cascading Failures: Targeted Exploration via Sensitivity Factors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-for-mitigating-cascading-failures-targeted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Electricity grid's resiliency and climate change strongly impact one another due to an array of technical and policy-related decisions that impact both.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-for-mitigating-cascading-failures-targeted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoLLM Knows When to Speak: Enhancing Time-Sensitive Video Comprehension with Video-Text Duet Interaction Format</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videollm-knows-when-to-speak-enhancing-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We construct MMDuetIT, a video-text training dataset designed to adapt VideoLLMs to video-text duet interaction format.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videollm-knows-when-to-speak-enhancing-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergence of Self-Identity in AI: A Mathematical Framework and Empirical Study with Generative Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-self-identity-in-ai-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a mathematical framework for defining and quantifying self-identity in artificial intelligence (AI) systems, addressing a critical gap in the theoretical foundations of artificial consciousness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-self-identity-in-ai-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUPE: Heuristic Underwater Perceptual Enhancement with Semantic Collaborative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hupe-heuristic-underwater-perceptual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To strike a balance between visual quality and application, we propose a heuristic invertible network for underwater perception enhancement, dubbed HUPE, which enhances visual quality and demonstrates flexibility in handling other downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hupe-heuristic-underwater-perceptual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helvipad: A Real-World Dataset for Omnidirectional Stereo Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helvipad-a-real-world-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite considerable progress in stereo depth estimation, omnidirectional imaging remains underexplored, mainly due to the lack of appropriate data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helvipad-a-real-world-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RITA: Automatic Framework for Designing of Resilient IoT Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rita-automatic-framework-for-designing-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing resilient Internet of Things (IoT) systems requires i) identification of IoT Critical Objects (ICOs) such as services, devices, and resources, ii) threat analysis, and iii) mitigation strategy selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rita-automatic-framework-for-designing-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Path: Multi-modal, Multi-granularity Path Representation Learning -- Extended Version</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-path-multi-modal-multi-granularity-path</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel Multi-modal, Multi-granularity Path Representation Learning Framework (MM-Path), which can learn a generic path representation by integrating modalities from both road paths and image paths.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-path-multi-modal-multi-granularity-path</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectral-Spatial Transformer with Active Transfer Learning for Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-spatial-transformer-with-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a novel multi-stage active transfer learning (ATL) framework that integrates a Spatial-Spectral Transformer (SST) with an active learning process for efficient HSI classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-spatial-transformer-with-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuaLLM-Health: An Adaptation of an LLM-Based Framework for Quantitative Data Extraction from Online Health Discussions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quallm-health-an-adaptation-of-an-llm-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present an adapted framework from QuaLLM into QuaLLM-Health for extracting clinically relevant quantitative data from Reddit discussions about glucagon-like peptide-1 (GLP-1) receptor agonists using large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quallm-health-an-adaptation-of-an-llm-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaVLN: Towards Visual Language Navigation in Continuous Indoor Environments with Moving Humans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adavln-towards-visual-language-navigation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Language Navigation is a task that challenges robots to navigate in realistic environments based on natural language instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adavln-towards-visual-language-navigation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isometry pursuit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isometry-pursuit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Isometry pursuit is a convex algorithm for identifying orthonormal column-submatrices of wide matrices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isometry-pursuit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeneQuery: A General QA-based Framework for Spatial Gene Expression Predictions from Histology Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genequery-a-general-qa-based-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gene expression profiling provides profound insights into molecular mechanisms, but its time-consuming and costly nature often presents significant challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genequery-a-general-qa-based-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Runtime-Adaptive Transformer Neural Network Accelerator on FPGAs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-runtime-adaptive-transformer-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, it achieves a speedup of 1. 7 to 2. 25$\times$ compared to some state-of-the-art FPGA-based accelerators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-runtime-adaptive-transformer-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Open Vocabulary to Open World: Teaching Vision Language Models to Detect Novel Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-open-vocabulary-to-open-world-teaching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address theses limitations, we propose a framework that enables OVD models to operate in open world settings, by identifying and incrementally learning novel objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-open-vocabulary-to-open-world-teaching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training and Evaluating Language Models with Template-based Data Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-evaluating-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we introduce Template-based Data Generation (TDG), a novel approach that leverages LLMs (GPT-4) to automatically generate parameterized meta-templates, which are then used to synthesize a vast array of high-quality problems and solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-evaluating-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuMapper: Towards Automatic Verification of Large-Scale POIs with Street Views at Baidu Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dumapper-towards-automatic-verification-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increased popularity of mobile devices, Web mapping services have become an indispensable tool in our daily lives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dumapper-towards-automatic-verification-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled Interpretable Representation for Efficient Long-term Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-interpretable-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing deep learning and linear models often suffer from excessive parameter complexity and lack intuitive interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-interpretable-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Client Selection with Personalization for Communication Efficient Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-client-selection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) is a distributed approach to collaboratively training machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-client-selection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Attention: Efficient LLM Inference over Long Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/star-attention-efficient-llm-inference-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inference with Transformer-based Large Language Models (LLMs) on long sequences is both costly and slow due to the quadratic complexity of the self-attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/star-attention-efficient-llm-inference-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DROID-Splat: Combining end-to-end SLAM with 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/droid-splat-combining-end-to-end-slam-with-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in scene synthesis makes standalone SLAM systems purely based on optimizing hyperprimitives with a Rendering objective possible \cite{monogs}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/droid-splat-combining-end-to-end-slam-with-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DWCL: Dual-Weighted Contrastive Learning for Multi-View Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dwcl-dual-weighted-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, to reduce the impact of unreliable cross-views, we introduce an innovative Best-Other (B-O) contrastive mechanism that enhances the representation of individual views at a low computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dwcl-dual-weighted-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NumGrad-Pull: Numerical Gradient Guided Tri-plane Representation for Surface Reconstruction from Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/numgrad-pull-numerical-gradient-guided-tri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements address this problem by training neural signed distance functions to pull 3D location queries to their closest points on a surface, following the predicted signed distances and the analytical gradients computed by the network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/numgrad-pull-numerical-gradient-guided-tri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-training for Action Recognition with Automatically Generated Fractal Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-for-action-recognition-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extend this trend to the video domain applying it to the task of action recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-for-action-recognition-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinyViM: Frequency Decoupling for Tiny Hybrid Vision Mamba</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyvim-frequency-decoupling-for-tiny-hybrid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the analyses, we introduce a novel Laplace mixer to decouple the features in terms of frequency and input only the low-frequency components into the Mamba block.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyvim-frequency-decoupling-for-tiny-hybrid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMWISE: Infusing wisdom in SAM2 for Text-Driven Video Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samwise-infusing-wisdom-in-sam2-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Referring Video Object Segmentation (RVOS) relies on natural language expressions to segment an object in a video clip.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samwise-infusing-wisdom-in-sam2-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inference Scaling $\scriptsize\mathtt{F}$Laws: The Limits of LLM Resampling with Imperfect Verifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-scaling-scriptsize-mathtt-f-laws</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The central thesis of this paper is that there is no free lunch for inference scaling: indefinite accuracy improvement through resampling can only be realized if the "verifier" (in this case, a set of unit tests) is perfect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-scaling-scriptsize-mathtt-f-laws</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Vision Diffusion Transformers with Skip Branches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-vision-diffusion-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion Transformers (DiT), an emerging image and video generation model architecture, has demonstrated great potential because of its high generation quality and scalability properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-vision-diffusion-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MotionLLaMA: A Unified Framework for Motion Synthesis and Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motionllama-a-unified-framework-for-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces MotionLLaMA, a unified framework for motion synthesis and comprehension, along with a novel full-body motion tokenizer called the HoMi Tokenizer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motionllama-a-unified-framework-for-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShowUI: One Vision-Language-Action Model for GUI Visual Agent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/showui-one-vision-language-action-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop a vision-language-action model in digital world, namely ShowUI, which features the following innovations: (i) UI-Guided Visual Token Selection to reduce computational costs by formulating screenshots as an UI connected graph, adaptively identifying their redundant relationship and serve as the criteria for token selection during self-attention blocks; (ii) Interleaved Vision-Language-Action Streaming that flexibly unifies diverse needs within GUI tasks, enabling effective management of visual-action history in navigation or pairing multi-turn query-action sequences per screenshot to enhance training efficiency; (iii) Small-scale High-quality GUI Instruction-following Datasets by careful data curation and employing a resampling strategy to address significant data type imbalances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/showui-one-vision-language-action-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boost 3D Reconstruction using Diffusion-based Monocular Camera Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boost-3d-reconstruction-using-diffusion-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monocular camera calibration is essential for many 3D vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boost-3d-reconstruction-using-diffusion-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoK: Decentralized AI (DeAI)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sok-decentralized-ai-deai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The centralization of Artificial Intelligence (AI) poses significant challenges, including single points of failure, inherent biases, data privacy concerns, and scalability issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sok-decentralized-ai-deai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-task Mutual Reinforcing Embedded Joint Video Paragraph Retrieval and Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-task-mutual-reinforcing-embedded-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The retrieval branch uses inter-video contrastive learning to roughly align the global features of paragraphs and videos, reducing modality differences and constructing a coarse-grained feature space to break free from the need for correspondence between paragraphs and videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-task-mutual-reinforcing-embedded-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Box for Mask and Mask for Box: weak losses for multi-task partially supervised learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/box-for-mask-and-mask-for-box-weak-losses-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Making use of one task's information to train the other would be beneficial for multi-task partially supervised learning where each training example is annotated only for a single task, having the potential to expand training sets with different-task datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/box-for-mask-and-mask-for-box-weak-losses-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
