<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 21:10:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tencent's Multilingual Machine Translation System for WMT22 Large-Scale African Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tencent-s-multilingual-machine-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes Tencent's multilingual machine translation systems for the WMT22 shared task on Large-Scale Machine Translation Evaluation for African Languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tencent-s-multilingual-machine-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAGAD: Data Augmentation for Graph Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dagad-data-augmentation-for-graph-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge the gaps, this paper devises a novel Data Augmentation-based Graph Anomaly Detection (DAGAD) framework for attributed graphs, equipped with three specially designed modules: 1) an information fusion module employing graph neural network encoders to learn representations, 2) a graph data augmentation module that fertilizes the training set with generated samples, and 3) an imbalance-tailored learning module to discriminate the distributions of the minority (anomalous) and majority (normal) classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dagad-data-augmentation-for-graph-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Tri-Layer Plugin to Improve Occluded Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tri-layer-plugin-to-improve-occluded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end we make the following four contributions: (1) We propose a simple 'plugin' module for the detection head of two-stage object detectors to improve the recall of partially occluded objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tri-layer-plugin-to-improve-occluded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning for Sample Efficient Imitation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planning-for-sample-efficient-imitation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the recent success of EfficientZero in RL, we propose EfficientImitate (EI), a planning-based imitation learning method that can achieve high in-environment sample efficiency and performance simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planning-for-sample-efficient-imitation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSE: Robust Selective Fine-tuning for Pre-trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rose-robust-selective-fine-tuning-for-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even though the large-scale language models have achieved excellent performances, they suffer from various adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rose-robust-selective-fine-tuning-for-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NADI 2022: The Third Nuanced Arabic Dialect Identification Shared Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nadi-2022-the-third-nuanced-arabic-dialect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe findings of the third Nuanced Arabic Dialect Identification Shared Task (NADI 2022).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nadi-2022-the-third-nuanced-arabic-dialect</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Science Simple: Corpora for the Lay Summarisation of Scientific Literature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-science-simple-corpora-for-the-lay</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lay summarisation aims to jointly summarise and simplify a given text, thus making its content more comprehensible to non-experts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-science-simple-corpora-for-the-lay</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple and Effective Method to Improve Zero-Shot Cross-Lingual Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-and-effective-method-to-improve-zero-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing zero-shot cross-lingual transfer methods rely on parallel corpora or bilingual dictionaries, which are expensive and impractical for low-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-and-effective-method-to-improve-zero-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrete Cross-Modal Alignment Enables Zero-Shot Speech Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-cross-modal-alignment-enables-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing zero-shot methods fail to align the two modalities of speech and text into a shared semantic space, resulting in much worse performance compared to the supervised ST methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-cross-modal-alignment-enables-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synergy with Translation Artifacts for Training and Inference in Multilingual Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synergy-with-translation-artifacts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Translation has played a crucial role in improving the performance on multilingual tasks: (1) to generate the target language data from the source language data for training and (2) to generate the source language data from the target language data for inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synergy-with-translation-artifacts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Practical, Progressively-Expressive GNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-progressively-expressive-gnn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model is practical and progressively-expressive, increasing in power with k and c. We demonstrate effectiveness on several benchmark datasets, achieving several state-of-the-art results with runtime and memory usage applicable to practical graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-progressively-expressive-gnn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntTower: the Next Generation of Two-Tower Model for Pre-Ranking System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inttower-the-next-generation-of-two-tower</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FE-Block module performs fine-grained and early feature interactions to capture the interactive signals between user and item towers explicitly and CIR module leverages a contrastive interaction regularization to further enhance the interactions implicitly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inttower-the-next-generation-of-two-tower</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Degradation-invariant Enhancement of Fundus Images via Pyramid Constraint Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/degradation-invariant-enhancement-of-fundus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For boosting the clinical deployment of fundus image enhancement, this paper proposes the pyramid constraint to develop a degradation-invariant enhancement network (PCE-Net), which mitigates the demand for clinical data and stably enhances unknown data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/degradation-invariant-enhancement-of-fundus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Hybrid System of Sound Event Detection Transformer and Frame-wise Model for DCASE 2022 Task 4</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-system-of-sound-event-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the frame-wise model, the ICT-TOSHIBA system of DCASE 2021 Task 4 is used.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-system-of-sound-event-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Anomaly Detection with Unsupervised GNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-anomaly-detection-with-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work aims to fill two gaps in the literature: We (1) design GLAM, an end-to-end graph-level anomaly detection model based on GNNs, and (2) focus on unsupervised model selection, which is notoriously hard due to lack of any labels, yet especially critical for deep NN based models with a long list of hyper-parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-anomaly-detection-with-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DisCup: Discriminator Cooperative Unlikelihood Prompt-tuning for Controllable Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discup-discriminator-cooperative-unlikelihood</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompt learning with immensely large Casual Language Models (CLMs) has been shown promising for attribute-controllable text generation (CTG).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discup-discriminator-cooperative-unlikelihood</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not All Poisons are Created Equal: Robust Training against Data Poisoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-poisons-are-created-equal-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data poisoning causes misclassification of test time target examples by injecting maliciously crafted samples in the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-poisons-are-created-equal-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAPO: An Adaptive Ranking Paradigm for Bilingual Lexicon Induction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapo-an-adaptive-ranking-paradigm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bilingual lexicon induction induces the word translations by aligning independently trained word embeddings in two languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapo-an-adaptive-ranking-paradigm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEIP: Combining Explicit and Implicit Priors for Reinforcement Learning with Demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ceip-combining-explicit-and-implicit-priors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better benefit from available demonstrations, we develop a method to Combine Explicit and Implicit Priors (CEIP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ceip-combining-explicit-and-implicit-priors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RibSeg v2: A Large-scale Benchmark for Rib Labeling and Anatomical Centerline Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ribseg-v2-a-large-scale-benchmark-for-rib</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the RibSeg v2, we develop a pipeline including deep learning-based methods for rib labeling, and a skeletonization-based method for centerline extraction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ribseg-v2-a-large-scale-benchmark-for-rib</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Data Augmentation for Weed Recognition Enhancement: A Diffusion Probabilistic Model and Transfer Learning Based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-data-augmentation-for-weed-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present the first work of applying diffusion probabilistic models (also known as diffusion models) to generate high-quality synthetic weed images based on transfer learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-data-augmentation-for-weed-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clustering Categorical Data: Soft Rounding k-modes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clustering-categorical-data-soft-rounding-k</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the last three decades, researchers have intensively explored various clustering tools for categorical data analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clustering-categorical-data-soft-rounding-k</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making a MIRACL: Multilingual Information Retrieval Across a Continuum of Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-a-miracl-multilingual-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MIRACL (Multilingual Information Retrieval Across a Continuum of Languages) is a multilingual dataset we have built for the WSDM 2023 Cup challenge that focuses on ad hoc retrieval across 18 different languages, which collectively encompass over three billion native speakers around the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-a-miracl-multilingual-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sentiment-Aware Word and Sentence Level Pre-training for Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentiment-aware-word-and-sentence-level-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing pre-trained language representation models (PLMs) are sub-optimal in sentiment analysis tasks, as they capture the sentiment information from word-level while under-considering sentence-level information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentiment-aware-word-and-sentence-level-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5th Place Solution to Kaggle Google Universal Image Embedding Competition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/5th-place-solution-to-kaggle-google-universal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present our solution, which placed 5th in the kaggle Google Universal Image Embedding Competition in 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/5th-place-solution-to-kaggle-google-universal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedForgery: Generalized Face Forgery Detection with Residual Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedforgery-generalized-face-forgery-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments conducted on publicly available face forgery detection datasets prove the superior performance of the proposed FedForgery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedforgery-generalized-face-forgery-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eye-tracking based classification of Mandarin Chinese readers with and without dyslexia using neural sequence models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eye-tracking-based-classification-of-mandarin</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Eye movements are known to reflect cognitive processes in reading, and psychological reading research has shown that eye gaze patterns differ between readers with and without dyslexia.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eye-tracking-based-classification-of-mandarin</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer learning with weak labels from radiology reports: application to glioma change detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-with-weak-labels-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the relationship between model size and TL, comparing a low-capacity VGG with a higher-capacity SEResNeXt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-with-weak-labels-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATCON: Attention Consistency for Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atcon-attention-consistency-for-vision-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an unsupervised fine-tuning method that optimizes the consistency of attention maps and show that it improves both classification performance and the quality of attention maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atcon-attention-consistency-for-vision-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Efficient and Effective Self-Supervised Learning of Visual Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-and-effective-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervision has emerged as a propitious method for visual representation learning after the recent paradigm shift from handcrafted pretext tasks to instance-similarity based approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-and-effective-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ULN: Towards Underspecified Vision-and-Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uln-towards-underspecified-vision-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-and-Language Navigation (VLN) is a task to guide an embodied agent moving to a target position using language instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uln-towards-underspecified-vision-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inception-Based Crowd Counting -- Being Fast while Remaining Accurate</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inception-based-crowd-counting-being-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent sophisticated CNN-based algorithms have demonstrated their extraordinary ability to automate counting crowds from images, thanks to their structures which are designed to address the issue of various head scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inception-based-crowd-counting-being-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Would The Viewer Feel? Estimating Wellbeing From Video Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-would-the-viewer-feel-estimating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In experiments, we show how video models that are primarily trained to recognize actions and find contours of objects can be repurposed to understand human preferences and the emotional content of videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-would-the-viewer-feel-estimating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SA-MLP: Distilling Graph Knowledge from GNNs into Structure-Aware MLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-mlp-distilling-graph-knowledge-from-gnns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we introduce a novel structure-mixing knowledge distillation strategy to enhance the learning ability of MLPs for structure information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-mlp-distilling-graph-knowledge-from-gnns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TFAD: A Decomposition Time Series Anomaly Detection Architecture with Time-Frequency Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tfad-a-decomposition-time-series-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series anomaly detection is a challenging problem due to the complex temporal dependencies and the limited label data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tfad-a-decomposition-time-series-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Value Function Learning for Generalization in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-value-function-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We focus on the problem of training RL agents on multiple training environments to improve observational generalization performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-value-function-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer learning with affine model transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-with-affine-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Supervised transfer learning (TL) has received considerable attention because of its potential to boost the predictive power of machine learning in cases with limited data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-with-affine-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised visualization of image datasets using contrastive learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-visualization-of-image-datasets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This problem can be circumvented by self-supervised approaches based on contrastive learning, such as SimCLR, relying on data augmentation to generate implicit neighbors, but these methods do not produce two-dimensional embeddings suitable for visualization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-visualization-of-image-datasets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ArtFacePoints: High-resolution Facial Landmark Detection in Paintings and Prints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artfacepoints-high-resolution-facial-landmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial landmark detection plays an important role for the similarity analysis in artworks to compare portraits of the same or similar artists.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artfacepoints-high-resolution-facial-landmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher Forcing Recovers Reward Functions for Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teacher-forcing-recovers-reward-functions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We additionally propose a simple modification to stabilize the RL training on non-parallel datasets with our induced reward function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teacher-forcing-recovers-reward-functions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrossRE: A Cross-Domain Dataset for Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crossre-a-cross-domain-dataset-for-relation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Relation Extraction (RE) has attracted increasing attention, but current RE evaluation is limited to in-domain evaluation setups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crossre-a-cross-domain-dataset-for-relation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EISeg: An Efficient Interactive Segmentation Tool based on PaddlePaddle</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eiseg-an-efficient-interactive-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the rapid development of deep learning has brought great advancements to image and video segmentation methods based on neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eiseg-an-efficient-interactive-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Positive-Unlabeled Learning Framework for Document-Level Relation Extraction with Different Levels of Labeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-positive-unlabeled-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve the common incomplete labeling problem, we propose a unified positive-unlabeled learning framework - shift and squared ranking loss positive-unlabeled (SSR-PU) learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-positive-unlabeled-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plug-and-Play VQA: Zero-shot VQA by Conjoining Large Pretrained Models with Zero Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-vqa-zero-shot-vqa-by-conjoining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual question answering (VQA) is a hallmark of vision and language reasoning and a challenging task under the zero-shot setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-vqa-zero-shot-vqa-by-conjoining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrapping the Relationship Between Images and Their Clean and Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bootstrapping-the-relationship-between-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many state-of-the-art noisy-label learning methods rely on learning mechanisms that estimate the samples' clean labels during training and discard their original noisy labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bootstrapping-the-relationship-between-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Analysis of Human Body Representations in Western Art</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-analysis-of-human-body</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The way the human body is depicted in classical and modern paintings is relevant for art historical analyses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-analysis-of-human-body</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Contact Fields: Tracking Extrinsic Contact with Tactile Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-contact-fields-tracking-extrinsic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In experiments, we find that Neural Contact Fields are able to localize multiple contact patches without making any assumptions about the geometry of the contact, and capture contact/no-contact transitions for known categories of objects with unseen shapes in unseen environment configurations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-contact-fields-tracking-extrinsic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIVE: A Toolbox for Identifying Video Instance Segmentation Errors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tive-a-toolbox-for-identifying-video-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More importantly, as the fundamental model abilities demanded by the task, spatial segmentation and temporal association are still understudied in both evaluation and interaction mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tive-a-toolbox-for-identifying-video-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Diagnosis of Retinal Blood Vessel Damage via Deep Learning-Powered Collective Intelligence Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-diagnosis-of-retinal-blood-vessel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The power of swarm algorithms is used to search for various combinations of convolutional, pooling, and normalization layers to provide the best model for the task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-diagnosis-of-retinal-blood-vessel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runner-Up Solution to Google Universal Image Embedding Competition 2022</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/runner-up-solution-to-google-universal-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image representations are a critical building block of computer vision applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/runner-up-solution-to-google-universal-image</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
