<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 21:06:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>FedSkip: Combatting Statistical Heterogeneity with Federated Skip Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedskip-combatting-statistical-heterogeneity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in addition to previous explorations for improvement in federated averaging, our analysis shows that another critical bottleneck is the poorer optima of client models in more heterogeneous conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedskip-combatting-statistical-heterogeneity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lorentz Group Equivariant Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lorentz-group-equivariant-autoencoders</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There has been significant work recently in developing machine learning models in high energy physics (HEP), for tasks such as classification, simulation, and anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lorentz-group-equivariant-autoencoders</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trust, but Verify: Cross-Modality Fusion for HD Map Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trust-but-verify-cross-modality-fusion-for-hd</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-definition (HD) map change detection is the task of determining when sensor data and map data are no longer in agreement with one another due to real-world changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trust-but-verify-cross-modality-fusion-for-hd</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reproducible scaling laws for contrastive language-image learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducible-scaling-laws-for-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these limitations, we investigate scaling laws for contrastive language-image pre-training (CLIP) with the public LAION dataset and the open-source OpenCLIP repository.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducible-scaling-laws-for-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared Coupling-bridge for Weakly Supervised Local Feature Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shared-coupling-bridge-for-weakly-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse local feature extraction is usually believed to be of important significance in typical vision tasks such as simultaneous localization and mapping, image matching and 3D reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shared-coupling-bridge-for-weakly-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Artifacts in Real-World Video Super-Resolution Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-artifacts-in-real-world-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To aggregate a new hidden state that contains fewer artifacts from the hidden state pool, we devise a Selective Cross Attention (SCA) module, in which the attention between input features and each hidden state is calculated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-artifacts-in-real-world-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Ethics on Blockchain: Topic Analysis on Twitter Data for Blockchain Security</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-ethics-on-blockchain-topic-analysis-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that the tweets discussed profound topics of ethical concern, including security, equity, emotional sentiments, and the desire for solutions to MEV.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-ethics-on-blockchain-topic-analysis-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3DHumanGAN: Towards Photo-Realistic 3D-Aware Human Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dhumangan-towards-photo-realistic-3d-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present 3DHumanGAN, a 3D-aware generative adversarial network (GAN) that synthesizes images of full-body humans with consistent appearances under different view-angles and body-poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dhumangan-towards-photo-realistic-3d-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tailoring Visual Object Representations to Human Requirements: A Case Study with a Recycling Robot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-visual-object-representations-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robots are well-suited to alleviate the burden of repetitive and tedious manipulation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-visual-object-representations-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECON: Explicit Clothed humans Obtained from Normals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/econ-explicit-clothed-humans-obtained-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The combination of artist-curated scans, and deep implicit functions (IF), is enabling the creation of detailed, clothed, 3D humans from images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/econ-explicit-clothed-humans-obtained-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Generalization by Learning and Removing Domain-specific Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalization-by-learning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the images output by the encoder-decoder network, another classifier is designed to learn the domain-invariant features to conduct image classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalization-by-learning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAGO: Recurrent Graph Optimizer For Multiple Rotation Averaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rago-recurrent-graph-optimizer-for-multiple-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our graph optimizer iteratively refines the global camera rotations by minimizing each node's single rotation objective function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rago-recurrent-graph-optimizer-for-multiple-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Negative Style Transfer in Hybrid Dialogue System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-negative-style-transfer-in-hybrid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the functionality of dialogue systems evolves, hybrid dialogue systems that accomplish user-specific goals and participate in open-topic chitchat with users are attracting growing attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-negative-style-transfer-in-hybrid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Establishing a stronger baseline for lightweight contrastive models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/establishing-a-stronger-baseline-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A common practice to address this problem is to introduce a pretrained contrastive teacher model and train the lightweight networks with distillation signals generated by the teacher.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/establishing-a-stronger-baseline-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-task Learning for Cross-Lingual Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-cross-lingual-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a cross-lingual sentiment analysis of news articles using zero-shot and few-shot learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-cross-lingual-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Category Theory for Quantum Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/category-theory-for-quantum-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The second chapter uses DisCopy to implement QNLP models as parameterised functors from grammar to quantum circuits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/category-theory-for-quantum-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverse Demonstrations Improve In-context Compositional Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-demonstrations-improve-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In-context learning has shown great success in i. i. d semantic parsing splits, where the training and test sets are drawn from the same distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-demonstrations-improve-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reliable extrapolation of deep neural operators informed by physics or sparse observations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliable-extrapolation-of-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural operators can learn nonlinear mappings between infinite-dimensional function spaces via deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliable-extrapolation-of-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OAMixer: Object-aware Mixing Layer for Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oamixer-object-aware-mixing-layer-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using the object labels, OAMixer computes a reweighting mask with a learnable scale parameter that intensifies the interaction of patches containing similar objects and applies the mask to the patch mixing layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oamixer-object-aware-mixing-layer-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularized Optimal Transport Layers for Generalized Global Pooling Operations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularized-optimal-transport-layers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Making the parameters of the ROT problem learnable, we develop a family of regularized optimal transport pooling (ROTP) layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularized-optimal-transport-layers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastMIM: Expediting Masked Image Modeling Pre-training for Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastmim-expediting-masked-image-modeling-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents FastMIM, a simple and generic framework for expediting masked image modeling with the following two steps: (i) pre-training vision backbones with low-resolution input images; and (ii) reconstructing Histograms of Oriented Gradients (HOG) feature instead of original RGB values of the input images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastmim-expediting-masked-image-modeling-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIER: Text-Image Entropy Regularization for CLIP-style models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tier-text-image-entropy-regularization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the effect of a novel regularization scheme on contrastive language-image pre-trained (CLIP) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tier-text-image-entropy-regularization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Sample-Level Out-of-Distribution Detection on 3D Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-sample-level-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Carefully discussing the limitations, we conclude that our method solves the sample-level OOD detection on 3D medical images in the current setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-sample-level-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can recurrent neural networks learn process model structure?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-recurrent-neural-networks-learn-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate the capabilities of such an LSTM to actually learn the underlying process model structure of an event log.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-recurrent-neural-networks-learn-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Brain Decoding: from fMRI to conceptually similar image reconstruction of visual stimuli</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-brain-decoding-from-fmri-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Brain decoding is a field of computational neuroscience that uses measurable brain activity to infer mental states or internal representations of perceptual inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-brain-decoding-from-fmri-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What do Vision Transformers Learn? A Visual Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-vision-transformers-learn-a-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we show that ViTs maintain spatial information in all layers except the final layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-vision-transformers-learn-a-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Neural Networks integrating genomics and histopathological images for predicting stages and survival time-to-event in colon cancer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-neural-networks-integrating-genomics-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unraveling this variation will bring about improved in staging and treatment outcome, hence motivated by the advancement of Deep Neural Network libraries and different structures and factors within some genomic dataset, we aggregate atypical patterns in histopathological images with diverse carcinogenic expression from mRNA, miRNA and DNA Methylation as an integrative input source into an ensemble deep neural network for colon cancer stages classification and samples stratification into low or high risk survival groups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-neural-networks-integrating-genomics-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unfolding Local Growth Rate Estimates for (Almost) Perfect Adversarial Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unfolding-local-growth-rate-estimates-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convolutional neural networks (CNN) define the state-of-the-art solution on many perceptual tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unfolding-local-growth-rate-estimates-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TencentPretrain: A Scalable and Flexible Toolkit for Pre-training Models of Different Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tencentpretrain-a-scalable-and-flexible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed pre-training models of different modalities are showing a rising trend of homogeneity in their model structures, which brings the opportunity to implement different pre-training models within a uniform framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tencentpretrain-a-scalable-and-flexible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiscale topology classifies and quantifies cell types in subcellular spatial transcriptomics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiscale-topology-classifies-and-quantifies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatial transcriptomics has the potential to transform our understanding of RNA expression in tissues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiscale-topology-classifies-and-quantifies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Losses over Labels: Weakly Supervised Learning via Direct Loss Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/losses-over-labels-weakly-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Owing to the prohibitive costs of generating large amounts of labeled data, programmatic weak supervision is a growing paradigm within machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/losses-over-labels-weakly-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structured Prompting: Scaling In-Context Learning to 1,000 Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-prompting-scaling-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models have exhibited intriguing in-context learning capability, achieving promising zero- and few-shot performance without updating the parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-prompting-scaling-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPViT: A High Resolution Non-Hierarchical Vision Transformer with Group Propagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpvit-a-high-resolution-non-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In each GP Block, features are first grouped together by a fixed number of learnable group tokens; we then perform Group Propagation where global information is exchanged between the grouped features; finally, global information in the updated grouped features is returned back to the image features through a transformer decoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpvit-a-high-resolution-non-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdvMIL: Adversarial Multiple Instance Learning for the Survival Analysis on Whole-Slide Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advmil-adversarial-multiple-instance-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The survival analysis on histological whole-slide images (WSIs) is one of the most important means to estimate patient prognosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advmil-adversarial-multiple-instance-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dilation-Erosion for Single-Frame Supervised Temporal Action Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilation-erosion-for-single-frame-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To balance the annotation labor and the granularity of supervision, single-frame annotation has been introduced in temporal action localization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilation-erosion-for-single-frame-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving generalization in reinforcement learning through forked agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-generalization-in-reinforcement-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An eco-system of agents each having their own policy with some, but limited, generalizability has proven to be a reliable approach to increase generalization across procedurally generated environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-generalization-in-reinforcement-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DifFace: Blind Face Restoration with Diffused Error Contraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difface-blind-face-restoration-with-diffused</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, the transition distribution can contract the error of the restoration backbone and thus makes our method more robust to unknown degradations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difface-blind-face-restoration-with-diffused</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LidarCLIP or: How I Learned to Talk to Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidarclip-or-how-i-learned-to-talk-to-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Research connecting text and images has recently seen several breakthroughs, with models like CLIP, DALL-E 2, and Stable Diffusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidarclip-or-how-i-learned-to-talk-to-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Knowledge Gain for MOOC Video Consumption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-knowledge-gain-for-mooc-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Informal learning on the Web using search engines as well as more structured learning on MOOC platforms have become very popular in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-knowledge-gain-for-mooc-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Mini-Batch Training with Varying Length Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-mini-batch-training-with-varying-length</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel method of normalizing the lengths of the time series in a dataset by exploiting the dynamic matching ability of Dynamic Time Warping (DTW).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-mini-batch-training-with-varying-length</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-objective Tree-structured Parzen Estimator Meets Meta-learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-tree-structured-parzen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperparameter optimization (HPO) is essential for the better performance of deep learning, and practitioners often need to consider the trade-off between multiple metrics, such as error rate, latency, memory requirements, robustness, and algorithmic fairness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-tree-structured-parzen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Statistical Model for Predicting Generalization in Few-Shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-statistical-model-for-predicting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such a set is hardly available in few-shot learning scenarios, a highly disregarded shortcoming in the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-statistical-model-for-predicting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distantly-Supervised Named Entity Recognition with Adaptive Teacher Learning and Fine-grained Student Ensemble</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distantly-supervised-named-entity-recognition-5</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Distantly-Supervised Named Entity Recognition (DS-NER) effectively alleviates the data scarcity problem in NER by automatically generating training samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distantly-supervised-named-entity-recognition-5</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Convolutional Networks for Traffic Forecasting with Missing Values</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-convolutional-networks-for-traffic-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose GCN-M, a Graph Convolutional Network model with the ability to handle the complex missing values in the Spatio-temporal context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-convolutional-networks-for-traffic-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Score-based Generative Modeling Secretly Minimizes the Wasserstein Distance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-based-generative-modeling-secretly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we prove that the Wasserstein distance is upper bounded by the square root of the objective function up to multiplicative constants and a fixed constant offset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-based-generative-modeling-secretly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RT-1: Robotics Transformer for Real-World Control at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rt-1-robotics-transformer-for-real-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By transferring knowledge from large, diverse, task-agnostic datasets, modern machine learning models can solve specific downstream tasks either zero-shot or with small task-specific datasets to a high level of performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rt-1-robotics-transformer-for-real-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning 3D Representations from 2D Pre-trained Models via Image-to-Point Masked Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-3d-representations-from-2d-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-training by numerous image data has become de-facto for robust 2D representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-3d-representations-from-2d-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prescriptive Process Monitoring in Intelligent Process Automation with Chatbot Orchestration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prescriptive-process-monitoring-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using this dataset, we demonstrate crowd-wisdom and goal-driven approaches to prescriptive process monitoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prescriptive-process-monitoring-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DA Wand: Distortion-Aware Selection using Neural Mesh Parameterization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/da-wand-distortion-aware-selection-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a neural technique for learning to select a local sub-region around a point which can be used for mesh parameterization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/da-wand-distortion-aware-selection-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPN: A Word Vector Level Data Augmentation Algorithm in Deep Learning for Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rpn-a-word-vector-level-data-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In subsequent experiments, we found that adding RPN to the training or fine-tuning model resulted in a stable boost on all 8 natural language processing tasks, including TweetEval, CoLA, and SST-2 datasets, and more significant improvements than other data augmentation algorithms. The RPN algorithm applies to all sentence-level tasks for language understanding and is used in any deep learning model with a word embedding layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rpn-a-word-vector-level-data-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
