<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 09:16:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Transformers with Spectrum-Preserving Token Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-transformers-with-spectrum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Increasing the throughput of the Transformer architecture, a foundational component used in numerous state-of-the-art models for vision and language tasks (e. g., GPT, LLaVa), is an important problem in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-transformers-with-spectrum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Noise Models and Advanced Filtering Algorithms for Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-noise-models-and-advanced-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It shows us the impact of different filters on noise models by applying a variety of filters to various kinds of noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-noise-models-and-advanced-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lighten CARAFE: Dynamic Lightweight Upsampling with Guided Reassemble Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lighten-carafe-dynamic-lightweight-upsampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on several mainstream vision tasks show that our DLU achieves comparable and even better performance to the original CARAFE, but with much lower complexity, e. g., DLU requires 91% fewer parameters and at least 63% fewer FLOPs (Floating Point Operations) than CARAFE in the case of 16x upsampling, but outperforms the CARAFE by 0. 3% mAP in object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lighten-carafe-dynamic-lightweight-upsampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-Swin: SAM-Driven Dual-Swin Transformers with Adaptive Lesion Enhancement for Laryngo-Pharyngeal Tumor Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-swin-sam-driven-dual-swin-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Laryngo-pharyngeal cancer (LPC) is a highly lethal malignancy in the head and neck region.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-swin-sam-driven-dual-swin-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RankUp: Boosting Semi-Supervised Regression with an Auxiliary Ranking Classifier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankup-boosting-semi-supervised-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present RankUp, a simple yet effective approach that adapts existing semi-supervised classification techniques to enhance the performance of regression tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankup-boosting-semi-supervised-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging LLMs for Hypothetical Deduction in Logical Inference: A Neuro-Symbolic Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-llms-for-hypothetical-deduction-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have exhibited remarkable potential across a wide array of reasoning tasks, including logical reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-llms-for-hypothetical-deduction-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Posterior Samples for Bayesian Optimization via Rootfinding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-posterior-samples-for-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian optimization devolves the global optimization of a costly objective function to the global optimization of a sequence of acquisition functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-posterior-samples-for-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Adversarial Attacks through Chain of Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-adversarial-attacks-through-chain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated impressive performance across various domains but remain susceptible to safety concerns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-adversarial-attacks-through-chain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capacity Control is an Effective Memorization Mitigation Mechanism in Text-Conditional Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/capacity-control-is-an-effective-memorization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present compelling evidence that controlling model capacity during fine-tuning can effectively mitigate memorization in diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/capacity-control-is-an-effective-memorization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CT to PET Translation: A Large-scale Dataset and Domain-Knowledge-Guided Diffusion Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ct-to-pet-translation-a-large-scale-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our contributions are twofold: First, we introduce a conditional diffusion model named CPDM, which, to our knowledge, is one of the initial attempts to employ a diffusion model for translating from CT to PET images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ct-to-pet-translation-a-large-scale-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-step feature fusion for natural disaster damage assessment on satellite images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-step-feature-fusion-for-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel damage assessment method using an original multi-step feature fusion network for the classification of the damage state of buildings based on pre- and post-disaster large-scale satellite images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-step-feature-fusion-for-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BenchX: A Unified Benchmark Framework for Medical Vision-Language Pretraining on Chest X-Rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchx-a-unified-benchmark-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical Vision-Language Pretraining (MedVLP) shows promise in learning generalizable and transferable visual representations from paired and unpaired medical images and reports.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchx-a-unified-benchmark-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PK-YOLO: Pretrained Knowledge Guided YOLO for Brain Tumor Detection in Multiplanar MRI Slices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pk-yolo-pretrained-knowledge-guided-yolo-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new You Only Look Once (YOLO)-based detection model that incorporates Pretrained Knowledge (PK), called PK-YOLO, to improve the performance for brain tumor detection in multiplane MRI slices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pk-yolo-pretrained-knowledge-guided-yolo-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimRec: Mitigating the Cold-Start Problem in Sequential Recommendation by Integrating Item Similarity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simrec-mitigating-the-cold-start-problem-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose SimRec - a new approach to mitigate the cold-start problem in sequential recommendation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simrec-mitigating-the-cold-start-problem-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volumetric Conditioning Module to Control Pretrained Diffusion Models for 3D Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volumetric-conditioning-module-to-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further investigate the potential applications for our spatial control method through axial super-resolution for medical images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volumetric-conditioning-module-to-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distinguishing Ignorance from Error in LLM Hallucinations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinguishing-ignorance-from-error-in-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To help distinguish between the two cases, we introduce Wrong Answer despite having Correct Knowledge (WACK), an approach for constructing model-specific datasets for the second hallucination type.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinguishing-ignorance-from-error-in-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Modality Adaptation with Text-to-Image Diffusion Models for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-modality-adaptation-with-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose Modality Adaptation with text-to-image Diffusion Models (MADM) for semantic segmentation task which utilizes text-to-image diffusion models pre-trained on extensive image-text pairs to enhance the model's cross-modality capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-modality-adaptation-with-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Class Textual-Inversion Secretly Yields a Semantic-Agnostic Classifier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-class-textual-inversion-secretly-yields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in many realistic scenarios, we only have access to few samples and knowledge of the class names (e. g., when considering instances of classes).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-class-textual-inversion-secretly-yields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PF3plat: Pose-Free Feed-Forward 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pf3plat-pose-free-feed-forward-3d-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then introduce lightweight, learnable modules to refine depth and pose estimates from the coarse alignments, improving the quality of 3D reconstruction and novel view synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pf3plat-pose-free-feed-forward-3d-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-Guided Prompt Learning for Request Quality Assurance in Public Code Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-guided-prompt-learning-for-request</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Public Code Review (PCR) is an assistant to the internal code review of the development team, in the form of a public Software Question Answering (SQA) community, to help developers access high-quality and efficient review services.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-guided-prompt-learning-for-request</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Relaxed Joint Training: Sample Selection for Severity Estimation with Ordinal Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-relaxed-joint-training-sample-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By appropriately using the soft and hard labels in the two techniques, we achieve more accurate sample selection and robust network training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-relaxed-joint-training-sample-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EconoJax: A Fast &amp; Scalable Economic Simulation in Jax</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/econojax-a-fast-scalable-economic-simulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate economic simulations often require many experimental runs, particularly when combined with reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/econojax-a-fast-scalable-economic-simulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Level Feature Distillation of Joint Teachers Trained on Distinct Image Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-feature-distillation-of-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel teacher-student framework to distill knowledge from multiple teachers trained on distinct datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-feature-distillation-of-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Policy Learning with Temporal Optimal Transport Reward</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robot-policy-learning-with-temporal-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, in this paper, we introduce the Temporal Optimal Transport (TemporalOT) reward to incorporate temporal order information for learning a more accurate OT-based proxy reward.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robot-policy-learning-with-temporal-optimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achilles, Neural Network to Predict the Gold Vs US Dollar Integration with Trading Bot for Automatic Trading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achilles-neural-network-to-predict-the-gold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Achilles, with a classical architecture of LSTM(Long Short Term Memory) neural network this model is able to predict the Gold vs USD commodity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achilles-neural-network-to-predict-the-gold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoBench-V: Can Large Vision-Language Models Benchmark Themselves?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autobench-v-can-large-vision-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Vision-Language Models (LVLMs) have become essential for advancing the integration of visual and linguistic information, facilitating a wide range of complex applications and tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autobench-v-can-large-vision-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoformalize Mathematical Statements by Symbolic Equivalence and Semantic Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoformalize-mathematical-statements-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoformalization, the task of automatically translating natural language descriptions into a formal language, poses a significant challenge across various domains, especially in mathematics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoformalize-mathematical-statements-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Study of Multiple Deep Learning Algorithms for Efficient Localization of Bone Joints in the Upper Limbs of Human Body</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-multiple-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper provides a detailed comparative study between diverse Deep Learning (DL) models - YOLOv3, YOLOv7, EfficientDet and CenterNet in multiple bone joint detections in the upper limbs of the human body.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-multiple-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Hamilton: Can A.I. Understand Hamiltonian Mechanics?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-hamilton-can-a-i-understand</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel framework based on neural network that reformulates classical mechanics as an operator learning problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-hamilton-can-a-i-understand</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robustness and Generalization in Quantum Reinforcement Learning via Lipschitz Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-and-generalization-in-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that training with RegQPG improves the robustness and generalization of the resulting policies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-and-generalization-in-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking Back the AI-Hacker: Prompt Injection as a Defense Against LLM-driven Cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hacking-back-the-ai-hacker-prompt-injection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are increasingly being harnessed to automate cyberattacks, making sophisticated exploits more accessible and scalable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hacking-back-the-ai-hacker-prompt-injection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-agnostic basis functions for the 2-point correlation function of dark matter in linear theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-agnostic-basis-functions-for-the-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider approximating the linearly evolved 2-point correlation function (2pcf) of dark matter $\xi_{\rm lin}(r;\boldsymbol{\theta})$ in a cosmological model with parameters $\boldsymbol{\theta}$ as the linear combination $\xi_{\rm lin}(r;\boldsymbol{\theta})\approx\sum_i\, b_i(r)\, w_i(\boldsymbol{\theta})$, where the functions $\mathcal{B}=\{b_i(r)\}$ form a $\textit{model-agnostic basis}$ for the linear 2pcf.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-agnostic-basis-functions-for-the-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMCBench: Benchmarking Large Language Model Compression for Efficient Deployment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmcbench-benchmarking-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we perform an in-depth analysis based on the evaluation and provide useful insight for LLM compression design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmcbench-benchmarking-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>uOttawa at LegalLens-2024: Transformer-based Classification Experiments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uottawa-at-legallens-2024-transformer-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results were 86. 3% in the L-NER subtask and 88. 25% in the L-NLI subtask.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uottawa-at-legallens-2024-transformer-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLAS: Adapting Trajectory Lengths and Step-Size for Hamiltonian Monte Carlo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atlas-adapting-trajectory-lengths-and-step</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hamiltonian Monte-Carlo (HMC) and its auto-tuned variant, the No U-Turn Sampler (NUTS) can struggle to accurately sample distributions with complex geometries, e. g., varying curvature, due to their constant step size for leapfrog integration and fixed mass matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atlas-adapting-trajectory-lengths-and-step</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CODES: Benchmarking Coupled ODE Surrogates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codes-benchmarking-coupled-ode-surrogates</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce CODES, a benchmark for comprehensive evaluation of surrogate architectures for coupled ODE systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codes-benchmarking-coupled-ode-surrogates</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-Enhanced Mutation Mastery: Augmenting Zero-Shot Prediction of Protein Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-enhanced-mutation-mastery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Enzyme engineering enables the modification of wild-type proteins to meet industrial and research demands by enhancing catalytic activity, stability, binding affinities, and other properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-enhanced-mutation-mastery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Yet Effective Corpus Construction Framework for Indonesian Grammatical Error Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-yet-effective-corpus-construction-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How to efficiently construct high-quality evaluation corpora for GEC in low-resource languages has become a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-yet-effective-corpus-construction-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Unauthorized Speech Synthesis for Voice Protection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-unauthorized-speech-synthesis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With just a few speech samples, it is possible to perfectly replicate a speaker's voice in recent years, while malicious voice exploitation (e. g., telecom fraud for illegal financial gain) has brought huge hazards in our daily lives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-unauthorized-speech-synthesis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Visual Prompt Tuning by Gaussian Neighborhood Minimization for Long-Tailed Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-visual-prompt-tuning-by-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel method called Random SAM prompt tuning (RSAM-PT) to improve the model generalization, requiring only one-step gradient computation at each step.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-visual-prompt-tuning-by-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Handle Complex Constraints for Vehicle Routing Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-handle-complex-constraints-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vehicle Routing Problems (VRPs) can model many real-world scenarios and often involve complex constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-handle-complex-constraints-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Detection of Person Class Using Dense Pooling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-detection-of-person-class-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further improve the performance of person detection we have conducted a different approach which gives the state-of-the-art conclusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-detection-of-person-class-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Tailed Out-of-Distribution Detection via Normalized Outlier Distribution Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-out-of-distribution-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel approach, namely normalized outlier distribution adaptation (AdaptOD), to tackle this distribution shift problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-out-of-distribution-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geo-FuB: A Method for Constructing an Operator-Function Knowledge Base for Geospatial Code Generation Tasks Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geo-fub-a-method-for-constructing-an-operator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, a retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) approach, utilizing an external knowledge base of geospatial functions and operators, is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geo-fub-a-method-for-constructing-an-operator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECMamba: Consolidating Selective State Space Model with Retinex Guidance for Efficient Multiple Exposure Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecmamba-consolidating-selective-state-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by Mamba which demonstrates powerful and highly efficient sequence modeling, we introduce a novel framework based on Mamba for Exposure Correction (ECMamba) with dual pathways, each dedicated to the restoration of reflectance and illumination map, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecmamba-consolidating-selective-state-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Spectral Attention for Long-Range Dependency in Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introducing-spectral-attention-for-long-range</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, we introduce a fast and effective Spectral Attention mechanism, which preserves temporal correlations among samples and facilitates the handling of long-range information while maintaining the base model structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introducing-spectral-attention-for-long-range</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NewTerm: Benchmarking Real-Time New Terms for Large Language Models with Annual Updates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/newterm-benchmarking-real-time-new-terms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their remarkable abilities in various tasks, large language models (LLMs) still struggle with real-time information (e. g., new facts and terms) due to the knowledge cutoff in their development process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/newterm-benchmarking-real-time-new-terms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Action Recognition by Leveraging the Hierarchical Structure of Actions and Textual Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-action-recognition-by-leveraging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we present a novel approach to improve action recognition by exploiting the hierarchical organization of actions and by incorporating contextualized textual information, including location and prior actions to reflect the sequential context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-action-recognition-by-leveraging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-Retro: Retrieval-based Inorganic Retrosynthesis with Expert Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-retro-retrieval-based-inorganic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Retrieval-Retro for inorganic retrosynthesis planning, which implicitly extracts the precursor information of reference materials that are retrieved from the knowledge base regarding domain expertise in the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-retro-retrieval-based-inorganic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuZip: Memory-Efficient Training and Inference with Dynamic Compression of Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuzip-memory-efficient-training-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the model sizes are constrained by the available on-device memory during training and inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuzip-memory-efficient-training-and</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
