<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 09:11:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>BAN-PL: a Novel Polish Dataset of Banned Harmful and Offensive Content from Wykop.pl web service</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ban-pl-a-novel-polish-dataset-of-banned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advances in automated detection of offensive language online, including hate speech and cyberbullying, require improved access to publicly available datasets comprising social media content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ban-pl-a-novel-polish-dataset-of-banned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Shadow Mapping for Efficient Inverse Graphics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-shadow-mapping-for-efficient-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show how shadows can be efficiently generated in differentiable rendering of triangle meshes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-shadow-mapping-for-efficient-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving Face Recognition Using Random Frequency Components</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-face-recognition-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ubiquitous use of face recognition has sparked increasing privacy concerns, as unauthorized access to sensitive face images could compromise the information of individuals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-face-recognition-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Entity Recognition with Noise-Robust Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/software-entity-recognition-with-noise-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizing software entities such as library names from free-form text is essential to enable many software engineering (SE) technologies, such as traceability link recovery, automated documentation, and API recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/software-entity-recognition-with-noise-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniM$^2$AE: Multi-modal Masked Autoencoders with Unified 3D Representation for 3D Perception in Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unim-2-ae-multi-modal-masked-autoencoders</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The extension makes it possible to back-project the informative features, obtained by fusing features from both modalities, into their native modalities to reconstruct the multiple masked inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unim-2-ae-multi-modal-masked-autoencoders</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Prompting for Data-Free Continual Unsupervised Domain Adaptive Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-prompting-for-data-free-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a Color Prompting (CoP) method for data-free continual unsupervised domain adaptive person Re-ID.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-prompting-for-data-free-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Dialogue Topic Segmentation in Hyperdimensional Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-dialogue-topic-segmentation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We open-source HyperSeg to provide a strong baseline for unsupervised topic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-dialogue-topic-segmentation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-Temporal Adaptive Embedding Makes Vanilla Transformer SOTA for Traffic Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-adaptive-embedding-makes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid development of the Intelligent Transportation System (ITS), accurate traffic forecasting has emerged as a critical challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-adaptive-embedding-makes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EigenPlaces: Training Viewpoint Robust Models for Visual Place Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigenplaces-training-viewpoint-robust-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Place Recognition is a task that aims to predict the place of an image (called query) based solely on its visual features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigenplaces-training-viewpoint-robust-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GBM-based Bregman Proximal Algorithms for Constrained Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gbm-based-bregman-proximal-algorithms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we adapt the GBM for constrained learning tasks within the framework of Bregman proximal algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gbm-based-bregman-proximal-algorithms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RaLLe: A Framework for Developing and Evaluating Retrieval-Augmented Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ralle-a-framework-for-developing-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-augmented large language models (R-LLMs) combine pre-trained large language models (LLMs) with information retrieval systems to improve the accuracy of factual question-answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ralle-a-framework-for-developing-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WanJuan: A Comprehensive Multimodal Dataset for Advancing English and Chinese Large Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wanjuan-a-comprehensive-multimodal-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise in popularity of ChatGPT and GPT-4 has significantly accelerated the development of large models, leading to the creation of numerous impressive large language models(LLMs) and multimodal large language models (MLLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wanjuan-a-comprehensive-multimodal-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataset Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-quantization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate that DQ is able to generate condensed small datasets for training unseen network architectures with state-of-the-art compression ratios for lossless model training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-quantization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Linear Concept Discovery Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-linear-concept-discovery-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent mass adoption of DNNs, even in safety-critical scenarios, has shifted the focus of the research community towards the creation of inherently intrepretable models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-linear-concept-discovery-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynDrone -- Multi-modal UAV Dataset for Urban Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syndrone-multi-modal-uav-dataset-for-urban</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of computer vision algorithms for Unmanned Aerial Vehicles (UAVs) imagery heavily relies on the availability of annotated high-resolution aerial data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syndrone-multi-modal-uav-dataset-for-urban</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGSL: A Unified Framework for Benchmarking Graph Structure Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ugsl-a-unified-framework-for-benchmarking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We implement a wide range of existing models in our framework and conduct extensive analyses of the effectiveness of different components in the framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ugsl-a-unified-framework-for-benchmarking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Less is Enough: Positive and Unlabeled Learning Model for Vulnerability Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-less-is-enough-positive-and-unlabeled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on the Positive and Unlabeled (PU) learning problem for vulnerability detection and propose a novel model named PILOT, i. e., PositIve and unlabeled Learning mOdel for vulnerability deTection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-less-is-enough-positive-and-unlabeled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Transferability of Adversarial Examples with Arbitrary Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-transferability-of-adversarial-7</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks are vulnerable to adversarial examples crafted by applying human-imperceptible perturbations on clean inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-transferability-of-adversarial-7</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approximately Equivariant Graph Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximately-equivariant-graph-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) are commonly described as being permutation equivariant with respect to node relabeling in the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximately-equivariant-graph-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoNe: Contrast Your Neighbours for Supervised Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cone-contrast-your-neighbours-for-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, to further boost the performance, we propose ``distributional consistency" as a more informative regularization to enable similar instances to have a similar probability distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cone-contrast-your-neighbours-for-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Joint Optimization of Layer-Adaptive Weight Pruning in Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-joint-optimization-of-layer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On ImageNet, we achieve up to 4. 7% and 4. 6% higher top-1 accuracy compared to other methods for VGG-16 and ResNet-50, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-joint-optimization-of-layer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEERER: Resolving Scale Variations for Counting and Localization via Selective Inheritance Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steerer-resolving-scale-variations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scale variation is a deep-rooted problem in object counting, which has not been effectively addressed by existing scale-aware algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steerer-resolving-scale-variations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Spherical Harmonics Improve Skeleton-Based Hand Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-spherical-harmonics-improve-skeleton</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method specifically designed for hand action recognition which uses relative angular embeddings and local Spherical Harmonics to create novel hand representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-spherical-harmonics-improve-skeleton</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Prompt-based Incremental Learning Does Not Meet Strong Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-prompt-based-incremental-learning-does</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing prompt-based methods heavily rely on strong pretraining (typically trained on ImageNet-21k), and we find that their models could be trapped if the potential gap between the pretraining task and unknown future tasks is large.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-prompt-based-incremental-learning-does</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image-free Classifier Injection for Zero-Shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-free-classifier-injection-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We achieve this with our proposed Image-free Classifier Injection with Semantics (ICIS) that injects classifiers for new, unseen classes into pre-trained classification models in a post-hoc fashion without relying on image data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-free-classifier-injection-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ST-RAP: A Spatio-Temporal Framework for Real Estate Appraisal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/st-rap-a-spatio-temporal-framework-for-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce ST-RAP, a novel Spatio-Temporal framework for Real estate APpraisal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/st-rap-a-spatio-temporal-framework-for-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bbOCR: An Open-source Multi-domain OCR Pipeline for Bengali Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bbocr-an-open-source-multi-domain-ocr</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present extensive component-level and system-level evaluation: both use a novel diversified evaluation dataset and comprehensive evaluation metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bbocr-an-open-source-multi-domain-ocr</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Effective Method using Phrase Mechanism in Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-effective-method-using-phrase-mechanism-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine Translation is one of the essential tasks in Natural Language Processing (NLP), which has massive applications in real life as well as contributing to other tasks in the NLP research community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-effective-method-using-phrase-mechanism-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SRFormer: Empowering Regression-Based Text Detection Transformer with Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srformer-empowering-regression-based-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In light of this, we constrain the incorporation of segmentation branches to the first few decoder layers and employ progressive regression refinement in subsequent layers, achieving performance gains while minimizing additional computational load from the mask.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srformer-empowering-regression-based-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-VoE: Measuring eXplanatory Violation of Expectation in Physical Events</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-voe-measuring-explanatory-violation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intuitive physics is pivotal for human understanding of the physical world, enabling prediction and interpretation of events even in infancy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-voe-measuring-explanatory-violation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Don't Need No Adam, All We Need Is EVE: On The Variance of Dual Learning Rate And Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/we-don-t-need-no-adam-all-we-need-is-eve-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the rapidly advancing field of deep learning, optimising deep neural networks is paramount.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/we-don-t-need-no-adam-all-we-need-is-eve-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentVerse: Facilitating Multi-Agent Collaboration and Exploring Emergent Behaviors in Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentverse-facilitating-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous agents empowered by Large Language Models (LLMs) have undergone significant improvements, enabling them to generalize across a broad spectrum of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentverse-facilitating-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning a CLIP Model into a Scene Text Spotter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/turning-a-clip-model-into-a-scene-text-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Utilizing only 10% of the supervised data, FastTCM-CR50 improves performance by an average of 26. 5% and 5. 5% for text detection and spotting tasks, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/turning-a-clip-model-into-a-scene-text-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Baselines for Interactive Video Retrieval with Questions and Answers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-baselines-for-interactive-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To date, the majority of video retrieval systems have been optimized for a "single-shot" scenario in which the user submits a query in isolation, ignoring previous interactions with the system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-baselines-for-interactive-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Topology-aware Analysis of Graph Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-topology-aware-analysis-of-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The successful integration of graph neural networks into recommender systems (RSs) has led to a novel paradigm in collaborative filtering (CF), graph collaborative filtering (graph CF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-topology-aware-analysis-of-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Transform Decoupling for Oriented Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-transform-decoupling-for-oriented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision Transformers (ViTs) have achieved remarkable success in computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-transform-decoupling-for-oriented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Empirical Evaluation on Online Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-empirical-evaluation-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online continual learning aims to get closer to a live learning experience by learning directly on a stream of data with temporally shifting distribution and by storing a minimum amount of data from that stream.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-empirical-evaluation-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiking-Diffusion: Vector Quantized Discrete Diffusion Model with Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-diffusion-vector-quantized-discrete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill the gap, we propose a Spiking-Diffusion model, which is based on the vector quantized discrete diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-diffusion-vector-quantized-discrete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Real-World Visual Tracking with Temporal Contexts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-visual-tracking-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To handle those problems, we propose a two-level framework (TCTrack) that can exploit temporal contexts efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-visual-tracking-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Spatiotemporal Traffic Prediction through Urban Human Activity Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-spatiotemporal-traffic-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traffic prediction is one of the key elements to ensure the safety and convenience of citizens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-spatiotemporal-traffic-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Global to Local: Multi-scale Out-of-distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-global-to-local-multi-scale-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-distribution (OOD) detection aims to detect "unknown" data whose labels have not been seen during the in-distribution (ID) training process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-global-to-local-multi-scale-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Adversarial Robustness of Masked Autoencoders via Test-time Frequency-domain Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-adversarial-robustness-of-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our analysis, we provide a simple yet effective way to boost the adversarial robustness of MAE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-adversarial-robustness-of-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LibriSQA: Pioneering Free-form and Open-ended Spoken Question Answering with a Novel Dataset and Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/librisqa-pioneering-free-form-and-open-ended</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated commendable performance across a myriad of domains and tasks, existing LLMs still exhibit a palpable deficit in handling multimodal functionalities, especially for the Spoken Question Answering (SQA) task which necessitates precise alignment and deep interaction between speech and text features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/librisqa-pioneering-free-form-and-open-ended</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>March in Chat: Interactive Prompting for Remote Embodied Referring Expression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/march-in-chat-interactive-prompting-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nevertheless, this poses more challenges than other VLN tasks since it requires agents to infer a navigation plan only based on a short instruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/march-in-chat-interactive-prompting-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning-powered Combinatorial Clock Auction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-powered-combinatorial-clock</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we address this shortcoming by designing an ML-powered combinatorial clock auction that elicits information from the bidders only via demand queries (i. e., ``At prices $p$, what is your most preferred bundle of items?'').]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-powered-combinatorial-clock</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wasserstein Geodesic Generator for Conditional Distributions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasserstein-geodesic-generator-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The conditional distributions given unobserved intermediate domains are on the Wasserstein geodesic between conditional distributions given two observed domain labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasserstein-geodesic-generator-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DVGaze: Dual-View Gaze Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dvgaze-dual-view-gaze-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further propose a dual-view transformer to estimate gaze from dual-view features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dvgaze-dual-view-gaze-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StableLLaVA: Enhanced Visual Instruction Tuning with Synthesized Image-Dialogue Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stablellava-enhanced-visual-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The remarkable multimodal capabilities demonstrated by OpenAI's GPT-4 have sparked significant interest in the development of multimodal Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stablellava-enhanced-visual-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient-VRNet: An Exquisite Fusion Network for Riverway Panoptic Perception based on Asymmetric Fair Fusion of Vision and 4D mmWave Radar</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-vrnet-an-exquisite-fusion-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on riverway panoptic perception based on USVs, which is a considerably unexplored field compared with road panoptic perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-vrnet-an-exquisite-fusion-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransFace: Calibrating Transformer Training for Face Recognition from a Data-Centric Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transface-calibrating-transformer-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the reasons for this phenomenon and discover that the existing data augmentation approach and hard sample mining strategy are incompatible with ViTs-based FR backbone due to the lack of tailored consideration on preserving face structural information and leveraging each local token information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transface-calibrating-transformer-training</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
