<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:09:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation-Free Training of Neural ODEs on Paired Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-free-training-of-neural-odes-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate a method for simulation-free training of Neural Ordinary Differential Equations (NODEs) for learning deterministic mappings between paired data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-free-training-of-neural-odes-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Triplet-Level Hallucination Evaluation for Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-triplet-level-hallucination</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core idea of our framework is to conduct hallucination evaluation on (object, relation, object) triplets extracted from LVLMs' responses, and thus, could be easily generalized to different vision-language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-triplet-level-hallucination</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Very fast Bayesian Additive Regression Trees on GPU</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/very-fast-bayesian-additive-regression-trees</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian Additive Regression Trees (BART) is a nonparametric Bayesian regression technique based on an ensemble of decision trees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/very-fast-bayesian-additive-regression-trees</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Personalization for LLM-based Recommendation with Customized In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-personalization-for-llm-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work explores adapting to dynamic user interests without any model updates by leveraging In-Context Learning (ICL), which allows LLMs to learn new tasks from few-shot examples provided in the input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-personalization-for-llm-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SFA-UNet: More Attention to Multi-Scale Contrast and Contextual Information in Infrared Small Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfa-unet-more-attention-to-multi-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SFA-UNet utilizes double convolution layers with the addition of SC and FFC in its encoder and decoder layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfa-unet-more-attention-to-multi-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Learning and Adversarial Disentanglement for Privacy-Preserving Task-Oriented Semantic Communications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-and-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Task-oriented semantic communication systems have emerged as a promising approach to achieving efficient and intelligent data transmission, where only information relevant to a specific task is communicated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-and-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FuseAnyPart: Diffusion-Driven Facial Parts Swapping via Multiple Reference Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fuseanypart-diffusion-driven-facial-parts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial parts swapping aims to selectively transfer regions of interest from the source image onto the target image while maintaining the rest of the target image unchanged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fuseanypart-diffusion-driven-facial-parts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparative Analysis of Demonstration Selection Algorithms for LLM In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-analysis-of-demonstration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In-context learning can help Large Language Models (LLMs) to adapt new tasks without additional training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-analysis-of-demonstration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unfolding Target Detection with State Space Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unfolding-target-detection-with-state-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We implement a lightweight model of only 260K parameters and conduct real-world experiments for human target detection using FMCW radars.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unfolding-target-detection-with-state-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOMATO: Assessing Visual Temporal Reasoning Capabilities in Multimodal Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tomato-assessing-visual-temporal-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study of existing benchmarks shows that this capability of MFMs is likely overestimated as many questions can be solved by using a single, few, or out-of-order frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tomato-assessing-visual-temporal-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fourier Amplitude and Correlation Loss: Beyond Using L2 Loss for Skillful Precipitation Nowcasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fourier-amplitude-and-correlation-loss-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method is generic, parameter-free and efficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fourier-amplitude-and-correlation-loss-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less is More: Pre-Training Cross-Lingual Small-Scale Language Models with Cognitively-Plausible Curriculum Learning Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-pre-training-cross-lingual-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Curriculum Learning has been a popular strategy to improve the cognitive plausibility of Small-Scale Language Models (SSLMs) in the BabyLM Challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-pre-training-cross-lingual-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Sampling for High Utility Patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-sampling-for-high-utility-patterns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, it becomes challenging when trying to identify representative patterns in quantitative databases, especially with large datasets, as enumeration-based strategies struggle due to the vast search space involved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-sampling-for-high-utility-patterns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMAL: A Convergent Meta-Algorithm for Aligning LLMs with General Preferences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comal-a-convergent-meta-algorithm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve robust alignment with general preferences, we model the alignment problem as a two-player zero-sum game, where the Nash equilibrium policy guarantees a 50% win rate against any competing policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comal-a-convergent-meta-algorithm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InjecGuard: Benchmarking and Mitigating Over-defense in Prompt Injection Guardrail Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/injecguard-benchmarking-and-mitigating-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NotInject contains 339 benign samples enriched with trigger words common in prompt injection attacks, enabling fine-grained evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/injecguard-benchmarking-and-mitigating-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective and Efficient Adversarial Detection for Vision-Language Models via A Single Vector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-and-efficient-adversarial-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the new RADAR dataset, we further develop a novel and effective iN-time Embedding-based AdveRSarial Image DEtection (NEARSIDE) method, which exploits a single vector that distilled from the hidden states of VLMs, which we call the attacking direction, to achieve the detection of adversarial images against benign ones in the input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-and-efficient-adversarial-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V2X-Assisted Distributed Computing and Control Framework for Connected and Automated Vehicles under Ramp Merging Scenario</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2x-assisted-distributed-computing-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, a centralized cooperative trajectory planning problem is formulated subject to the safely constraints and traffic performance in ramp merging scenario, where the trajectories of all vehicles are jointly optimized.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2x-assisted-distributed-computing-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causality-Enhanced Behavior Sequence Modeling in LLMs for Personalized Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-enhanced-behavior-sequence-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in recommender systems have focused on leveraging Large Language Models (LLMs) to improve user preference modeling, yielding promising outcomes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-enhanced-behavior-sequence-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Threshold-based Two-layer Online Unsupervised Anomaly Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-threshold-based-two-layer-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proliferation of the Internet of Things (IoT) has heightened the vulnerability to cyber threats, making it imperative to develop Anomaly Detection Systems (ADSs) capable of adapting to emerging or novel attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-threshold-based-two-layer-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Individual Identity-Driven Framework for Animal Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-individual-identity-driven-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reliable re-identification of individuals within large wildlife populations is crucial for biological studies, ecological research, and wildlife conservation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-individual-identity-driven-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Ontology in Dialogue State Tracking for Goal-Oriented Chatbot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-ontology-in-dialogue-state-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Goal-oriented chatbots are essential for automating user tasks, such as booking flights or making restaurant reservations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-ontology-in-dialogue-state-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offline Behavior Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-behavior-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this issue, we formulate offline behavior distillation (OBD), which synthesizes limited expert behavioral data from sub-optimal RL data, enabling rapid policy learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-behavior-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffLight: A Partial Rewards Conditioned Diffusion Model for Traffic Signal Control with Missing Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difflight-a-partial-rewards-conditioned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The application of reinforcement learning in traffic signal control (TSC) has been extensively researched and yielded notable achievements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difflight-a-partial-rewards-conditioned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Transformers with Spectrum-Preserving Token Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-transformers-with-spectrum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Increasing the throughput of the Transformer architecture, a foundational component used in numerous state-of-the-art models for vision and language tasks (e. g., GPT, LLaVa), is an important problem in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-transformers-with-spectrum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$100K or 100 Days: Trade-offs when Pre-Training with Academic Resources</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/100k-or-100-days-trade-offs-when-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a benchmark to measure the time to pre-train models on given GPUs and also identify ideal settings for maximizing training speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/100k-or-100-days-trade-offs-when-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HelloMeme: Integrating Spatial Knitting Attentions to Embed High-Level and Fidelity-Rich Conditions in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hellomeme-integrating-spatial-knitting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an effective method for inserting adapters into text-to-image foundation models, which enables the execution of complex downstream tasks while preserving the generalization ability of the base model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hellomeme-integrating-spatial-knitting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIS: NL2SQL Service Evaluation Benchmark for Business Intelligence Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bis-nl2sql-service-evaluation-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NL2SQL (Natural Language to Structured Query Language) transformation has seen wide adoption in Business Intelligence (BI) applications in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bis-nl2sql-service-evaluation-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrossEarth: Geospatial Vision Foundation Model for Domain Generalizable Remote Sensing Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crossearth-geospatial-vision-foundation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of Remote Sensing Domain Generalization (RSDG) has emerged as a critical and valuable research frontier, focusing on developing models that generalize effectively across diverse scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crossearth-geospatial-vision-foundation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGU-SLAM: Learnable Gaussian Uncertainty Matching with Deformable Correlation Sampling for Deep Visual SLAM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgu-slam-learnable-gaussian-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In general, they heavily rely on global visual similarity matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgu-slam-learnable-gaussian-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZ: Beehive-structured Sparse KV Cache with Segmented Heavy Hitters for Efficient LLM Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/buzz-beehive-structured-sparse-kv-cache-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key-value (KV) cache mechanism reduces computational overhead in transformer models, but challenges in maintaining contextual understanding remain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/buzz-beehive-structured-sparse-kv-cache-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TokenFormer: Rethinking Transformer Scaling with Tokenized Model Parameters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenformer-rethinking-transformer-scaling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By treating model parameters as tokens, we replace all the linear projections in Transformers with our token-parameter attention layer, where input tokens act as queries and model parameters as keys and values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenformer-rethinking-transformer-scaling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compositional Segmentation of Cardiac Images Leveraging Metadata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-segmentation-of-cardiac-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by coarse-to-fine approaches in image analysis, we propose a novel multitask compositional segmentation approach that can simultaneously localize the heart in a cardiac image and perform part-based segmentation of different regions of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-segmentation-of-cardiac-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparison of Prompt Engineering Techniques for Task Planning and Execution in Service Robotics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-of-prompt-engineering-techniques</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in LLM have been instrumental in autonomous robot control and human-robot interaction by leveraging their vast general knowledge and capabilities to understand and reason across a wide range of tasks and scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-of-prompt-engineering-techniques</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FT-PrivacyScore: Personalized Privacy Scoring Service for Machine Learning Participation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ft-privacyscore-personalized-privacy-scoring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training data privacy has been a top concern in AI modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ft-privacyscore-personalized-privacy-scoring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VPO: Leveraging the Number of Votes in Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vpo-leveraging-the-number-of-votes-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Preference datasets are typically created by selecting preferred sentences through a voting process involving multiple individuals, as opinions can vary due to the subjective nature of human preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vpo-leveraging-the-number-of-votes-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Fidelity Document Stain Removal via A Large-Scale Real-World Dataset and A Memory-Augmented Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-fidelity-document-stain-removal-via-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we construct StainDoc, the first large-scale, high-resolution ($2145\times2245$) dataset specifically designed for document stain removal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-fidelity-document-stain-removal-via-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReasoningRec: Bridging Personalized Recommendations and Human-Interpretable Explanations through LLM Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoningrec-bridging-personalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents ReasoningRec, a reasoning-based recommendation framework that leverages Large Language Models (LLMs) to bridge the gap between recommendations and human-interpretable explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoningrec-bridging-personalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ContextIQ: A Multimodal Expert-Based Video Retrieval System for Contextual Advertising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextiq-a-multimodal-expert-based-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that our system, without joint training, achieves better or comparable results to state-of-the-art models and commercial solutions on multiple text-to-video retrieval benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextiq-a-multimodal-expert-based-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Class Textual-Inversion Secretly Yields a Semantic-Agnostic Classifier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-class-textual-inversion-secretly-yields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in many realistic scenarios, we only have access to few samples and knowledge of the class names (e. g., when considering instances of classes).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-class-textual-inversion-secretly-yields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pushing the Performance Envelope of DNN-based Recommendation Systems Inference on GPUs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pushing-the-performance-envelope-of-dnn-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental evaluations using A100 GPUs with large models and datasets show that our proposed techniques improve performance by up to 103% for the embedding stage, and up to 77% for the overall DLRM inference pipeline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pushing-the-performance-envelope-of-dnn-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LipKernel: Lipschitz-Bounded Convolutional Neural Networks via Dissipative Layers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lipkernel-lipschitz-bounded-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Collectively, these layer-wise LMIs ensure Lipschitz boundedness for the input-output mapping of the neural network, yielding a more expressive parameterization than through spectral bounds or orthogonal layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lipkernel-lipschitz-bounded-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distinguishing Ignorance from Error in LLM Hallucinations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinguishing-ignorance-from-error-in-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To help distinguish between the two cases, we introduce Wrong Answer despite having Correct Knowledge (WACK), an approach for constructing model-specific datasets for the second hallucination type.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinguishing-ignorance-from-error-in-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Guided Attention is All You Need for Zero-Shot Robustness in Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-attention-is-all-you-need-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our goal is to maintain the generalization of the CLIP model and enhance its adversarial robustness: The Attention Refinement module aligns the text-guided attention obtained from the target model via adversarial examples with the text-guided attention acquired from the original model via clean examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-attention-is-all-you-need-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PerSRV: Personalized Sticker Retrieval with Vision-Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persrv-personalized-sticker-retrieval-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The online retrieval part follows the paradigm of relevant recall and personalized ranking, supported by the offline pre-calculation parts, which are sticker semantic understanding, utility evaluation and personalization modules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persrv-personalized-sticker-retrieval-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProMQA: Question Answering Dataset for Multimodal Procedural Activity Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promqa-question-answering-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal systems have great potential to assist humans in procedural activities, where people follow instructions to achieve their goals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promqa-question-answering-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lighten CARAFE: Dynamic Lightweight Upsampling with Guided Reassemble Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lighten-carafe-dynamic-lightweight-upsampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on several mainstream vision tasks show that our DLU achieves comparable and even better performance to the original CARAFE, but with much lower complexity, e. g., DLU requires 91% fewer parameters and at least 63% fewer FLOPs (Floating Point Operations) than CARAFE in the case of 16x upsampling, but outperforms the CARAFE by 0. 3% mAP in object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lighten-carafe-dynamic-lightweight-upsampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-Swin: SAM-Driven Dual-Swin Transformers with Adaptive Lesion Enhancement for Laryngo-Pharyngeal Tumor Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-swin-sam-driven-dual-swin-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Laryngo-pharyngeal cancer (LPC) is a highly lethal malignancy in the head and neck region.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-swin-sam-driven-dual-swin-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHORDONOMICON: A Dataset of 666,000 Songs and their Chord Progressions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chordonomicon-a-dataset-of-666000-songs-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chord progressions encapsulate important information about music, pertaining to its structure and conveyed emotions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chordonomicon-a-dataset-of-666000-songs-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Path-based summary explanations for graph recommenders -- extended version</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/path-based-summary-explanations-for-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose summary explanations, i. e., explanations that highlight why a user or a group of users receive a set of item recommendations and why an item, or a group of items, is recommended to a set of users as an effective means to provide insights into the collective behavior of the recommender.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/path-based-summary-explanations-for-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volumetric Conditioning Module to Control Pretrained Diffusion Models for 3D Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volumetric-conditioning-module-to-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further investigate the potential applications for our spatial control method through axial super-resolution for medical images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volumetric-conditioning-module-to-control</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
