<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 21:07:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MoveFormer: a Transformer-based model for step-selection animal movement modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moveformer-a-transformer-based-model-for-step</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose MoveFormer, a new step-based model of movement capable of learning directly from full animal trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moveformer-a-transformer-based-model-for-step</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSH-Det3D: Improving 3D Object Detection with BEV Shape Heatmap</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bsh-det3d-improving-3d-object-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we design the Pillar-based Shape Completion (PSC) module to predict the probability of occupancy whether a pillar contains object shapes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bsh-det3d-improving-3d-object-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Diffusions in Augmented Spaces: A Complete Recipe</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-diffusions-in-augmented-spaces-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Score-based Generative Models (SGMs) have achieved state-of-the-art synthesis results on diverse tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-diffusions-in-augmented-spaces-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONTAIN: A Community-based Algorithm for Network Immunization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contain-a-community-based-algorithm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within the network analysis field, network immunization refers to the task of protecting a network from some arbitrary diffusion that tries to infect it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contain-a-community-based-algorithm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPGym: Benchmarking Partially Observable Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/popgym-benchmarking-partially-observable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real world applications of Reinforcement Learning (RL) are often partially observable, thus requiring memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/popgym-benchmarking-partially-observable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing Text-to-Image Diffusion Models for Visual Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-text-to-image-diffusion-models-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose VPD (Visual Perception with a pre-trained Diffusion model), a new framework that exploits the semantic information of a pre-trained text-to-image diffusion model in visual perception tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-text-to-image-diffusion-models-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAGE: A Position-Aware Graph-Based Model for Emotion Cause Entailment in Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/page-a-position-aware-graph-based-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational Causal Emotion Entailment (C2E2) is a task that aims at recognizing the causes corresponding to a target emotion in a conversation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/page-a-position-aware-graph-based-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rule-based Out-Of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rule-based-out-of-distribution-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-distribution detection is one of the most critical issue in the deployment of machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rule-based-out-of-distribution-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DWFormer: Dynamic Window transFormer for Speech Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dwformer-dynamic-window-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-attention mechanism is applied within windows for capturing temporal important information locally in a fine-grained way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dwformer-dynamic-window-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T360RRD: A dataset for 360 degree rotated rectangular box table detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t360rrd-a-dataset-for-360-degree-rotated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the problem of scarcity and high annotation costs of rotated image table detection datasets, this chapter proposes a method for building a rotated image table detection dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t360rrd-a-dataset-for-360-degree-rotated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depth-based 6DoF Object Pose Estimation using Swin Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-based-6dof-object-pose-estimation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this challenge, we propose a novel framework called SwinDePose, that uses only geometric information from depth images to achieve accurate 6D pose estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-based-6dof-object-pose-estimation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUSformer: Improving Prostate Cancer Detection from Micro-Ultrasound Using Attention and Self-Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trusformer-improving-prostate-cancer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze this method using a dataset of micro-ultrasound acquired from 578 patients who underwent prostate biopsy, and compare our model to baseline models and other large-scale studies in the literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trusformer-improving-prostate-cancer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine learning using magnetic stochastic synapses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-using-magnetic-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For single measurements, the rule results in binary synapses with minimal stochasticity, sacrificing potential performance for robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-using-magnetic-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asymptotic Bayes risk of semi-supervised multitask learning on Gaussian mixture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymptotic-bayes-risk-of-semi-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the supervised case, we derive a simple algorithm that attains the Bayes optimal performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymptotic-bayes-risk-of-semi-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Graph Neural Networks for Particle Track Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-graph-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel variant of GNN for particle tracking called Hierarchical Graph Neural Network (HGNN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-graph-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovery and Recognition of Formula Concepts using Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovery-and-recognition-of-formula-concepts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our long-term goal is to generalize citation-based IR methods and apply this generalized method to both classical references and mathematical concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovery-and-recognition-of-formula-concepts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparsity May Cry: Let Us Fail (Current) Sparse Neural Networks Together!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsity-may-cry-let-us-fail-current-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In pursuit of a more general evaluation and unveiling the true potential of sparse algorithms, we introduce "Sparsity May Cry" Benchmark (SMC-Bench), a collection of carefully-curated 4 diverse tasks with 10 datasets, that accounts for capturing a wide range of domain-specific and sophisticated knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsity-may-cry-let-us-fail-current-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Energy Conserving Dynamics Efficiently with Hamiltonian Gaussian Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-energy-conserving-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hamiltonian mechanics is one of the cornerstones of natural sciences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-energy-conserving-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedML Parrot: A Scalable Federated Learning System via Heterogeneity-aware Scheduling on Sequential and Hierarchical Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedml-parrot-a-scalable-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It improves the training efficiency, remarkably relaxes the requirements on the hardware, and supports efficient large-scale FL experiments with stateful clients by: (1) sequential training clients on devices; (2) decomposing original aggregation into local and global aggregation on devices and server respectively; (3) scheduling tasks to mitigate straggler problems and enhance computing utility; (4) distributed client state manager to support various FL algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedml-parrot-a-scalable-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convex Bounds on the Softmax Function with Applications to Robustness Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convex-bounds-on-the-softmax-function-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The softmax function is a ubiquitous component at the output of neural networks and increasingly in intermediate layers as well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convex-bounds-on-the-softmax-function-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the Translation Performance of a Large Multilingual Language Model: the Case of BLOOM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-translation-performance-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The NLP community recently saw the release of a new large open-access multilingual language model, BLOOM (BigScience et al., 2022) covering 46 languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-translation-performance-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Permutation-Invariant Embeddings for Description Logic Concepts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-permutation-invariant-embeddings-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We reformulate the learning problem as a multi-label classification problem and propose a neural embedding model (NERO) that learns permutation-invariant embeddings for sets of examples tailored towards predicting $F_1$ scores of pre-selected description logic concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-permutation-invariant-embeddings-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Detection Outcome: A Metric for Pathology Detection in Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-detection-outcome-a-metric-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, we propose Robust Detection Outcome (RoDeO); a novel metric for evaluating algorithms for pathology detection in medical images, especially in chest X-rays.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-detection-outcome-a-metric-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skeletal Point Representations with Geometric Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeletal-point-representations-with-geometric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Skeletonization has been a popular shape analysis technique that models both the interior and exterior of an object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeletal-point-representations-with-geometric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking White Blood Cell Classification Under Domain Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-white-blood-cell-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizing the types of white blood cells (WBCs) in microscopic images of human blood smears is a fundamental task in the fields of pathology and hematology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-white-blood-cell-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Adversarial Training for ImageNet: Architectures, Training and Generalization across Threat Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-adversarial-training-for-imagenet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While adversarial training has been extensively studied for ResNet architectures and low resolution datasets like CIFAR, much less is known for ImageNet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-adversarial-training-for-imagenet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NovPhy: A Testbed for Physical Reasoning in Open-world Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novphy-a-testbed-for-physical-reasoning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[But is it enough to only have physical reasoning capabilities to operate in a real physical environment?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novphy-a-testbed-for-physical-reasoning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Multi-Object Tracking Based on Uncertainty-Guided Data Association</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-multi-object-tracking-based-on-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the existing literature, most 3D multi-object tracking algorithms based on the tracking-by-detection framework employed deterministic tracks and detections for similarity calculation in the data association stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-multi-object-tracking-based-on-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying the LiDAR Sim-to-Real Domain Shift: A Detailed Investigation Using Object Detectors and Analyzing Point Clouds at Target-Level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-the-lidar-sim-to-real-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additional experiments reveal that this domain shift can be lowered by introducing a simple noise model in simulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-the-lidar-sim-to-real-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When does Privileged Information Explain Away Label Noise?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-does-privileged-information-explain-away</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging privileged information (PI), or features available during training but not at test time, has recently been shown to be an effective method for addressing label noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-does-privileged-information-explain-away</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt, Generate, then Cache: Cascade of Foundation Models makes Strong Few-shot Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-generate-then-cache-cascade-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our CaFo incorporates CLIP's language-contrastive knowledge, DINO's vision-contrastive knowledge, DALL-E's vision-generative knowledge, and GPT-3's language-generative knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-generate-then-cache-cascade-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Common Rationale to Improve Self-Supervised Representation for Fine-Grained Visual Recognition Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-common-rationale-to-improve-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we fit the GradCAM with a branch with limited fitting capacity, which allows the branch to capture the common rationales and discard the less common discriminative patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-common-rationale-to-improve-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLANet: Multi-Level Attention Network with Sub-instruction for Continuous Vision-and-Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlanet-multi-level-attention-network-with-sub</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For a better performance in continuous VLN, we design a multi-level instruction understanding procedure and propose a novel model, Multi-Level Attention Network (MLANet).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlanet-multi-level-attention-network-with-sub</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Specformer: Spectral Graph Neural Networks Meet Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/specformer-spectral-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these issues, we introduce Specformer, which effectively encodes the set of all eigenvalues and performs self-attention in the spectral domain, leading to a learnable set-to-set spectral filter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/specformer-spectral-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAP-IQ: Unified Approximation of any-order Shapley Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shap-iq-unified-approximation-of-any-order</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SHAP-IQ is based on a novel representation and, in contrast to existing methods, we provide theoretical guarantees for its approximation quality, as well as estimates for the variance of the point estimates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shap-iq-unified-approximation-of-any-order</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indirect reciprocity with stochastic rules</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indirect-reciprocity-with-stochastic-rules</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we allow social norms to be stochastic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indirect-reciprocity-with-stochastic-rules</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparison of High-Dimensional Bayesian Optimization Algorithms on BBOB</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-of-high-dimensional-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian Optimization (BO) is a class of black-box, surrogate-based heuristics that can efficiently optimize problems that are expensive to evaluate, and hence admit only small evaluation budgets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-of-high-dimensional-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimization-Based Deep learning methods for Magnetic Resonance Imaging Reconstruction and Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-based-deep-learning-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This dissertation is devoted to provide advanced nonconvex nonsmooth variational models of (Magnetic Resonance Image) MRI reconstruction, efficient learnable image reconstruction algorithms and parameter training algorithms that improve the accuracy and robustness of the optimization-based deep learning methods for compressed sensing MRI reconstruction and synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-based-deep-learning-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auxiliary Functions as Koopman Observables: Data-Driven Polynomial Optimization for Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auxiliary-functions-as-koopman-observables</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a flexible data-driven method for dynamical system analysis that does not require explicit model discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auxiliary-functions-as-koopman-observables</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matching-based Term Semantics Pre-training for Spoken Patient Query Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matching-based-term-semantics-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical Slot Filling (MSF) task aims to convert medical queries into structured information, playing an essential role in diagnosis dialogue systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matching-based-term-semantics-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperparameter Tuning and Model Evaluation in Causal Effect Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameter-tuning-and-model-evaluation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also find hyperparameter tuning and model evaluation are much more important than causal estimators and ML methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameter-tuning-and-model-evaluation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixPHM: Redundancy-Aware Parameter-Efficient Tuning for Low-Resource Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixphm-redundancy-aware-parameter-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments conducted on VQA v2, GQA, and OK-VQA with different low-resource settings show that our MixPHM outperforms state-of-the-art parameter-efficient methods and is the only one consistently surpassing full finetuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixphm-redundancy-aware-parameter-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In all LikelihoodS: How to Reliably Select Pseudo-Labeled Data for Self-Training in Semi-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-all-likelihoods-how-to-reliably-select</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a practical proof of concept, we spotlight the application of three of our robust extensions on simulated and real-world data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-all-likelihoods-how-to-reliably-select</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Perturbation Augmentation for Reliable Evaluation of Importance Estimators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-perturbation-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the change in the prediction outcome may stem from perturbation artifacts, since perturbed samples in the test dataset are out of distribution (OOD) compared to the training dataset and can therefore potentially disturb the model in an unexpected manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-perturbation-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geometric Visual Similarity Learning in 3D Medical Image Self-supervised Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-visual-similarity-learning-in-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel visual similarity learning paradigm, Geometric Visual Similarity Learning, which embeds the prior of topological invariance into the measurement of the inter-image similarity for consistent representation of semantic regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-visual-similarity-learning-in-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Hamiltonian Descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-hamiltonian-descent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Quantum Hamiltonian Descent (QHD), which is derived from the path integral of dynamical systems referring to the continuous-time limit of classical gradient descent algorithms, as a truly quantum counterpart of classical gradient methods where the contribution from classically-prohibited trajectories can significantly boost QHD's performance for non-convex optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-hamiltonian-descent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESceme: Vision-and-Language Navigation with Episodic Scene Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/esceme-vision-and-language-navigation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The episodic scene memory allows the agent to envision a bigger picture of the next prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/esceme-vision-and-language-navigation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning-Based Software Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-based-software-testing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Reasoning-Based Software Testing (RBST), a new way of thinking at the testing problem as a causal reasoning task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-based-software-testing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Source Soft Pseudo-Label Learning with Domain Similarity-based Weighting for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-soft-pseudo-label-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes a method of domain adaptive training for semantic segmentation using multiple source datasets that are not necessarily relevant to the target dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-soft-pseudo-label-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoLab: Geometry-based Tractography Parcellation of Superficial White Matter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geolab-geometry-based-tractography</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Superficial white matter (SWM) has been less studied than long-range connections despite being of interest to clinical research, andfew tractography parcellation methods have been adapted to SWM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geolab-geometry-based-tractography</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
