<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 21:07:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SGDA: Towards 3D Universal Pulmonary Nodule Detection via Slice Grouped Domain Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgda-towards-3d-universal-pulmonary-nodule</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a slice grouped domain attention (SGDA) module to enhance the generalization capability of the pulmonary nodule detection networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgda-towards-3d-universal-pulmonary-nodule</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zeroth-Order Optimization Meets Human Feedback: Provable Learning via Ranking Oracles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zeroth-order-optimization-meets-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on a novel optimization problem in which the objective function is a black-box and can only be evaluated through a ranking oracle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zeroth-order-optimization-meets-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face: Fast, Accurate and Context-Aware Audio Annotation and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-fast-accurate-and-context-aware-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a context-aware framework for feature selection and classification procedures to realize a fast and accurate audio event annotation and classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-fast-accurate-and-context-aware-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Hamiltonian Systems with Mono-Implicit Runge-Kutta Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-hamiltonian-systems-with-mono</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerical integrators could be used to form interpolation conditions when training neural networks to approximate the vector field of an ordinary differential equation (ODE) from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-hamiltonian-systems-with-mono</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning multi-scale local conditional probability models of images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-multi-scale-local-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We instantiate this model using convolutional neural networks (CNNs) with local receptive fields, which enforce both the stationarity and Markov properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-multi-scale-local-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-guided Prototype Modulating for Few-shot Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-guided-prototype-modulating-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning from large-scale contrastive language-image pre-training like CLIP has shown remarkable success in a wide range of downstream tasks recently, but it is still under-explored on the challenging few-shot action recognition (FSAR) task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-guided-prototype-modulating-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Parametric Outlier Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-parametric-outlier-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Importantly, our proposed synthesis approach does not make any distributional assumption on the ID embeddings, thereby offering strong flexibility and generality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-parametric-outlier-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guiding Energy-based Models via Contrastive Latent Variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-energy-based-models-via-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enable the joint training of EBM and CRL, we also design a new class of latent-variable EBMs for learning the joint density of data and the contrastive latent variable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-energy-based-models-via-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiCLIP: Contrastive Language-Image Pretraining with Hierarchy-aware Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiclip-contrastive-language-image-pretraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of large-scale contrastive vision-language pretraining (CLIP) has benefited both visual recognition and multimodal content understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiclip-contrastive-language-image-pretraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structured Kernel Estimation for Photon-Limited Deconvolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-kernel-estimation-for-photon</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By modeling the blur kernel using a low-dimensional representation with the key points on the motion trajectory, we significantly reduce the search space and improve the regularity of the kernel estimation problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-kernel-estimation-for-photon</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Feedback Attention Framework via Boundary-Aware Auxiliary and Progressive Semantic Optimization for Salient Object Detection in Optical Remote Sensing Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-feedback-attention-framework-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, existing methods do not pay sufficient attention to the boundary of the object, and the completeness of the final saliency map still needs improvement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-feedback-attention-framework-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centroid Distance Distillation for Effective Rehearsal in Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centroid-distance-distillation-for-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rehearsal, retraining on a stored small data subset of old tasks, has been proven effective in solving catastrophic forgetting in continual learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centroid-distance-distillation-for-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeCap: Decoding CLIP Latents for Zero-Shot Captioning via Text-Only Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decap-decoding-clip-latents-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This decoder is both data-efficient and computation-efficient: 1) it only requires the text data for training, easing the burden on the collection of paired data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decap-decoding-clip-latents-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoveFormer: a Transformer-based model for step-selection animal movement modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moveformer-a-transformer-based-model-for-step</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose MoveFormer, a new step-based model of movement capable of learning directly from full animal trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moveformer-a-transformer-based-model-for-step</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Algebraic Perspective on Lipschitz Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-algebraic-perspective-on-lipschitz</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Important research efforts have focused on the design and training of neural networks with a controlled Lipschitz constant.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-algebraic-perspective-on-lipschitz</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Referring Multi-Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/referring-multi-object-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new and general referring understanding task, termed referring multi-object tracking (RMOT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/referring-multi-object-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRIN: Rotation-Invariant Point Cloud Analysis and Rotation Estimation via Centrifugal Reference Frame</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crin-rotation-invariant-point-cloud-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CRIN directly takes the coordinates of points as input and transforms local points into rotation-invariant representations via centrifugal reference frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crin-rotation-invariant-point-cloud-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUREL+: Moving from Walks to Sets for Scalable Subgraph-based Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surel-moving-from-walks-to-sets-for-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel framework SUREL+ that upgrades SUREL by using node sets instead of walks to represent subgraphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surel-moving-from-walks-to-sets-for-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Confidence Calibration for Failure Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-confidence-calibration-for-failure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate this problem and reveal that popular confidence calibration methods often lead to worse confidence separation between correct and incorrect samples, making it more difficult to decide whether to trust a prediction or not.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-confidence-calibration-for-failure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SC-Block: Supervised Contrastive Blocking within Entity Resolution Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sc-block-supervised-contrastive-blocking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reduce these runtimes, entity resolution pipelines are constructed of two parts: a blocker that applies a computationally cheap method to select candidate record pairs, and a matcher that afterwards identifies matching pairs from this set using more expensive methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sc-block-supervised-contrastive-blocking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KBNet: Kernel Basis Network for Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kbnet-kernel-basis-network-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a kernel basis attention (KBA) module, which introduces learnable kernel bases to model representative image patterns for spatial information aggregation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kbnet-kernel-basis-network-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symbolic Synthesis of Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-synthesis-of-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks adapt very well to distributed and continuous representations, but struggle to learn and generalize from small amounts of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-synthesis-of-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Deep Models for Practical Gait Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-deep-models-for-practical-gait</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a unified perspective to explore how to construct deep models for state-of-the-art outdoor gait recognition, including the classical CNN-based and emerging Transformer-based architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-deep-models-for-practical-gait</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Differentiable Causal Discovery via Adaptive Sample Reweighting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-differentiable-causal-discovery-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite great success in low-dimensional linear systems, it has been observed that these approaches overly exploit easier-to-fit samples, thus inevitably learning spurious edges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-differentiable-causal-discovery-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Activity Prediction Models in Drug Discovery with the Ability to Understand Human Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-activity-prediction-models-in-drug</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Activity and property prediction models are the central workhorses in drug discovery and materials sciences, but currently they have to be trained or fine-tuned for new tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-activity-prediction-models-in-drug</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Searching for Effective Neural Network Architectures for Heart Murmur Detection from Phonocardiogram</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/searching-for-effective-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aim: The George B. Moody PhysioNet Challenge 2022 raised problems of heart murmur detection and related abnormal cardiac function identification from phonocardiograms (PCGs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/searching-for-effective-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Zero-Shot Functional Compositionality of Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-zero-shot-functional-compositionality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Pre-trained Language Models (PLM) have become the most desirable starting point in the field of NLP, as they have become remarkably good at solving many individual tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-zero-shot-functional-compositionality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A System for Generalized 3D Multi-Object Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-system-for-generalized-3d-multi-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GenMOS takes as input point cloud observations of the local region, object detection results, and localization of the robot's view pose, and outputs a 6D viewpoint to move to through online planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-system-for-generalized-3d-multi-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faithfulness-Aware Decoding Strategies for Abstractive Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithfulness-aware-decoding-strategies-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a systematic study of the effect of generation techniques such as beam search and nucleus sampling on faithfulness in abstractive summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithfulness-aware-decoding-strategies-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenICL: An Open-Source Framework for In-context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openicl-an-open-source-framework-for-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the implementation of ICL is sophisticated due to the diverse retrieval and inference methods involved, as well as the varying pre-processing requirements for different models, datasets, and tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openicl-an-open-source-framework-for-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster Learning of Temporal Action Proposal via Sparse Multilevel Boundary Generator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-learning-of-temporal-action-proposal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal action localization in videos presents significant challenges in the field of computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-learning-of-temporal-action-proposal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighborhood Contrastive Transformer for Change Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neighborhood-contrastive-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Change captioning is to describe the semantic change between a pair of similar images in natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neighborhood-contrastive-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Place Recognition: A Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-place-recognition-a-tutorial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It unifies the terminology of VPR and complements prior research in two important directions: 1) It provides a systematic introduction for newcomers to the field, covering topics such as the formulation of the VPR problem, a general-purpose algorithmic pipeline, an evaluation methodology for VPR approaches, and the major challenges for VPR and how they may be addressed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-place-recognition-a-tutorial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Grained Self-Interpretable Symbolic-Neural Model For Single/Multi-Labeled Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-grained-self-interpretable-symbolic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the structured language model learns to predict constituency trees in a self-supervised manner, only raw texts and sentence-level labels are required as training data, which makes it essentially a general constituent-level self-interpretable classification model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-grained-self-interpretable-symbolic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MABNet: Master Assistant Buddy Network with Hybrid Learning for Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mabnet-master-assistant-buddy-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel Master Assistant Buddy Network (MABNet) for image retrieval which incorporates both learning mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mabnet-master-assistant-buddy-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Prompting with Missing Modalities for Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-prompting-with-missing-modalities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we tackle two challenges in multimodal learning for visual recognition: 1) when missing-modality occurs either during training or testing in real-world situations; and 2) when the computation resources are not available to finetune on heavy transformer models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-prompting-with-missing-modalities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MotionVideoGAN: A Novel Video Generator Based on the Motion Space Learned from Image Pairs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motionvideogan-a-novel-video-generator-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present MotionVideoGAN, a novel video generator synthesizing videos based on the motion space learned by pre-trained image pair generators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motionvideogan-a-novel-video-generator-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynthASpoof: Developing Face Presentation Attack Detection Based on Privacy-friendly Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthaspoof-developing-face-presentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To target these legal and technical challenges, this work presents the first synthetic-based face PAD dataset, named SynthASpoof, as a large-scale PAD development dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthaspoof-developing-face-presentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the universal distribution of the coverage in split conformal prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-universal-distribution-of-the-coverage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two additional universal properties are established in the split conformal prediction framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-universal-distribution-of-the-coverage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event-based Camera Simulation using Monte Carlo Path Tracing with Adaptive Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-based-camera-simulation-using-monte</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes an algorithm for obtaining an event-based video from a noisy input video given by physics-based Monte Carlo path tracing of synthetic 3D scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-based-camera-simulation-using-monte</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Approximate Cross-Validation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-approximate-cross-validation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-validation (CV) is one of the most popular tools for assessing and selecting predictive models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-approximate-cross-validation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Active Learning with Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-active-learning-with-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Active learning is perhaps most naturally posed as an online learning problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-active-learning-with-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust affine feature matching via quadratic assignment on Grassmannians</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-affine-feature-matching-via-quadratic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The algorithm is based on the Grassmannian of $k$--dimensional planes in $\mathbb{R}^n$ and minimizing the Frobenius norm between the two elements of the Grassmannian.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-affine-feature-matching-via-quadratic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximizing Spatio-Temporal Entropy of Deep 3D CNNs for Efficient Video Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximizing-spatio-temporal-entropy-of-deep-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose to automatically design efficient 3D CNN architectures via a novel training-free neural architecture search approach tailored for 3D CNNs considering the model complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximizing-spatio-temporal-entropy-of-deep-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Graph Learning for Acoustic Event Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-learning-for-acoustic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Heterogeneous graphs provide a compact, efficient, and scalable way to model data involving multiple disparate modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-learning-for-acoustic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Formal Metareasoning Model of Concurrent Planning and Execution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-formal-metareasoning-model-of-concurrent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When timing is tight, there may be insufficient time to complete the search for a plan before it is time to act.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-formal-metareasoning-model-of-concurrent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-Resolution Neural Operator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolution-neural-operator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Super-resolution Neural Operator (SRNO), a deep operator learning framework that can resolve high-resolution (HR) images at arbitrary scales from the low-resolution (LR) counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolution-neural-operator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swim: A General-Purpose, High-Performing, and Efficient Activation Function for Locomotion Control Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swim-a-general-purpose-high-performing-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then conclude that Swim is a state-of-the-art activation function for continuous control locomotion tasks and recommend using it with TD3 as a working framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swim-a-general-purpose-high-performing-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expectation consistency for calibration of neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expectation-consistency-for-calibration-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their incredible performance, it is well reported that deep neural networks tend to be overoptimistic about their prediction confidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expectation-consistency-for-calibration-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VTQA: Visual Text Question Answering via Entity Alignment and Cross-Media Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vtqa-visual-text-question-answering-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ideal form of Visual Question Answering requires understanding, grounding and reasoning in the joint space of vision and language and serves as a proxy for the AI task of scene understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vtqa-visual-text-question-answering-via</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
