<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 21:08:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>BoK: Introducing Bag-of-Keywords Loss for Interpretable Dialogue Response Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bok-introducing-bag-of-keywords-loss-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One such auxiliary loss function is Bag-of-Words (BoW) loss, defined as the cross-entropy loss for predicting all the words/tokens of the next utterance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bok-introducing-bag-of-keywords-loss-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Preventing Overreliance on Task-Oriented Conversational AI Through Accountability Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-preventing-overreliance-on-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our empirical findings demonstrate that this approach not only enables reliable estimation of AI agent errors but also guides the LLM decoder in generating more accurate actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-preventing-overreliance-on-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Actions for Enhanced Embodied Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-actions-for-enhanced-embodied</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training on diverse, internet-scale data is a key factor in the success of recent large foundation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-actions-for-enhanced-embodied</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple but Effective Closed-form Solution for Extreme Multi-label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-but-effective-closed-form-solution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many current high-performance XML models are composed of a lot of hyperparameters, which complicates the tuning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-but-effective-closed-form-solution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PandaSkill -- Player Performance and Skill Rating in Esports: Application to League of Legends</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pandaskill-player-performance-and-skill</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To take the esports scene to the next level, we introduce PandaSkill, a framework for assessing player performance and skill rating.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pandaskill-player-performance-and-skill</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-shot Structure-Informed Machinery Part Segmentation with Foundation Models and Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-structure-informed-machinery-part</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method's fast training times and effective generalization to real data make it a valuable tool for autonomous systems interacting with machinery and infrastructure, and illustrate the potential of combined and orchestrated foundation models for few-shot segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-structure-informed-machinery-part</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Graph MLP Mixer for Spatio-Temporal Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-graph-mlp-mixer-for-spatio-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatiotemporal forecasting is critical in applications such as traffic prediction, climate modeling, and environmental monitoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-graph-mlp-mixer-for-spatio-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>landmarker: a Toolkit for Anatomical Landmark Localization in 2D/3D Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/landmarker-a-toolkit-for-anatomical-landmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although many general-purpose tools exist for landmark localization in classical computer vision tasks, such as pose estimation, they lack the specialized features and modularity necessary for anatomical landmark localization applications in the medical domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/landmarker-a-toolkit-for-anatomical-landmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study on a Fast Solver for Combined Field Integral Equations of 3D Conducting Bodies Based on Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/study-on-a-fast-solver-for-combined-field</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a graph neural networks (GNNs)-based fast solver (GraphSolver) for solving combined field integral equations (CFIEs) of 3D conducting bodies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/study-on-a-fast-solver-for-combined-field</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrete Prior-based Temporal-coherent Content Prediction for Blind Face Video Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-prior-based-temporal-coherent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further enhance the temporal coherence of the predicted content, a motion statistics modulation module is designed to adjust the content, based on discrete motion priors in terms of cross-frame mean and variance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-prior-based-temporal-coherent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-Dyna: Expressive Dynamic Human Image Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-dyna-expressive-dynamic-human-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the core of our approach is the Dynamics-Adapter, a lightweight module that effectively integrates reference appearance context into the spatial attentions of the diffusion backbone while preserving the capacity of motion modules in synthesizing fluid and intricate dynamic details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-dyna-expressive-dynamic-human-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LWGANet: A Lightweight Group Attention Backbone for Remote Sensing Visual Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lwganet-a-lightweight-group-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article introduces LWGANet, a specialized lightweight backbone network tailored for RS visual tasks, incorporating a novel lightweight group attention (LWGA) module designed to address these specific challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lwganet-a-lightweight-group-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FiLo++: Zero-/Few-Shot Anomaly Detection by Fused Fine-Grained Descriptions and Deformable Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filo-zero-few-shot-anomaly-detection-by-fused</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, their handcrafted generic descriptions fail to capture the diverse range of anomalies that may emerge in different objects, and simple patch-level image-text matching often struggles to localize anomalous regions of varying shapes and sizes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filo-zero-few-shot-anomaly-detection-by-fused</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaceXBench: Evaluating Multimodal LLMs on Face Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facexbench-evaluating-multimodal-llms-on-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we introduce FaceXBench, a comprehensive benchmark designed to evaluate MLLMs on complex face understanding tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facexbench-evaluating-multimodal-llms-on-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSHNet: A Novel Information Asymmetric Image Translation Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cshnet-a-novel-information-asymmetric-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose the CNN-Swin Hybrid Network (CSHNet), which combines two key modules: Swin Embedded CNN (SEC) and CNN Embedded Swin (CES), forming the SEC-CES-Bottleneck (SCB).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cshnet-a-novel-information-asymmetric-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topology-Driven Attribute Recovery for Attribute Missing Graph Learning in Social Internet of Things</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-driven-attribute-recovery-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text Attribute Graphs (TAGs) capture both topological structures and semantic attributes, enhancing the analysis of complex interactions within the SIoT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-driven-attribute-recovery-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Inference for Sequential Feature Selection after Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-inference-for-sequential-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In high-dimensional regression, feature selection methods, such as sequential feature selection (SeqFS), are commonly used to identify relevant features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-inference-for-sequential-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surface-SOS: Self-Supervised Object Segmentation via Neural Surface Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surface-sos-self-supervised-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To make better use of the above information, we propose Surface representation based Self-supervised Object Segmentation (Surface-SOS), a new framework to segment objects for each view by 3D surface representation from multi-view images of a scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surface-sos-self-supervised-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSTS: A Multimodal Safety Test Suite for Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msts-a-multimodal-safety-test-suite-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we explore the automation of VLM safety assessments, finding even the best safety classifiers to be lacking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msts-a-multimodal-safety-test-suite-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ComplexFuncBench: Exploring Multi-Step and Constrained Function Calling under Long-Context Scenario</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complexfuncbench-exploring-multi-step-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, evaluating the function calling abilities of LLMs in real-world scenarios remains under-explored due to the complexity of data collection and evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complexfuncbench-exploring-multi-step-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Spatiotemporal Augmentation for Improving Dynamic Graph Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-spatiotemporal-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic graph augmentation is used to improve the performance of dynamic GNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-spatiotemporal-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning for Early Alzheimer Disease Detection with MRI Scans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-early-alzheimer-disease</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's Disease is a neurodegenerative condition characterized by dementia and impairment in neurological function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-early-alzheimer-disease</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modal Attention Networks for Enhanced Segmentation and Depth Estimation of Subsurface Defects in Pulse Thermography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-attention-networks-for-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, this work proposes PT-Fusion, a multi-modal attention-based fusion network that fuses both PCA and TSR modalities for defect segmentation and depth estimation of subsurface defects in PT setups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-attention-networks-for-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation and Efficiency Comparison of Evolutionary Algorithms for Service Placement Optimization in Fog Architectures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-and-efficiency-comparison-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study compares three evolutionary algorithms for the problem of fog service placement: weighted sum genetic algorithm (WSGA), non-dominated sorting genetic algorithm II (NSGA-II), and multiobjective evolutionary algorithm based on decomposition (MOEA/D).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-and-efficiency-comparison-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aneumo: A Large-Scale Comprehensive Synthetic Dataset of Aneurysm Hemodynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aneumo-a-large-scale-comprehensive-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although clinical practice is usually based on individual factors and morphological features of the aneurysm, its pathophysiology and hemodynamic mechanisms remain controversial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aneumo-a-large-scale-comprehensive-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRCHITECT v2: Learning the Hardware Accelerator Design Space through Unified Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/airchitect-v2-learning-the-hardware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results evaluated on 10^5 real DNN workloads demonstrate that, on average, AIrchitect v2 outperforms existing techniques by 15% in identifying optimal design points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/airchitect-v2-learning-the-hardware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiPruner: Balanced Structure Removal in Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multipruner-balanced-structure-removal-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, state-of-the-art approaches for pruning large pre-trained models (LPMs) have demonstrated that the training-free removal of non-critical residual blocks in Transformers is viable for reducing model size, achieving results that outperform previous training-free pruning approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multipruner-balanced-structure-removal-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMPLest-X: Ultimate Scaling for Expressive Human Pose and Shape Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smplest-x-ultimate-scaling-for-expressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To exclude the influence of algorithmic design, we base our experiments on two minimalist architectures: SMPLer-X, which consists of an intermediate step for hand and face localization, and SMPLest-X, an even simpler version that reduces the network to its bare essentials and highlights significant advances in the capture of articulated hands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smplest-x-ultimate-scaling-for-expressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Aerial Detection Baseline of Multimodal Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-aerial-detection-baseline-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a simple baseline for applying MLMs to aerial detection for the first time, named LMMRotate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-aerial-detection-baseline-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NS-Gym: Open-Source Simulation Environments and Benchmarks for Non-Stationary Markov Decision Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ns-gym-open-source-simulation-environments</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This toolkit is the first effort to develop a set of standardized interfaces and benchmark problems to enable consistent and reproducible evaluation of algorithms under non-stationary conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ns-gym-open-source-simulation-environments</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MatrixNet: Learning over symmetry groups using learned group representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matrixnet-learning-over-symmetry-groups-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Group theory has been used in machine learning to provide a theoretically grounded approach for incorporating known symmetry transformations in tasks from robotics to protein modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matrixnet-learning-over-symmetry-groups-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Learning Informative Trajectory Embeddings for Imitation, Classification and Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-learning-informative-trajectory-embeddings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In real-world sequential decision making tasks like autonomous driving, robotics, and healthcare, learning from observed state-action trajectories is critical for tasks like imitation, classification, and clustering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-learning-informative-trajectory-embeddings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class Incremental Fault Diagnosis under Limited Fault Data via Supervised Contrastive Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-incremental-fault-diagnosis-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Class-incremental fault diagnosis requires a model to adapt to new fault classes while retaining previous knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-incremental-fault-diagnosis-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Reward Hacking: Causal Rewards for Large Language Model Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-reward-hacking-causal-rewards-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a drop-in enhancement to the existing RLHF workflow, our causal reward modeling provides a practical way to improve the trustworthiness and fairness of LLM finetuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-reward-hacking-causal-rewards-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CyberMentor: AI Powered Learning Tool Platform to Address Diverse Student Needs in Cybersecurity Education</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cybermentor-ai-powered-learning-tool-platform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many non-traditional students in cybersecurity programs often lack access to advice from peers, family members and professors, which can hinder their educational experiences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cybermentor-ai-powered-learning-tool-platform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Study of In-Context-Learning-Based Text-to-SQL Errors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-study-of-in-context-learning-based-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that text-to-SQL errors are widespread and summarize 29 error types of 7 categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-study-of-in-context-learning-based-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dataset Generation Toolbox for Dynamic Security Assessment: On the Role of the Security Boundary</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dataset-generation-toolbox-for-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While importance and generic sampling techniques often focus on operating points near the system's security boundary, systematic methods for sampling in this region remain scarce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dataset-generation-toolbox-for-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorporating Quantum Advantage in Quantum Circuit Generation through Genetic Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-quantum-advantage-in-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing efficient quantum circuits that leverage quantum advantage compared to classical computing has become increasingly critical.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-quantum-advantage-in-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVIA: A Street View Image Anonymization Framework for Self-Driving Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svia-a-street-view-image-anonymization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, there has been an increasing interest in image anonymization, particularly focusing on the de-identification of faces and individuals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svia-a-street-view-image-anonymization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Normal-NeRF: Ambiguity-Robust Normal Estimation for Highly Reflective Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normal-nerf-ambiguity-robust-normal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combined with a reflection-aware appearance model, our proposed method achieves robust reconstruction and high-fidelity rendering of scenes featuring both highly specular reflections and intricate geometric structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normal-nerf-ambiguity-robust-normal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling up self-supervised learning for improved surgical foundation models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-self-supervised-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trained on the largest reported surgical dataset to date, comprising over 4. 7 million video frames, SurgeNetXL achieves consistent top-tier performance across six datasets spanning four surgical procedures and three tasks, including semantic segmentation, phase recognition, and critical view of safety (CVS) classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-self-supervised-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overshoot: Taking advantage of future gradients in momentum-based stochastic optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overshoot-taking-advantage-of-future</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rather than calculating gradient at the current model weights, Overshoot calculates the gradient at model weights shifted in the direction of the current momentum.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overshoot-taking-advantage-of-future</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FineMedLM-o1: Enhancing the Medical Reasoning Ability of LLM from Supervised Fine-Tuning to Test-Time Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finemedlm-o1-enhancing-the-medical-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We proposed FineMedLM-o1, which leverages high-quality synthetic medical data and long-form reasoning data for Supervised Fine-Tuning (SFT) and Direct Preference Optimization (DPO), enabling advanced dialogue and deep reasoning capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finemedlm-o1-enhancing-the-medical-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metrics for Inter-Dataset Similarity with Example Applications in Synthetic Data and Feature Selection Evaluation -- Extended Version</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metrics-for-inter-dataset-similarity-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose two novel metrics for measuring inter-dataset similarity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metrics-for-inter-dataset-similarity-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Hallucinations in Large Vision-Language Models via DPO: On-Policy Data Hold the Key</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-hallucinations-in-large-vision-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hallucination remains a major challenge for Large Vision-Language Models (LVLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-hallucinations-in-large-vision-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFOM-Stereo: Depth Foundation Model Based Stereo Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defom-stereo-depth-foundation-model-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, to facilitate robust stereo matching with monocular depth cues, we incorporate a robust monocular relative depth model into the recurrent stereo-matching framework, building a new framework for depth foundation model-based stereo-matching, DEFOM-Stereo.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defom-stereo-depth-foundation-model-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merging Models on the Fly Without Retraining: A Sequential Approach to Scalable Continual Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merging-models-on-the-fly-without-retraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a training-free projection-based continual merging method that processes models sequentially through orthogonal projections of weight matrices and adaptive scaling mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merging-models-on-the-fly-without-retraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weight for Robustness: A Comprehensive Approach towards Optimal Fault-Tolerant Asynchronous ML</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weight-for-robustness-a-comprehensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the challenges of Byzantine-robust training in asynchronous distributed machine learning systems, aiming to enhance efficiency amid massive parallelization and heterogeneous computing resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weight-for-robustness-a-comprehensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust and Realistic Human Pose Estimation via WiFi Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-and-realistic-human-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust WiFi-based human pose estimation is a challenging task that bridges discrete and subtle WiFi signals to human skeletons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-and-realistic-human-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChartInsighter: An Approach for Mitigating Hallucination in Time-series Chart Summary Generation with A Benchmark Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chartinsighter-an-approach-for-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce ChartInsighter, which automatically generates chart summaries of time-series data, effectively reducing hallucinations in chart summary generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chartinsighter-an-approach-for-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
