<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 09:11:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Optical Aberration Correction in Postprocessing using Imaging Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optical-aberration-correction-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the spatial variation in optical aberrations, which cannot be avoided during the lens design process, recent commercial cameras have shifted some of these correction tasks from optical design to postprocessing systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optical-aberration-correction-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUTS+: High-dimensional Causal Discovery from Irregular Time-series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuts-high-dimensional-causal-discovery-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal discovery in time-series is a fundamental problem in the machine learning community, enabling causal reasoning and decision-making in complex scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuts-high-dimensional-causal-discovery-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CosmoPower-JAX: high-dimensional Bayesian inference with differentiable cosmological emulators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosmopower-jax-high-dimensional-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then consider a combination of three Stage IV surveys, each performing a joint cosmic shear and galaxy clustering (3x2pt) analysis, for a total of 157 model parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosmopower-jax-high-dimensional-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks and 3-Dimensional Topology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-and-3-dimensional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we consider reinforcement learning by a GNN to find a sequence of Neumann moves that relates the pair of graphs if the answer is positive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-and-3-dimensional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say What You Mean! Large Language Models Speak Too Positively about Negative Commonsense Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/say-what-you-mean-large-language-models-speak</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have been widely studied for their ability to store and utilize positive knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/say-what-you-mean-large-language-models-speak</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Similarity of Neural Network Models: A Survey of Functional and Representational Measures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/similarity-of-neural-network-models-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Measuring similarity of neural networks has become an issue of great importance and research interest to understand and utilize differences of neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/similarity-of-neural-network-models-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Classification of Feedback Loops and Their Relation to Biases in Automated Decision-Making Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-classification-of-feedback-loops-and-their</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By qualitative analysis, and through a simulation example of recommender systems, we show which specific types of ML biases are affected by each type of feedback loop.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-classification-of-feedback-loops-and-their</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Dense Retrieval Training with Web Anchors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-dense-retrieval-training-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on their commonalities, we train an unsupervised dense retriever, Anchor-DR, with a contrastive learning task that matches the anchor text and the linked document.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-dense-retrieval-training-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Effective Visual Representations for Partial-Label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-effective-visual-representations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under partial-label learning (PLL) where, for each training instance, only a set of ambiguous candidate labels containing the unknown true label is accessible, contrastive learning has recently boosted the performance of PLL on vision tasks, attributed to representations learned by contrasting the same/different classes of entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-effective-visual-representations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XTab: Cross-table Pretraining for Tabular Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xtab-cross-table-pretraining-for-tabular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of self-supervised learning in computer vision and natural language processing has motivated pretraining methods on tabular data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xtab-cross-table-pretraining-for-tabular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHS-Net: Learning Signed Hyper Surfaces for Oriented Normal Estimation of Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shs-net-learning-signed-hyper-surfaces-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce signed hyper surfaces (SHS), which are parameterized by multi-layer perceptron (MLP) layers, to learn to estimate oriented normals from point clouds in an end-to-end manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shs-net-learning-signed-hyper-surfaces-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Level-line Guided Edge Drawing for Robust Line Segment Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/level-line-guided-edge-drawing-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Line segment detection plays a cornerstone role in computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/level-line-guided-edge-drawing-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoChat: Chat-Centric Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videochat-chat-centric-video-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we initiate an exploration into video understanding by introducing VideoChat, an end-to-end chat-centric video understanding system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videochat-chat-centric-video-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPMLBench: Holistic Evaluation of Differentially Private Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpmlbench-holistic-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also explore some improvements that can maintain model utility and defend against MIAs more effectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpmlbench-holistic-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think Twice before Driving: Towards Scalable Decoders for End-to-End Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/think-twice-before-driving-towards-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[End-to-end autonomous driving has made impressive progress in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/think-twice-before-driving-towards-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing the Performance of Transformer-based Spiking Neural Networks by Improved Downsampling with Precise Gradient Backpropagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-the-performance-of-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep spiking neural networks (SNNs) have drawn much attention in recent years because of their low power consumption, biological rationality and event-driven property.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-the-performance-of-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-modal Garden Dataset and Hybrid 3D Dense Reconstruction Framework Based on Panoramic Stereo Images for a Trimming Robot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-modal-garden-dataset-and-hybrid-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, the refined disparity maps are converted into full-view point clouds or single-view point clouds for the pose fusion module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-modal-garden-dataset-and-hybrid-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>K-UniMorph: Korean Universal Morphology and its Feature Schema</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-unimorph-korean-universal-morphology-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This dataset adopts morphological feature schema from Sylak-Glassman et al. (2015) and Sylak-Glassman (2016) for the Korean language as we extract inflected verb forms from the Sejong morphologically analyzed corpus that is one of the largest annotated corpora for Korean.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-unimorph-korean-universal-morphology-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoCA: Memory-Centric, Adaptive Execution for Multi-Tenant Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moca-memory-centric-adaptive-execution-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driven by the wide adoption of deep neural networks (DNNs) across different application domains, multi-tenancy execution, where multiple DNNs are deployed simultaneously on the same hardware, has been proposed to satisfy the latency requirements of different applications while improving the overall system utilization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moca-memory-centric-adaptive-execution-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust multi-agent coordination via evolutionary generation of auxiliary adversarial attackers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-multi-agent-coordination-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, to avoid the ego-system overfitting to a specific attacker, we maintain a set of attackers, which is optimized to guarantee the attackers high attacking quality and behavior diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-multi-agent-coordination-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfoMetIC: An Informative Metric for Reference-free Image Caption Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infometic-an-informative-metric-for-reference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing metrics only provide a single score to measure caption qualities, which are less explainable and informative.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infometic-an-informative-metric-for-reference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-training Model Quantization Using GANs for Synthetic Data Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-training-model-quantization-using-gans</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we investigate the use of synthetic data as a substitute for the calibration with real data for the quantization method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-training-model-quantization-using-gans</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly-supervised ROI extraction method based on contrastive learning for remote sensing images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-roi-extraction-method-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ROI extraction is an active but challenging task in remote sensing because of the complicated landform, the complex boundaries and the requirement of annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-roi-extraction-method-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DaGAN++: Depth-Aware Generative Adversarial Network for Talking Head Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dagan-depth-aware-generative-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, firstly, we present a novel self-supervised method for learning dense 3D facial geometry (ie, depth) from face videos, without requiring camera parameters and 3D geometry annotations in training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dagan-depth-aware-generative-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V2X-Seq: A Large-Scale Sequential Dataset for Vehicle-Infrastructure Cooperative Perception and Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2x-seq-a-large-scale-sequential-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Utilizing infrastructure and vehicle-side information to track and forecast the behaviors of surrounding traffic participants can significantly improve decision-making and safety in autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2x-seq-a-large-scale-sequential-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Multimodal Misinformation Detection with Logic Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-multimodal-misinformation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal misinformation on online social platforms is becoming a critical concern due to increasing credibility and easier dissemination brought by multimedia content, compared to traditional text-only information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-multimodal-misinformation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auditing Cross-Cultural Consistency of Human-Annotated Labels for Recommendation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auditing-cross-cultural-consistency-of-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommendation systems increasingly depend on massive human-labeled datasets; however, the human annotators hired to generate these labels increasingly come from homogeneous backgrounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auditing-cross-cultural-consistency-of-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Intent Enhanced Graph Neural Network for Session-based New Item Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-intent-enhanced-graph-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We design a dual-intent network to learn user intent from an attention mechanism and the distribution of historical data respectively, which can simulate users' decision-making process in interacting with a new item.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-intent-enhanced-graph-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAI at SemEval-2023 Task 2: A Universal System for Named Entity Recognition with External Entity Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pai-at-semeval-2023-task-2-a-universal-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The MultiCoNER II task aims to detect complex, ambiguous, and fine-grained named entities in low-context situations and noisy scenarios like the presence of spelling mistakes and typos for multiple languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pai-at-semeval-2023-task-2-a-universal-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Better Graph Representation Learning with Parameterized Decomposition &amp; Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-graph-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Proposing an effective and flexible matrix to represent a graph is a fundamental challenge that has been explored from multiple perspectives, e. g., filtering in Graph Fourier Transforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-graph-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Prompt with Depth Partitioned Cross-Modal Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-prompt-with-depth-partitioned-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, soft prompt learning methods have been proposed to fine-tune large-scale vision-language pre-trained models for various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-prompt-with-depth-partitioned-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vārta: A Large-Scale Headline-Generation Dataset for Indic Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/varta-a-large-scale-headline-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present V\=arta, a large-scale multilingual dataset for headline generation in Indic languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/varta-a-large-scale-headline-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributional Multi-Objective Decision Making</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-multi-objective-decision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For effective decision support in scenarios with conflicting objectives, sets of potentially optimal solutions can be presented to the decision maker.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-multi-objective-decision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMAClite: A Lightweight Environment for Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smaclite-a-lightweight-environment-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Starcraft Multi-Agent Challenge (SMAC) has been widely used in MARL research, but is built on top of a heavy, closed-source computer game, StarCraft II.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smaclite-a-lightweight-environment-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LSAS: Lightweight Sub-attention Strategy for Alleviating Attention Bias Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lsas-lightweight-sub-attention-strategy-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In computer vision, the performance of deep neural networks (DNNs) is highly related to the feature extraction ability, i. e., the ability to recognize and focus on key pixel regions in an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lsas-lightweight-sub-attention-strategy-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilevel Sentence Embeddings for Personality Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilevel-sentence-embeddings-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representing text into a multidimensional space can be done with sentence embedding models such as Sentence-BERT (SBERT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilevel-sentence-embeddings-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiking Neural Networks in the Alexiewicz Topology: A New Perspective on Analysis and Error Bounds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-neural-networks-in-the-alexiewicz</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A central question is the adequate structure for a space of spike trains and its implication for the design of error measurements of SNNs including time delay, threshold deviations, and the design of the reinitialization mode of the leaky-integrate-and-fire (LIF) neuron model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-neural-networks-in-the-alexiewicz</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Teacher Knowledge Distillation For Text Image Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-teacher-knowledge-distillation-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text image machine translation (TIMT) has been widely used in various real-world applications, which translates source language texts in images into another target language sentence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-teacher-knowledge-distillation-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing the Cost of Cycle-Time Tuning for Real-World Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-the-cost-of-cycle-time-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate the widely-used baseline hyper-parameter values of two policy gradient algorithms -- PPO and SAC -- across different cycle times.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-the-cost-of-cycle-time-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMIL: Context-Aware Multiple Instance Learning for Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camil-context-aware-multiple-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly supervised approaches often use image subsections or tiles as input, with the overall classification of the WSI based on attention scores assigned to each tile.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camil-context-aware-multiple-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplicial Hopfield networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplicial-hopfield-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hopfield networks are artificial neural networks which store memory patterns on the states of their neurons by choosing recurrent connection weights and update rules such that the energy landscape of the network forms attractors around the memories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplicial-hopfield-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DietCNN: Multiplication-free Inference for Quantized CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dietcnn-multiplication-free-inference-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rising demand for networked embedded systems with machine intelligence has been a catalyst for sustained attempts by the research community to implement Convolutional Neural Networks (CNN) based inferencing on embedded resource-limited devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dietcnn-multiplication-free-inference-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dialogue Planning via Brownian Bridge Stochastic Process for Goal-directed Proactive Dialogue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialogue-planning-via-brownian-bridge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key to achieving this task lies in planning dialogue paths that smoothly and coherently direct conversations towards the target.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialogue-planning-via-brownian-bridge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architectural Vision for Quantum Computing in the Edge-Cloud Continuum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/architectural-vision-for-quantum-computing-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discuss the necessity, challenges, and solution approaches for extending existing work on classical edge computing to integrate QPUs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/architectural-vision-for-quantum-computing-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedNoRo: Towards Noise-Robust Federated Learning by Addressing Class Imbalance and Label Noise Heterogeneity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fednoro-towards-noise-robust-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated noisy label learning (FNLL) is emerging as a promising tool for privacy-preserving multi-source decentralized learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fednoro-towards-noise-robust-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Energy System Scheduling Using A Constraint-Aware Reinforcement Learning Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-energy-system-scheduling-using-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this, in this paper, a DRL algorithm (namely MIP-DQN) is proposed, capable of \textit{strictly} enforcing all operational constraints in the action space, ensuring the feasibility of the defined schedule in real-time operation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-energy-system-scheduling-using-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rotation Synchronization via Deep Matrix Factorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rotation-synchronization-via-deep-matrix</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we address the rotation synchronization problem, where the objective is to recover absolute rotations starting from pairwise ones, where the unknowns and the measures are represented as nodes and edges of a graph, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rotation-synchronization-via-deep-matrix</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLA: Contextualized Commonsense Causal Reasoning from the Causal Inference Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cola-contextualized-commonsense-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a new task to detect commonsense causation between two events in an event sequence (i. e., context), called contextualized commonsense causal reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cola-contextualized-commonsense-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TPS++: Attention-Enhanced Thin-Plate Spline for Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tps-attention-enhanced-thin-plate-spline-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce TPS++, an attention-enhanced TPS transformation that incorporates the attention mechanism to text rectification for the first time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tps-attention-enhanced-thin-plate-spline-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimal Learning Machine for Multi-Label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimal-learning-machine-for-multi-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Distance-based supervised method, the minimal learning machine, constructs a predictive model from data by learning a mapping between input and output distance matrices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimal-learning-machine-for-multi-label</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
