<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 09:15:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>How to Teach: Learning Data-Free Knowledge Distillation from Curriculum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-teach-learning-data-free-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore how to teach students the model from a curriculum learning (CL) perspective and propose a new approach, namely "CuDFKD", i. e., "Data-Free Knowledge Distillation with Curriculum".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-teach-learning-data-free-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affective Manifolds: Modeling Machine's Mind to Like, Dislike, Enjoy, Suffer, Worry, Fear, and Feel Like A Human</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affective-manifolds-modeling-machine-s-mind</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More affective manifolds in the machine's mind can make it more realistic and effective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affective-manifolds-modeling-machine-s-mind</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainability of Deep Learning models for Urban Space perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainability-of-deep-learning-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the blackbox nature of deep learning models hampers urban planners to understand what landscape objects contribute to a particularly high quality or low quality urban space perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainability-of-deep-learning-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying the COVID-19 vaccine discourse on Twitter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-the-covid-19-vaccine-discourse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While pro-vax tweets (37 million) far outnumbered anti-vax tweets (10 million), a majority of tweets from both stances (63% anti-vax and 53% pro-vax tweets) came from dual-stance users who posted both pro- and anti-vax tweets during the observation period.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-the-covid-19-vaccine-discourse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedEgo: Privacy-preserving Personalized Federated Graph Learning with Ego-graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedego-privacy-preserving-personalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As special information carriers containing both structure and feature information, graphs are widely used in graph mining, e. g., Graph Neural Networks (GNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedego-privacy-preserving-personalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Reliable Simulation-Based Inference with Balanced Neural Ratio Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-reliable-simulation-based-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Balanced Neural Ratio Estimation (BNRE), a variation of the NRE algorithm designed to produce posterior approximations that tend to be more conservative, hence improving their reliability, while sharing the same Bayes optimal solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-reliable-simulation-based-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reweighting Strategy based on Synthetic Data Identification for Sentence Similarity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reweighting-strategy-based-on-synthetic-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To analyze this, we first train a classifier that identifies machine-written sentences, and observe that the linguistic features of the sentences identified as written by a machine are significantly different from those of human-written sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reweighting-strategy-based-on-synthetic-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Vision-Language Pretraining with Visual Concepts and Hierarchical Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-vision-language-pretraining-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision and Language Pretraining has become the prevalent approach for tackling multimodal downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-vision-language-pretraining-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boundary-Aware Network for Kidney Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-aware-network-for-kidney-parsing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although numerous deep learning models have achieved remarkable success in many medical image segmentation tasks, accurate segmentation of kidney structures on computed tomography angiography (CTA) images remains challenging, due to the variable sizes of kidney tumors and the ambiguous boundaries between kidney structures and their surroundings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-aware-network-for-kidney-parsing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label Propagation for 3D Carotid Vessel Wall Segmentation and Atherosclerosis Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-propagation-for-3d-carotid-vessel-wall</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Carotid vessel wall segmentation is a crucial yet challenging task in the computer-aided diagnosis of atherosclerosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-propagation-for-3d-carotid-vessel-wall</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Explaining Demographic Bias through the Eyes of Face Recognition Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explaining-demographic-bias-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the trustfulness of such ML decision systems, it is crucial to be aware of the inherent biases in these solutions and to make them more transparent to the public and developers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explaining-demographic-bias-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIRCLe: Color Invariant Representation Learning for Unbiased Classification of Skin Lesions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circle-color-invariant-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While deep learning based approaches have demonstrated expert-level performance in dermatological diagnosis tasks, they have also been shown to exhibit biases toward certain demographic attributes, particularly skin types (e. g., light versus dark), a fairness concern that must be addressed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circle-color-invariant-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Practical Calibration Method for RGB Micro-Grid Polarimetric Cameras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-calibration-method-for-rgb-micro</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new method to overcome the need for complex optical systems to efficiently calibrate these cameras.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-calibration-method-for-rgb-micro</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The PWLR Graph Representation: A Persistent Weisfeiler-Lehman scheme with Random Walks for Graph Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-pwlr-graph-representation-a-persistent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the Persistent Weisfeiler-Lehman Random walk scheme (abbreviated as PWLR) for graph representations, a novel mathematical framework which produces a collection of explainable low-dimensional representations of graphs with discrete and continuous node features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-pwlr-graph-representation-a-persistent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing high-dimensional loss landscapes with Hessian directions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualizing-high-dimensional-loss-landscapes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that saddle points in the original space are rarely correctly identified as such in lower-dimensional representations if random projections are used.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualizing-high-dimensional-loss-landscapes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podcast Summary Assessment: A Resource for Evaluating Summary Assessment Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/podcast-summary-assessment-a-resource-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The podcast summary assessment data is available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/podcast-summary-assessment-a-resource-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Heterogeneous Interaction Strengths by Trajectory Prediction with Graph Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-heterogeneous-interaction-strengths</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model employs a novel pairwise attention (PA) mechanism to refine the trajectory representations and a graph transformer to extract heterogeneous interaction weights for each pair of agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-heterogeneous-interaction-strengths</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delving into the Continuous Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delving-into-the-continuous-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing domain adaptation methods assume that domain discrepancies are caused by a few discrete attributes and variations, e. g., art, real, painting, quickdraw, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delving-into-the-continuous-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-domain Cross-architecture Black-box Attacks on Fine-tuned Models with Transferred Evolutionary Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-cross-architecture-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To successfully attack fine-tuned models under both settings, we propose to first train an adversarial generator against the source model, which adopts an encoder-decoder architecture and maps a clean input to an adversarial example.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-cross-architecture-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Neural Network Language Modeling for Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-neural-network-language-modeling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art neural network language models (NNLMs) represented by long short term memory recurrent neural networks (LSTM-RNNs) and Transformers are becoming highly complex.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-neural-network-language-modeling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANDO: Multi-Level Heterogeneous Graph Embeddings for Fine-Grained Detection of Smart Contract Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mando-multi-level-heterogeneous-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, it develops a multi-metapath heterogeneous graph attention network to learn multi-level embeddings of different types of nodes and their metapaths in the heterogeneous contract graphs, which can capture the code semantics of smart contracts more accurately and facilitate both fine-grained line-level and coarse-grained contract-level vulnerability detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mando-multi-level-heterogeneous-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study on the Usage of Automated Machine Learning Tools</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-the-usage-of-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning (ML) practitioners use AutoML tools to automate and optimize the process of feature engineering, model training, and hyperparameter optimization and so on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-the-usage-of-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grounded Affordance from Exocentric View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounded-affordance-from-exocentric-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the diversity of interactive affordance, the uniqueness of different individuals leads to diverse interactions, which makes it difficult to establish an explicit link between object parts and affordance labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounded-affordance-from-exocentric-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAB-Net: LAB Color-Space Oriented Lightweight Network for Shadow Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lab-net-lab-color-space-oriented-lightweight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, the LSA modules are further developed to fully use the prior information in non-shadow regions to cleanse the shadow regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lab-net-lab-color-space-oriented-lightweight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDIA: A Benchmark for Multilingual Dialogue Generation in 46 Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdia-a-benchmark-for-multilingual-dialogue</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present mDIA, the first large-scale multilingual benchmark for dialogue generation across low- to high-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdia-a-benchmark-for-multilingual-dialogue</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor-identified Spatiotemporal Action Detection -- Detecting Who Is Doing What in Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actor-identified-spatiotemporal-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By using MOT, the spatiotemporal boundary of each actor is obtained and assigned to a unique actor identity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actor-identified-spatiotemporal-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOX-PAI: An Improved YOLOX Version by PAI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolox-pai-an-improved-yolox-version-by-pai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop an all-in-one computer vision toolbox named EasyCV to facilitate the use of various SOTA computer vision methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolox-pai-an-improved-yolox-version-by-pai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geometrical Homogeneous Clustering for Image Data Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometrical-homogeneous-clustering-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The intuition behind the first approach, RHCKON, is that the boundary points contribute significantly towards the representation of clusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometrical-homogeneous-clustering-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AesUST: Towards Aesthetic-Enhanced Universal Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aesust-towards-aesthetic-enhanced-universal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our approach introduces an aesthetic discriminator to learn the universal human-delightful aesthetic features from a large corpus of artist-created paintings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aesust-towards-aesthetic-enhanced-universal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Outputs Is All You Need For Deblur</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-outputs-is-all-you-need-for-deblur</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose to make the network learn the distribution of feasible solutions, and design based on this consideration a novel multi-head output architecture and corresponding loss function for distribution learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-outputs-is-all-you-need-for-deblur</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Specific NER via Retrieving Correlated Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-specific-ner-via-retrieving-correlated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Successful Machine Learning based Named Entity Recognition models could fail on texts from some special domains, for instance, Chinese addresses and e-commerce titles, where requires adequate background knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-specific-ner-via-retrieving-correlated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network-Level Adversaries in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-level-adversaries-in-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is a popular strategy for training models on distributed, sensitive data, while preserving data privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-level-adversaries-in-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Electricity Market Economy via Closed-Loop Predict-and-Optimize</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-electricity-market-economy-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The electricity market clearing is usually implemented via an open-loop predict-then-optimize (O-PO) process: it first predicts the available power of renewable energy sources (RES) and the system reserve requirements; then, given the predictions, the markets are cleared via optimization models, i. e., unit commitment (UC) and economic dispatch (ED), to pursue the optimal electricity market economy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-electricity-market-economy-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Context-Aware Active Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-context-aware-active-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Active Domain Adaptation (ADA) queries the label of selected target samples to help adapting a model from a related source domain to a target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-context-aware-active-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMD: Self-supervised 3D Action Representation Learning with Cross-modal Mutual Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmd-self-supervised-3d-action-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we formulate the cross-modal interaction as a bidirectional knowledge distillation problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmd-self-supervised-3d-action-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laplacian Pyramid-like Autoencoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplacian-pyramid-like-autoencoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LPAE decomposes an image into the approximation image and the detail image in the encoder part and then tries to reconstruct the original image in the decoder part using the two components.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplacian-pyramid-like-autoencoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partially Relevant Video Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partially-relevant-video-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill the gap, we propose in this paper a novel T2VR subtask termed Partially Relevant Video Retrieval (PRVR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partially-relevant-video-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Adaptation with Adversarial Training on Penultimate Activations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptation-with-adversarial-training-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that this strategy is more efficient and better correlated with the objective of boosting prediction confidence than adversarial training on input images or intermediate features, as used in previous works.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptation-with-adversarial-training-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Bandits for Linear Structural Equation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-bandits-for-linear-structural-equation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two linear mechanisms, one soft intervention and one observational, are assumed for each node, giving rise to $2^N$ possible interventions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-bandits-for-linear-structural-equation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arbitrary Shape Text Detection via Segmentation with Probability Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbitrary-shape-text-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To be concrete, we adopt a Sigmoid Alpha Function (SAF) to transfer the distances between boundaries and their inside pixels to a probability map.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbitrary-shape-text-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Automated Imbalanced Learning with Deep Hierarchical Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-automated-imbalanced-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, we investigate developing a learning-based over-sampling algorithm to optimize the classification performance, which is a challenging task because of the huge and hierarchical decision space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-automated-imbalanced-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ammunition Component Classification Using Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ammunition-component-classification-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The trained models are tested against unseen data in order to evaluate the performance of the applied method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ammunition-component-classification-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Framework for Inherently Interpretable Optimization Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-inherently-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One major barrier is that the optimization software can be perceived as a black box, which may produce solutions of high quality, but can create completely different solutions when circumstances change leading to low acceptance of optimized solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-inherently-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Lingual Cross-Modal Retrieval with Noise-Robust Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-cross-modal-retrieval-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a noise-robust cross-lingual cross-modal retrieval method for low-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-cross-modal-retrieval-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVD-GCN: A Simplified Graph Convolution Paradigm for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svd-gcn-a-simplified-graph-convolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the tremendous success of Graph Convolutional Networks (GCNs), they have been widely applied to recommender systems and have shown promising performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svd-gcn-a-simplified-graph-convolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Synthetic Data to Learn Video Stabilization Under Adverse Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-synthetic-data-to-learn-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a synthetic-aware adverse weather robust algorithm for video stabilization that does not require real data and can be trained only on synthetic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-synthetic-data-to-learn-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESC-Rules: Explainable, Semantically Constrained Rule Sets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/esc-rules-explainable-semantically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe a novel approach to explainable prediction of a continuous variable based on learning fuzzy weighted rules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/esc-rules-explainable-semantically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User-Controllable Latent Transformer for StyleGAN Image Layout Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-controllable-latent-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our framework, the user annotates a StyleGAN image with locations they want to move or not and specifies a movement direction by mouse dragging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-controllable-latent-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Path Towards Clinical Adaptation of Accelerated MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-path-towards-clinical-adaptation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accelerated MRI reconstructs images of clinical anatomies from sparsely sampled signal data to reduce patient scan times.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-path-towards-clinical-adaptation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Randomization of Affine Diffusion Processes with Application to Pricing of Options on VIX and S&amp;P 500</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-randomization-of-affine-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Any non-affine model must pass the strict requirement of quick calibration -- which is often challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-randomization-of-affine-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
