<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 21:06:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Characteristics and prevalence of fake social media profiles with AI-generated faces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characteristics-and-prevalence-of-fake-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applying this method to a random sample of active Twitter users, we estimate a lower bound for the prevalence of profiles using GAN-generated faces between 0. 021% and 0. 044% -- around 10K daily active accounts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characteristics-and-prevalence-of-fake-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detection and Classification of Diabetic Retinopathy using Deep Learning Algorithms for Segmentation to Facilitate Referral Recommendation for Test and Treatment Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-and-classification-of-diabetic-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research paper addresses the critical challenge of diabetic retinopathy (DR), a severe complication of diabetes leading to potential blindness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-and-classification-of-diabetic-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised hard Negative Augmentation for contrastive learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-hard-negative-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Unsupervised hard Negative Augmentation (UNA), a method that generates synthetic negative instances based on the term frequency-inverse document frequency (TF-IDF) retrieval model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-hard-negative-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Stage Contrastive Regression for Action Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stage-contrastive-regression-for-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, there has been growing interest in the video-based action quality assessment (AQA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stage-contrastive-regression-for-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED-NeRF: Achieve High 3D Consistency and Temporal Coherence for Face Video Editing on Dynamic NeRF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fed-nerf-achieve-high-3d-consistency-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, achieving simultaneously multi-view consistency and temporal coherence while editing video sequences remains a formidable challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fed-nerf-achieve-high-3d-consistency-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dagma-DCE: Interpretable, Non-Parametric Differentiable Causal Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dagma-dce-interpretable-non-parametric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Dagma-DCE, an interpretable and model-agnostic scheme for differentiable causal discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dagma-dce-interpretable-non-parametric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's Get It Started: Fostering the Discoverability of New Releases on Deezer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-s-get-it-started-fostering-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents our recent initiatives to foster the discoverability of new releases on the music streaming service Deezer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-s-get-it-started-fostering-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verifying Relational Explanations: A Probabilistic Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifying-relational-explanations-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Explanations on relational data are hard to verify since the explanation structures are more complex (e. g. graphs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifying-relational-explanations-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrisisViT: A Robust Vision Transformer for Crisis Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crisisvit-a-robust-vision-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We leverage the new Incidents1M crisis image dataset to develop a range of new transformer-based image classification models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crisisvit-a-robust-vision-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading Between the Frames: Multi-Modal Depression Detection in Videos from Non-Verbal Cues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reading-between-the-frames-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Depression, a prominent contributor to global disability, affects a substantial portion of the population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reading-between-the-frames-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locally Adaptive Neural 3D Morphable Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locally-adaptive-neural-3d-morphable-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Locally Adaptive Morphable Model (LAMM), a highly flexible Auto-Encoder (AE) framework for learning to generate and manipulate 3D meshes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locally-adaptive-neural-3d-morphable-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLLM-Protector: Ensuring MLLM's Safety without Hurting Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mllm-protector-ensuring-mllm-s-safety-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The deployment of multimodal large language models (MLLMs) has brought forth a unique vulnerability: susceptibility to malicious attacks through visual inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mllm-protector-ensuring-mllm-s-safety-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AG-ReID.v2: Bridging Aerial and Ground Views for Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ag-reid-v2-bridging-aerial-and-ground-views</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce AG-ReID. v2, a dataset specifically designed for person Re-ID in mixed aerial and ground scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ag-reid-v2-bridging-aerial-and-ground-views</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Credence: Augmenting Datacenter Switch Buffer Sharing with ML Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/credence-augmenting-datacenter-switch-buffer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This suggests that augmenting drop-tail algorithms with predictions about the future arrivals has the potential to significantly improve performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/credence-augmenting-datacenter-switch-buffer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedNS: A Fast Sketching Newton-Type Algorithm for Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedns-a-fast-sketching-newton-type-algorithm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide convergence analysis based on statistical learning for the federated Newton sketch approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedns-a-fast-sketching-newton-type-algorithm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German Text Embedding Clustering Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/german-text-embedding-clustering-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces a benchmark assessing the performance of clustering German text embeddings in different domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/german-text-embedding-clustering-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHGCN: Dynamic Hop Graph Convolution Network for Self-supervised Point Cloud Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dhgcn-dynamic-hop-graph-convolution-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works attempt to extend Graph Convolution Networks (GCNs) to point clouds for classification and segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dhgcn-dynamic-hop-graph-convolution-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Non-Stationary Textures using Self-Rectification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-non-stationary-textures-using-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the challenge of example-based non-stationary texture synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-non-stationary-textures-using-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identification of 4FGL uncertain sources at Higher Resolutions with Inverse Discrete Wavelet Transform</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identification-of-4fgl-uncertain-sources-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the forthcoming era of big astronomical data, it is a burden to find out target sources from ground-based and space-based telescopes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identification-of-4fgl-uncertain-sources-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Image Demoireing from Unpaired Real Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-image-demoireing-from-unpaired-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method, referred to as Unpaired Demoireing (UnDeM), synthesizes pseudo moire images from unpaired datasets, generating pairs with clean images for training demoireing models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-image-demoireing-from-unpaired-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeFoMed: Parameter Efficient Fine-tuning on Multimodal Large Language Models for Medical Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pefomed-parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal large language models (MLLMs) represent an evolutionary expansion in the capabilities of traditional large language models, enabling them to tackle challenges that surpass the scope of purely text-based applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pefomed-parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffbody: Diffusion-based Pose and Shape Editing of Human Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffbody-diffusion-based-pose-and-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because this initial textured body model has artifacts due to occlusion and the inaccurate body shape, the rendered image undergoes a diffusion-based refinement, in which strong noise destroys body structure and identity whereas insufficient noise does not help.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffbody-diffusion-based-pose-and-shape</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing targeted transferability via feature space fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-targeted-transferability-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial examples (AEs) have been extensively studied due to their potential for privacy protection and inspiring robust neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-targeted-transferability-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Vocabulary SAM: Segment and Recognize Twenty-thousand Classes Interactively</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-sam-segment-and-recognize</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The CLIP and Segment Anything Model (SAM) are remarkable vision foundation models (VFMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-sam-segment-and-recognize</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling and Masking: A New Paradigm of Data Sampling for Image and Video Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-and-masking-a-new-paradigm-of-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, instead of stacking up models, a more elegant data sampling method (named as SAMA, scaling and masking) is explored, which compacts both the local and global content in a regular input size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-and-masking-a-new-paradigm-of-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mining Fine-Grained Image-Text Alignment for Zero-Shot Captioning via Text-Only Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-fine-grained-image-text-alignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we observe that the CLIP's visual feature of image subregions can achieve closer proximity to the paired caption due to the inherent information loss in text descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-fine-grained-image-text-alignment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task Oriented Dialogue as a Catalyst for Self-Supervised Automatic Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-oriented-dialogue-as-a-catalyst-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that our CLC family of approaches can improve the performance of ASR models on OD3, a new public large-scale semi-synthetic meta-dataset of audio task-oriented dialogues, by up to 19. 2%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-oriented-dialogue-as-a-catalyst-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>t-DGR: A Trajectory-Based Deep Generative Replay Method for Continual Learning in Decision Making</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-dgr-a-trajectory-based-deep-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep generative replay has emerged as a promising approach for continual learning in decision-making tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-dgr-a-trajectory-based-deep-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Human Parsing Modality for Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explore-human-parsing-modality-for-action-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal-based action recognition methods have achieved high success using pose and RGB modality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explore-human-parsing-modality-for-action-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cool-Chic: Perceptually Tuned Low Complexity Overfitted Image Coder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cool-chic-perceptually-tuned-low-complexity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper summarises the design of the Cool-Chic candidate for the Challenge on Learned Image Compression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cool-chic-perceptually-tuned-low-complexity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spikformer V2: Join the High Accuracy Club on ImageNet with an SNN Ticket</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spikformer-v2-join-the-high-accuracy-club-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this is the first time that the SNN achieves 80+% accuracy on ImageNet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spikformer-v2-join-the-high-accuracy-club-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distillation-based fabric anomaly detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-based-fabric-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the extensive variability in colors, textures, and defect types, fabric defect detection poses a complex and challenging problem in the field of patterned textures inspection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-based-fabric-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Prompt with Text Only Supervision for Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-prompt-with-text-only-supervision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While effective, most of these works require labeled data which is not practical, and often struggle to generalize towards new datasets due to over-fitting on the source data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-prompt-with-text-only-supervision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks for Tabular Data Learning: A Survey with Taxonomy and Directions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-for-tabular-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this survey, we dive into Tabular Data Learning (TDL) using Graph Neural Networks (GNNs), a domain where deep learning-based approaches have increasingly shown superior performance in both classification and regression tasks compared to traditional methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-for-tabular-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy-regularized Offline Multi-objective Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-regularized-offline-multi-objective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to utilize only offline trajectory data to train a policy for multi-objective RL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-regularized-offline-multi-objective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClassWise-SAM-Adapter: Parameter Efficient Fine-tuning Adapts Segment Anything to SAR Domain for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classwise-sam-adapter-parameter-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to conventional state-of-the-art semantic segmentation algorithms by extensive experiments, CWSAM showcases enhanced performance with fewer computing resources, highlighting the potential of leveraging foundational models like SAM for specific downstream tasks in the SAR domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classwise-sam-adapter-parameter-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Diffusion-Based Rigid and Non-Rigid Editing with Text and Image Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-diffusion-based-rigid-and-non-rigid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing text-to-image editing methods tend to excel either in rigid or non-rigid editing but encounter challenges when combining both, resulting in misaligned outputs with the provided text prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-diffusion-based-rigid-and-non-rigid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCR-Consistency: Divide-Conquer-Reasoning for Consistency Evaluation and Improvement of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcr-consistency-divide-conquer-reasoning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating the quality and variability of text generated by Large Language Models (LLMs) poses a significant, yet unresolved research challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcr-consistency-divide-conquer-reasoning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Control of Connected and Automated Vehicles Using Trust-Aware Robust Event-Triggered Control Barrier Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secure-control-of-connected-and-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the security of a network of Connected and Automated Vehicles (CAVs) cooperating to safely navigate through a conflict area (e. g., traffic intersections, merging roadways, roundabouts).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secure-control-of-connected-and-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siamese Residual Neural Network for Musical Shape Evaluation in Piano Performance Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siamese-residual-neural-network-for-musical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding and identifying musical shape plays an important role in music education and performance assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siamese-residual-neural-network-for-musical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot-Assisted Deep Venous Thrombosis Ultrasound Examination using Virtual Fixture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robot-assisted-deep-venous-thrombosis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To ensure the biometric measurements obtained in different examinations are comparable, the 6D scanning path is determined in a coarse-to-fine manner using both an external RGBD camera and US images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robot-assisted-deep-venous-thrombosis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reassessing the Exon-Foldon correspondence using Frustration Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reassessing-the-exon-foldon-correspondence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Protein folding and evolution are intimately linked phenomena.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reassessing-the-exon-foldon-correspondence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linguistic Profiling of Deepfakes: An Open Database for Next-Generation Deepfake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linguistic-profiling-of-deepfakes-an-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The two distinguished features enable DFLIP-3K to develop a benchmark that promotes progress in linguistic profiling of deepfakes, which includes three sub-tasks namely deepfake detection, model identification, and prompt prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linguistic-profiling-of-deepfakes-an-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUESS:GradUally Enriching SyntheSis for Text-Driven Human Motion Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guess-gradually-enriching-synthesis-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The whole text-driven human motion synthesis problem is then divided into multiple abstraction levels and solved with a multi-stage generation framework with a cascaded latent diffusion model: an initial generator first generates the coarsest human motion guess from a given text description; then, a series of successive generators gradually enrich the motion details based on the textual description and the previous synthesized results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guess-gradually-enriching-synthesis-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating synthetic data for neural operators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-synthetic-data-for-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new approach to generating synthetic functional training data that does not require solving a PDE numerically.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-synthetic-data-for-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinyLlama: An Open-Source Small Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyllama-an-open-source-small-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present TinyLlama, a compact 1. 1B language model pretrained on around 1 trillion tokens for approximately 3 epochs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyllama-an-open-source-small-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaVA-$φ$: Efficient Multi-Modal Assistant with Small Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-ph-efficient-multi-modal-assistant-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce LLaVA-$\phi$ (LLaVA-Phi), an efficient multi-modal assistant that harnesses the power of the recently advanced small language model, Phi-2, to facilitate multi-modal dialogues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-ph-efficient-multi-modal-assistant-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffusionEdge: Diffusion Probabilistic Model for Crisp Edge Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusionedge-diffusion-probabilistic-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the recent success of the diffusion probabilistic model (DPM), we found it is especially suitable for accurate and crisp edge detection since the denoising process is directly applied to the original image size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusionedge-diffusion-probabilistic-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BA-SAM: Scalable Bias-Mode Attention Mask for Segment Anything Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ba-sam-scalable-bias-mode-attention-mask-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we reformulate this issue as a length extrapolation problem, where token sequence length varies while maintaining a consistent patch size for images of different sizes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ba-sam-scalable-bias-mode-attention-mask-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaMA Pro: Progressive LLaMA with Block Expansion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-pro-progressive-llama-with-block</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Humans generally acquire new skills without compromising the old; however, the opposite holds for Large Language Models (LLMs), e. g., from LLaMA to CodeLLaMA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-pro-progressive-llama-with-block</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
