<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 21:08:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Learning In-Distribution Representations for Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-in-distribution-representations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that FIRM surpasses other contrastive methods in standard benchmarks, significantly enhancing anomaly detection compared to both traditional and supervised contrastive learning objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-in-distribution-representations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparison Study: Glacier Calving Front Delineation in Synthetic Aperture Radar Images With Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-study-glacier-calving-front</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Calving front position variation of marine-terminating glaciers is an indicator of ice mass loss and a crucial parameter in numerical glacier models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-study-glacier-calving-front</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compression with Global Guidance: Towards Training-free High-Resolution MLLMs Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compression-with-global-guidance-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal large language models (MLLMs) have attracted considerable attention due to their exceptional performance in visual content understanding and reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compression-with-global-guidance-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search-o1: Agentic Search-Enhanced Large Reasoning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/search-o1-agentic-search-enhanced-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we introduce \textbf{Search-o1}, a framework that enhances LRMs with an agentic retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) mechanism and a Reason-in-Documents module for refining retrieved documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/search-o1-agentic-search-enhanced-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$DPF^*$: improved Depth Potential Function for scale-invariant sulcal depth estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpf-improved-depth-potential-function-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The shape of human brain is complex and highly variable, with interactions between brain size, cortical folding, and age well-documented in the literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpf-improved-depth-potential-function-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GAN is dead; long live the GAN! A Modern GAN Baseline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-gan-is-dead-long-live-the-gan-a-modern</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a widely-spread claim that GANs are difficult to train, and GAN architectures in the literature are littered with empirical tricks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-gan-is-dead-long-live-the-gan-a-modern</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWE-Fixer: Training Open-Source LLMs for Effective and Efficient GitHub Issue Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swe-fixer-training-open-source-llms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The retrieval module employs BM25 along with a lightweight LLM model to achieve coarse-to-fine file retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swe-fixer-training-open-source-llms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Continual Learning: A Systematic Literature Review of Approaches, Challenges, and Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-continual-learning-a-systematic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online Continual Learning (OCL) is a critical area in machine learning, focusing on enabling models to adapt to evolving data streams in real-time while addressing challenges such as catastrophic forgetting and the stability-plasticity trade-off.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-continual-learning-a-systematic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Decomposed Dual-domain Deep Learning for Sparse-View CT Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-decomposed-dual-domain-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, deep learning strategies employing image-domain networks have demonstrated remarkable performance in eliminating the streaking artifact caused by analytic reconstruction methods with sparse projection views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-decomposed-dual-domain-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Mastery: Enhancing Soft Constraint Following Ability of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/step-by-step-mastery-enhancing-soft</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is crucial for large language models (LLMs) to follow instructions that involve multiple constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/step-by-step-mastery-enhancing-soft</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V2C-CBM: Building Concept Bottlenecks with Vision-to-Concept Tokenizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2c-cbm-building-concept-bottlenecks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concept Bottleneck Models (CBMs) offer inherent interpretability by initially translating images into human-comprehensible concepts, followed by a linear combination of these concepts for classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2c-cbm-building-concept-bottlenecks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relative Pose Estimation through Affine Corrections of Monocular Depth Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relative-pose-estimation-through-affine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we develop three solvers for relative pose estimation that explicitly account for independent affine (scale and shift) ambiguities, covering both calibrated and uncalibrated conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relative-pose-estimation-through-affine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Load Forecasting for Households and Energy Communities: Are Deep Learning Models Worth the Effort?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/load-forecasting-for-households-and-energy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Key findings of this research include: (1) Simple persistence benchmarks outperform deep learning models for short-term load forecasting when the available training data is limited to six months or less; (2) Pretraining with publicly available synthetic load profiles improves the normalized Mean Absolute Error (nMAE) by an average of 1. 28%pt during the first nine months of training data; (3) Increased aggregation significantly enhances the performance of deep learning models relative to persistence benchmarks; (4) Improved load forecasting, with an nMAE reduction of 1. 1%pt, translates to an economic benefit of approximately 600EUR per year in an energy community comprising 50 households.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/load-forecasting-for-households-and-energy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Measuring Unnoticeability of Graph Adversarial Attacks: Observations, New Measure, and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-measuring-unnoticeability-of-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, to mitigate the bypass problem, HideNSeek learns to distinguish the original and (potential) attack edges using a learnable edge scorer (LEO), which scores each edge on its likelihood of being an attack.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-measuring-unnoticeability-of-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stream Aligner: Efficient Sentence-Level Alignment via Distribution Induction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stream-aligner-efficient-sentence-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of large language models (LLMs) has led to significant improvements in their capabilities, but also to increased concerns about their alignment with human values and intentions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stream-aligner-efficient-sentence-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Portable Solution for Simultaneous Human Movement and Mobile EEG Acquisition: Readiness Potentials for Basketball Free-throw Shooting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-portable-solution-for-simultaneous-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we investigated whether the RP differs between successful and unsuccessful free-throw attempts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-portable-solution-for-simultaneous-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Learning with Evolving Tasks and Performance Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-learning-with-evolving-tasks-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing techniques for learning tasks that are in a sequence are tailored to specific scenarios, lacking adaptability to others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-learning-with-evolving-tasks-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-aware Knowledge Tracing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-knowledge-tracing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous research commonly adopts deterministic representation to capture students' knowledge states, which neglects the uncertainty during student interactions and thus fails to model the true knowledge state in learning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-knowledge-tracing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Mesh Completion to AI Designed Crown</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-mesh-completion-to-ai-designed-crown</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The set of feature vectors is then fed into a transformer to predict a new set of feature vectors for the missing region (crown).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-mesh-completion-to-ai-designed-crown</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Needles in Emb(a)dding Haystacks: Legal Document Retrieval via Bagging and SVR Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-needles-in-emb-a-dding-haystacks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a retrieval approach leveraging Support Vector Regression (SVR) ensembles, bootstrap aggregation (bagging), and embedding spaces on the German Dataset for Legal Information Retrieval (GerDaLIR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-needles-in-emb-a-dding-haystacks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPDN: Image-enhanced Prompt Decoding Network for 3D Referring Expression Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ipdn-image-enhanced-prompt-decoding-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle intent ambiguity, we designed a Prompt-Aware Decoder (PAD) that guides the decoding process by deriving task-driven signals from the interaction between the expression and visual features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ipdn-image-enhanced-prompt-decoding-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving the Catastrophic Forgetting Problem in Generalized Category Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-the-catastrophic-forgetting-problem-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The LER optimizes the distribution of potential known class samples in unlabeled data, thus ensuring the preservation of knowledge related to known categories while learning novel classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-the-catastrophic-forgetting-problem-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Flexible and Scalable Framework for Video Moment Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-flexible-and-scalable-framework-for-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieved segments are then merged into coarse-grained moment proposals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-flexible-and-scalable-framework-for-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AD-L-JEPA: Self-Supervised Spatial World Models with Joint Embedding Predictive Architecture for Autonomous Driving with LiDAR Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ad-l-jepa-self-supervised-spatial-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present AD-L-JEPA (aka Autonomous Driving with LiDAR data via a Joint Embedding Predictive Architecture), a novel self-supervised pre-training framework for autonomous driving with LiDAR data that, as opposed to existing methods, is neither generative nor contrastive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ad-l-jepa-self-supervised-spatial-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Plagiarism Detection in Marathi with a Weighted Ensemble of TF-IDF and BERT Embeddings for Low-Resource Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-plagiarism-detection-in-marathi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Plagiarism involves using another person's work or concepts without proper attribution, presenting them as original creations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-plagiarism-detection-in-marathi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CellViT++: Energy-Efficient and Adaptive Cell Segmentation and Classification Using Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cellvit-energy-efficient-and-adaptive-cell</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Digital Pathology is a cornerstone in the diagnosis and treatment of diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cellvit-energy-efficient-and-adaptive-cell</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAQ: Joint Efficient Architecture Design and Low-Bit Quantization with Hardware-Software Co-Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jaq-joint-efficient-architecture-design-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The co-design of neural network architectures, quantization precisions, and hardware accelerators offers a promising approach to achieving an optimal balance between performance and efficiency, particularly for model deployment on resource-constrained edge devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jaq-joint-efficient-architecture-design-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D3RM: A Discrete Denoising Diffusion Refinement Model for Piano Transcription</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d3rm-a-discrete-denoising-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on discrete diffusion model's refinement capabilities and present a novel architecture for piano transcription.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d3rm-a-discrete-denoising-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpecTf: Transformers Enable Data-Driven Imaging Spectroscopy Cloud Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectf-transformers-enable-data-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Spectroscopic Transformer (SpecTf) addresses these challenges with a spectroscopy-specific deep learning architecture that performs cloud detection using only spectral information (no spatial or temporal data are required).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectf-transformers-enable-data-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Skeleton-based Action Recognition with Interactive Object Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-skeleton-based-action-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new action recognition framework introducing object nodes to supplement absent interactive object information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-skeleton-based-action-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Perspective on Privacy Protection in Federated Learning with Granular-Ball Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-perspective-on-privacy-protection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) facilitates collaborative model training while prioritizing privacy by avoiding direct data sharing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-perspective-on-privacy-protection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FairCode: Evaluating Social Bias of LLMs in Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faircode-evaluating-social-bias-of-llms-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce FairCode, a novel benchmark for evaluating bias in code generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faircode-evaluating-social-bias-of-llms-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SensorQA: A Question Answering Benchmark for Daily-Life Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensorqa-a-question-answering-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we introduce \Dataset, the first human-created question-answering (QA) dataset for long-term time-series sensor data for daily life monitoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensorqa-a-question-answering-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing Domain Shift via Imbalance-Aware Domain Adaptation in Embryo Development Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-domain-shift-via-imbalance-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning models in medical imaging face dual challenges: domain shift, where models perform poorly when deployed in settings different from their training environment, and class imbalance, where certain disease conditions are naturally underrepresented.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-domain-shift-via-imbalance-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battling the Non-stationarity in Time Series Forecasting via Test-time Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/battling-the-non-stationarity-in-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Neural Networks have spearheaded remarkable advancements in time series forecasting (TSF), one of the major tasks in time series modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/battling-the-non-stationarity-in-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Adaptive Ising Machines for Constrained Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-adaptive-ising-machines-for-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using a probabilistic-bit (p-bit) IM emulated in software, we benchmark our algorithm with multidimensional knapsack problems (MKP) and quadratic knapsack problems (QKP), the latter being an Ising problem with linear constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-adaptive-ising-machines-for-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM4SR: A Survey on Large Language Models for Scientific Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm4sr-a-survey-on-large-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the rapid advancement of Large Language Models (LLMs) has transformed the landscape of scientific research, offering unprecedented support across various stages of the research cycle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm4sr-a-survey-on-large-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining YOLO and Visual Rhythm for Vehicle Counting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-yolo-and-visual-rhythm-for-vehicle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video-based vehicle detection and counting play a critical role in managing transport infrastructure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-yolo-and-visual-rhythm-for-vehicle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Plug-and-Play Bregman ADMM Module for Inferring Event Branches in Temporal Point Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-plug-and-play-bregman-admm-module-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we formulate the inference of event branches as an optimization problem for the event transition matrix under sparse and low-rank constraints, which is embedded in existing TPP models or their learning paradigms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-plug-and-play-bregman-admm-module-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Examination of Unrolled Networks for Linear Inverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-examination-of-unrolled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unrolled networks have become prevalent in various computer vision and imaging tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-examination-of-unrolled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Low-Cost Video Editing with Lightweight Adaptors and Temporal-Aware Inversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-low-cost-video-editing-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in text-to-image (T2I) generation using diffusion models have enabled cost-effective video-editing applications by leveraging pre-trained models, eliminating the need for resource-intensive training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-low-cost-video-editing-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look on Gender Stereotypes in Movie Recommender Systems and Their Implications with Privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-on-gender-stereotypes-in-movie</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the second phase, four inference algorithms were applied to detect gender stereotypes by combining the findings from the first phase with users' feedback data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-on-gender-stereotypes-in-movie</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCIts -- Deep Convolutional Interpreter for time series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcits-deep-convolutional-interpreter-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an interpretable deep learning model for multivariate time series forecasting that prioritizes both predictive performance and interpretability - key requirements for understanding complex physical phenomena.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcits-deep-convolutional-interpreter-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolution of Spots and Stripes in Cellular Automata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolution-of-spots-and-stripes-in-cellular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of engineering cellular automata, we propose evolving cellular automata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolution-of-spots-and-stripes-in-cellular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoDFL: A Scalable and Automated Reputation-Aware Decentralized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autodfl-a-scalable-and-automated-reputation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reputation-aware BFL poses even more challenges, as blockchain validators are tasked with processing federated learning transactions along with the transactions that evaluate FL tasks and aggregate reputations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autodfl-a-scalable-and-automated-reputation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On weight and variance uncertainty in neural networks for regression tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-weight-and-variance-uncertainty-in-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Variance uncertainty enhances the generalization of the model {by} considering the posterior distribution over the variance parameter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-weight-and-variance-uncertainty-in-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfiGUIAgent: A Multimodal Generalist GUI Agent with Native Reasoning and Reflection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infiguiagent-a-multimodal-generalist-gui</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graphical User Interface (GUI) Agents, powered by multimodal large language models (MLLMs), have shown great potential for task automation on computing devices such as computers and mobile phones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infiguiagent-a-multimodal-generalist-gui</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Listened Speech Decoding from EEG via Parallel Phoneme Sequence Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-listened-speech-decoding-from-eeg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed approach allows users to obtain decoded listened speech from EEG signals in both modalities (speech waveforms and textual phoneme sequences) simultaneously, eliminating the need for a concatenated sequential pipeline for each modality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-listened-speech-decoding-from-eeg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOLBENCH: Benchmarking LLMs on Linguistic Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iolbench-benchmarking-llms-on-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the remarkable advancements and widespread applications of deep neural networks, their ability to perform reasoning tasks remains limited, particularly in domains requiring structured, abstract thought.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iolbench-benchmarking-llms-on-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical artificial intelligence toolbox (MAIT): an explainable machine learning framework for binary classification, survival modelling, and regression analyses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-artificial-intelligence-toolbox-mait</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While machine learning offers diverse techniques suitable for exploring various medical research questions, a cohesive synergistic framework can facilitate the integration and understanding of new approaches within unified model development and interpretation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-artificial-intelligence-toolbox-mait</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
