<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:26:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Short Distance Graph Neural Networks and Improved Curriculum Learning for Emotion Recognition in Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-short-distance-graph-neural-networks-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Emotion Recognition in Conversation (ERC) is a practical and challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-short-distance-graph-neural-networks-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Step is Enough: Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning based on One-Step Policy Optimization for Order Dispatch on Ride-Sharing Platforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-step-is-enough-multi-agent-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On-demand ride-sharing platforms face the fundamental challenge of dynamically bundling passengers with diverse origins and destinations and matching them with vehicles in real time, all under significant uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-step-is-enough-multi-agent-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Context for Multimodal Fallacy Classification in Political Debates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-context-for-multimodal-fallacy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present our submission to the MM-ArgFallacy2025 shared task, which aims to advance research in multimodal argument mining, focusing on logical fallacies in political debates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-context-for-multimodal-fallacy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real Time Captioning of Sign Language Gestures in Video Meetings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-captioning-of-sign-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent studies, it has been found that people with hearing disabilities prefer to sign over typing during these video calls.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-captioning-of-sign-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Multi-Agent Reasoning via Automated Workflow Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-multi-agent-reasoning-via-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Nexus Architect, an enhanced iteration of our multi-agent system framework, Nexus, equipped with a novel automated workflow synthesis mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-multi-agent-reasoning-via-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RaMen: Multi-Strategy Multi-Modal Learning for Bundle Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ramen-multi-strategy-multi-modal-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing studies on bundle construction have relied merely on user feedback via bipartite graphs or enhanced item representations using semantic information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ramen-multi-strategy-multi-modal-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OntView: What you See is What you Meant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontview-what-you-see-is-what-you-meant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present OntView, an ontology viewer that is designed to provide users with an intuitive visual representation of ontology concepts and their formal definitions through a user-friendly interface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontview-what-you-see-is-what-you-meant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Reproducibility Study of Product-side Fairness in Bundle Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reproducibility-study-of-product-side</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This emerging task introduces additional complexity: recommendations are generated at the bundle level, yet user satisfaction and product (or supplier) exposure depend on both the bundle and the individual items it contains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reproducibility-study-of-product-side</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APTx Neuron: A Unified Trainable Neuron Architecture Integrating Activation and Computation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aptx-neuron-a-unified-trainable-neuron</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the APTx Neuron, a novel, unified neural computation unit that integrates non-linear activation and linear transformation into a single trainable expression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aptx-neuron-a-unified-trainable-neuron</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tri-Learn Graph Fusion Network for Attributed Graph Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tri-learn-graph-fusion-network-for-attributed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, this study proposes a novel deep clustering framework that comprising GCN, Autoencoder (AE), and Graph Transformer, termed the Tri-Learn Graph Fusion Network (Tri-GFN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tri-learn-graph-fusion-network-for-attributed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-Structured Data Analysis of Component Failure in Autonomous Cargo Ships Based on Feature Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-structured-data-analysis-of-component</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the challenges posed by cascading reactions caused by component failures in autonomous cargo ships (ACS) and the uncertainties in emergency decision-making, this paper proposes a novel hybrid feature fusion framework for constructing a graph-structured dataset of failure modes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-structured-data-analysis-of-component</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Language Model a Hierarchical Classifier and Generator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-language-model-a-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language heads of the last layer are copied to different selected intermediate layers, and fine-tuned with different task inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-language-model-a-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergence of Functionally Differentiated Structures via Mutual Information Optimization in Recurrent Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-functionally-differentiated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analysis of network performance, correlation patterns, and weight matrices reveals that mutual information minimization yields high task performance alongside clear functional modularity and moderate structural modularity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-functionally-differentiated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Roots to Rewards: Dynamic Tree Reasoning with RL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-roots-to-rewards-dynamic-tree-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern language models address complex questions through chain-of-thought (CoT) reasoning (Wei et al., 2023) and retrieval augmentation (Lewis et al., 2021), yet struggle with error propagation and knowledge integration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-roots-to-rewards-dynamic-tree-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLEXITOKENS: Flexible Tokenization for Evolving Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexitokens-flexible-tokenization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models (LMs) are challenging to adapt to new data distributions by simple finetuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexitokens-flexible-tokenization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DVFL-Net: A Lightweight Distilled Video Focal Modulation Network for Spatio-Temporal Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dvfl-net-a-lightweight-distilled-video-focal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We employ forward Kullback-Leibler (KL) divergence alongside spatio-temporal focal modulation to effectively transfer both local and global context from the Video-FocalNet Base (teacher) to the proposed VFL-Net (student).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dvfl-net-a-lightweight-distilled-video-focal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices for Large-Scale, Pixel-Wise Crop Mapping and Transfer Learning Workflows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/best-practices-for-large-scale-pixel-wise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study presents the first comprehensive review of large-scale, pixel-wise crop mapping workflows, encompassing both conventional supervised methods and emerging transfer learning approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/best-practices-for-large-scale-pixel-wise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Object Hallucinations via Sentence-Level Early Intervention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-object-hallucinations-via-sentence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal large language models (MLLMs) have revolutionized cross-modal understanding but continue to struggle with hallucinations - fabricated content contradicting visual inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-object-hallucinations-via-sentence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifications are Absolutists: How Simplified Language Reduces Word Sense Awareness in LLM-Generated Definitions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifications-are-absolutists-how</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the scope of the definition changes for different target groups, like children or language learners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifications-are-absolutists-how</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAC: A Dynamic Attention-aware Approach for Task-Agnostic Prompt Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dac-a-dynamic-attention-aware-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Task-agnostic prompt compression leverages the redundancy in natural language to reduce computational overhead and enhance information density within prompts, especially in long-context scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dac-a-dynamic-attention-aware-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructFLIP: Exploring Unified Vision-Language Model for Face Anti-spoofing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructflip-exploring-unified-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate the effectiveness of InstructFLIP by outperforming SOTA models in accuracy and substantially reducing training redundancy across diverse domains in FAS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructflip-exploring-unified-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Choosing the Better Bandit Algorithm under Data Sharing: When Do A/B Experiments Work?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/choosing-the-better-bandit-algorithm-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, units under the treatment and control algorithms contribute to a shared pool of data that subsequently train both algorithms, resulting in interference between the two groups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/choosing-the-better-bandit-algorithm-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FourCastNet 3: A geometric approach to probabilistic machine-learning weather forecasting at scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fourcastnet-3-a-geometric-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FourCastNet 3 advances global weather modeling by implementing a scalable, geometric machine learning (ML) approach to probabilistic ensemble forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fourcastnet-3-a-geometric-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arctic Inference with Shift Parallelism: Fast and Efficient Open Source Inference System for Enterprise AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arctic-inference-with-shift-parallelism-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inference is now the dominant AI workload, yet existing systems force trade-offs between latency, throughput, and cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arctic-inference-with-shift-parallelism-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Calisthenics Skills Classification through Foreground Instance Selection and Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-calisthenics-skills-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional methods for calisthenics skill recognition are based on pose estimation methods to determine the position of skeletal data from images, which is later fed to a classification algorithm to infer the performed skill.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-calisthenics-skills-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpatialTrackerV2: 3D Point Tracking Made Easy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatialtrackerv2-3d-point-tracking-made-easy-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SpatialTrackerV2, a feed-forward 3D point tracking method for monocular videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatialtrackerv2-3d-point-tracking-made-easy-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developing Visual Augmented Q&amp;A System using Scalable Vision Embedding Retrieval &amp; Late Interaction Re-ranker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/developing-visual-augmented-q-a-system-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose multi-step custom implementation utilizing widely adopted hybrid search (metadata & embedding) and state of the art late interaction re-ranker to retrieve best matching pages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/developing-visual-augmented-q-a-system-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhysX: Physical-Grounded 3D Asset Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physx-physical-grounded-3d-asset-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D modeling is moving from virtual to physical.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physx-physical-grounded-3d-asset-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assay2Mol: large language model-based drug design using BioAssay context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assay2mol-large-language-model-based-drug</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientific databases aggregate vast amounts of quantitative data alongside descriptive text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assay2mol-large-language-model-based-drug</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Describe Anything Model for Visual Question Answering on Text-rich Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/describe-anything-model-for-visual-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress has been made in region-aware vision-language modeling, particularly with the emergence of the Describe Anything Model (DAM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/describe-anything-model-for-visual-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analytic estimation of parameters of stochastic volatility diffusion models with exponential-affine characteristic function for currency option pricing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analytic-estimation-of-parameters-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chapter four discusses calibration methods for stochastic volatility models, particularly the Heston model, and presents the new Implied Central Moments method to estimate parameters in the Heston and Sch\"obel-Zhu models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analytic-estimation-of-parameters-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Fuzzy Approach to Project Success: Measuring What Matters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fuzzy-approach-to-project-success-measuring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel approach to project success evaluation by integrating fuzzy logic into an existing construct.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fuzzy-approach-to-project-success-measuring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Task-Specific Reasoning: A Unified Conditional Generative Framework for Abstract Visual Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-task-specific-reasoning-a-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we illustrate that, under the proposed framework, training one conditional generative model can solve various AVR tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-task-specific-reasoning-a-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relative Entropy Pathwise Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relative-entropy-pathwise-policy-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on these insights, we propose Relative Entropy Pathwise Policy Optimization (REPPO), an efficient on-policy algorithm that combines the sample-efficiency of pathwise policy gradients with the simplicity and minimal memory footprint of standard on-policy learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relative-entropy-pathwise-policy-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Langevin Flows for Modeling Neural Latent Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/langevin-flows-for-modeling-neural-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural populations exhibit latent dynamical structures that drive time-evolving spiking activities, motivating the search for models that capture both intrinsic network dynamics and external unobserved influences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/langevin-flows-for-modeling-neural-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleviating Textual Reliance in Medical Language-guided Segmentation via Prototype-driven Semantic Approximation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alleviating-textual-reliance-in-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical language-guided segmentation, integrating textual clinical reports as auxiliary guidance to enhance image segmentation, has demonstrated significant improvements over unimodal approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alleviating-textual-reliance-in-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Sensor Scheduling and Selection for Continuous-Discrete Kalman Filtering with Auxiliary Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-sensor-scheduling-and-selection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our focus extends to scenarios in which the measurement process is coupled with the states of an auxiliary SSM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-sensor-scheduling-and-selection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Throughput Distributed Reinforcement Learning via Adaptive Policy Synchronization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-throughput-distributed-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scaling reinforcement learning (RL) workloads often requires distributing environment simulation across compute clusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-throughput-distributed-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hashed Watermark as a Filter: Defeating Forging and Overwriting Attacks in Weight-based Neural Network Watermarking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hashed-watermark-as-a-filter-defeating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we utilize a hash function to generate an irreversible binary watermark from a secret key, which is then used as a filter to select the model parameters for embedding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hashed-watermark-as-a-filter-defeating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoDistill: Geometry-Guided Self-Distillation for Weakly Supervised Cross-View Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geodistill-geometry-guided-self-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In GeoDistill, the teacher model localizes a panoramic image, while the student model predicts locations from a limited FoV counterpart created by FoV-based masking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geodistill-geometry-guided-self-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Wizards at CheckThat! 2025: Enhancing Transformer-Based Embeddings with Sentiment for Subjectivity Detection in News Articles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-wizards-at-checkthat-2025-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents AI Wizards' participation in the CLEF 2025 CheckThat!]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-wizards-at-checkthat-2025-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Bayesian Tensor Network Kernel Machines with Automatic Rank and Feature Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-bayesian-tensor-network-kernel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Bayesian Tensor Network Kernel Machines, a fully probabilistic framework that uses sparsity-inducing hierarchical priors on TN factors to automatically infer model complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-bayesian-tensor-network-kernel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SystolicAttention: Fusing FlashAttention within a Single Systolic Array</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/systolicattention-fusing-flashattention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The frequent data swaps between the systolic array and external vector units result in low systolic array utilization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/systolicattention-fusing-flashattention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precision Spatio-Temporal Feature Fusion for Robust Remote Sensing Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precision-spatio-temporal-feature-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remote sensing change detection is vital for monitoring environmental and urban transformations but faces challenges like manual feature extraction and sensitivity to noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precision-spatio-temporal-feature-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try Harder: Hard Sample Generation and Learning for Clothes-Changing Person Re-ID</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/try-harder-hard-sample-generation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hard samples pose a significant challenge in person re-identification (ReID) tasks, particularly in clothing-changing person Re-ID (CC-ReID).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/try-harder-hard-sample-generation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMOne: Representing Multiple Modalities in One Scene</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmone-representing-multiple-modalities-in-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the essential distinctions among modalities by disentangling multimodal information into shared and modality-specific components, resulting in a more compact and efficient multimodal scene representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmone-representing-multiple-modalities-in-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neurosymbolic Reasoning Shortcuts under the Independence Assumption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurosymbolic-reasoning-shortcuts-under-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ubiquitous independence assumption among symbolic concepts in neurosymbolic (NeSy) predictors is a convenient simplification: NeSy predictors use it to speed up probabilistic reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurosymbolic-reasoning-shortcuts-under-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U-RWKV: Lightweight medical image segmentation with direction-adaptive RWKV</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-rwkv-lightweight-medical-image-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Achieving equity in healthcare accessibility requires lightweight yet high-performance solutions for medical image segmentation, particularly in resource-limited settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-rwkv-lightweight-medical-image-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Parallelizable Approach for Characterizing NE in Zero-Sum Games After a Linear Number of Iterations of Gradient Descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-parallelizable-approach-for-characterizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study online optimization methods for zero-sum games, a fundamental problem in adversarial learning in machine learning, economics, and many other domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-parallelizable-approach-for-characterizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaMuon: Adaptive Muon Optimizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adamuon-adaptive-muon-optimizer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose AdaMuon, an adaptive learning-rate framework built upon the recently validated Muon optimizer, which has demonstrated substantial efficiency gains over AdamW in large-scale model training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adamuon-adaptive-muon-optimizer</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
