<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 09:15:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Training on the Test Task Confounds Evaluation and Emergence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-on-the-test-task-confounds</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This also applies to reported instances of emergent behavior that cannot be explained by the choice of evaluation metric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-on-the-test-task-confounds</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSA: Random Subspace Adaptation for Efficient Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rosa-random-subspace-adaptation-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing methods such as adapters, prompt tuning or low-rank adaptation (LoRA) either introduce latency overhead at inference time or achieve subpar downstream performance compared with full fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rosa-random-subspace-adaptation-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly-supervised Medical Image Segmentation with Gaze Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-medical-image-segmentation-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to collect dense weak supervision for medical image segmentation with a gaze annotation scheme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-medical-image-segmentation-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FUNAvg: Federated Uncertainty Weighted Averaging for Datasets with Diverse Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/funavg-federated-uncertainty-weighted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is one popular paradigm to train a joint model in a distributed, privacy-preserving environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/funavg-federated-uncertainty-weighted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained Classification for Poisonous Fungi Identification with Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-classification-for-poisonous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FungiCLEF 2024 addresses the fine-grained visual categorization (FGVC) of fungi species, with a focus on identifying poisonous species.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-classification-for-poisonous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDA-VLM: Towards Movie Understanding via ID-Aware Large Vision-Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ida-vlm-towards-movie-understanding-via-id</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of Large Vision-Language models (LVLMs) has demonstrated a spectrum of emergent capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ida-vlm-towards-movie-understanding-via-id</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pan-cancer Histopathology WSI Pre-training with Position-aware Masked Autoencoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pan-cancer-histopathology-wsi-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results have demonstrated the effectiveness of PAMA in generalized and discriminative WSI representation learning and pan-cancer WSI pre-training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pan-cancer-histopathology-wsi-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMix: Mixup with Semantic and Uncertain Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sumix-mixup-with-semantic-and-uncertain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mixup data augmentation approaches have been applied for various tasks of deep learning to improve the generalization ability of deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sumix-mixup-with-semantic-and-uncertain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Few-shot Class-incremental Learning: Learning from Yourself</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-few-shot-class-incremental-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, as a complement to existing metrics, we offer a new metric called generalized average accuracy (gAcc) which is designed to provide an extra equitable evaluation by incorporating different perspectives of the performance under the guidance of a parameter $\alpha$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-few-shot-class-incremental-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Large Language Models with Grid-Based Game Competitions: An Extensible LLM Benchmark and Leaderboard</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-large-language-models-with-grid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel and extensible benchmark for large language models (LLMs) through grid-based games such as Tic-Tac-Toe, Connect-Four, and Gomoku.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-large-language-models-with-grid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable Navigation Instruction Generation with Chain of Thought Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-navigation-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging the capabilities of Large Language Models (LLMs), we propose C-Instructor, which utilizes the chain-of-thought-style prompt for style-controllable and content-controllable instruction generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-navigation-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OV-DINO: Unified Open-Vocabulary Detection with Language-Aware Selective Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ov-dino-unified-open-vocabulary-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate the performance of the proposed OV-DINO on popular open-vocabulary detection benchmark datasets, achieving state-of-the-art results with an AP of 50. 6\% on the COCO dataset and 40. 0\% on the LVIS dataset in a zero-shot manner, demonstrating its strong generalization ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ov-dino-unified-open-vocabulary-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MNeRV: A Multilayer Neural Representation for Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mnerv-a-multilayer-neural-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a novel video representation method, Neural Representations for Videos (NeRV) has shown great potential in the fields of video compression, video restoration, and video interpolation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mnerv-a-multilayer-neural-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequential Kalman Monte Carlo for gradient-free inference in Bayesian inverse problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-kalman-monte-carlo-for-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the method is based on the assumption that we proceed through a sequence of Gaussian measures in moving from the prior to the posterior, and that the forward model is linear.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-kalman-monte-carlo-for-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-modal Crowd Counting via a Broker Modality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-crowd-counting-via-a-broker</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal crowd counting involves estimating crowd density from both visual and thermal/depth images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-crowd-counting-via-a-broker</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViTime: A Visual Intelligence-Based Foundation Model for Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitime-a-visual-intelligence-based-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of large pretrained models in natural language processing (NLP) and computer vision (CV) has opened new avenues for constructing foundation models for time series forecasting (TSF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitime-a-visual-intelligence-based-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pairwise Distance Distillation for Unsupervised Real-World Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pairwise-distance-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Standard single-image super-resolution creates paired training data from high-resolution images through fixed downsampling kernels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pairwise-distance-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Masked Autoencoders for Unsupervised Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-masked-autoencoders-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain Generalization (DG), designed to enhance out-of-distribution (OOD) generalization, is all about learning invariance against domain shifts utilizing sufficient supervision signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-masked-autoencoders-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Source-Free Domain Adaptation for Object Detection: Effective Self-Training Strategies and Performance Insights</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-source-free-domain-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper focuses on source-free domain adaptation for object detection in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-source-free-domain-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Embedding Aggregation Methods in Computational Pathology: A Clinical Data Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-embedding-aggregation-methods-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in artificial intelligence (AI), in particular self-supervised learning of foundation models (FMs), are revolutionizing medical imaging and computational pathology (CPath).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-embedding-aggregation-methods-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARS: Mixture of Auto-Regressive Models for Fine-grained Text-to-image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mars-mixture-of-auto-regressive-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Auto-regressive models have made significant progress in the realm of language generation, yet they do not perform on par with diffusion models in the domain of image synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mars-mixture-of-auto-regressive-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite Image Time Series Semantic Change Detection: Novel Architecture and Analysis of Domain Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/satellite-image-time-series-semantic-change</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the spatial domain shift represents the most complex setting and that the impact of temporal shift on performance is more pronounced on change detection than on semantic segmentation, highlighting that it is a specific issue deserving further attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/satellite-image-time-series-semantic-change</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Discovery in Semi-Stationary Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-in-semi-stationary-time-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The structural causal model (SCM) of this type of time series, called the semi-stationary time series, exhibits that a finite number of different causal mechanisms occur sequentially and periodically across time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-in-semi-stationary-time-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secondary Structure-Guided Novel Protein Sequence Generation with Latent Graph Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secondary-structure-guided-novel-protein</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advent of deep learning has introduced efficient approaches for de novo protein sequence design, significantly improving success rates and reducing development costs compared to computational or experimental methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secondary-structure-guided-novel-protein</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Partial Observability in Sequential Decision Processes via the Lambda Discrepancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-partial-observability-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our metric, the $\lambda$-discrepancy, is the difference between two distinct temporal difference (TD) value estimates, each computed using TD($\lambda$) with a different value of $\lambda$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-partial-observability-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Systematic Evaluation of Neural Retrieval Models on the Touché 2020 Argument Retrieval Subset of BEIR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/systematic-evaluation-of-neural-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our black-box evaluation reveals an inherent bias of neural models towards retrieving short passages from the Touch\'e 2020 data, and we also find that quite a few of the neural models' results are unjudged in the Touch\'e 2020 data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/systematic-evaluation-of-neural-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Foundation Model for Cardiac CT Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-foundation-model-for-cardiac-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) is a renowned technique for utilizing decentralized data while preserving privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-foundation-model-for-cardiac-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PosFormer: Recognizing Complex Handwritten Mathematical Expression with Position Forest Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posformer-recognizing-complex-handwritten</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this challenge, we propose a position forest transformer (PosFormer) for HMER, which jointly optimizes two tasks: expression recognition and position recognition, to explicitly enable position-aware symbol feature representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posformer-recognizing-complex-handwritten</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Embedding Alignment for Open-Vocabulary Video Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-embedding-alignment-for-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discover that the domain gap between the VLM features (e. g., CLIP) and the instance queries and the underutilization of temporal consistency are two central causes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-embedding-alignment-for-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Deep Stereo Matching in the Twenties</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-deep-stereo-matching-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stereo matching is close to hitting a half-century of history, yet witnessed a rapid evolution in the last decade thanks to deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-deep-stereo-matching-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaVA-NeXT-Interleave: Tackling Multi-image, Video, and 3D in Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-next-interleave-tackling-multi-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce LLaVA-NeXT-Interleave, which simultaneously tackles Multi-image, Multi-frame (video), Multi-view (3D), and Multi-patch (single-image) scenarios in LMMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-next-interleave-tackling-multi-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLBench: A Comprehensive Benchmark for Graph with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glbench-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce GLBench, the first comprehensive benchmark for evaluating GraphLLM methods in both supervised and zero-shot scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glbench-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pseudo-RIS: Distinctive Pseudo-supervision Generation for Referring Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-ris-distinctive-pseudo-supervision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose two-fold strategies that generate distinctive captions: 1) 'distinctive caption sampling', a new decoding method for the captioning model, to generate multiple expression candidates with detailed words focusing on the target.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-ris-distinctive-pseudo-supervision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SvANet: A Scale-variant Attention-based Network for Small Medical Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svanet-a-scale-variant-attention-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Early detection and accurate diagnosis can predict the risk of malignant disease transformation, thereby increasing the probability of effective treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svanet-a-scale-variant-attention-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRSAM: Advancing Segment Anything Model for Infrared Small Target Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irsam-advancing-segment-anything-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent Segment Anything Model (SAM) is a significant advancement in natural image segmentation, exhibiting potent zero-shot performance suitable for various downstream image segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irsam-advancing-segment-anything-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inference Performance Optimization for Large Language Models on CPUs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-performance-optimization-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown exceptional performance and vast potential across diverse tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-performance-optimization-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoBus: A Multimodal Dataset for Controllable Road Networks and Building Layouts Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robus-a-multimodal-dataset-for-controllable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we design new baselines that incorporate urban characteristics, such as road orientation and building density, in the process of generating road networks and building layouts using the RoBus dataset, enhancing the practicality of automated urban design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robus-a-multimodal-dataset-for-controllable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rectifier: Code Translation with Corrector via LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rectifier-code-translation-with-corrector-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Software migration is garnering increasing attention with the evolution of software and society.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rectifier-code-translation-with-corrector-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Coding-Theoretic Analysis of Hyperspherical Prototypical Learning Geometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-coding-theoretic-analysis-of-hyperspherical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperspherical Prototypical Learning (HPL) is a supervised approach to representation learning that designs class prototypes on the unit hypersphere.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-coding-theoretic-analysis-of-hyperspherical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLRS-PDS: A Meta-learning recommendation of dynamic ensemble selection pipelines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlrs-pds-a-meta-learning-recommendation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic Selection (DS), where base classifiers are chosen from a classifier's pool for each new instance at test time, has shown to be highly effective in pattern recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlrs-pds-a-meta-learning-recommendation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Resolution Cloud Detection Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-cloud-detection-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The complexity of clouds, particularly in terms of texture detail at high resolutions, has not been well explored by most existing cloud detection networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-cloud-detection-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CM-DQN: A Value-Based Deep Reinforcement Learning Model to Simulate Confirmation Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cm-dqn-a-value-based-deep-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a new algorithm in Deep Reinforcement Learning, CM-DQN, which applies the idea of different update strategies for positive or negative prediction errors, to simulate the human decision-making process when the task's states are continuous while the actions are discrete.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cm-dqn-a-value-based-deep-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHERL: Synthesizing High Accuracy and Efficient Memory for Resource-Limited Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sherl-synthesizing-high-accuracy-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parameter-efficient transfer learning (PETL) has emerged as a flourishing research field for adapting large pre-trained models to downstream tasks, greatly reducing trainable parameters while grappling with memory challenges during fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sherl-synthesizing-high-accuracy-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing HNSW Index for Real-Time Updates: Addressing Unreachable Points and Performance Degradation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-hnsw-index-for-real-time-updates</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed MN-RU algorithm effectively improves update efficiency and suppresses the growth rate of unreachable points, ensuring better overall performance and maintaining the integrity of the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-hnsw-index-for-real-time-updates</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated PCA on Grassmann Manifold for IoT Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-pca-on-grassmann-manifold-for-iot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results on the UNSW-NB15 and TON-IoT datasets show that our proposed methods offer performance in anomaly detection comparable to nonlinear baselines, while providing significant improvements in communication and memory efficiency, underscoring their potential for securing IoT networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-pca-on-grassmann-manifold-for-iot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resource Allocation for Twin Maintenance and Computing Task Processing in Digital Twin Vehicular Edge Computing Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resource-allocation-for-twin-maintenance-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By integrating DT with VEC, a virtual vehicle DT can be created in the VEC server to monitor the real-time operating status of vehicles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resource-allocation-for-twin-maintenance-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attribute or Abstain: Large Language Models as Long Document Assistants</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attribute-or-abstain-large-language-models-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is crucially different from the long document setting, where retrieval is not needed, but could help.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attribute-or-abstain-large-language-models-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rigorous Probabilistic Guarantees for Robust Counterfactual Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rigorous-probabilistic-guarantees-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of assessing the robustness of counterfactual explanations for deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rigorous-probabilistic-guarantees-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-stage Hyperspectral Image Classification Model with Spectral Supertoken</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-stage-hyperspectral-image-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperspectral image classification, a task that assigns pre-defined classes to each pixel in a hyperspectral image of remote sensing scenes, often faces challenges due to the neglect of correlations between spectrally similar pixels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-stage-hyperspectral-image-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIP: Tabular-Image Pre-training for Multimodal Classification with Incomplete Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tip-tabular-image-pre-training-for-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, TIP proposes a versatile tabular encoder tailored for incomplete, heterogeneous tabular data and a multimodal interaction module for inter-modality representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tip-tabular-image-pre-training-for-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
