<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 21:08:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CSAD: Unsupervised Component Segmentation for Logical Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csad-unsupervised-component-segmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve logical anomaly detection, some previous works have integrated segmentation techniques with conventional anomaly detection methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csad-unsupervised-component-segmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing and Accelerating Large Language Models via Instruction-Aware Contextual Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-and-accelerating-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have garnered widespread attention due to their remarkable performance across various tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-and-accelerating-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Agents: Simulating Counselor-Client Psychological Counseling via Role-Playing LLM-to-LLM Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-agents-simulating-counselor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Virtual counselors powered by large language models (LLMs) aim to create interactive support systems that effectively assist clients struggling with mental health challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-agents-simulating-counselor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Named Entity Recognition Using Few-Shot Prompting with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-named-entity-recognition-using-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper evaluates Few-Shot Prompting with Large Language Models for Named Entity Recognition (NER).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-named-entity-recognition-using-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>chemtrain: Learning Deep Potential Models via Automatic Differentiation and Statistical Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chemtrain-learning-deep-potential-models-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Networks (NNs) are promising models for refining the accuracy of molecular dynamics, potentially opening up new fields of application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chemtrain-learning-deep-potential-models-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBF-LLM: Safe Control for LLM Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbf-llm-safe-control-for-llm-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a control-based framework for aligning large language models (LLMs) by leveraging a control barrier function (CBF) to ensure user-desirable text generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbf-llm-safe-control-for-llm-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleRemix: Interpretable Authorship Obfuscation via Distillation and Perturbation of Style Elements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styleremix-interpretable-authorship</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Authorship obfuscation, rewriting a text to intentionally obscure the identity of the author, is an important but challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styleremix-interpretable-authorship</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstanSeg: an embedding-based instance segmentation algorithm optimized for accurate, efficient and portable cell segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instanseg-an-embedding-based-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cell and nucleus segmentation are fundamental tasks for quantitative bioimage analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instanseg-an-embedding-based-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEAR: Depth-Enhanced Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dear-depth-enhanced-action-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method involves processing estimated depth maps through a separate branch from the RGB feature encoder and fusing the features to understand the scene and actions comprehensively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dear-depth-enhanced-action-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaVA-MoD: Making LLaVA Tiny via MoE Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-mod-making-llava-tiny-via-moe-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce LLaVA-MoD, a novel framework designed to enable the efficient training of small-scale Multimodal Language Models (s-MLLM) by distilling knowledge from large-scale MLLM (l-MLLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-mod-making-llava-tiny-via-moe-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SITransformer: Shared Information-Guided Transformer for Extreme Multimodal Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sitransformer-shared-information-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extreme Multimodal Summarization with Multimodal Output (XMSMO) becomes an attractive summarization approach by integrating various types of information to create extremely concise yet informative summaries for individual modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sitransformer-shared-information-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Benefits of Visual Stabilization for Frame- and Event-based Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-benefits-of-visual-stabilization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assuming that the camera's attitude is available, we evaluate the benefits of stabilization in two perception applications: feature tracking and estimating the translation component of the camera's ego-motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-benefits-of-visual-stabilization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Facial Expression Recognition of Static and Dynamic Emotions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-facial-expression-recognition-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial expression recognition (FER) aims to analyze emotional states from static images and dynamic sequences, which is pivotal in enhancing anthropomorphic communication among humans, robots, and digital avatars by leveraging AI technologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-facial-expression-recognition-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emulating Brain-like Rapid Learning in Neuromorphic Edge Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emulating-brain-like-rapid-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we emulate the multiple stages of learning with digital neuromorphic technology that simulates the neural and synaptic processes of the brain using two stages of learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emulating-brain-like-rapid-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Mixture Analysis via Structural Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-mixture-analysis-via-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, analysis of the chemical relevance of a molecule is important when determining which species are present in a mixture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-mixture-analysis-via-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Adaptation on a Tight Academic Compute Budget: Tokenizer Swapping Works and Pure bfloat16 Is Enough</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-adaptation-on-a-tight-academic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate continued pretraining of LLMs for language adaptation on a tight academic budget: a setting in which only a few GPUs can be used in parallel, for a heavily constrained duration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-adaptation-on-a-tight-academic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merging and Splitting Diffusion Paths for Semantically Coherent Panoramas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merging-and-splitting-diffusion-paths-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this limitation, we propose the Merge-Attend-Diffuse operator, which can be plugged into different types of pretrained diffusion models used in a joint diffusion setting to improve the perceptual and semantical coherence of the generated panorama images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merging-and-splitting-diffusion-paths-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Attention for Cross-View Sequential Image Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-attention-for-cross-view-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel approach to enhancing cross-view localization, focusing on the fine-grained, sequential localization of street-view images within a single known satellite image patch, a significant departure from traditional one-to-one image retrieval methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-attention-for-cross-view-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIaM: Self-Improving Code-Assisted Mathematical Reasoning of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siam-self-improving-code-assisted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a growing trend of teaching large language models (LLMs) to solve mathematical problems through coding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siam-self-improving-code-assisted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distribution Backtracking Builds A Faster Convergence Trajectory for One-step Diffusion Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-backtracking-builds-a-faster</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Degradation Recording is designed to obtain the convergence trajectory of teacher models, which records the degradation path from the trained teacher model to the untrained initial student generator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-backtracking-builds-a-faster</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConsistencyTrack: A Robust Multi-Object Tracker with a Generation Strategy of Consistency Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistencytrack-a-robust-multi-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-object tracking (MOT) is a critical technology in computer vision, designed to detect multiple targets in video sequences and assign each target a unique ID per frame.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistencytrack-a-robust-multi-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VFLIP: A Backdoor Defense for Vertical Federated Learning via Identification and Purification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vflip-a-backdoor-defense-for-vertical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, VFLIP conducts purification which removes the embeddings identified as malicious and reconstructs all the embeddings based on the remaining embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vflip-a-backdoor-defense-for-vertical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divide, Conquer and Combine: A Training-Free Framework for High-Resolution Image Perception in Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divide-conquer-and-combine-a-training-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon this insight, we propose Divide, Conquer and Combine (DC$^2$), a novel training-free framework for enhancing MLLM perception of HR images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divide-conquer-and-combine-a-training-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMDRFuse: Distilled Mini-Model with Dynamic Refresh for Multi-Modality Image Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmdrfuse-distilled-mini-model-with-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, a lightweight Distilled Mini-Model with a Dynamic Refresh strategy (MMDRFuse) is proposed to achieve this objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmdrfuse-distilled-mini-model-with-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legilimens: Practical and Unified Content Moderation for Large Language Model Services</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/legilimens-practical-and-unified-content</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a practical and unified content moderation framework for LLM services, named Legilimens, which features both effectiveness and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/legilimens-practical-and-unified-content</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network transferability of adversarial patches in real-time object detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-transferability-of-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial patches in computer vision can be used, to fool deep neural networks and manipulate their decision-making process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-transferability-of-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagle: Exploring The Design Space for Multimodal LLMs with Mixture of Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eagle-exploring-the-design-space-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discover that simply concatenating visual tokens from a set of complementary vision encoders is as effective as more complex mixing architectures or strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eagle-exploring-the-design-space-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoGen: Learning from Feedback with Coupled Comprehension and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cogen-learning-from-feedback-with-coupled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work studies coupling comprehension and generation with focus on continually learning from interaction with users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cogen-learning-from-feedback-with-coupled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Fully Autonomous Research Powered by LLMs: Case Study on Simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-fully-autonomous-research-powered-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advent of Large Language Models (LLMs) has created new opportunities for the automation of scientific research, spanning both experimental processes and computational simulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-fully-autonomous-research-powered-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Levenshtein: Leveraging Multiple Algorithms for Robust Word Error Rate Computations And Granular Error Classifications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-levenshtein-leveraging-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Word Error Rate (WER) is the common measure of accuracy for Automatic Speech Recognition (ASR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-levenshtein-leveraging-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAS-BNN: Neural Architecture Search for Binary Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nas-bnn-neural-architecture-search-for-binary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we propose a novel neural architecture search scheme for binary neural networks, named NAS-BNN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nas-bnn-neural-architecture-search-for-binary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TrafficGamer: Reliable and Flexible Traffic Simulation for Safety-Critical Scenarios with Game-Theoretic Oracles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trafficgamer-reliable-and-flexible-traffic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In evaluating the empirical performance across various real-world datasets, TrafficGamer ensures both fidelity and exploitability of the simulated scenarios, guaranteeing that they not only statically align with real-world traffic distribution but also efficiently capture equilibriums for representing safety-critical scenarios involving multiple agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trafficgamer-reliable-and-flexible-traffic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Blockmodelling for Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-blockmodelling-for-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The work presented in this paper provides the first step for the further application of stochastic blockmodels for knowledge graphs on a larger scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-blockmodelling-for-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>μgat: Improving Single-Page Document Parsing by Providing Multi-Page Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgat-improving-single-page-document-parsing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Regesta are catalogs of summaries of other documents and, in some cases, are the only source of information about the content of such full-length documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgat-improving-single-page-document-parsing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TagOOD: A Novel Approach to Out-of-Distribution Detection via Vision-Language Representations and Class Center Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tagood-a-novel-approach-to-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct extensive experiments to evaluate TagOOD on several benchmark datasets and demonstrate its superior performance compared to existing OOD detection methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tagood-a-novel-approach-to-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeFF: Tracking-enhanced Forgetting-free Few-shot 3D LiDAR Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teff-tracking-enhanced-forgetting-free-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this approach introduces a data imbalance biased to novel data that presents a new challenge of catastrophic forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teff-tracking-enhanced-forgetting-free-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mamba or Transformer for Time Series Forecasting? Mixture of Universals (MoU) Is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-or-transformer-for-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we introduce Mixture of Universals (MoU), a versatile model to capture both short-term and long-term dependencies for enhancing performance in time series forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-or-transformer-for-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Pose Fusion for Occlusion-Aware 3D Human Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-pose-fusion-for-occlusion-aware-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach outperforms state-of-the-art multi-view human pose estimation techniques and demonstrates superior capabilities in handling challenging scenarios with strong occlusions, representing a reliable and effective solution for real human-robot collaboration setups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-pose-fusion-for-occlusion-aware-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Force-Guided Bridge Matching for Full-Atom Time-Coarsened Dynamics of Peptides</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/force-guided-bridge-matching-for-full-atom</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Molecular Dynamics (MD) simulations are irreplaceable and ubiquitous in fields of materials science, chemistry, pharmacology just to name a few.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/force-guided-bridge-matching-for-full-atom</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Credit VIX (CDS IV) Prediction Methods with Incremental Batch Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-credit-vix-cds-iv-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the experimental process and results of SVM, Gradient Boosting, and an Attention-GRU Hybrid model in predicting the Implied Volatility of rolled-over five-year spread contracts of credit default swaps (CDS) on European corporate debt during the quarter following mid-May '24, as represented by the iTraxx/Cboe Europe Main 1-Month Volatility Index (BP Volatility).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-credit-vix-cds-iv-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTMamba++: Enhancing Multi-Task Dense Scene Understanding via Mamba-Based Decoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtmamba-enhancing-multi-task-dense-scene-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-task dense scene understanding, which trains a model for multiple dense prediction tasks, has a wide range of application scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtmamba-enhancing-multi-task-dense-scene-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAT: Pruning-Aware Tuning for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pat-pruning-aware-tuning-for-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the model fine-tuning refines the general and chaotic knowledge in pre-trained models, we aim to incorporate structural pruning with the fine-tuning, and propose the Pruning-Aware Tuning (PAT) paradigm to eliminate model redundancy while preserving the model performance to the maximum extend.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pat-pruning-aware-tuning-for-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRL-Based Federated Self-Supervised Learning for Task Offloading and Resource Allocation in ISAC-Enabled Vehicle Edge Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drl-based-federated-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our improved algorithm offloads partial task to RSU and optimizes energy consumption by adjusting transmission power, CPU frequency, and task assignment ratios, balancing local and RSU-based training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drl-based-federated-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIFR3CT: Latent Diffusion for Probabilistic 3D CT Reconstruction from Few Planar X-Rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difr3ct-latent-diffusion-for-probabilistic-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computed Tomography (CT) scans are the standard-of-care for the visualization and diagnosis of many clinical ailments, and are needed for the treatment planning of external beam radiotherapy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difr3ct-latent-diffusion-for-probabilistic-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using LLMs for Explaining Sets of Counterfactual Examples to Final Users</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-llms-for-explaining-sets-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causality is vital for understanding true cause-and-effect relationships between variables within predictive models, rather than relying on mere correlations, making it highly relevant in the field of Explainable AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-llms-for-explaining-sets-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mamba in the Llama: Distilling and Accelerating Hybrid Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-mamba-in-the-llama-distilling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Linear RNN architectures, like Mamba, can be competitive with Transformer models in language modeling while having advantageous deployment characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-mamba-in-the-llama-distilling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAW-Adapter: Adapting Pre-trained Visual Model to Camera RAW Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raw-adapter-adapting-pre-trained-visual-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[sRGB images are now the predominant choice for pre-training visual models in computer vision research, owing to their ease of acquisition and efficient storage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raw-adapter-adapting-pre-trained-visual-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TourSynbio: A Multi-Modal Large Model and Agent Framework to Bridge Text and Protein Sequences for Protein Engineering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toursynbio-a-multi-modal-large-model-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While large language models (LLMs) have achieved much progress in the domain of natural language processing, their potential in protein engineering remains largely unexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toursynbio-a-multi-modal-large-model-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Event-Triggered Switching for Frequency Control in Power Grids with Variable Inertia</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-event-triggered-switching-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing integration of renewable energy resources into power grids has led to time-varying system inertia and consequent degradation in frequency dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-event-triggered-switching-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIFT-SW: Gaussian noise Injected Fine-Tuning of Salient Weights for LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gift-sw-gaussian-noise-injected-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parameter Efficient Fine-Tuning (PEFT) methods have gained popularity and democratized the usage of Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gift-sw-gaussian-noise-injected-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
