<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 21:06:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>BoostTrack: boosting the similarity measure and detection confidence for improved multiple object tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosttrack-boosting-the-similarity-measure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To utilize low-detection score bounding boxes in one-stage association, we propose to boost the confidence scores of two groups of detections: the detections we assume to correspond to the existing tracked object, and the detections we assume to correspond to a previously undetected object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosttrack-boosting-the-similarity-measure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lyapunov-stable Neural Control for State and Output Feedback: A Novel Formulation for Efficient Synthesis and Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lyapunov-stable-neural-control-for-state-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The flexibility and efficiency of our framework allow us to demonstrate Lyapunov-stable output feedback control with synthesized NN-based controllers and NN-based observers with formal stability guarantees, for the first time in literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lyapunov-stable-neural-control-for-state-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TBSN: Transformer-Based Blind-Spot Network for Self-Supervised Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tbsn-transformer-based-blind-spot-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For channel self-attention, we observe that it may leak the blind-spot information when the channel number is greater than spatial size in the deep layers of multi-scale architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tbsn-transformer-based-blind-spot-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming Stable Diffusion for Text to 360° Panorama Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-stable-diffusion-for-text-to-360deg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative models, e. g., Stable Diffusion, have enabled the creation of photorealistic images from text prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-stable-diffusion-for-text-to-360deg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RMAFF-PSN: A Residual Multi-Scale Attention Feature Fusion Photometric Stereo Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmaff-psn-a-residual-multi-scale-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting accurate normal maps of objects from two-dimensional images in regions of complex structure and spatial material variations is challenging using photometric stereo methods due to the influence of surface reflection properties caused by variations in object geometry and surface materials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmaff-psn-a-residual-multi-scale-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable All-pole Filters for Time-varying Audio Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-all-pole-filters-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Infinite impulse response filters are an essential building block of many time-varying audio systems, such as audio effects and synthesisers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-all-pole-filters-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Vehicle Motion Planning Generalize to Realistic Long-tail Scenarios?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-vehicle-motion-planning-generalize-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We assess existing state-of-the-art planners on our benchmark and show that neither rule-based nor learning-based planners can safely navigate the interPlan scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-vehicle-motion-planning-generalize-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global versus Local: Evaluating AlexNet Architectures for Tropical Cyclone Intensity Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-versus-local-evaluating-alexnet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first model, trained on the entire dataset, is called the global AlexNet model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-versus-local-evaluating-alexnet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep learning-driven pulmonary arteries and veins segmentation reveals demography-associated pulmonary vasculature anatomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-driven-pulmonary-arteries-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we propose a High-abundant Pulmonary Artery-vein Segmentation (HiPaS) framework achieving accurate artery-vein segmentation on both non-contrast CT and CTPA across various spatial resolutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-driven-pulmonary-arteries-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive-Based Deep Embeddings for Label Noise-Resilient Histopathology Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-based-deep-embeddings-for-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in deep learning have proven highly effective in medical image classification, notably within histopathology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-based-deep-embeddings-for-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manipulating Large Language Models to Increase Product Visibility</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manipulating-large-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that adding a strategic text sequence (STS) -- a carefully crafted message -- to a product's information page can significantly increase its likelihood of being listed as the LLM's top recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manipulating-large-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion posterior sampling for simulation-based inference in tall data settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-posterior-sampling-for-simulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Determining which parameters of a non-linear model could best describe a set of experimental data is a fundamental problem in science and it has gained much traction lately with the rise of complex large-scale simulators (a. k. a.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-posterior-sampling-for-simulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Data Augmentation for Process Information Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-data-augmentation-for-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study shows, that data augmentation is an important component in enabling machine learning methods for the task of business process model generation from natural language text, where currently mostly rule-based systems are still state of the art.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-data-augmentation-for-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuasiSim: Parameterized Quasi-Physical Simulators for Dexterous Manipulations Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quasisim-parameterized-quasi-physical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore the dexterous manipulation transfer problem by designing simulators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quasisim-parameterized-quasi-physical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HGRN2: Gated Linear RNNs with State Expansion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgrn2-gated-linear-rnns-with-state-expansion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hierarchically gated linear RNN (HGRN, Qin et al. 2023) has demonstrated competitive training speed and performance in language modeling, while offering efficient inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgrn2-gated-linear-rnns-with-state-expansion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuroNCAP: Photorealistic Closed-loop Safety Testing for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuroncap-photorealistic-closed-loop-safety</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a versatile NeRF-based simulator for testing autonomous driving (AD) software systems, designed with a focus on sensor-realistic closed-loop evaluation and the creation of safety-critical scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuroncap-photorealistic-closed-loop-safety</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring Change Points in High-Dimensional Linear Regression via Approximate Message Passing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-change-points-in-high-dimensional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of localizing change points in high-dimensional linear regression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-change-points-in-high-dimensional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Language Model with Generalized Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-language-model-with-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce the Scalable Language Model (SLM) to overcome these limitations within a more challenging and generalized setting, representing a significant advancement toward practical applications for continual learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-language-model-with-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming detection of significant delay changes in public transport systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-detection-of-significant-delay</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The method we propose can be used with different change detectors, such as ADWIN, applied to location data stream shuffled to individual edges of a transport graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-detection-of-significant-delay</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content-Adaptive Non-Local Convolution for Remote Sensing Pansharpening</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/content-adaptive-non-local-convolution-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a so-called content-adaptive non-local convolution (CANConv), a novel method tailored for remote sensing image pansharpening.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/content-adaptive-non-local-convolution-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calibration of Continual Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibration-of-continual-learning-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual Learning (CL) focuses on maximizing the predictive performance of a model across a non-stationary stream of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibration-of-continual-learning-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do You Remember? Dense Video Captioning with Cross-Modal Memory Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-you-remember-dense-video-captioning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There has been significant attention to the research on dense video captioning, which aims to automatically localize and caption all events within untrimmed video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-you-remember-dense-video-captioning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dealing with Subject Similarity in Differential Morphing Attack Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dealing-with-subject-similarity-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advent of morphing attacks has posed significant security concerns for automated Face Recognition systems, raising the pressing need for robust and effective Morphing Attack Detection (MAD) methods able to effectively address this issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dealing-with-subject-similarity-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behavior Trees Enable Structured Programming of Language Model Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behavior-trees-enable-structured-programming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models trained on internet-scale data sets have shown an impressive ability to solve problems in Natural Language Processing and Computer Vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behavior-trees-enable-structured-programming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resolve Domain Conflicts for Generalizable Remote Physiological Measurement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resolve-domain-conflicts-for-generalizable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remote photoplethysmography (rPPG) technology has become increasingly popular due to its non-invasive monitoring of various physiological indicators, making it widely applicable in multimedia interaction, healthcare, and emotion analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resolve-domain-conflicts-for-generalizable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenTrench3D: A Photogrammetric 3D Point Cloud Dataset for Semantic Segmentation of Underground Utilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opentrench3d-a-photogrammetric-3d-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present OpenTrench3D, a novel and comprehensive 3D Semantic Segmentation point cloud dataset, designed to advance research and development in underground utility surveying and mapping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opentrench3d-a-photogrammetric-3d-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heron-Bench: A Benchmark for Evaluating Vision Language Models in Japanese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heron-bench-a-benchmark-for-evaluating-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision Language Models (VLMs) have undergone a rapid evolution, giving rise to significant advancements in the realm of multimodal understanding tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heron-bench-a-benchmark-for-evaluating-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ai-research</title>
      <link>https://github.com/faceonlive/ai-research</link>
      <description><![CDATA[None]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/faceonlive/ai-research</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precise spiking motifs in neurobiological and neuromorphic data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precise-spiking-motifs-in-neurobiological-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Why do neurons communicate through spikes?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precise-spiking-motifs-in-neurobiological-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PillarTrack: Redesigning Pillar-based Transformer Network for Single Object Tracking on Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pillartrack-redesigning-pillar-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LiDAR-based 3D single object tracking (3D SOT) is a critical issue in robotics and autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pillartrack-redesigning-pillar-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoMVS: Geometrically Consistent Cost Aggregation for Multi-View Stereo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gomvs-geometrically-consistent-cost</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More specifically, we correspond and propagate adjacent costs to the reference pixel by leveraging the local geometric smoothness in conjunction with surface normals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gomvs-geometrically-consistent-cost</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PINNACLE: PINN Adaptive ColLocation and Experimental points selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pinnacle-pinn-adaptive-collocation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Physics-Informed Neural Networks (PINNs), which incorporate PDEs as soft constraints, train with a composite loss function that contains multiple training point types: different types of collocation points chosen during training to enforce each PDE and initial/boundary conditions, and experimental points which are usually costly to obtain via experiments or simulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pinnacle-pinn-adaptive-collocation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Hoc Reversal: Are We Selecting Models Prematurely?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-hoc-reversal-are-we-selecting-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This phenomenon is especially prominent in high-noise settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-hoc-reversal-are-we-selecting-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comments as Natural Logic Pivots: Improve Code Generation via Comment Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comments-as-natural-logic-pivots-improve-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we suggest that code comments are the natural logic pivot between natural language and code language and propose using comments to boost the code generation ability of code LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comments-as-natural-logic-pivots-improve-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Dataset Distillation: A Good Compression Is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-dataset-distillation-a-good</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we consider addressing this task through the new lens of model informativeness in the compression stage on the original dataset pretraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-dataset-distillation-a-good</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DesignQA: A Multimodal Benchmark for Evaluating Large Language Models' Understanding of Engineering Documentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designqa-a-multimodal-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research introduces DesignQA, a novel benchmark aimed at evaluating the proficiency of multimodal large language models (MLLMs) in comprehending and applying engineering requirements in technical documentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designqa-a-multimodal-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnnoCTR: A Dataset for Detecting and Linking Entities, Tactics, and Techniques in Cyber Threat Reports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/annoctr-a-dataset-for-detecting-and-linking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our few-shot scenario, we find that for identifying the MITRE ATT&CK concepts that are mentioned explicitly or implicitly in a text, concept descriptions from MITRE ATT&CK are an effective source for training data augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/annoctr-a-dataset-for-detecting-and-linking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Words to Numbers: Your Large Language Model Is Secretly A Capable Regressor When Given In-Context Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-words-to-numbers-your-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze how well pre-trained large language models (e. g., Llama2, GPT-4, Claude 3, etc) can do linear and non-linear regression when given in-context examples, without any additional training or gradient updates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-words-to-numbers-your-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetMoE: Reaching Llama2 Performance with 0.1M Dollars</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jetmoe-reaching-llama2-performance-with-0-1m</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have achieved remarkable results, but their increasing resource demand has become a major obstacle to the development of powerful and accessible super-human intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jetmoe-reaching-llama2-performance-with-0-1m</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transferable and Principled Efficiency for Open-Vocabulary Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferable-and-principled-efficiency-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of efficient OVS, we target achieving performance that is comparable to or even better than prior OVS works based on large vision-language foundation models, by utilizing smaller models that incur lower training costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferable-and-principled-efficiency-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLoCO: Learning Long Contexts Offline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lloco-learning-long-contexts-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce LLoCO, a technique that combines context compression, retrieval, and parameter-efficient finetuning using LoRA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lloco-learning-long-contexts-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Aggregation Network for Dichotomous Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-aggregation-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dichotomous Image Segmentation (DIS) has recently emerged towards high-precision object segmentation from high-resolution natural images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-aggregation-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guiding Large Language Models to Post-Edit Machine Translation with Error Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-large-language-models-to-post-edit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine Translation (MT) remains one of the last NLP tasks where large language models (LLMs) have not yet replaced dedicated supervised systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-large-language-models-to-post-edit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Imbalance Can Boost Cross-lingual Generalisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-imbalance-can-boost-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In controlled experiments on perfectly equivalent cloned languages, we observe that the existence of a predominant language during training boosts the performance of less frequent languages and leads to stronger alignment of model representations across languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-imbalance-can-boost-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rho-1: Not All Tokens Are What You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rho-1-not-all-tokens-are-what-you-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After fine-tuning, Rho-1-1B and 7B achieved state-of-the-art results of 40. 6% and 51. 8% on MATH dataset, respectively - matching DeepSeekMath with only 3% of the pretraining tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rho-1-not-all-tokens-are-what-you-need</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DGMamba: Domain Generalization via Generalized State Space Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgmamba-domain-generalization-via-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SPR strives to encourage the model to concentrate more on objects rather than context, consisting of two designs: Prior-Free Scanning~(PFS), and Domain Context Interchange~(DCI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgmamba-domain-generalization-via-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monte Carlo Tree Search with Boltzmann Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-tree-search-with-boltzmann-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monte-Carlo Tree Search (MCTS) methods, such as Upper Confidence Bound applied to Trees (UCT), are instrumental to automated planning techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-tree-search-with-boltzmann-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curated Datasets and Neural Models for Machine Translation of Informal Registers between Mayan and Spanish Vernaculars</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curated-datasets-and-neural-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Mayan languages comprise a language family with an ancient history, millions of speakers, and immense cultural value, that, nevertheless, remains severely underrepresented in terms of resources and global exposure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curated-datasets-and-neural-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViM-UNet: Vision Mamba for Biomedical Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vim-unet-vision-mamba-for-biomedical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we introduce ViM-UNet, a novel segmentation architecture based on it and compare it to UNet and UNETR for two challenging microscopy instance segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vim-unet-vision-mamba-for-biomedical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Concept Drift Detection based on Parallel Activations of Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-concept-drift-detection-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Practical applications of artificial intelligence increasingly often have to deal with the streaming properties of real data, which, considering the time factor, are subject to phenomena such as periodicity and more or less chaotic degeneration - resulting directly in the concept drifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-concept-drift-detection-based-on</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
