<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 09:12:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SODA: Robust Training of Test-Time Data Adaptors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soda-robust-training-of-test-time-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adapting models deployed to test distributions can mitigate the performance degradation caused by distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soda-robust-training-of-test-time-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficiently Visualizing Large Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiently-visualizing-large-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Performing SPLEE to obtain a high-dimensional embedding of the large-scale graph and then using t-SGNE to reduce its dimension for visualization, we are able to visualize graphs with up to 300K nodes and 1M edges within 5 minutes and achieve approximately 10% improvement in visualization quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiently-visualizing-large-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Pairwise Encodings for Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-pairwise-encodings-for-link</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, a new class of methods has emerged that combines the advantages of message-passing neural networks (MPNN) and heuristics methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-pairwise-encodings-for-link</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xMEN: A Modular Toolkit for Cross-Lingual Medical Entity Normalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xmen-a-modular-toolkit-for-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly supervised cross-encoders are effective when no training data is available for the target task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xmen-a-modular-toolkit-for-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NICE: Improving Panoptic Narrative Detection and Segmentation with Cascading Collaborative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nice-improving-panoptic-narrative-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce two cascading modules based on the barycenter of the mask, which are Coordinate Guided Aggregation (CGA) and Barycenter Driven Localization (BDL), responsible for segmentation and detection, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nice-improving-panoptic-narrative-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study of Translation Hypothesis Ensembling with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-translation-hypothesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are becoming a one-fits-many solution, but they sometimes hallucinate or produce unreliable output.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-translation-hypothesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse-DySta: Sparsity-Aware Dynamic and Static Scheduling for Sparse Multi-DNN Workloads</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-dysta-sparsity-aware-dynamic-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Running multiple deep neural networks (DNNs) in parallel has become an emerging workload in both edge devices, such as mobile phones where multiple tasks serve a single user for daily activities, and data centers, where various requests are raised from millions of users, as seen with large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-dysta-sparsity-aware-dynamic-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXMODD: An EXplanatory Multimodal Open-Domain Dialogue dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exmodd-an-explanatory-multimodal-open-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The need for high-quality data has been a key issue hindering the research of dialogue tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exmodd-an-explanatory-multimodal-open-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Contrastive Learning via Distributionally Robust Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-contrastive-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study reveals the inherent tolerance of contrastive learning (CL) towards sampling bias, wherein negative samples may encompass similar semantics (\eg labels).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-contrastive-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Generic Semi-Supervised Framework for Volumetric Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-generic-semi-supervised-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, there is growing interest in using semi-supervised learning (SSL) techniques to train models with limited labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-generic-semi-supervised-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermarking LLMs with Weight Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watermarking-llms-with-weight-quantization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Abuse of large language models reveals high risks as large language models are being deployed at an astonishing speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watermarking-llms-with-weight-quantization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unanswerable Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unanswerable-visual-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Teaching Visual Question Answering (VQA) models to abstain from unanswerable questions is indispensable for building a trustworthy AI system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unanswerable-visual-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating LLMs for Privilege-Escalation Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-llms-for-privilege-escalation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore the intersection of LLMs and penetration testing to gain insight into their capabilities and challenges in the context of privilige escalation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-llms-for-privilege-escalation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEQ: Trainable Equivalent Transformation for Quantization of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teq-trainable-equivalent-transformation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As large language models (LLMs) become more prevalent, there is a growing need for new and improved quantization methods that can meet the computationalast layer demands of these modern architectures while maintaining the accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teq-trainable-equivalent-transformation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compatible Transformer for Irregularly Sampled Multivariate Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compatible-transformer-for-irregularly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To analyze multivariate time series, most previous methods assume regular subsampling of time series, where the interval between adjacent measurements and the number of samples remain unchanged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compatible-transformer-for-irregularly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Simple Spectral Clustering in Theory and Practice</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-simple-spectral-clustering-in-theory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spectral clustering is a popular and effective algorithm designed to find $k$ clusters in a graph $G$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-simple-spectral-clustering-in-theory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Context Few-Shot Relation Extraction via Pre-Trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-few-shot-relation-extraction-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, we are the first to reformulate the relation extraction task as a tailored in-context few-shot learning paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-few-shot-relation-extraction-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VcT: Visual change Transformer for Remote Sensing Image Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vct-visual-change-transformer-for-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, each pixel of feature map is regarded as a graph node and the graph neural network is proposed to model the structured information for coarse change map prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vct-visual-change-transformer-for-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An active learning convolutional neural network for predicting river flow in a human impacted system</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-active-learning-convolutional-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we find that a convolutional Long Short-Term Memory (LSTM) network is well suited to modeling flow in parts of this basin that are strongly impacted by water projects as well as ones that are relatively free from direct human modifications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-active-learning-convolutional-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instilling Inductive Biases with Subnetworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instilling-inductive-biases-with-subnetworks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method discovers a functional subnetwork that implements a particular subtask within a trained model and uses it to instill inductive biases towards solutions utilizing that subtask.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instilling-inductive-biases-with-subnetworks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Modified EXP3 and Its Adaptive Variant in Adversarial Bandits with Multi-User Delayed Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modified-exp3-and-its-adaptive-variant-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we formulate an adversarial multi-armed bandit problem with multi-user delayed feedback and design a modified EXP3 algorithm named MUD-EXP3, which makes a decision at each round by considering the importance-weighted estimator of the received feedback from different users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modified-exp3-and-its-adaptive-variant-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A voxel-level approach to brain age prediction: A method to assess regional brain aging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-voxel-level-approach-to-brain-age</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Brain aging is a regional phenomenon, a facet that remains relatively under-explored within the realm of brain age prediction research using machine learning methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-voxel-level-approach-to-brain-age</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent-Specific Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-specific-effects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These challenges are particularly prominent in the context of multi-agent sequential decision-making, where the causal effect of an agent's action on the outcome depends on how the other agents respond to that action.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-specific-effects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogenous Memory Augmented Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogenous-memory-augmented-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It has been shown that semi-parametric methods, which combine standard neural networks with non-parametric components such as external memory modules and data retrieval, are particularly helpful in data scarcity and out-of-distribution (OOD) scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogenous-memory-augmented-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Cognitive Architecture: Incorporating Biases and Multi-Memory Systems for Lifelong Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-cognitive-architecture-incorporating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial neural networks (ANNs) exhibit a narrow scope of expertise on stationary independent data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-cognitive-architecture-incorporating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMTLab: An Open-Source Platform for Building, Evaluating, and Diagnosing Interactive Machine Translation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imtlab-an-open-source-platform-for-building</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present IMTLab, an open-source end-to-end interactive machine translation (IMT) system platform that enables researchers to quickly build IMT systems with state-of-the-art models, perform an end-to-end evaluation, and diagnose the weakness of systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imtlab-an-open-source-platform-for-building</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Attention: Enhancing QKV Calculation in Self-Attention Mechanism with Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-attention-enhancing-qkv-calculation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of deep learning, the self-attention mechanism has substantiated its pivotal role across a myriad of tasks, encompassing natural language processing and computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-attention-enhancing-qkv-calculation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zipformer: A faster and better encoder for automatic speech recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipformer-a-faster-and-better-encoder-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Conformer has become the most popular encoder model for automatic speech recognition (ASR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipformer-a-faster-and-better-encoder-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QADYNAMICS: Training Dynamics-Driven Synthetic QA Diagnostic for Zero-Shot Commonsense Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qadynamics-training-dynamics-driven-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zero-shot commonsense Question-Answering (QA) requires models to reason about general situations beyond specific benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qadynamics-training-dynamics-driven-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MonoSKD: General Distillation Framework for Monocular 3D Object Detection via Spearman Correlation Coefficient</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monoskd-general-distillation-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monocular 3D object detection is an inherently ill-posed problem, as it is challenging to predict accurate 3D localization from a single image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monoskd-general-distillation-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELA: Learning Parameter-Efficient Models with Low-Rank Approximation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pela-learning-parameter-efficient-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This allows for direct and efficient utilization of the low-rank model for downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pela-learning-parameter-efficient-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Learning Framework for Cost-Effective TCR-Epitope Binding Affinity Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-framework-for-cost-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reduce annotation cost, we present ActiveTCR, a framework that incorporates active learning and TCR-epitope binding affinity prediction models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-framework-for-cost-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Classification by Density Estimation Using Gaussian Mixture Model and Masked Autoregressive Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-classification-by-density</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A family of density estimators is mixture models, such as Gaussian Mixture Model (GMM) by expectation maximization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-classification-by-density</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Persona Consistent Dialogue Agents with Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-persona-consistent-dialogue-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our automatic and human evaluations show that our framework improves both the persona consistency and dialogue quality of a state-of-the-art social chatbot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-persona-consistent-dialogue-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DemoNSF: A Multi-task Demonstration-based Generative Framework for Noisy Slot Filling Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demonsf-a-multi-task-demonstration-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, prompt-based generative frameworks have shown impressive capabilities in sequence labeling tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demonsf-a-multi-task-demonstration-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoTTA: Robust Test-Time Adaptation on Noisy Data Streams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sotta-robust-test-time-adaptation-on-noisy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we present Screening-out Test-Time Adaptation (SoTTA), a novel TTA algorithm that is robust to noisy samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sotta-robust-test-time-adaptation-on-noisy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image super-resolution via dynamic network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-super-resolution-via-dynamic-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a dynamic network for image super-resolution (DSRNet), which contains a residual enhancement block, wide enhancement block, feature refinement block and construction block.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-super-resolution-via-dynamic-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Body Neural Scene Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-body-neural-scene-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The test-time optimization of scene flow - using a coordinate network as a neural prior - has gained popularity due to its simplicity, lack of dataset bias, and state-of-the-art performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-body-neural-scene-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Generalized Intent Discovery: Marching Towards Dynamic and Open-world Intent Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-generalized-intent-discovery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a practical dialogue system, users may input out-of-domain (OOD) queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-generalized-intent-discovery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAgents: An Open Platform for Language Agents in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openagents-an-open-platform-for-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language agents show potential in being capable of utilizing natural language for varied and intricate tasks in diverse environments, particularly when built upon large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openagents-an-open-platform-for-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Video Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-video-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing surveys mainly focus on diffusion models in the context of image generation, with few up-to-date reviews on their application in the video domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-video-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Transferability of Learning Models for Semantic Segmentation for Remote Sensing Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-transferability-of-learning-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, there is no comprehensive analysis of their transferability, i. e., to which extent a model trained on a source domain can be readily applicable to a target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-transferability-of-learning-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time Photorealistic Dynamic Scene Representation and Rendering with 4D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-photorealistic-dynamic-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstructing dynamic 3D scenes from 2D images and generating diverse views over time is challenging due to scene complexity and temporal dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-photorealistic-dynamic-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit regularization via soft ascent-descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-regularization-via-soft-ascent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As models grow larger and more complex, achieving better off-sample generalization with minimal trial-and-error is critical to the reliability and economy of machine learning workflows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-regularization-via-soft-ascent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Word Sense Distribution Detect Semantic Changes of Words?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-word-sense-distribution-detect-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given this relationship between WSD and SCD, we explore the possibility of predicting whether a target word has its meaning changed between two corpora collected at different time steps, by comparing the distributions of senses of that word in each corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-word-sense-distribution-detect-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA: Denoised Neighborhood Aggregation for Fine-grained Category Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dna-denoised-neighborhood-aggregation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we retrieve k-nearest neighbors of a query as its positive keys to capture semantic similarities between data and then aggregate information from the neighbors to learn compact cluster representations, which can make fine-grained categories more separatable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dna-denoised-neighborhood-aggregation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning visual-based deformable object rearrangement with local graph neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-visual-based-deformable-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method reaches much higher success rates on a variety of deformable rearrangement tasks (96. 3% on average) than state-of-the-art method in simulation experiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-visual-based-deformable-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A cross Transformer for image denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cross-transformer-for-image-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To avoid loss of key information, PB uses three heterogeneous networks to implement multiple interactions of multi-level features to broadly search for extra information for improving the adaptability of an obtained denoiser for complex scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cross-transformer-for-image-denoising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models Meet Open-World Intent Discovery and Recognition: An Evaluation of ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-meet-open-world-intent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The tasks of out-of-domain (OOD) intent discovery and generalized intent discovery (GID) aim to extend a closed intent classifier to open-world intent sets, which is crucial to task-oriented dialogue (TOD) systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-meet-open-world-intent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZoomTrack: Target-aware Non-uniform Resizing for Efficient Visual Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zoomtrack-target-aware-non-uniform-resizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we non-uniformly resize the cropped image to have a smaller input size while the resolution of the area where the target is more likely to appear is higher and vice versa.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zoomtrack-target-aware-non-uniform-resizing</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
