<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 21:09:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Reasoning Capabilities of LLMs via Principled Synthetic Logic Corpus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-reasoning-capabilities-of-llms-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are capable of solving a wide range of tasks, yet they have struggled with reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-reasoning-capabilities-of-llms-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multimodal Approach Combining Structural and Cross-domain Textual Guidance for Weakly Supervised OCT Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multimodal-approach-combining-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate segmentation of Optical Coherence Tomography (OCT) images is crucial for diagnosing and monitoring retinal diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multimodal-approach-combining-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RedPajama: an Open Dataset for Training Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redpajama-an-open-dataset-for-training-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we release RedPajama-V2, a massive web-only dataset consisting of raw, unfiltered text data together with quality signals and metadata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redpajama-an-open-dataset-for-training-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SG-LRA: Self-Generating Automatic Scoliosis Cobb Angle Measurement with Low-Rank Approximation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sg-lra-self-generating-automatic-scoliosis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic Cobb angle measurement from X-ray images is crucial for scoliosis screening and diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sg-lra-self-generating-automatic-scoliosis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Procedural Knowledge in Pretraining Drives Reasoning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procedural-knowledge-in-pretraining-drives</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that, while the models rely on mostly distinct sets of data for each factual question, a document often has a similar influence across different reasoning questions within the same task, indicating the presence of procedural knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procedural-knowledge-in-pretraining-drives</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M3D: Dual-Stream Selective State Spaces and Depth-Driven Framework for High-Fidelity Single-View 3D Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3d-dual-stream-selective-state-spaces-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing neural implicit 3D representation methods face significant difficulties in balancing the extraction of global and local features, particularly in diverse and complex environments, leading to insufficient reconstruction precision and quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3d-dual-stream-selective-state-spaces-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recall and Refine: A Simple but Effective Source-free Open-set Domain Adaptation Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recall-and-refine-a-simple-but-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-set Domain Adaptation (OSDA) aims to adapt a model from a labeled source domain to an unlabeled target domain, where novel classes - also referred to as target-private unknown classes - are present.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recall-and-refine-a-simple-but-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Prompt Steerability of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-prompt-steerability-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Achieving this requires first being able to evaluate the degree to which a given model is capable of reflecting various personas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-prompt-steerability-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised denoising of visual field data improves detection of glaucoma progression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-denoising-of-visual-field</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This denoising model can be integrated into future models for visual field analysis to enhance detection of glaucoma progression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-denoising-of-visual-field</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Action-Attentive Deep Reinforcement Learning for Autonomous Alignment of Beamlines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/action-attentive-deep-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synchrotron radiation sources play a crucial role in fields such as materials science, biology, and chemistry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/action-attentive-deep-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invariant Shape Representation Learning For Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-shape-representation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel framework that for the first time develops invariant shape representation learning (ISRL) to further strengthen the robustness of image classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-shape-representation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A data driven approach to classify descriptors based on their efficiency in translating noisy trajectories into physically-relevant information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-driven-approach-to-classify</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, $d_5$, initially among the weakest, becomes the most effective at resolving the system's non-local dynamical complexity after denoising.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-driven-approach-to-classify</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contourlet Refinement Gate Framework for Thermal Spectrum Distribution Regularized Infrared Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contourlet-refinement-gate-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we emphasize the infrared spectral distribution fidelity and propose a Contourlet refinement gate framework to restore infrared modal-specific features while preserving spectral distribution fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contourlet-refinement-gate-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoM: Efficient Image and Video Generation with the Polynomial Mixer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pom-efficient-image-and-video-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate this problem, we propose a drop-in replacement for MHA called the Polynomial Mixer (PoM) that has the benefit of encoding the entire sequence into an explicit state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pom-efficient-image-and-video-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motif Channel Opened in a White-Box: Stereo Matching via Motif Correlation Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motif-channel-opened-in-a-white-box-stereo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, learning-based stereo matching methods inherently suffer from the loss of geometric structures in certain feature channels, creating a bottleneck in achieving precise detail matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motif-channel-opened-in-a-white-box-stereo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-Inspired Cold Start with Sufficient Prior in Computerized Adaptive Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-inspired-cold-start-with-sufficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Redundant and extraneous cognitive states can lead to limited transfer and negative transfer effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-inspired-cold-start-with-sufficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrast Similarity-Aware Dual-Pathway Mamba for Multivariate Time Series Node Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrast-similarity-aware-dual-pathway-mamba</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, to obtain the dynamic similarity of each sample, we initially use temporal contrast learning module to acquire MTS representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrast-similarity-aware-dual-pathway-mamba</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barttender: An approachable &amp; interpretable way to compare medical imaging and non-imaging data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/barttender-an-approachable-interpretable-way</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce Barttender, an interpretable framework that uses deep learning for the direct comparison of the utility of imaging versus non-imaging tabular data for tasks like disease prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/barttender-an-approachable-interpretable-way</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-Guided Detector for SAR Airplanes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-guided-detector-for-sar-airplanes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main contributions of PGD include the physics-guided self-supervised learning, feature enhancement, and instance perception, denoted as PGSSL, PGFE, and PGIP, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-guided-detector-for-sar-airplanes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Grained Preference Enhanced Transformer for Multi-Behavior Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-grained-preference-enhanced-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, a novel multi-scale transformer architecture equipped with multi-grained user preference extraction is proposed to encode the interaction-aware sequential pattern enhanced by capturing temporal behavior-aware multi-grained preference .]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-grained-preference-enhanced-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UrbanDiT: A Foundation Model for Open-World Urban Spatio-Temporal Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/urbandit-a-foundation-model-for-open-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This allows the model to unify both multi-data and multi-task learning, and effectively support a wide range of spatio-temporal applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/urbandit-a-foundation-model-for-open-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACING: Actor-Critic for Instruction Learning in Black-Box Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acing-actor-critic-for-instruction-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The effectiveness of Large Language Models (LLMs) in solving tasks vastly depends on the quality of the instructions, which often require fine-tuning through extensive human effort.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acing-actor-critic-for-instruction-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyAWD: A Library for Generating Large Synthetic Datasets of Acoustic Wave Propagation with Devito</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyawd-a-library-for-generating-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Seismic data is often sparse and unevenly distributed due to the high costs and logistical challenges associated with deploying physical seismometers, limiting the application of Machine Learning (ML) in earthquake analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyawd-a-library-for-generating-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph as a feature: improving node classification with non-neural graph-aware logistic regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-as-a-feature-improving-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) and their message passing framework that leverages both structural and feature information, have become a standard method for solving graph-based machine learning problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-as-a-feature-improving-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CV-Cities: Advancing Cross-View Geo-Localization in Global Cities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cv-cities-advancing-cross-view-geo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-view geo-localization (CVGL), which involves matching and retrieving satellite images to determine the geographic location of a ground image, is crucial in GNSS-constrained scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cv-cities-advancing-cross-view-geo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PR-ENDO: Physically Based Relightable Gaussian Splatting for Endoscopy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pr-endo-physically-based-relightable-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Endoscopic procedures are crucial for colorectal cancer diagnosis, and three-dimensional reconstruction of the environment for real-time novel-view synthesis can significantly enhance diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pr-endo-physically-based-relightable-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DLBacktrace: A Model Agnostic Explainability for any Deep Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dlbacktrace-a-model-agnostic-explainability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of artificial intelligence has led to increasingly sophisticated deep learning models, which frequently operate as opaque 'black boxes' with limited transparency in their decision-making processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dlbacktrace-a-model-agnostic-explainability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>libcll: an Extendable Python Toolkit for Complementary-Label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/libcll-an-extendable-python-toolkit-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Complementary-label learning (CLL) is a weakly supervised learning paradigm for multiclass classification, where only complementary labels -- indicating classes an instance does not belong to -- are provided to the learning algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/libcll-an-extendable-python-toolkit-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Positional Encodings for GNNs and Graph Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-positional-encodings-for-gnns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) and Graph Transformers (GTs) have been driven by innovations in architectures and Positional Encodings (PEs), which are critical for augmenting node features and capturing graph topology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-positional-encodings-for-gnns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM Carries the Burden: A Semi-Supervised Approach Refining Pseudo Labels for Medical Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-carries-the-burden-a-semi-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our work, we leverage SAM's abstract object understanding for medical image segmentation to provide pseudo labels for semi-supervised learning, thereby mitigating the need for extensive annotated training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-carries-the-burden-a-semi-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NMT-Obfuscator Attack: Ignore a sentence in translation with only one word</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nmt-obfuscator-attack-ignore-a-sentence-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new type of adversarial attack against NMT models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nmt-obfuscator-attack-ignore-a-sentence-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Leaf It: Accelerating Diffusion Classifiers with Hierarchical Class Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/just-leaf-it-accelerating-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models, known for their generative capabilities, have recently shown unexpected potential in image classification tasks by using Bayes' theorem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/just-leaf-it-accelerating-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifted Model Construction without Normalisation: A Vectorised Approach to Exploit Symmetries in Factor Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifted-model-construction-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lifted probabilistic inference exploits symmetries in a probabilistic model to allow for tractable probabilistic inference with respect to domain sizes of logical variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifted-model-construction-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSPRank: Bridging Pairwise and Listwise Methods with a Bilinear Travelling Salesman Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsprank-bridging-pairwise-and-listwise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TSPRank reframes the ranking problem as a Travelling Salesman Problem (TSP), a well-known combinatorial optimisation challenge that has been extensively studied for its numerous solution algorithms and applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsprank-bridging-pairwise-and-listwise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITACLIP: Boosting Training-Free Semantic Segmentation with Image, Text, and Architectural Enhancements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/itaclip-boosting-training-free-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in foundational Vision Language Models (VLMs) have reshaped the evaluation paradigm in computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/itaclip-boosting-training-free-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Geometric-Physical-Driven Robot Manipulation Skill Transfer via Skill Library and Tactile Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-geometric-physical-driven-robot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The framework hierarchically organizes operational knowledge by constructing a "task graph" and a "scene graph" to represent task and scene semantic information, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-geometric-physical-driven-robot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Artificial Intelligence for Quantifying Compatibility Mechanisms in Traditional Chinese Medicine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-artificial-intelligence-for-quantifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional Chinese Medicine (TCM) involves complex compatibility mechanisms characterized by multi-component and multi-target interactions, which are challenging to quantify.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-artificial-intelligence-for-quantifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuvis.Ai: An Open-Source, Low-Code Software Ecosystem for Hyperspectral Processing and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuvis-ai-an-open-source-low-code-software</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning is an important tool for analyzing high-dimension hyperspectral data; however, existing software solutions are either closed-source or inextensible research products.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuvis-ai-an-open-source-low-code-software</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preempting Text Sanitization Utility in Resource-Constrained Privacy-Preserving LLM Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preempting-text-sanitization-utility-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Individuals have been increasingly interacting with online Large Language Models (LLMs), both in their work and personal lives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preempting-text-sanitization-utility-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Unlearning Truly Unlearn? A Black Box Evaluation of LLM Unlearning Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-unlearning-truly-unlearn-a-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language model unlearning aims to remove harmful information that LLMs have learnt to prevent their use for malicious purposes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-unlearning-truly-unlearn-a-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual-Semantic Graph Matching Net for Zero-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-semantic-graph-matching-net-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, methods trained under this paradigm often struggle to learn robust embedding space because they align the two modalities in an isolated manner among classes, which ignore the crucial class relationship during the alignment process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-semantic-graph-matching-net-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoomed In, Diffused Out: Towards Local Degradation-Aware Multi-Diffusion for Extreme Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zoomed-in-diffused-out-towards-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale, pre-trained Text-to-Image (T2I) diffusion models have gained significant popularity in image generation tasks and have shown unexpected potential in image Super-Resolution (SR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zoomed-in-diffused-out-towards-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syllabus: Portable Curricula for Reinforcement Learning Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syllabus-portable-curricula-for-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Syllabus provides a universal API for curriculum learning algorithms, implementations of popular curriculum learning methods, and infrastructure for easily integrating them with distributed training code written in nearly any RL library.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syllabus-portable-curricula-for-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking pre-trained text embedding models in aligning built asset information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-pre-trained-text-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate mapping of the built asset information to established data classification systems and taxonomies is crucial for effective asset management, whether for compliance at project handover or ad-hoc data integration scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-pre-trained-text-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moral Persuasion in Large Language Models: Evaluating Susceptibility and Ethical Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moral-persuasion-in-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore how large language models (LLMs) can be influenced by prompting them to alter their initial decisions and align them with established ethical frameworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moral-persuasion-in-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACE2: Accurately learning subseasonal to decadal atmospheric variability and forced responses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ace2-accurately-learning-subseasonal-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing machine learning models of weather variability are not formulated to enable assessment of their response to varying external boundary conditions such as sea surface temperature and greenhouse gases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ace2-accurately-learning-subseasonal-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variable Rate Neural Compression for Sparse Detector Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-rate-neural-compression-for-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, emerging deep learning-based models, particularly those utilizing convolutional neural networks for compression, have outperformed these conventional methods in terms of compression ratios and reconstruction accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-rate-neural-compression-for-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advacheck at GenAI Detection Task 1: AI Detection Powered by Domain-Aware Multi-Tasking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advacheck-at-genai-detection-task-1-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper describes a system designed by Advacheck team to recognise machine-generated and human-written texts in the monolingual subtask of GenAI Detection Task 1 competition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advacheck-at-genai-detection-task-1-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Few-Step Diffusion Models with Dense Reward Difference Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-few-step-diffusion-models-with-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results demonstrate that SDPO consistently outperforms prior methods in reward-based alignment across diverse step configurations, underscoring its robust step generalization capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-few-step-diffusion-models-with-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMURAI: Adapting Segment Anything Model for Zero-Shot Visual Tracking with Motion-Aware Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samurai-adapting-segment-anything-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Segment Anything Model 2 (SAM 2) has demonstrated strong performance in object segmentation tasks but faces challenges in visual object tracking, particularly when managing crowded scenes with fast-moving or self-occluding objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samurai-adapting-segment-anything-model-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
