<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 21:06:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SQLdepth: Generalizable Self-Supervised Fine-Structured Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sqldepth-generalizable-self-supervised-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Each individual slice of the volume signifies the relative distances between points and objects within a latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sqldepth-generalizable-self-supervised-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patent image retrieval using transformer-based deep metric learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patent-image-retrieval-using-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intellectual property work covers a wide range of areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patent-image-retrieval-using-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenIns3D: Snap and Lookup for 3D Open-vocabulary Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openins3d-snap-and-lookup-for-3d-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The "Snap" module generates synthetic scene-level images at multiple scales and leverages 2D vision language models to extract interesting objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openins3d-snap-and-lookup-for-3d-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusing Monocular Images and Sparse IMU Signals for Real-time Human Motion Capture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusing-monocular-images-and-sparse-imu</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe that the combination is complementary and able to solve the inherent difficulties of using one modality input, including occlusions, extreme lighting/texture, and out-of-view for visual mocap and global drifts for inertial mocap.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusing-monocular-images-and-sparse-imu</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Theoretical and Practical Framework for Evaluating Uncertainty Calibration in Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-theoretical-and-practical-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proliferation of Deep Neural Networks has resulted in machine learning systems becoming increasingly more present in various real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-theoretical-and-practical-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Text-based Approach For Link Prediction on Wikipedia Articles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-text-based-approach-for-link-prediction-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper present our work in the DSAA 2023 Challenge about Link Prediction for Wikipedia Articles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-text-based-approach-for-link-prediction-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Active Learning for Preference Elicitation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-active-learning-for-preference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We implement the proposed preference elicitation methodology for food recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-active-learning-for-preference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple transformation function estimation for image enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-transformation-function-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we develop a histogram-based multiple transformation function estimation network (HMTF-Net) to estimate multiple transformation functions by exploiting both the spatial and statistical information of the input images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-transformation-function-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffuGen: Adaptable Approach for Generating Labeled Image Datasets using Stable Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffugen-adaptable-approach-for-generating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating high-quality labeled image datasets is crucial for training accurate and robust machine learning models in the field of computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffugen-adaptable-approach-for-generating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-Inspired Facial Sketch Synthesis with Dynamic Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-inspired-facial-sketch-synthesis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, different artists may use diverse drawing techniques and create multiple styles of sketches; but the style is globally consistent in a sketch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-inspired-facial-sketch-synthesis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SparseSat-NeRF: Dense Depth Supervised Neural Radiance Fields for Sparse Satellite Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsesat-nerf-dense-depth-supervised-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, NeRF and its variants require many views to produce convincing scene's geometries which in earth observation satellite imaging is rare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsesat-nerf-dense-depth-supervised-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrete Morphological Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-morphological-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A DMNN architecture, which is represented by a Morphological Computational Graph, is designed as in the classical heuristic design of morphological operators, in which the designer should combine a set of MM operators and Boolean operations based on prior information and theoretical knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-morphological-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuroSurgeon: A Toolkit for Subnetwork Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurosurgeon-a-toolkit-for-subnetwork</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advances in the field of explainability, much remains unknown about the algorithms that neural networks learn to represent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurosurgeon-a-toolkit-for-subnetwork</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly Shareable Clinical Large Language Model Built on Synthetic Clinical Notes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/publicly-shareable-clinical-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of large language models tailored for handling patients' clinical notes is often hindered by the limited accessibility and usability of these notes due to strict privacy regulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/publicly-shareable-clinical-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Locality-based Neural Solver for Optical Motion Capture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-locality-based-neural-solver-for-optical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we propose a training regime based on representation learning and data augmentation, by training the model on data with masking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-locality-based-neural-solver-for-optical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FederatedScope-LLM: A Comprehensive Package for Fine-tuning Large Language Models in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federatedscope-llm-a-comprehensive-package</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When several entities have similar interested tasks, but their data cannot be shared because of privacy concerns regulations, federated learning (FL) is a mainstream solution to leverage the data of different entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federatedscope-llm-a-comprehensive-package</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeMig -- A Bilingual News Collection and Knowledge Graph about Migration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nemig-a-bilingual-news-collection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[News recommendation plays a critical role in shaping the public's worldviews through the way in which it filters and disseminates information about different topics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nemig-a-bilingual-news-collection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-fidelity reduced-order surrogate modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-fidelity-reduced-order-surrogate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-fidelity numerical simulations of partial differential equations (PDEs) given a restricted computational budget can significantly limit the number of parameter configurations considered and/or time window evaluated for modeling a given system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-fidelity-reduced-order-surrogate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JoTR: A Joint Transformer and Reinforcement Learning Framework for Dialog Policy Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jotr-a-joint-transformer-and-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, JoTR employs reinforcement learning with a reward-shaping mechanism to efficiently finetune the word-level dialogue policy, which allows the model to learn from its interactions, improving its performance over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jotr-a-joint-transformer-and-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copiloting the Copilots: Fusing Large Language Models with Completion Engines for Automated Program Repair</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copiloting-the-copilots-fusing-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose Repilot, a framework to further copilot the AI "copilots" (i. e., LLMs) by synthesizing more valid patches during the repair process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copiloting-the-copilots-fusing-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretation of High-Dimensional Linear Regression: Effects of Nullspace and Regularization Demonstrated on Battery Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretation-of-high-dimensional-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We developed an optimization formulation to compare regression coefficients and coefficients obtained by physical engineering knowledge to understand which part of the coefficient differences are close to the nullspace.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretation-of-high-dimensional-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mechanism of feature learning in convolutional neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mechanism-of-feature-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then demonstrate the generality of our result by using the patch-based AGOP to enable deep feature learning in convolutional kernel machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mechanism-of-feature-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General and Practical Tuning Method for Off-the-Shelf Graph-Based Index: SISAP Indexing Challenge Report by Team UTokyo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-and-practical-tuning-method-for-off</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the efficacy of graph-based algorithms for Approximate Nearest Neighbor (ANN) searches, the optimal tuning of such systems remains unclear.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-and-practical-tuning-method-for-off</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning-based NLOS Detection and Uncertainty Prediction of GNSS Observations with Transformer-Enhanced LSTM Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-nlos-detection-and-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes a Deep-Learning-based method to detect NLOS receptions and predict GNSS pseudorange errors by analyzing GNSS observations as a spatio-temporal modeling problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-nlos-detection-and-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-Bind &amp; Point-LLM: Aligning Point Cloud with Multi-modality for 3D Understanding, Generation, and Instruction Following</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-bind-point-llm-aligning-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Point-Bind, a 3D multi-modality model aligning point clouds with 2D image, language, audio, and video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-bind-point-llm-aligning-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Declarative Reasoning on Explanations Using Constraint Logic Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/declarative-reasoning-on-explanations-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Explaining opaque Machine Learning (ML) models is an increasingly relevant problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/declarative-reasoning-on-explanations-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Programming Languages Boost Each Other via Instruction Tuning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-programming-languages-boost-each-other</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results demonstrate that programming languages can significantly improve each other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-programming-languages-boost-each-other</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Variable Multi-output Gaussian Processes for Hierarchical Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-variable-multi-output-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-output Gaussian processes (MOGPs) have been introduced to deal with multiple tasks by exploiting the correlations between different outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-variable-multi-output-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Gender-GAP Pipeline: A Gender-Aware Polyglot Pipeline for Gender Characterisation in 55 Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-gender-gap-pipeline-a-gender-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We showcase it to report gender representation in WMT training data and development data for the News task, confirming that current data is skewed towards masculine representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-gender-gap-pipeline-a-gender-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Link Prediction for Wikipedia Articles as a Natural Language Inference Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-prediction-for-wikipedia-articles-as-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Drawing inspiration from recent advancements in natural language processing and understanding, we cast link prediction as an NLI task, wherein the presence of a link between two articles is treated as a premise, and the task is to determine whether this premise holds based on the information presented in the articles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-prediction-for-wikipedia-articles-as-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficacy of Neural Prediction-Based NAS for Zero-Shot NAS Paradigm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficacy-of-neural-prediction-based-nas-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, handcrafted performance indicators (zero-shot NAS), which use the same architecture with random initialization, can generalize across multiple search spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficacy-of-neural-prediction-based-nas-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curvature-based Pooling within Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvature-based-pooling-within-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CurvPool exploits the notion of curvature of a graph to adaptively identify structures responsible for both over-smoothing and over-squashing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvature-based-pooling-within-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointOcc: Cylindrical Tri-Perspective View for Point-based 3D Semantic Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointocc-cylindrical-tri-perspective-view-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose a cylindrical tri-perspective view to represent point clouds effectively and comprehensively and a PointOcc model to process them efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointocc-cylindrical-tri-perspective-view-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BenchTemp: A General Benchmark for Evaluating Temporal Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchtemp-a-general-benchmark-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To handle graphs in which features or connectivities are evolving over time, a series of temporal graph neural networks (TGNNs) have been proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchtemp-a-general-benchmark-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointLLM: Empowering Large Language Models to Understand Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointllm-empowering-large-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The unprecedented advancements in Large Language Models (LLMs) have created a profound impact on natural language processing but are yet to fully embrace the realm of 3D understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointllm-empowering-large-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BioCoder: A Benchmark for Bioinformatics Code Generation with Contextual Pragmatic Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biocoder-a-benchmark-for-bioinformatics-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BioCoder incorporates a fuzz-testing framework for evaluation, and we have applied it to evaluate many models including InCoder, CodeGen, CodeGen2, SantaCoder, StarCoder, StarCoder+, InstructCodeT5+, and ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biocoder-a-benchmark-for-bioinformatics-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple LLM Prompting is State-of-the-Art for Robust and Multilingual Dialogue Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-llm-prompting-is-state-of-the-art-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant research effort in the development of automatic dialogue evaluation metrics, little thought is given to evaluating dialogues other than in English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-llm-prompting-is-state-of-the-art-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoMA: Momentum Contrastive Learning with Multi-head Attention-based Knowledge Distillation for Histopathology Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moma-momentum-contrastive-learning-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we employ a student-teacher framework to learn a target model from a pre-trained, teacher model without direct access to source data and distill relevant knowledge via momentum contrastive learning with multi-head attention mechanism, which provides consistent and context-aware feature representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moma-momentum-contrastive-learning-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate Your Own Scotland: Satellite Image Generation Conditioned on Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generate-your-own-scotland-satellite-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advancements in image generation, diffusion models still remain largely underexplored in Earth Observation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generate-your-own-scotland-satellite-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScrollNet: Dynamic Weight Importance for Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scrollnet-dynamic-weight-importance-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The importance of weights for each task can be determined either explicitly through learning a task-specific mask during training (e. g., parameter isolation-based approaches) or implicitly by introducing a regularization term (e. g., regularization-based approaches).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scrollnet-dynamic-weight-importance-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Optimal Patch Size in Vision Transformers for Tumor Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-optimal-patch-size-in-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although transformers can capture long-range features, their segmentation performance decreases with various tumor sizes due to the model sensitivity to the input patch size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-optimal-patch-size-in-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illumination Distillation Framework for Nighttime Person Re-Identification and A New Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illumination-distillation-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The illumination enhancement branch first estimates an enhanced image from the nighttime image using a nonlinear curve mapping method and then extracts the enhanced features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illumination-distillation-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Lens Flare Removal with General Purpose Pipeline and Multiple Light Sources Recovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-lens-flare-removal-with-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a solution to improve the performance of lens flare removal by revisiting the ISP and remodeling the principle of automatic exposure in the synthesis pipeline and design a more reliable light sources recovery strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-lens-flare-removal-with-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Gradient Regularizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-gradient-regularizer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NGR is applicable to various image types and different image processing tasks, functioning in a zero-shot learning fashion, making it a versatile and plug-and-play regularizer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-gradient-regularizer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D-STMN: Dependency-Driven Superpoint-Text Matching Network for End-to-End 3D Referring Expression Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-stmn-dependency-driven-superpoint-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In 3D Referring Expression Segmentation (3D-RES), the earlier approach adopts a two-stage paradigm, extracting segmentation proposals and then matching them with referring expressions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-stmn-dependency-driven-superpoint-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised CT Metal Artifact Reduction by Plugging Diffusion Priors in Dual Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-ct-metal-artifact-reduction-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an unsupervised MAR method based on the diffusion model, a generative model with a high capacity to represent data distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-ct-metal-artifact-reduction-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpeechTokenizer: Unified Speech Tokenizer for Speech Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechtokenizer-unified-speech-tokenizer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose SpeechTokenizer, a unified speech tokenizer for speech large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechtokenizer-unified-speech-tokenizer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleInV: A Temporal Style Modulated Inversion Network for Unconditional Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styleinv-a-temporal-style-modulated-inversion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel motion generator design that uses a learning-based inversion network for GAN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styleinv-a-temporal-style-modulated-inversion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpreting Sentiment Composition with Latent Semantic Tree</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-sentiment-composition-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the key to sentiment analysis, sentiment composition considers the classification of a constituent via classifications of its contained sub-constituents and rules operated on them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-sentiment-composition-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-pruning Graph Neural Network for Predicting Inflammatory Disease Activity in Multiple Sclerosis from Brain MR Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-pruning-graph-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a two-stage MS inflammatory disease activity prediction approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-pruning-graph-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
