<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 09:14:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Training with Pseudo-Label Scorer for Aspect Sentiment Quad Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-training-with-pseudo-label-scorer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aspect Sentiment Quad Prediction (ASQP) aims to predict all quads (aspect term, aspect category, opinion term, sentiment polarity) for a given review, which is the most representative and challenging task in aspect-based sentiment analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-training-with-pseudo-label-scorer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Classification of Time Series: Taxonomy and Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-classification-of-time-series-taxonomy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many situations, the measurements of a studied phenomenon are provided sequentially, and the prediction of its class needs to be made as early as possible so as not to incur too high a time penalty, but not too early and risk paying the cost of misclassification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-classification-of-time-series-taxonomy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining Automated Optimisation of Hyperparameters and Reward Shape</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-automated-optimisation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then propose a methodology for the combined optimisation of hyperparameters and the reward function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-automated-optimisation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S3: A Simple Strong Sample-effective Multimodal Dialog System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s3-a-simple-strong-sample-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a conceptually simple yet powerful baseline for the multimodal dialog task, an S3 model, that achieves near state-of-the-art results on two compelling leaderboards: MMMU and AI Journey Contest 2023.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s3-a-simple-strong-sample-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EmT: A Novel Transformer for Generalized Cross-subject EEG Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emt-a-novel-transformer-for-generalized-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we design a temporal contextual transformer module (TCT) with two types of token mixers to learn the temporal contextual information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emt-a-novel-transformer-for-generalized-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weak Reward Model Transforms Generative Models into Robust Causal Event Extraction Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weak-reward-model-transforms-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The inherent ambiguity of cause and effect boundaries poses a challenge in evaluating causal event extraction tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weak-reward-model-transforms-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ArzEn-LLM: Code-Switched Egyptian Arabic-English Translation and Speech Recognition Using LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arzen-llm-code-switched-egyptian-arabic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our models and code are available as open-source resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arzen-llm-code-switched-egyptian-arabic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Soft Q-Learning by Bounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-soft-q-learning-by-bounding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An agent's ability to leverage past experience is critical for efficiently solving new tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-soft-q-learning-by-bounding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Surprising Effectiveness of Multimodal Large Language Models for Video Moment Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-surprising-effectiveness-of-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We achieve a new state-of-the-art in moment retrieval on the widely used benchmarks Charades-STA, QVHighlights, and ActivityNet Captions and illustrate our method's versatility with a new state-of-the-art in temporal action localization on ActivityNet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-surprising-effectiveness-of-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Compositionality in Concept Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-compositionality-in-concept-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To automatically discover compositional concept representations, we identify two salient properties of such representations, and propose Compositional Concept Extraction (CCE) for finding concepts which obey these properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-compositionality-in-concept-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective Prompting Tuning for Personalized Conversations with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-prompting-tuning-for-personalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate those issues, we propose \textbf{S}elective \textbf{P}rompt \textbf{T}uning (SPT), which softly prompts LLMs for personalized conversations in a selective way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-prompting-tuning-for-personalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming Data and Transformers for Audio Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-data-and-transformers-for-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating ambient sounds and effects is a challenging problem due to data scarcity and often insufficient caption quality, making it difficult to employ large-scale generative models for the task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-data-and-transformers-for-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Context Pruning: Optimizing Real-World Code Completion with Repository-Level Pretrained Code LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-context-pruning-optimizing-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We applied the HCP strategy in experiments with six Repo-Code LLMs, and the results demonstrate that our proposed method can significantly enhance completion accuracy while substantially reducing the length of input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-context-pruning-optimizing-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Brittle Decisions for Free: Leveraging Margin Consistency in Deep Robust Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-brittle-decisions-for-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we establish that margin consistency is a necessary and sufficient condition to use a model's logit margin as a score for identifying non-robust samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-brittle-decisions-for-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look into Mixture-of-Experts in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-into-mixture-of-experts-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mixture-of-experts (MoE) is gaining increasing attention due to its unique properties and remarkable performance, especially for language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-into-mixture-of-experts-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Diffusion Segmentation for Biomedical Images with Single-step Reverse Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-diffusion-segmentation-for-biomedical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have demonstrated their effectiveness across various generative tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-diffusion-segmentation-for-biomedical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Unknown: Conditional Evidence Decoupling for Unknown Rejection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-unknown-conditional-evidence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate this issue, we develop a novel open-set object detection framework, which delves into conditional evidence decoupling for the unknown rejection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-unknown-conditional-evidence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Scaling Up 3D Gaussian Splatting Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-scaling-up-3d-gaussian-splatting-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluations using large-scale, high-resolution scenes show that Grendel enhances rendering quality by scaling up 3DGS parameters across multiple GPUs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-scaling-up-3d-gaussian-splatting-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BADGE: BADminton report Generation and Evaluation with LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badge-badminton-report-generation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Following report generation, the LLM evaluates and scores the reports to assess their quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badge-badminton-report-generation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy spectroscopy without spectra: Galaxy properties from photometric images with conditional diffusion models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galaxy-spectroscopy-without-spectra-galaxy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we report the development of a generative AI method capable of predicting optical galaxy spectra from photometric broad-band images alone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galaxy-spectroscopy-without-spectra-galaxy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaZeta: Adaptive Zeroth-Order Tensor-Train Adaption for Memory-Efficient Large Language Models Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adazeta-adaptive-zeroth-order-tensor-train</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the Adaptive Zeroth-order Tensor-Train Adaption (AdaZeta) framework, specifically designed to improve the performance and convergence of the ZO methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adazeta-adaptive-zeroth-order-tensor-train</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniRec: A Dual Enhancement of Uniformity and Frequency in Sequential Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unirec-a-dual-enhancement-of-uniformity-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[UniRec leverages sequence uniformity and item frequency to enhance performance, particularly improving the representation of non-uniform sequences and less-frequent items.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unirec-a-dual-enhancement-of-uniformity-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial-temporal Hierarchical Reinforcement Learning for Interpretable Pathology Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-temporal-hierarchical-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the higher-level spatial manager is proposed to pick out the most corrupted patch for the lower-level patch worker.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-temporal-hierarchical-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symbolic Learning Enables Self-Evolving Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-learning-enables-self-evolving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce agent symbolic learning, a systematic framework that enables language agents to optimize themselves on their own in a data-centric way using symbolic optimizers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-learning-enables-self-evolving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start from Zero: Triple Set Prediction for Automatic Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/start-from-zero-triple-set-prediction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel graph-level automatic KG completion task called Triple Set Prediction (TSP) which assumes none of the elements in the missing triples is given.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/start-from-zero-triple-set-prediction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Barrier: Enhanced Utility and Robustness in Smoothed DRL Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-barrier-enhanced-utility-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, a notable gap exists in the performance of current smoothed DRL agents, often characterized by significantly low clean rewards and weak robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-barrier-enhanced-utility-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Human-Level 3D Relative Pose Estimation: Generalizable, Training-Free, with Single Reference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-human-level-3d-relative-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, we propose a novel 3D generalizable relative pose estimation method by elaborating (i) with a 2. 5D shape from an RGB-D reference, (ii) with an off-the-shelf differentiable renderer, and (iii) with semantic cues from a pretrained model like DINOv2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-human-level-3d-relative-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expressive Keypoints for Skeleton-based Action Recognition via Skeleton Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressive-keypoints-for-skeleton-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of skeleton-based action recognition, the traditional methods which rely on coarse body keypoints fall short of capturing subtle human actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressive-keypoints-for-skeleton-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidirectional-Reachable Hierarchical Reinforcement Learning with Mutually Responsive Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-reachable-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hierarchical reinforcement learning (HRL) addresses complex long-horizon tasks by skillfully decomposing them into subgoals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-reachable-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising as Adaptation: Noise-Space Domain Adaptation for Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-as-adaptation-noise-space-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results on three classical image restoration tasks, namely denoising, deblurring, and deraining, demonstrate the effectiveness of the proposed method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-as-adaptation-noise-space-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Image Segmentation Using Directional Window Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-image-segmentation-using-directional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The focus of our design is the introduction of Dwin block within DwinFormer that effectively captures local and global information along the horizontal, vertical, and depthwise directions of the input feature map by separately performing attention in each of these directional volumes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-image-segmentation-using-directional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grass: Compute Efficient Low-Memory LLM Training with Structured Sparse Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grass-compute-efficient-low-memory-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language model (LLM) training and finetuning are often bottlenecked by limited GPU memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grass-compute-efficient-low-memory-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaLMQA: Exploring culturally specific long-form question answering across 23 languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calmqa-exploring-culturally-specific-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are commonly used for long-form question answering, which requires them to generate paragraph-length answers to complex questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calmqa-exploring-culturally-specific-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models are Interpretable Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the proposed LLM-based Symbolic Programs (LSPs), the pretrained LLM with natural language prompts provides a massive set of interpretable modules that can transform raw input into natural language concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the Big Five Personality Traits in Chinese Counselling Dialogues Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-big-five-personality-traits-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study exams whether Large Language Models (LLMs) can predict the Big Five personality traits directly from counseling dialogues and introduces an innovative framework to perform the task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-big-five-personality-traits-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LumberChunker: Long-Form Narrative Document Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lumberchunker-long-form-narrative-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern NLP tasks increasingly rely on dense retrieval methods to access up-to-date and relevant contextual information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lumberchunker-long-form-narrative-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask-Guided Attention U-Net for Enhanced Neonatal Brain Extraction and Image Preprocessing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-guided-attention-u-net-for-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The network employs a common encoder and two decoders: one for brain mask extraction and the other for brain region reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-guided-attention-u-net-for-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Recursive Encoding for Cuneiform Signs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-recursive-encoding-for-cuneiform-signs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the most significant problems in cuneiform pedagogy is the process of looking up unknown signs, which often involves a tedious page-by-page search through a sign list.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-recursive-encoding-for-cuneiform-signs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Universal Medical Image Registration via Sharpness-Aware Meta-Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-universal-medical-image-registration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current deep learning approaches in medical image registration usually face the challenges of distribution shift and data collection, hindering real-world deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-universal-medical-image-registration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Cross-Task Interaction for Survival Analysis in Whole Slide Pathological Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-cross-task-interaction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the joint representation of pathological images and genomic data, we further introduce a Transport-Guided Attention (TGA) module that uses optimal transport theory to model the correlation between subtype classification and survival analysis tasks, effectively transferring potential information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-cross-task-interaction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRIP: Trainable Region-of-Interest Prediction for Hardware-Efficient Neuromorphic Processing on Event-based Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trip-trainable-region-of-interest-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduced extensive hardware-aware optimizations for TRIP and implemented the hardware-optimized algorithm on the SENECA neuromorphic processor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trip-trainable-region-of-interest-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MG-LLaVA: Towards Multi-Granularity Visual Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mg-llava-towards-multi-granularity-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the integration of an additional high-resolution visual encoder to capture fine-grained details, which are then fused with base visual features through a Conv-Gate fusion network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mg-llava-towards-multi-granularity-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Admission Control and Resource Allocation of Virtual Network Embedding via Hierarchical Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-admission-control-and-resource</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the whole VNE process is decomposed into an upper-level policy for deciding whether to admit the arriving VNR or not and a lower-level policy for allocating resources of the physical network to meet the requirement of VNR through the HRL approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-admission-control-and-resource</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimsChat: A Customisable Persona-Driven Role-Playing Agent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simschat-a-customisable-persona-driven-role</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce the Customisable Conversation Agent Framework, which employs LLMs to simulate real-world characters that can be freely customised according to different user preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simschat-a-customisable-persona-driven-role</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Programming Language and Natural Language: Exploring Design Choices in Multi-Modal Transformer-Based Embedding for Bug Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-programming-language-and-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bug localization refers to the identification of source code files which is in a programming language and also responsible for the unexpected behavior of software using the bug report, which is a natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-programming-language-and-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Distributional to Overton Pluralism: Investigating Large Language Model Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-distributional-to-overton-pluralism</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Alignment suppresses irrelevant and unhelpful content while shifting the output distribution toward longer responses that cover information spanning several responses from the base LLM, essentially presenting diverse information in a single response.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-distributional-to-overton-pluralism</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Space Knowledge Distillation for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-space-knowledge-distillation-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, this discrepancy also hinders the KD process between models with different vocabularies, which is common for current LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-space-knowledge-distillation-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-SAM: Promptable 3D Segmentation Model for Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-sam-promptable-3d-segmentation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of 2D foundation models for image segmentation has been significantly advanced by the Segment Anything Model (SAM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-sam-promptable-3d-segmentation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic speech recognition for the Nepali language using CNN, bidirectional LSTM and ResNet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-speech-recognition-for-the-nepali</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an end-to-end deep learning model for Automatic Speech Recognition (ASR) that transcribes Nepali speech to text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-speech-recognition-for-the-nepali</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XAMI -- A Benchmark Dataset for Artefact Detection in XMM-Newton Optical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xami-a-benchmark-dataset-for-artefact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hand-annotated a sample of 1000 images with artefacts which we use to train automated ML methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xami-a-benchmark-dataset-for-artefact</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
