<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 09:14:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing social media with crowdsourcing in Crowd4SDG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-social-media-with-crowdsourcing-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, finding relevant information among millions of posts being posted every day can be difficult, and developing a data analysis project usually requires time and technical skills.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-social-media-with-crowdsourcing-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformers as Meta-Learners for Implicit Neural Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-as-meta-learners-for-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by a generalized formulation of gradient-based meta-learning, we propose a formulation that uses Transformers as hypernetworks for INRs, where it can directly build the whole set of INR weights with Transformers specialized as set-to-set mapping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-as-meta-learners-for-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constructing Balance from Imbalance for Long-tailed Image Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-balance-from-imbalance-for-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous methods tackle with data imbalance from the viewpoints of data distribution, feature space, and model design, etc. In this work, instead of directly learning a recognition model, we suggest confronting the bottleneck of head-to-tail bias before classifier learning, from the previously omitted perspective of balancing label space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-balance-from-imbalance-for-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact Makes a Sound and Sound Makes an Impact: Sound Guides Representations and Explorations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-makes-a-sound-and-sound-makes-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sound is one of the most informative and abundant modalities in the real world while being robust to sense without contacts by small and cheap sensors that can be placed on mobile devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-makes-a-sound-and-sound-makes-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>N-best Response-based Analysis of Contradiction-awareness in Neural Response Generation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/n-best-response-based-analysis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this scenario, the quality of the n-best list considerably affects the occurrence of contradictions because the final response is chosen from this n-best list.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/n-best-response-based-analysis-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Data-Centric Properties for Contrastive Learning on Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-data-centric-properties-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, our work rigorously contextualizes, both empirically and theoretically, the effects of data-centric properties on augmentation strategies and learning paradigms for graph SSL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-data-centric-properties-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modular Grammatical Evolution for the Generation of Artificial Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modular-grammatical-evolution-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, the proposed representation mitigates two important drawbacks of GE, namely the low scalability and weak locality of representation, towards generating modular and multi-layer networks with a high number of neurons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modular-grammatical-evolution-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heart rate estimation in intense exercise videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heart-rate-estimation-in-intense-exercise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing work can robustly measure heart rate under some degree of motion by face tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heart-rate-estimation-in-intense-exercise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Interleaving Global Channel Attention for Multilabel Remote Sensing Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-interleaving-global-channel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, the label co-occurrence graph is obtained according to the statistical information of the data set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-interleaving-global-channel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo Kion-On: Query-Based Generative Sonification of Atmospheric Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokyo-kion-on-query-based-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Amid growing environmental concerns, interactive displays of data constitute an important tool for exploring and understanding the impact of climate change on the planet's ecosystemic integrity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokyo-kion-on-query-based-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domestic Activity Clustering from Audio via Depthwise Separable Convolutional Autoencoder Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domestic-activity-clustering-from-audio-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic estimation of domestic activities from audio can be used to solve many problems, such as reducing the labor cost for nursing the elderly people.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domestic-activity-clustering-from-audio-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-modal volumetric concept activation to explain detection and classification of metastatic prostate cancer on PSMA-PET/CT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-volumetric-concept-activation-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal volumetric concept activation was used to provide global and local explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-volumetric-concept-activation-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expanding Language-Image Pretrained Models for General Video Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expanding-language-image-pretrained-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate that our approach is effective and can be generalized to different video recognition scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expanding-language-image-pretrained-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UTOPIC: Uncertainty-aware Overlap Prediction Network for Partial Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utopic-uncertainty-aware-overlap-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Beyond the current wisdom, we propose a novel uncertainty-aware overlap prediction network, dubbed UTOPIC, to tackle the ambiguous overlap prediction problem; to our knowledge, this is the first to explicitly introduce overlap uncertainty to point cloud registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utopic-uncertainty-aware-overlap-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relict landslide detection in rainforest areas using a combination of k-means clustering algorithm and Deep-Learning semantic segmentation models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relict-landslide-detection-in-rainforest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A new CNN approach is proposed for semi-automatic detection of relict landslides, which uses a dataset generated by a k-means clustering algorithm and has a pre-training step.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relict-landslide-detection-in-rainforest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving Action Recognition via Motion Difference Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-action-recognition-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is followed by the Difference module to apply a pixel-wise intensity subtraction between consecutive frames to highlight motion features and suppress obvious high-level privacy attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-action-recognition-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGPIE: Machine Automated General Performance Improvement via Evolution of Software</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magpie-machine-automated-general-performance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that, used independently, all techniques find significant running time improvements: up to 25% for compiler optimisation, 97% for algorithm configuration, and 61% for evolving source code using genetic improvement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magpie-machine-automated-general-performance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformal Risk Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-risk-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extend conformal prediction to control the expected value of any monotone loss function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-risk-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Modal-Invariant and Temporal-Memory for Video-based Visible-Infrared Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-modal-invariant-and-temporal-memory-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our constructed dataset, we prove that with the increase of frames in a tracklet, the performance does meet more enhancement, demonstrating the significance of video-to-video matching in RGB-IR person Re-ID.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-modal-invariant-and-temporal-memory-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visually Evaluating Generative Adversarial Networks Using Itself under Multivariate Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visually-evaluating-generative-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visually evaluating the goodness of generated Multivariate Time Series (MTS) are difficult to implement, especially in the case that the generative model is Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visually-evaluating-generative-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Act-Aware Slot-Value Predicting in Multi-Domain Dialogue State Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/act-aware-slot-value-predicting-in-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As an essential component in task-oriented dialogue systems, dialogue state tracking (DST) aims to track human-machine interactions and generate state representations for managing the dialogue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/act-aware-slot-value-predicting-in-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Kind of Adversarial Example</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-kind-of-adversarial-example</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Almost all adversarial attacks are formulated to add an imperceptible perturbation to an image in order to fool a model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-kind-of-adversarial-example</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keyword Spotting System and Evaluation of Pruning and Quantization Methods on Low-power Edge Microcontrollers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/keyword-spotting-system-and-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The result also verified that the performance improvement for quantization and SIMD instruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/keyword-spotting-system-and-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolutionary bagged ensemble learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-bagged-ensemble-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In conventional bagged ensemble learning, the bags are created once and the content, in terms of the training examples, is fixed over the learning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-bagged-ensemble-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision-Centric BEV Perception: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-centric-bev-perception-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To stimulate its future research, this paper presents a comprehensive survey of recent progress of vision-centric BEV perception and its extensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-centric-bev-perception-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled Representation Learning for RF Fingerprint Extraction under Unknown Channel Statistics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-representation-learning-for-rf</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning (DL) applied to a device's radio-frequency fingerprint~(RFF) has attracted significant attention in physical-layer authentications due to its extraordinary classification performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-representation-learning-for-rf</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customs Import Declaration Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/customs-import-declaration-datasets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the huge volume of cross-border flows, effective and efficient control of trades becomes more crucial in protecting people and society from illicit trades while facilitating legitimate trades.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/customs-import-declaration-datasets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural network accelerator for quantum control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-accelerator-for-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficient quantum control is necessary for practical quantum computing implementations with current technologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-accelerator-for-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P2P: Tuning Pre-trained Image Models for Point Cloud Analysis with Point-to-Pixel Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p2p-tuning-pre-trained-image-models-for-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nowadays, pre-training big models on large-scale datasets has become a crucial topic in deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p2p-tuning-pre-trained-image-models-for-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusing Sentence Embeddings Into LSTM-based Autoregressive Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusing-sentence-embeddings-into-lstm-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an LSTM-based autoregressive language model which uses prefix embeddings (from a pretrained masked language model) via fusion (e. g. concatenation) to obtain a richer context representation for language modelling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusing-sentence-embeddings-into-lstm-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Tuning for Generative Multimodal Pretrained Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-tuning-for-generative-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompt tuning has become a new paradigm for model tuning and it has demonstrated success in natural language pretraining and even vision pretraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-tuning-for-generative-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Prior Feature and Attention Enhanced Image Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-prior-feature-and-attention-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, this paper incorporates the pre-training based Masked AutoEncoder (MAE) into the inpainting model, which enjoys richer informative priors to enhance the inpainting process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-prior-feature-and-attention-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiCu: Leveraging Hierarchy for Curriculum Learning in Automated ICD Coding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hicu-leveraging-hierarchy-for-curriculum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the challenges in curriculum learning is the design of curricula -- i. e., in the sequential design of tasks that gradually increase in difficulty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hicu-leveraging-hierarchy-for-curriculum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PalQuant: Accelerating High-precision Networks on Low-precision Accelerators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/palquant-accelerating-high-precision-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the PArallel Low-precision Quantization (PalQuant) method that approximates high-precision computations via learning parallel low-precision representations from scratch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/palquant-accelerating-high-precision-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLO-FaceV2: A Scale and Occlusion Aware Face Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo-facev2-a-scale-and-occlusion-aware-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a real-time face detector based on the one-stage detector YOLOv5, named YOLO-FaceV2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo-facev2-a-scale-and-occlusion-aware-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XCon: Learning with Experts for Fine-grained Category Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xcon-learning-with-experts-for-fine-grained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the problem of generalized category discovery (GCD) in this paper, i. e. clustering the unlabeled images leveraging the information from a set of seen classes, where the unlabeled images could contain both seen classes and unseen classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xcon-learning-with-experts-for-fine-grained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable bilinear attention network with domain adaptation improves drug-target prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-bilinear-attention-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent deep learning-based methods show promising performance but two challenges remain: (i) how to explicitly model and learn local interactions between drugs and targets for better prediction and interpretation; (ii) how to generalize prediction performance on novel drug-target pairs from different distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-bilinear-attention-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Per-Clip Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/per-clip-video-object-segmentation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this per-clip inference scheme, we update the memory with an interval and simultaneously process a set of consecutive frames (i. e. clip) between the memory updates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/per-clip-video-object-segmentation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Feature Vision Transformer via Self-Supervised Representation Learning for Improvement of COVID-19 Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-feature-vision-transformer-via-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the diagnostic performance of CXR imaging a growing number of studies have investigated whether supervised deep learning methods can provide additional support.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-feature-vision-transformer-via-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Lingual Knowledge Transfer for Clinical Phenotyping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-knowledge-transfer-for-clinical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clinical phenotyping enables the automatic extraction of clinical conditions from patient records, which can be beneficial to doctors and clinics worldwide.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-knowledge-transfer-for-clinical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image-based Detection of Surface Defects in Concrete during Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-based-detection-of-surface-defects-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Defects increase the cost and duration of construction projects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-based-detection-of-surface-defects-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Negative Frames Matter in Egocentric Visual Query 2D Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/negative-frames-matter-in-egocentric-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The repeated gradient computation of the same object lead to an inefficient training; (2) The false positive rate is high on background frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/negative-frames-matter-in-egocentric-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Feature-space Multimodal Data Augmentation Technique for Text-video Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-feature-space-multimodal-data-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data augmentation techniques were introduced to increase the performance on unseen test examples by creating new training samples with the application of semantics-preserving techniques, such as color space or geometric transformations on images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-feature-space-multimodal-data-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaCat: Adaptive Categorical Discretization for Autoregressive Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adacat-adaptive-categorical-discretization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoregressive generative models can estimate complex continuous data distributions, like trajectory rollouts in an RL environment, image intensities, and audio.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adacat-adaptive-categorical-discretization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RealPatch: A Statistical Matching Framework for Model Patching with Real Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realpatch-a-statistical-matching-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the effectiveness of RealPatch on three benchmark datasets, CelebA, Waterbirds and a subset of iWildCam, showing improvements in worst-case subgroup performance and in subgroup performance gap in binary classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realpatch-a-statistical-matching-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequence Model Imitation Learning with Unobserved Contexts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequence-model-imitation-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider imitation learning problems where the expert has access to a per-episode context that is hidden from the learner, both in the demonstrations and at test-time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequence-model-imitation-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperLine3D: Self-supervised Line Segmentation and Description for LiDAR Point Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superline3d-self-supervised-line-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To repetitively extract them as features and perform association between discrete LiDAR frames for registration, we propose the first learning-based feature segmentation and description model for 3D lines in LiDAR point cloud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superline3d-self-supervised-line-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EgPDE-Net: Building Continuous Neural Networks for Time Series Prediction with Exogenous Variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egpde-net-building-continuous-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While exogenous variables have a major impact on performance improvement in time series analysis, inter-series correlation and time dependence among them are rarely considered in the present continuous methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egpde-net-building-continuous-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Fine-Grained Classification with Self-Supervised Target Relation Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-fine-grained-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such target coding schemes are less flexible to model inter-class correlation and are sensitive to sparse and imbalanced data distribution as well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-fine-grained-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MinVIS: A Minimal Video Instance Segmentation Framework without Video-based Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minvis-a-minimal-video-instance-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By only training a query-based image instance segmentation model, MinVIS outperforms the previous best result on the challenging Occluded VIS dataset by over 10% AP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minvis-a-minimal-video-instance-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
