<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 09:11:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Detail Preservation for Customized Text-to-Image Generation: A Regularization-Free Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-detail-preservation-for-customized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, generating images of novel concept provided by the user input image is still a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-detail-preservation-for-customized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Learning to Summarize with Large Language Models as References</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-learning-to-summarize-with-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we investigate a new learning paradigm of text summarization models that considers the LLMs as the reference or the gold-standard oracle on commonly used summarization datasets such as the CNN/DailyMail dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-learning-to-summarize-with-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPEECH: Structured Prediction with Energy-Based Event-Centric Hyperspheres</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-structured-prediction-with-energy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event-centric structured prediction involves predicting structured outputs of events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-structured-prediction-with-energy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Focal Loss for Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-focal-loss-for-calibration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While different variants of focal loss have been explored, it is difficult to find a balance between over-confidence and under-confidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-focal-loss-for-calibration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models are Frame-level Directors for Zero-shot Text-to-Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-frame-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the paradigm of AI-generated content (AIGC), there has been increasing attention in extending pre-trained text-to-image (T2I) models to text-to-video (T2V) generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-frame-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Generate Novel Scientific Directions with Contextualized Literature-based Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generate-novel-scientific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Literature-Based Discovery (LBD) aims to discover new scientific knowledge by mining papers and generating hypotheses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generate-novel-scientific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covariate balancing using the integral probability metric for causal inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covariate-balancing-using-the-integral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the existing weighting methods have desirable theoretical properties only when a certain model, either the propensity score or outcome regression model, is correctly specified.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covariate-balancing-using-the-integral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Chat Language Models by Scaling High-quality Instructional Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-chat-language-models-by-scaling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning on instruction data has been widely validated as an effective practice for implementing chat language models like ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-chat-language-models-by-scaling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Model Selection with Large Language Models for Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-model-selection-with-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chain-of-Thought and Program-Aided Language Models represent two distinct reasoning methods, each with its own strengths and weaknesses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-model-selection-with-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting and Mitigating Hallucinations in Multilingual Summarisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-and-mitigating-hallucinations-in-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the existing faithful metrics focusing on English, even measuring the extent of this phenomenon in cross-lingual settings is hard.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-and-mitigating-hallucinations-in-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Link Prediction without Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-prediction-without-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Link prediction, which consists of predicting edges based on graph features, is a fundamental task in many graph applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-prediction-without-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoupled Rationalization with Asymmetric Learning Rates: A Flexible Lipshitz Restraint</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-rationalization-with-asymmetric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, such a cooperative game may incur the degeneration problem where the predictor overfits to the uninformative pieces generated by a not yet well-trained generator and in turn, leads the generator to converge to a sub-optimal model that tends to select senseless pieces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-rationalization-with-asymmetric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USB: A Unified Summarization Benchmark Across Tasks and Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/usb-a-unified-summarization-benchmark-across</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that for some tasks, the amount of training data matters more than the domain where it comes from, while for other tasks training specifically on data from the target domain, even if limited, is more beneficial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/usb-a-unified-summarization-benchmark-across</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QLoRA: Efficient Finetuning of Quantized LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qlora-efficient-finetuning-of-quantized-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our best model family, which we name Guanaco, outperforms all previous openly released models on the Vicuna benchmark, reaching 99. 3% of the performance level of ChatGPT while only requiring 24 hours of finetuning on a single GPU.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qlora-efficient-finetuning-of-quantized-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAPR: A Benchmark on Document-Aware Passage Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dapr-a-benchmark-on-document-aware-passage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill this gap, we propose and name this task Document-Aware Passage Retrieval (DAPR) and build a benchmark including multiple datasets from various domains, covering both DAPR and whole-document retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dapr-a-benchmark-on-document-aware-passage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EfficientSpeech: An On-Device Text to Speech Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficientspeech-an-on-device-text-to-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State of the art (SOTA) neural text to speech (TTS) models can generate natural-sounding synthetic voices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficientspeech-an-on-device-text-to-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AxomiyaBERTa: A Phonologically-aware Transformer Model for Assamese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/axomiyaberta-a-phonologically-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we show that AxomiyaBERTa can leverage phonological signals for even more challenging tasks, such as a novel cross-document coreference task on a translated version of the ECB+ corpus, where we present a new SOTA result for an LRL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/axomiyaberta-a-phonologically-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequence-Level Knowledge Distillation for Class-Incremental End-to-End Spoken Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequence-level-knowledge-distillation-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to learn new concepts sequentially is a major weakness for modern neural networks, which hinders their use in non-stationary environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequence-level-knowledge-distillation-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Copy Rather Than Memorize: A Vertical Learning Paradigm for Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-copy-rather-than-memorize-a-vertical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Embedding models have shown great power in knowledge graph completion (KGC) task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-copy-rather-than-memorize-a-vertical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not All Image Regions Matter: Masked Vector Quantization for Autoregressive Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-image-regions-matter-masked-vector-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing autoregressive models follow the two-stage generation paradigm that first learns a codebook in the latent space for image reconstruction and then completes the image generation autoregressively based on the learned codebook.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-image-regions-matter-masked-vector-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Prompting Assists Large Language Model on Web Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-prompting-assists-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) struggle on processing complicated observations in interactive decision making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-prompting-assists-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisorGPT: Learning Visual Prior via Generative Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visorgpt-learning-visual-prior-via-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results demonstrate that \our~can effectively model the visual prior, which can be employed for many vision tasks, such as customizing accurate human pose for conditional image synthesis models like ControlNet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visorgpt-learning-visual-prior-via-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Factual Consistency of Summaries with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-factual-consistency-of-summaries</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting factual errors in summaries has been an important and challenging subject in summarization research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-factual-consistency-of-summaries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAD: Semi-Supervised Anomaly Detection on Dynamic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sad-semi-supervised-anomaly-detection-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Anomaly detection aims to distinguish abnormal instances that deviate significantly from the majority of benign ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sad-semi-supervised-anomaly-detection-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Echo Denoising in Adverse Weather</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-echo-denoising-in-adverse-weather</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the task of multi-echo denoising, where the goal is to pick the echo that represents the objects of interest and discard other echoes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-echo-denoising-in-adverse-weather</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse4D v2: Recurrent Temporal Fusion with Sparse Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse4d-v2-recurrent-temporal-fusion-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, it reduces the computational complexity of temporal fusion from $O(T)$ to $O(1)$, resulting in significant improvements in inference speed and memory usage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse4d-v2-recurrent-temporal-fusion-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging BEV Representation for 360-degree Visual Place Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-bev-representation-for-360-degree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, the image and point cloud cues can be easily stated in the same coordinates, which benefits sensor fusion for place recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-bev-representation-for-360-degree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Granularity Detector for Vulnerability Fixes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-detector-for-vulnerability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges and boost the effectiveness of prior works, we propose MiDas (Multi-Granularity Detector for Vulnerability Fixes).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-detector-for-vulnerability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and Improving Optimization in Predictive Coding Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-improving-optimization-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Backpropagation (BP), the standard learning algorithm for artificial neural networks, is often considered biologically implausible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-improving-optimization-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototype Adaption and Projection for Few- and Zero-shot 3D Point Cloud Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-adaption-and-projection-for-few-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address the challenging task of few-shot and zero-shot 3D point cloud semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-adaption-and-projection-for-few-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IdEALS: Idiomatic Expressions for Advancement of Language Skills</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ideals-idiomatic-expressions-for-advancement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although significant progress has been made in developing methods for Grammatical Error Correction (GEC), addressing word choice improvements has been notably lacking and enhancing sentence expressivity by replacing phrases with advanced expressions is an understudied aspect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ideals-idiomatic-expressions-for-advancement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIVA: A Dirichlet Process Based Incremental Deep Clustering Algorithm via Variational Auto-Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diva-a-dirichlet-process-based-incremental</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative model-based deep clustering frameworks excel in classifying complex data, but are limited in handling dynamic and complex features because they require prior knowledge of the number of clusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diva-a-dirichlet-process-based-incremental</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Remote Sensing Object Detection with Single Point Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-remote-sensing-object-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we make the first attempt to achieve RS object detection with single point supervision, and propose a PSOD framework tailored with RS images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-remote-sensing-object-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Open-vocabulary Segmentation with Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-open-vocabulary-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-vocabulary segmentation of 3D scenes is a fundamental function of human perception and thus a crucial objective in computer vision research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-open-vocabulary-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Speech Technology to 1,000+ Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-speech-technology-to-1000-languages</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Expanding the language coverage of speech technology has the potential to improve access to information for many more people.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-speech-technology-to-1000-languages</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parts of Speech-Grounded Subspaces in Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parts-of-speech-grounded-subspaces-in-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to separate representations of the different visual modalities in CLIP's joint vision-language space by leveraging the association between parts of speech and specific visual modes of variation (e. g. nouns relate to objects, adjectives describe appearance).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parts-of-speech-grounded-subspaces-in-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WinDB: HMD-free and Distortion-free Panoptic Video Fixation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/windb-hmd-free-and-distortion-free-panoptic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main reason is that there always exist "blind zooms" when using HMD to collect fixations since the participants cannot keep spinning their heads to explore the entire panoptic scene all the time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/windb-hmd-free-and-distortion-free-panoptic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIANet: Aggregating Unbiased Instance and General Information for Few-Shot Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mianet-aggregating-unbiased-instance-and-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing few-shot segmentation methods are based on the meta-learning strategy and extract instance knowledge from a support set and then apply the knowledge to segment target objects in a query set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mianet-aggregating-unbiased-instance-and-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NORM: Knowledge Distillation via N-to-One Representation Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/norm-knowledge-distillation-via-n-to-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By sequentially splitting the expanded student representation into N non-overlapping feature segments having the same number of feature channels as the teacher's, they can be readily forced to approximate the intact teacher representation simultaneously, formulating a novel many-to-one representation matching mechanism conditioned on a single teacher-student layer pair.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/norm-knowledge-distillation-via-n-to-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Adaptive Voxel-guided Sampling for Real-time Applications in Large-scale Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-adaptive-voxel-guided-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While point-based neural architectures have demonstrated their efficacy, the time-consuming sampler currently prevents them from performing real-time reasoning on scene-level point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-adaptive-voxel-guided-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Low-Resource Entity Recognition Through Translation and Annotation Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-low-resource-entity-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained multilingual language models have enabled significant advancements in cross-lingual transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-low-resource-entity-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind the spikes: Benign overfitting of kernels and neural networks in fixed dimension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-the-spikes-benign-overfitting-of-kernels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show that the smoothness of the estimators, and not the dimension, is the key: benign overfitting is possible if and only if the estimator's derivatives are large enough.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-the-spikes-benign-overfitting-of-kernels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch-Mix Contrastive Learning with Audio Spectrogram Transformer on Respiratory Sound Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-mix-contrastive-learning-with-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Respiratory sound contains crucial information for the early diagnosis of fatal lung diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-mix-contrastive-learning-with-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Laplacian Pyramid Based Generative H&amp;E Stain Augmentation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-laplacian-pyramid-based-generative-h-e</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hematoxylin and Eosin (H&E) staining is a widely used sample preparation procedure for enhancing the saturation of tissue sections and the contrast between nuclei and cytoplasm in histology images for medical diagnostics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-laplacian-pyramid-based-generative-h-e</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query Structure Modeling for Inductive Logical Reasoning Over Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-structure-modeling-for-inductive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results demonstrate the effectiveness of our method on logical reasoning over KGs in both inductive and transductive settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-structure-modeling-for-inductive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConGraT: Self-Supervised Contrastive Pretraining for Joint Graph and Text Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/congrat-self-supervised-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose ConGraT(Contrastive Graph-Text pretraining), a general, self-supervised method for jointly learning separate representations of texts and nodes in a parent (or ``supervening'') graph, where each text is associated with one of the nodes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/congrat-self-supervised-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TalkUp: A Novel Dataset Paving the Way for Understanding Empowering Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/talkup-a-novel-dataset-paving-the-way-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empowering language is important in many real-world contexts, from education to workplace dynamics to healthcare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/talkup-a-novel-dataset-paving-the-way-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mPMR: A Multilingual Pre-trained Machine Reader at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpmr-a-multilingual-pre-trained-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[mPMR aims to guide multilingual pre-trained language models (mPLMs) to perform natural language understanding (NLU) including both sequence classification and span extraction in multiple languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpmr-a-multilingual-pre-trained-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QTSumm: A New Benchmark for Query-Focused Table Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qtsumm-a-new-benchmark-for-query-focused</link>
      <description><![CDATA[People primarily consult tables to conduct data analysis or answer specific questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qtsumm-a-new-benchmark-for-query-focused</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Open Dataset and Model for Language Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-open-dataset-and-model-for-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We achieve this by training on a curated dataset of monolingual data, the reliability of which we ensure by auditing a sample from each source and each language manually.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-open-dataset-and-model-for-language</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
