<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 09:15:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Better by Default: Strong Pre-Tuned MLPs and Boosted Trees on Tabular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-by-default-strong-pre-tuned-mlps-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For classification and regression on tabular data, the dominance of gradient-boosted decision trees (GBDTs) has recently been challenged by often much slower deep learning methods with extensive hyperparameter tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-by-default-strong-pre-tuned-mlps-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CanonicalFusion: Generating Drivable 3D Human Avatars from Multiple Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/canonicalfusion-generating-drivable-3d-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel framework for reconstructing animatable human avatars from multiple images, termed CanonicalFusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/canonicalfusion-generating-drivable-3d-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient GANs for Document Image Binarization Based on DWT and Normalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-gans-for-document-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this problem, this work introduces an efficient GAN method based on the three-stage network architecture that incorporates the Discrete Wavelet Transformation and normalization to reduce the input image size, which in turns, decrease both training and inference times.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-gans-for-document-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering symbolic expressions with parallelized tree search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-symbolic-expressions-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Symbolic regression plays a crucial role in modern scientific research thanks to its capability of discovering concise and interpretable mathematical expressions from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-symbolic-expressions-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneRestore: A Universal Restoration Framework for Composite Degradation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onerestore-a-universal-restoration-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In real-world scenarios, image impairments often manifest as composite degradations, presenting a complex interplay of elements such as low light, haze, rain, and snow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onerestore-a-universal-restoration-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoPreRo: A New Dataset for Popularity Prediction of Romanian Reddit Posts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poprero-a-new-dataset-for-popularity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We thus believe that PoPreRo is a valuable resource that can be used to evaluate models on predicting the popularity of social media posts in Romanian.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poprero-a-new-dataset-for-popularity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embracing Massive Medical Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embracing-massive-medical-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, training AI all at once on such massive data is impractical as new scans/sources/classes continuously arrive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embracing-massive-medical-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDiscoFormer: Relaxing Part Discovery Constraints with Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdiscoformer-relaxing-part-discovery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computer vision methods that explicitly detect object parts and reason on them are a step towards inherently interpretable models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdiscoformer-relaxing-part-discovery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiosERC: Integrating Biography Speakers Supported by LLMs for ERC Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bioserc-integrating-biography-speakers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the Emotion Recognition in Conversation task, recent investigations have utilized attention mechanisms exploring relationships among utterances from intra- and inter-speakers for modeling emotional interaction between them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bioserc-integrating-biography-speakers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-modal Masked Siamese Network Improves Chest X-Ray Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-masked-siamese-network-improves</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our approach on three publicly available chest X-ray datasets, MIMIC-CXR, CheXpert, and NIH-14, using two vision transformer (ViT) backbones, specifically ViT-Tiny and ViT-Small.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-masked-siamese-network-improves</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Role of Invariance in Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-role-of-invariance-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using these datasets, we a) show that for learning representations with high transfer performance, invariance to the right transformations is as, or often more, important than most other factors such as the number of training samples, the model architecture and the identity of the pretraining classes, b) show conditions under which invariance can harm the ability to transfer representations and c) explore how transferable invariance is between tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-role-of-invariance-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperspectral Dataset and Deep Learning methods for Waste from Electric and Electronic Equipment Identification (WEEE)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperspectral-dataset-and-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we evaluate the performance of diverse deep learning architectures for hyperspectral image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperspectral-dataset-and-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Branch Auxiliary Fusion YOLO with Re-parameterization Heterogeneous Convolutional for accurate object detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-branch-auxiliary-fusion-yolo-with-re</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, the Advanced Assisted Fusion (AAF) module deeply embedded within the neck conveys a more diverse range of gradient information to the output layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-branch-auxiliary-fusion-yolo-with-re</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T2IShield: Defending Against Backdoors on Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t2ishield-defending-against-backdoors-on-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, for the first time, we propose a comprehensive defense method named T2IShield to detect, localize, and mitigate such attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t2ishield-defending-against-backdoors-on-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hindsight Preference Learning for Offline Preference-based Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hindsight-preference-learning-for-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Offline preference-based reinforcement learning (RL), which focuses on optimizing policies using human preferences between pairs of trajectory segments selected from an offline dataset, has emerged as a practical avenue for RL applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hindsight-preference-learning-for-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Learning of Category-Level 3D Pose from Object-Centric Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-of-category-level-3d-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a second step, the canonical poses and reconstructed meshes enable us to train a model for 3D pose estimation from a single image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-of-category-level-3d-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAM: Retrieval-Based Affordance Transfer for Generalizable Zero-Shot Robotic Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ram-retrieval-based-affordance-transfer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, RAM extracts unified affordance at scale from diverse sources of demonstrations including robotic data, human-object interaction (HOI) data, and custom data to construct a comprehensive affordance memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ram-retrieval-based-affordance-transfer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnySR: Realizing Image Super-Resolution as Any-Scale, Any-Resource</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anysr-realizing-image-super-resolution-as-any</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a contrast to off-the-shelf methods that solve SR tasks across various scales with the same computing costs, our AnySR innovates in: 1) building arbitrary-scale tasks as any-resource implementation, reducing resource requirements for smaller scales without additional parameters; 2) enhancing any-scale performance in a feature-interweaving fashion, inserting scale pairs into features at regular intervals and ensuring correct feature/scale processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anysr-realizing-image-super-resolution-as-any</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Vision-Language Reasoners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-vision-language-reasoners</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, we employ the abstractions given in the SMART task (Simple Multimodal Algorithmic Reasoning Task) introduced in \cite{cherian2022deep} as meta-reasoning and problem-solving skills along eight axes: math, counting, path, measure, logic, spatial, and pattern.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-vision-language-reasoners</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pretraining End-to-End Keyword Search with Automatically Discovered Acoustic Units</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pretraining-end-to-end-keyword-search-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[End-to-end (E2E) keyword search (KWS) has emerged as an alternative and complimentary approach to conventional keyword search which depends on the output of automatic speech recognition (ASR) systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pretraining-end-to-end-keyword-search-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AriGraph: Learning Knowledge Graph World Models with Episodic Memory for LLM Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arigraph-learning-knowledge-graph-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that our Ariadne LLM agent, equipped with this proposed memory architecture augmented with planning and decision-making, effectively handles complex tasks on a zero-shot basis in the TextWorld environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arigraph-learning-knowledge-graph-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PartCraft: Crafting Creative Objects by Parts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partcraft-crafting-creative-objects-by-parts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper propels creative control in generative visual AI by allowing users to "select".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partcraft-crafting-creative-objects-by-parts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Written Term Detection Improves Spoken Term Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/written-term-detection-improves-spoken-term</link>
      <description><![CDATA[End-to-end (E2E) approaches to keyword search (KWS) are considerably simpler in terms of training and indexing complexity when compared to approaches which use the output of automatic speech recognition (ASR) systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/written-term-detection-improves-spoken-term</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploration of Class Center for Fine-Grained Visual Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploration-of-class-center-for-fine-grained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, our method achieves state-of-the-art performance on the FGVC-Aircraft and CUB-200-2011 datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploration-of-class-center-for-fine-grained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Q-Learning for finite ambiguity sets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-q-learning-for-finite-ambiguity-sets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we propose a novel $Q$-learning algorithm allowing to solve distributionally robust Markov decision problems for which the ambiguity set of probability measures can be chosen arbitrarily as long as it comprises only a finite amount of measures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-q-learning-for-finite-ambiguity-sets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to (Learn at Test Time): RNNs with Expressive Hidden States</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-learn-at-test-time-rnns-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our instantiations at the scale of 125M to 1. 3B parameters, comparing with a strong Transformer and Mamba, a modern RNN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-learn-at-test-time-rnns-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SH17: A Dataset for Human Safety and Personal Protective Equipment Detection in Manufacturing Industry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sh17-a-dataset-for-human-safety-and-personal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Workplace accidents continue to pose significant risks for human safety, particularly in industries such as construction and manufacturing, and the necessity for effective Personal Protective Equipment (PPE) compliance has become increasingly paramount.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sh17-a-dataset-for-human-safety-and-personal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARS: Paying more attention to visual attributes for text-based person search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mars-paying-more-attention-to-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task is that of retrieving one or more images of a specific individual based on a textual description.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mars-paying-more-attention-to-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isomorphic Pruning for Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isomorphic-pruning-for-vision-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For instance, we improve the accuracy of DeiT-Tiny from 74. 52% to 77. 50% by pruning an off-the-shelf DeiT-Base model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isomorphic-pruning-for-vision-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Driven Tissue- and Subject-Specific Elastic Regularization for Medical Image Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-tissue-and-subject-specific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Physics-inspired regularization is desired for intra-patient image registration since it can effectively capture the biomechanical characteristics of anatomical structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-tissue-and-subject-specific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Complex Instruction-Following with Multiple Constraints Composition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-complex-instruction-following</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing benchmarks mainly focus on modeling different types of constraints in human instructions while neglecting the composition of different constraints, which is an indispensable constituent in complex instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-complex-instruction-following</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Pixels: Semi-Supervised Semantic Segmentation with a Multi-scale Patch-based Multi-Label Classifier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-pixels-semi-supervised-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This patch classifier is trained to identify classes present within an image region, which facilitates the elimination of distractors and enhances the classification of small object segments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-pixels-semi-supervised-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Self-supervised Pre-training using Accent-Specific Codebooks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-self-supervised-pre-training-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speech accents present a serious challenge to the performance of state-of-the-art end-to-end Automatic Speech Recognition (ASR) systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-self-supervised-pre-training-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BM25S: Orders of magnitude faster lexical search via eager sparse scoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bm25s-orders-of-magnitude-faster-lexical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce BM25S, an efficient Python-based implementation of BM25 that only depends on Numpy and Scipy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bm25s-orders-of-magnitude-faster-lexical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Core: Robust Factual Precision Scoring with Informative Sub-Claim Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/core-robust-factual-precision-scoring-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hallucinations -- the generation of untrue claims -- pose a challenge to the application of large language models (LLMs) [1] thereby motivating the development of metrics to evaluate factual precision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/core-robust-factual-precision-scoring-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future Events as Backdoor Triggers: Investigating Temporal Vulnerabilities in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/future-events-as-backdoor-triggers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Backdoors are hidden behaviors that are only triggered once an AI system has been deployed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/future-events-as-backdoor-triggers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Autoencoder Architecture for L-band Passive Microwave Retrieval of Landscape Freeze-Thaw Cycle</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-autoencoder-architecture-for-l-band</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimating the landscape and soil freeze-thaw (FT) dynamics in the Northern Hemisphere is crucial for understanding permafrost response to global warming and changes in regional and global carbon budgets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-autoencoder-architecture-for-l-band</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Craftium: An Extensible Framework for Creating Reinforcement Learning Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/craftium-an-extensible-framework-for-creating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most Reinforcement Learning (RL) environments are created by adapting existing physics simulators or video games.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/craftium-an-extensible-framework-for-creating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DotaMath: Decomposition of Thought with Code Assistance and Self-correction for Mathematical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dotamath-decomposition-of-thought-with-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a series of LLMs that employs the Decomposition of thought with code assistance and self-correction for mathematical reasoning, dubbed as DotaMath.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dotamath-decomposition-of-thought-with-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROER: Regularized Optimal Experience Replay</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roer-regularized-optimal-experience-replay</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We specifically explore the KL divergence as the regularizer and obtain a new form of prioritization scheme, the regularized optimal experience replay (ROER).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roer-regularized-optimal-experience-replay</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Workflows and Smells of Leaderboard Operations (LBOps): An Exploratory Study of Foundation Model Leaderboards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-workflows-and-smells-of-leaderboard</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then identify 8 unique types of leaderboard smells in LBOps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-workflows-and-smells-of-leaderboard</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALENT: A Tabular Analytics and Learning Toolbox</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/talent-a-tabular-analytics-and-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tabular data is one of the most common data sources in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/talent-a-tabular-analytics-and-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biometric Authentication Based on Enhanced Remote Photoplethysmography Signal Morphology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biometric-authentication-based-on-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the second training stage, an rPPG-cPPG hybrid training is performed by incorporating external cPPG datasets to achieve rPPG biometric authentication and enhance rPPG signal morphology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biometric-authentication-based-on-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoMix: A Comprehensive Benchmark for Multi-Task Comic Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comix-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel benchmark, CoMix, designed to evaluate the multi-task capabilities of models in comic analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comix-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argument Mining in Data Scarce Settings: Cross-lingual Transfer and Few-shot Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/argument-mining-in-data-scarce-settings-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrary to previous work, we show that for Argument Mining data transfer obtains better results than model-transfer and that fine-tuning outperforms few-shot methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/argument-mining-in-data-scarce-settings-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Latent Diffusion Models for Training-Free In-Distribution Data Augmentation for Surface Defect Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-latent-diffusion-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Usually, defect detection classifiers are trained on ground-truth data formed by normal samples (negative data) and samples with defects (positive data), where the latter are consistently fewer than normal samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-latent-diffusion-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOWA: Adapting Hierarchical Frozen Window Self-Attention to Visual-Language Models for Better Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sowa-adapting-hierarchical-frozen-window-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual anomaly detection is critical in industrial manufacturing, but traditional methods often rely on extensive normal datasets and custom models, limiting scalability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sowa-adapting-hierarchical-frozen-window-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoencoded Image Compression for Secure and Fast Transmission</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoded-image-compression-for-secure-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With an exponential growth in the use of digital image data, the need for efficient transmission methods has become imperative.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoded-image-compression-for-secure-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Robust Fundus Photography-based Vision Loss Estimation for High Myopia</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-robust-fundus-photography-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High myopia significantly increases the risk of irreversible vision loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-robust-fundus-photography-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-DR: Textual Knowledge-Guided Diabetic Retinopathy Grading with Ranking-aware Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-dr-textual-knowledge-guided-diabetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diabetic retinopathy (DR) is a complication of diabetes and usually takes decades to reach sight-threatening levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-dr-textual-knowledge-guided-diabetic</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
