<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 21:08:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Parallel transport on matrix manifolds and Exponential Action</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-transport-on-matrix-manifolds-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We express parallel transport for several common matrix Lie groups with a family of pseudo-Riemannian metrics in terms of matrix exponential and exponential actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-transport-on-matrix-manifolds-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polyp SAM 2: Advancing Zero shot Polyp Segmentation in Colorectal Cancer Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyp-sam-2-advancing-zero-shot-polyp</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Polyp segmentation plays a crucial role in the early detection and diagnosis of colorectal cancer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyp-sam-2-advancing-zero-shot-polyp</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Sharpness Based Loss Function for Removing Out-of-Focus Blur</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-sharpness-based-loss-function-for-removing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of modern Deep Neural Network (DNN) approaches can be attributed to the use of complex optimization criteria beyond standard losses such as mean absolute error (MAE) or mean squared error (MSE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-sharpness-based-loss-function-for-removing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FruitNeRF: A Unified Neural Radiance Field based Fruit Counting Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fruitnerf-a-unified-neural-radiance-field</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce FruitNeRF, a unified novel fruit counting framework that leverages state-of-the-art view synthesis methods to count any fruit type directly in 3D.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fruitnerf-a-unified-neural-radiance-field</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blind-Match: Efficient Homomorphic Encryption-Based 1:N Matching for Privacy-Preserving Biometric Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-match-efficient-homomorphic-encryption</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Blind-Match, a novel biometric identification system that leverages homomorphic encryption (HE) for efficient and privacy-preserving 1:N matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-match-efficient-homomorphic-encryption</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MR3D-Net: Dynamic Multi-Resolution 3D Sparse Voxel Grid Fusion for LiDAR-Based Collective Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mr3d-net-dynamic-multi-resolution-3d-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose MR3D-Net, a dynamic multi-resolution 3D sparse voxel grid fusion backbone architecture for LiDAR-based collective perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mr3d-net-dynamic-multi-resolution-3d-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ControlNeXt: Powerful and Efficient Control for Image and Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlnext-powerful-and-efficient-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose ControlNeXt: a powerful and efficient method for controllable image and video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlnext-powerful-and-efficient-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUNE: A Machine Learning Deep UNet++ based Ensemble Approach to Monthly, Seasonal and Annual Climate Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dune-a-machine-learning-deep-unet-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ERA5 monthly mean data is used as input for T2m over land, SST over oceans, and solar radiation at the top of the atmosphere for each month of 40 years to train the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dune-a-machine-learning-deep-unet-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mambular: A Sequential Model for Tabular Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambular-a-sequential-model-for-tabular-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results highlight Mambulars potential as a versatile and powerful architecture for tabular data analysis, expanding the scope of deep learning applications in this domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambular-a-sequential-model-for-tabular-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastFiD: Improve Inference Efficiency of Open Domain Question Answering via Sentence Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastfid-improve-inference-efficiency-of-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open Domain Question Answering (ODQA) has been advancing rapidly in recent times, driven by significant developments in dense passage retrieval and pretrained language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastfid-improve-inference-efficiency-of-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contexts Matter: An Empirical Study on Contextual Influence in Fairness Testing for Deep Learning Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contexts-matter-an-empirical-study-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Background: Fairness testing for deep learning systems has been becoming increasingly important.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contexts-matter-an-empirical-study-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HcNet: Image Modeling with Heat Conduction Equation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hcnet-image-modeling-with-heat-conduction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This finding inspired us to model images by the heat conduction equation, where the essential idea is to conceptualize image features as temperatures and model their information interaction as the diffusion of thermal energy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hcnet-image-modeling-with-heat-conduction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CogVideoX: Text-to-Video Diffusion Models with An Expert Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cogvideox-text-to-video-diffusion-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the text-video alignment, we propose an expert transformer with the expert adaptive LayerNorm to facilitate the deep fusion between the two modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cogvideox-text-to-video-diffusion-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MovieSum: An Abstractive Summarization Dataset for Movie Screenplays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moviesum-an-abstractive-summarization-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Movie screenplay summarization is challenging, as it requires an understanding of long input contexts and various elements unique to movies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moviesum-an-abstractive-summarization-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depth Linear Discriminant Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-linear-discriminant-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study introduces a novel linear discriminant method, called Depth Linear Discriminant Analysis (D-LDA) to enhance the robustness of the original LDA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-linear-discriminant-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Vision-Language Representation for Weakly Supervised Temporal Action Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-vision-language-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these problems, we propose a novel framework that aligns human action knowledge and VLP knowledge in a probabilistic embedding space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-vision-language-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Patterns in Ambiguity: Interpretable Stress Testing in the Decision~Boundary</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-patterns-in-ambiguity-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing use of deep learning across various domains highlights the importance of understanding the decision-making processes of these black-box models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-patterns-in-ambiguity-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISurConv: Rotation Invariant Surface Attention-Augmented Convolutions for 3D Point Cloud Classification and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risurconv-rotation-invariant-surface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We achieve an overall accuracy of 96. 0% (+4. 7%) on ModelNet40, 93. 1% (+12. 8%) on ScanObjectNN, and class accuracies of 91. 5% (+3. 6%), 82. 7% (+5. 1%), and 78. 5% (+9. 2%) on the three categories of the FG3D dataset for the fine-grained classification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risurconv-rotation-invariant-surface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisualAgentBench: Towards Large Multimodal Models as Visual Foundation Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualagentbench-towards-large-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Multimodal Models (LMMs) have ushered in a new era in artificial intelligence, merging capabilities in both language and vision to form highly capable Visual Foundation Agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualagentbench-towards-large-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Byzantine Robustness in Federated Learning with A Black-box Server</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-byzantine-robustness-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) becomes vulnerable to Byzantine attacks where some of participators tend to damage the utility or discourage the convergence of the learned model via sending their malicious model updates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-byzantine-robustness-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Case Study on the Performance of Machine Learning Methods on the Classification of Solar Panel Electroluminescence Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-case-study-on-the-performance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we comprehensively compare different machine learning and deep learning methods under different performance metrics on the classification of solar cell EL images from monocrystalline and polycrystalline modules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-case-study-on-the-performance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling Surprisal in Music Generation via Information Content Curve Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-surprisal-in-music-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This enables the comparison of surprisal across different musical content even if the musical events occur in irregular time intervals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-surprisal-in-music-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI Scientist: Towards Fully Automated Open-Ended Scientific Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ai-scientist-towards-fully-automated-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach signifies the beginning of a new era in scientific discovery in machine learning: bringing the transformative benefits of AI agents to the entire research process of AI itself, and taking us closer to a world where endless affordable creativity and innovation can be unleashed on the world's most challenging problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ai-scientist-towards-fully-automated-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BI-MDRG: Bridging Image History in Multimodal Dialogue Response Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-mdrg-bridging-image-history-in-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose BI-MDRG that bridges the response generation path such that the image history information is utilized for enhanced relevance of text responses to the image content and the consistency of objects in sequential image responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-mdrg-bridging-image-history-in-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GFlowNet Training by Policy Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gflownet-training-by-policy-gradients</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative Flow Networks (GFlowNets) have been shown effective to generate combinatorial objects with desired properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gflownet-training-by-policy-gradients</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalization capabilities of MeshGraphNets to unseen geometries for fluid dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalization-capabilities-of-meshgraphnets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our numerical tests, we show that MGNs can sometimes generalize well to various shapes by training on a dataset of one obstacle shape and testing on a dataset of another obstacle shape.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalization-capabilities-of-meshgraphnets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unseen No More: Unlocking the Potential of CLIP for Generative Zero-shot HOI Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unseen-no-more-unlocking-the-potential-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we extract realistic features of seen samples and mix them with synthetic features together, allowing the model to train seen and unseen classes jointly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unseen-no-more-unlocking-the-potential-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdTEC: A Unified Benchmark for Evaluating Text Quality in Search Engine Advertising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adtec-a-unified-benchmark-for-evaluating-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increase in the more fluent ad texts automatically created by natural language generation technology, it is in the high demand to verify the quality of these creatives in a real-world setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adtec-a-unified-benchmark-for-evaluating-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Large Language Models for Phishing Webpage Detection and Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-large-language-models-for-phishing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we take steps to study the efficacy of large language models (LLMs), in particular the multimodal LLMs, in detecting phishing webpages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-large-language-models-for-phishing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markov Senior -- Learning Markov Junior Grammars to Generate User-specified Content</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/markov-senior-learning-markov-junior-grammars</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed method ``Markov Senior'' focuses on extracting positional and distance relations from single input samples to construct probabilistic rules to be used by Markov Junior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/markov-senior-learning-markov-junior-grammars</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClickAttention: Click Region Similarity Guided Interactive Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clickattention-click-region-similarity-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interactive segmentation algorithms based on click points have garnered significant attention from researchers in recent years. However, existing studies typically use sparse click maps as model inputs to segment specific target objects, which primarily affect local regions and have limited abilities to focus on the whole target object, leading to increased times of clicks. In addition, most existing algorithms can not balance well between high performance and efficiency. To address this issue, we propose a click attention algorithm that expands the influence range of positive clicks based on the similarity between positively-clicked regions and the whole input. We also propose a discriminative affinity loss to reduce the attention coupling between positive and negative click regions to avoid an accuracy decrease caused by mutual interference between positive and negative clicks. Extensive experiments demonstrate that our approach is superior to existing methods and achieves cutting-edge performance in fewer parameters. An interactive demo and all reproducible codes will be released at https://github. com/hahamyt/ClickAttention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clickattention-click-region-similarity-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Method-of-Moments Inference for GLMs and Doubly Robust Functionals under Proportional Asymptotics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/method-of-moments-inference-for-glms-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we consider the estimation of regression coefficients and signal-to-noise (SNR) ratio in high-dimensional Generalized Linear Models (GLMs), and explore their implications in inferring popular estimands such as average treatment effects in high-dimensional observational studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/method-of-moments-inference-for-glms-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perceptual Similarity for Measuring Decision-Making Style and Policy Diversity in Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perceptual-similarity-for-measuring-decision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Defining and measuring decision-making styles, also known as playstyles, is crucial in gaming, where these styles reflect a broad spectrum of individuality and diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perceptual-similarity-for-measuring-decision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy Game-Playing with Size-Constrained State Abstraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strategy-game-playing-with-size-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the major challenges is the large search space due to a diverse set of game components.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strategy-game-playing-with-size-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BooW-VTON: Boosting In-the-Wild Virtual Try-On via Mask-Free Pseudo Data Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boow-vton-boosting-in-the-wild-virtual-try-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods always employ an accurate mask to remove the original garment in the source image, thus achieving realistic synthesized images in simple and conventional try-on scenarios based on powerful diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boow-vton-boosting-in-the-wild-virtual-try-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTSCI: A Conditional Diffusion Model for Multivariate Time Series Consistent Imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtsci-a-conditional-diffusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key research question is how to ensure imputation consistency, i. e., intra-consistency between observed and imputed values, and inter-consistency between adjacent windows after imputation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtsci-a-conditional-diffusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-Informed Beam Search Decoding for Multilingual Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-informed-beam-search-decoding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Beam search decoding is the de-facto method for decoding auto-regressive Neural Machine Translation (NMT) models, including multilingual NMT where the target language is specified as an input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-informed-beam-search-decoding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U-DECN: End-to-End Underwater Object Detection ConvNet with Improved DeNoising Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-decn-end-to-end-underwater-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As for the detrimental effect of underwater color cast noise, recent underwater object detectors make network architecture or training complex, which also hinders their application and deployment on underwater vehicle platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-decn-end-to-end-underwater-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On zero-shot learning in neural state estimation of power distribution systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-zero-shot-learning-in-neural-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the challenge of neural state estimation in power distribution systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-zero-shot-learning-in-neural-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Decoding Acceleration Framework for Industrial Deployable LLM-based Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-decoding-acceleration-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This generation inefficiency stems from the autoregressive nature of LLMs, and a promising direction for acceleration is speculative decoding, a Draft-then-Verify paradigm that increases the number of generated tokens per decoding step.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-decoding-acceleration-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PS-TTL: Prototype-based Soft-labels and Test-Time Learning for Few-shot Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ps-ttl-prototype-based-soft-labels-and-test</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we design a Test-Time Learning (TTL) module that employs a mean-teacher network for self-training to discover novel instances from test data, allowing detectors to learn better representations and classifiers for novel classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ps-ttl-prototype-based-soft-labels-and-test</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HySparK: Hybrid Sparse Masking for Large Scale Medical Image Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyspark-hybrid-sparse-masking-for-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The generative self-supervised learning strategy exhibits remarkable learning representational capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyspark-hybrid-sparse-masking-for-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Training-Free Framework for Video License Plate Tracking and Recognition with Only One-Shot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-training-free-framework-for-video-license</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose OneShotLP, a training-free framework for video-based license plate detection and recognition, leveraging these advanced models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-training-free-framework-for-video-license</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TC-KANRecon: High-Quality and Accelerated MRI Reconstruction via Adaptive KAN Mechanisms and Intelligent Feature Scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tc-kanrecon-high-quality-and-accelerated-mri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the MC-Model module incorporates full-sampling k-space information, realizing efficient fusion of conditional information, enhancing the model's ability to process complex data, and improving the realism and detail richness of reconstructed images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tc-kanrecon-high-quality-and-accelerated-mri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAGA: A Participant-specific Examination of Story Alternatives and Goal Applicability for a Deeper Understanding of Complex Events</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saga-a-participant-specific-examination-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is important to be able to acquire the knowledge needed for this understanding, though doing so is challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saga-a-participant-specific-examination-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Virtual World with Delta-Engine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-virtual-world-with-delta-engine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key feature of the delta-engine is its scalability to unknown elements within the world, Technically, it derives from the prefect co-work of the neural proxy and the base engine, and the alignment with high-quality data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-virtual-world-with-delta-engine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototype Learning Guided Hybrid Network for Breast Tumor Segmentation in DCE-MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-learning-guided-hybrid-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To strike an optimal trade-off between computational costs and segmentation performance, we propose a hybrid network via the combination of convolution neural network (CNN) and transformer layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-learning-guided-hybrid-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StealthDiffusion: Towards Evading Diffusion Forensic Detection through Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stealthdiffusion-towards-evading-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid progress in generative models has given rise to the critical task of AI-Generated Content Stealth (AIGC-S), which aims to create AI-generated images that can evade both forensic detectors and human inspection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stealthdiffusion-towards-evading-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoder Pre-Training with only Text for Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoder-pre-training-with-only-text-for-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments across various STR decoders and language recognition tasks underscore the broad applicability and remarkable performance of DPTR, providing a novel insight for STR pre-training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoder-pre-training-with-only-text-for-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PixelFade: Privacy-preserving Person Re-identification with Noise-guided Progressive Replacement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixelfade-privacy-preserving-person-re</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous privacy-preserving person re-identification methods are unable to resist recovery attacks and compromise accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixelfade-privacy-preserving-person-re</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
