<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 21:06:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Class-Aware Mask-Guided Feature Refinement for Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-aware-mask-guided-feature-refinement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By enhancing the alignment between the canonical mask feature and the text feature, the module ensures more effective fusion, ultimately leading to improved recognition performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-aware-mask-guided-feature-refinement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongWanjuan: Towards Systematic Measurement for Long Text Quality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longwanjuan-towards-systematic-measurement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The quality of training data are crucial for enhancing the long-text capabilities of foundation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longwanjuan-towards-systematic-measurement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distinctive Image Captioning: Leveraging Ground Truth Captions in CLIP Guided Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinctive-image-captioning-leveraging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, they can serve as additional trajectories in the RL strategy, resulting in a teacher forcing loss weighted by the similarity of the GT to the image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinctive-image-captioning-leveraging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure Ombudsman: Mining Future Failure Concerns from Structural Disaster Response</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infrastructure-ombudsman-mining-future</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current research concentrates on studying discussions on social media related to structural failures to improve disaster response strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infrastructure-ombudsman-mining-future</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GradSafe: Detecting Unsafe Prompts for LLMs via Safety-Critical Gradient Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradsafe-detecting-unsafe-prompts-for-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose GradSafe, which effectively detects unsafe prompts by scrutinizing the gradients of safety-critical parameters in LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradsafe-detecting-unsafe-prompts-for-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the HISCO Barrier: Automatic Occupational Standardization with OccCANINE</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-hisco-barrier-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a new tool, OccCANINE, to automatically transform occupational descriptions into the HISCO classification system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-hisco-barrier-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProSparse: Introducing and Enhancing Intrinsic Activation Sparsity within Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prosparse-introducing-and-enhancing-intrinsic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some recent efforts have explored introducing ReLU or its variants as the substitutive activation function to help LLMs achieve activation sparsity and inference acceleration, but few can simultaneously obtain high sparsity and comparable model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prosparse-introducing-and-enhancing-intrinsic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delving into Dark Regions for Robust Shadow Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delving-into-dark-regions-for-robust-shadow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our key insight to this problem is that existing methods typically learn discriminative shadow features from the whole image globally, covering the full range of intensity values, and may not learn the subtle differences between shadow and non-shadow pixels in dark regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delving-into-dark-regions-for-robust-shadow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PQA: Zero-shot Protein Question Answering for Free-form Scientific Enquiry with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pqa-zero-shot-protein-question-answering-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the novel task of zero-shot Protein Question Answering (PQA) for free-form scientific enquiry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pqa-zero-shot-protein-question-answering-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BenchCloudVision: A Benchmark Analysis of Deep Learning Approaches for Cloud Detection and Segmentation in Remote Sensing Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchcloudvision-a-benchmark-analysis-of-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within this context, this paper focus on the cloud segmentation from remote sensing imagery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchcloudvision-a-benchmark-analysis-of-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple and Yet Fairly Effective Defense for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-and-yet-fairly-effective-defense-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Successful combinations of our NoisyGNN approach with existing defense techniques demonstrate even further improved adversarial defense results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-and-yet-fairly-effective-defense-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse and Structured Hopfield Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-and-structured-hopfield-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern Hopfield networks have enjoyed recent interest due to their connection to attention in transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-and-structured-hopfield-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Reinforcement Learning Agents with Local Guides</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-reinforcement-learning-agents-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the problem of integrating local guide policies into a Reinforcement Learning agent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-reinforcement-learning-agents-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neeko: Leveraging Dynamic LoRA for Efficient Multi-Character Role-Playing Agent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neeko-leveraging-dynamic-lora-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have revolutionized open-domain dialogue agents but encounter challenges in multi-character role-playing (MCRP) scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neeko-leveraging-dynamic-lora-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PaCKD: Pattern-Clustered Knowledge Distillation for Compressing Memory Access Prediction Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/packd-pattern-clustered-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNNs) have proven to be effective models for accurate Memory Access Prediction (MAP), a critical task in mitigating memory latency through data prefetching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/packd-pattern-clustered-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Update of Regression Trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-update-of-regression-trees</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim to use the notion of empirical stability and design algorithms for updating regression trees that provide a way to balance between predictability and empirical stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-update-of-regression-trees</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Effectiveness of Graph Contrastive Learning on Mathematical Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effectiveness-of-graph-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper details an empirical investigation into using Graph Contrastive Learning (GCL) to generate mathematical equation representations, a critical aspect of Mathematical Information Retrieval (MIR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effectiveness-of-graph-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Effect of Batch Size on Contrastive Self-Supervised Speech Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-batch-size-on-contrastive-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then show that the quality of the pre-trained model depends mainly on the amount of speech data seen during training, i. e., on the product of batch size and number of iterations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-batch-size-on-contrastive-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ActiveRAG: Revealing the Treasures of Knowledge via Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activerag-revealing-the-treasures-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) has introduced a new paradigm for Large Language Models (LLMs), aiding in the resolution of knowledge-intensive tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activerag-revealing-the-treasures-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STENCIL: Submodular Mutual Information Based Weak Supervision for Cold-Start Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stencil-submodular-mutual-information-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As supervised fine-tuning of pre-trained models within NLP applications increases in popularity, larger corpora of annotated data are required, especially with increasing parameter counts in large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stencil-submodular-mutual-information-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysing The Impact of Sequence Composition on Language Model Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysing-the-impact-of-sequence-composition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we find that applying causal masking can lead to the inclusion of distracting information from previous documents during pre-training, which negatively impacts the performance of the models on language modelling and downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysing-the-impact-of-sequence-composition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual Coreference Resolution in Low-resource South Asian Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-coreference-resolution-in-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a Translated dataset for Multilingual Coreference Resolution (TransMuCoRes) in 31 South Asian languages using off-the-shelf tools for translation and word-alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-coreference-resolution-in-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimPro: A Simple Probabilistic Framework Towards Realistic Long-Tailed Semi-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simpro-a-simple-probabilistic-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in semi-supervised learning have focused on a more realistic yet challenging task: addressing imbalances in labeled data while the class distribution of unlabeled data remains both unknown and potentially mismatched.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simpro-a-simple-probabilistic-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSLR: Diversity Enhancement and Structure Learning for Rehearsal-based Graph Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dslr-diversity-enhancement-and-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the replay buffer in rehearsal-based approaches for graph continual learning (GCL) methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dslr-diversity-enhancement-and-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Round Trip Translation Defence against Large Language Model Jailbreaking Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/round-trip-translation-defence-against-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose the Round Trip Translation (RTT) method, the first algorithm specifically designed to defend against social-engineered attacks on LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/round-trip-translation-defence-against-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preserving Near-Optimal Gradient Sparsification Cost for Scalable Distributed Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-near-optimal-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Communication overhead is a major obstacle to scaling distributed training systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-near-optimal-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ouroboros: Speculative Decoding with Large Model Enhanced Drafting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ouroboros-speculative-decoding-with-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Ouroboros, which constructs a phrase candidate pool from the verification process of LLMs to provide candidates for draft generation of the small model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ouroboros-speculative-decoding-with-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KInIT at SemEval-2024 Task 8: Fine-tuned LLMs for Multilingual Machine-Generated Text Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kinit-at-semeval-2024-task-8-fine-tuned-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SemEval-2024 Task 8 is focused on multigenerator, multidomain, and multilingual black-box machine-generated text detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kinit-at-semeval-2024-task-8-fine-tuned-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coercing LLMs to do and reveal (almost) anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coercing-llms-to-do-and-reveal-almost</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It has recently been shown that adversarial attacks on large language models (LLMs) can "jailbreak" the model into making harmful statements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coercing-llms-to-do-and-reveal-almost</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLXP: A framework for conducting replicable Machine Learning eXperiments in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlxp-a-framework-for-conducting-replicable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Replicability in machine learning (ML) research is increasingly concerning due to the utilization of complex non-deterministic algorithms and the dependence on numerous hyper-parameter choices, such as model architecture and training datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlxp-a-framework-for-conducting-replicable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Poison Large Language Models During Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-poison-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advent of Large Language Models (LLMs) has marked significant achievements in language processing and reasoning capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-poison-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models for Data Annotation: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-data-annotation-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the paper includes an in-depth taxonomy of methodologies employing LLMs for data annotation, a comprehensive review of learning strategies for models incorporating LLM-generated annotations, and a detailed discussion on primary challenges and limitations associated with using LLMs for data annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-data-annotation-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structured Tree Alignment for Evaluation of (Speech) Constituency Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-tree-alignment-for-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the structured average intersection-over-union ratio (STRUCT-IOU), a similarity metric between constituency parse trees motivated by the problem of evaluating speech parsers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-tree-alignment-for-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOOM: Robust Visual Object Odometry and Mapping using Hierarchical Landmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voom-robust-visual-object-odometry-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, local bundle adjustment is performed utilizing the objects and points-based covisibility graphs in our visual object mapping process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voom-robust-visual-object-odometry-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Debiasing for Graph-based Collaborative Filtering via Adversarial Graph Dropout</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-debiasing-for-graph-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we have discovered that this aggregation mechanism comes with a drawback, which amplifies biases present in the interaction graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-debiasing-for-graph-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffPLF: A Conditional Diffusion Model for Probabilistic Forecasting of EV Charging Load</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffplf-a-conditional-diffusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accordingly, we devise a novel Diffusion model termed DiffPLF for Probabilistic Load Forecasting of EV charging, which can explicitly approximate the predictive load distribution conditioned on historical data and related covariates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffplf-a-conditional-diffusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear-Time Graph Neural Networks for Scalable Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-time-graph-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Linear-Time Graph Neural Network (LTGNN) to scale up GNN-based recommender systems to achieve comparable scalability as classic MF approaches while maintaining GNNs' powerful expressiveness for superior prediction accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-time-graph-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOv9: Learning What You Want to Learn Using Programmable Gradient Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov9-learning-what-you-want-to-learn-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It can be used to obtain complete information, so that train-from-scratch models can achieve better results than state-of-the-art models pre-trained using large datasets, the comparison results are shown in Figure 1.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov9-learning-what-you-want-to-learn-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Building Multilingual Language Model for Medicine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-building-multilingual-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to develop an open-source, multilingual language model for medicine, that the benefits a wider, linguistically diverse audience from different regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-building-multilingual-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RealCompo: Dynamic Equilibrium between Realism and Compositionality Improves Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realcompo-dynamic-equilibrium-between-realism</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new training-free and transferred-friendly text-to-image generation framework, namely RealCompo, which aims to leverage the advantages of text-to-image and layout-to-image models to enhance both realism and compositionality of the generated images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realcompo-dynamic-equilibrium-between-realism</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Softmax Probabilities (Mostly) Predict Large Language Model Correctness on Multiple-Choice Q&amp;A</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softmax-probabilities-mostly-predict-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although large language models (LLMs) perform impressively on many tasks, overconfidence remains a problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softmax-probabilities-mostly-predict-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Graph Reasoning for Fact Checking over Texts and Tables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-reasoning-for-fact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose a novel word-level Heterogeneous-graph-based model for Fact Checking over unstructured and structured information, namely HeterFC.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-reasoning-for-fact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multivariate Functional Linear Discriminant Analysis for the Classification of Short Time Series with Missing Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multivariate-functional-linear-discriminant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in the age of large multivariate and incomplete data, statistical dependencies between features must be estimated in a computationally tractable way, while also dealing with missing data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multivariate-functional-linear-discriminant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FormulaQA: A Question Answering Dataset for Formula-Based Numerical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/formulaqa-a-question-answering-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The application of formulas is a fundamental ability of humans when addressing numerical reasoning problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/formulaqa-a-question-answering-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards accelerating physical discovery via non-interactive and interactive multi-fidelity Bayesian Optimization: Current challenges and future opportunities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-accelerating-physical-discovery-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Both computational and experimental material discovery bring forth the challenge of exploring multidimensional and often non-differentiable parameter spaces, such as phase diagrams of Hamiltonians with multiple interactions, composition spaces of combinatorial libraries, processing spaces, and molecular embedding spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-accelerating-physical-discovery-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling physics-informed hard constraints with mixture-of-experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-physics-informed-hard-constraints</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach imposes the constraint over smaller decomposed domains, each of which is solved by an "expert" through differentiable optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-physics-informed-hard-constraints</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuanTest: Entanglement-Guided Testing of Quantum Neural Network Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantest-entanglement-guided-testing-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, QuanTest formulates the problem of generating test inputs that maximize the quantum entanglement sufficiency and capture incorrect behaviors of the QNN system as a joint optimization problem and solves it in a gradient-based manner to generate quantum adversarial examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantest-entanglement-guided-testing-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIDLAR: Forecast-Informed Deep Learning Architecture for Flood Mitigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fidlar-forecast-informed-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FIDLAR seamlessly integrates two neural network modules: one called the Flood Manager, which is responsible for generating water pre-release schedules, and another called the Flood Evaluator, which assesses these generated schedules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fidlar-forecast-informed-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLO-Ant: A Lightweight Detector via Depthwise Separable Convolutional and Large Kernel Design for Antenna Interference Source Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo-ant-a-lightweight-detector-via-depthwise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, an antenna dataset is created to address important antenna interference source detection issues and serves as the basis for subsequent research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo-ant-a-lightweight-detector-via-depthwise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhythmFormer: Extracting rPPG Signals Based on Hierarchical Temporal Periodic Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rhythmformer-extracting-rppg-signals-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the periodicity nature of rPPG, the long-range dependency capturing capacity of the Transformer was assumed to be advantageous for such signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rhythmformer-extracting-rppg-signals-based-on</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
