<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 09:13:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Radiograph Representation Learning with Masked Record Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-radiograph-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern studies in radiograph representation learning rely on either self-supervision to encode invariant semantics or associated radiology reports to incorporate medical expertise, while the complementarity between them is barely noticed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-radiograph-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Persistent Homology provide an efficient alternative for Evaluation of Knowledge Graph Completion Methods?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-persistent-homology-provide-an-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[$\mathcal{KP}$ addresses this by representing the topology of the KG completion methods through the lens of topological data analysis, concretely using persistent homology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-persistent-homology-provide-an-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Attributed Graph Alignment via Joint Structure Learning and Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-attributed-graph-alignment-via-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the graphs to be aligned are usually constructed from different sources, the inconsistency issues of structures and features between two graphs are ubiquitous in real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-attributed-graph-alignment-via-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then extend the count-min sketch to a Higher-Order sketch to capture complex relations in graph data, and to reduce detecting suspicious dense subgraph problem to finding a dense submatrix in constant time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaming-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winning Solution of Real Robot Challenge III</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/winning-solution-of-real-robot-challenge-iii</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our experiments, when learning from the expert datasets, we find standard Behavioral Cloning (BC) outperforms state-of-the-art offline RL algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/winning-solution-of-real-robot-challenge-iii</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Efficacy of Metrics to Describe Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-efficacy-of-metrics-to-describe</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To test defenses, diverse adversarial attacks are crafted, that are usually described in terms of their evading capability and the L0, L1, L2, and Linf norms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-efficacy-of-metrics-to-describe</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying Context Mixing in Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-context-mixing-in-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-attention weights and their transformed variants have been the main source of information for analyzing token-to-token interactions in Transformer-based models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-context-mixing-in-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalization on the Unseen, Logic Reasoning and Degree Curriculum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalization-on-the-unseen-logic-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper considers the learning of logical (Boolean) functions with focus on the generalization on the unseen (GOTU) setting, a strong case of out-of-distribution generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalization-on-the-unseen-logic-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Neuron Interpretation Methods of NLP Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-neuron-interpretation-methods-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose an evaluation framework that measures the compatibility of a neuron analysis method with other methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-neuron-interpretation-methods-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Secret of Metaphor on Expressing Stronger Emotion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-secret-of-metaphor-on-expressing-stronger</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Metaphors are proven to have stronger emotional impact than literal expressions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-secret-of-metaphor-on-expressing-stronger</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A theory of continuous generative flow networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-theory-of-continuous-generative-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative flow networks (GFlowNets) are amortized variational inference algorithms that are trained to sample from unnormalized target distributions over compositional objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-theory-of-continuous-generative-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Meta-Learning for Partially Observable Few-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-meta-learning-for-partially</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our approach on an adaptation of a comprehensive few-shot learning benchmark, Meta-Dataset, and demonstrate the benefits of POEM over other meta-learning methods at representation learning from partial observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-meta-learning-for-partially</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLIP-2: Bootstrapping Language-Image Pre-training with Frozen Image Encoders and Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blip-2-bootstrapping-language-image-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The cost of vision-and-language pre-training has become increasingly prohibitive due to end-to-end training of large-scale models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blip-2-bootstrapping-language-image-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AudioEar: Single-View Ear Reconstruction for Personalized Spatial Audio</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audioear-single-view-ear-reconstruction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose to achieve personalized spatial audio by reconstructing 3D human ears with single-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audioear-single-view-ear-reconstruction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edge-guided Multi-domain RGB-to-TIR image Translation for Training Vision Tasks with Challenging Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge-guided-multi-domain-rgb-to-tir-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The insufficient number of annotated thermal infrared (TIR) image datasets not only hinders TIR image-based deep learning networks to have comparable performances to that of RGB but it also limits the supervised learning of TIR image-based tasks with challenging labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge-guided-multi-domain-rgb-to-tir-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedFA: Federated Feature Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedfa-federated-feature-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reach this goal, we propose FedFA to tackle federated learning from a distinct perspective of federated feature augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedfa-federated-feature-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeaFormer: Squeeze-enhanced Axial Transformer for Mobile Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seaformer-squeeze-enhanced-axial-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Coupled with a light segmentation head, we achieve the best trade-off between segmentation accuracy and latency on the ARM-based mobile devices on the ADE20K and Cityscapes datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seaformer-squeeze-enhanced-axial-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSR-TA: Sequence to Sequence based expert recurrent recommendation for ticket automation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssr-ta-sequence-to-sequence-based-expert</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recurrent recommendation network recommends the appropriate expert based on the assumption that the previous expert in the recommendation sequence cannot solve the expert.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssr-ta-sequence-to-sequence-based-expert</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protein Representation Learning via Knowledge Enhanced Primary Structure Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/protein-representation-learning-via-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Protein representation learning has primarily benefited from the remarkable development of language models (LMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/protein-representation-learning-via-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding the Law: Enhancing Statutory Article Retrieval via Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-the-law-enhancing-statutory-article</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Statutory article retrieval (SAR), the task of retrieving statute law articles relevant to a legal question, is a promising application of legal text processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-the-law-enhancing-statutory-article</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TrFedDis: Trusted Federated Disentangling Network for Non-IID Domain Feature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trfeddis-trusted-federated-disentangling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, our proposed TrFedDis is the first work to develop an FL approach based on evidential uncertainty combined with feature disentangling, which enhances the performance and reliability of FL in non-IID domain features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trfeddis-trusted-federated-disentangling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio-Visual Segmentation with Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-visual-segmentation-with-semantics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To deal with these problems, we propose a new baseline method that uses a temporal pixel-wise audio-visual interaction module to inject audio semantics as guidance for the visual segmentation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-visual-segmentation-with-semantics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Slot Attention by Changing Optimal Transport Costs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-slot-attention-by-changing-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Slot attention is a powerful method for object-centric modeling in images and videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-slot-attention-by-changing-optimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularized Weight Aggregation in Networked Federated Learning for Glioblastoma Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularized-weight-aggregation-in-networked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a practical and cost-efficient method for regularized weight aggregation and propose a laborsaving technique to select collaborators per round.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularized-weight-aggregation-in-networked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Tuning Deteriorates General Textual Out-of-Distribution Detection by Distorting Task-Agnostic Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-deteriorates-general-textual-out</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that: (1) no existing method behaves well in both settings; (2) fine-tuning PLMs on in-distribution data benefits detecting semantic shifts but severely deteriorates detecting non-semantic shifts, which can be attributed to the distortion of task-agnostic features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-deteriorates-general-textual-out</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Robustness to Adversarial Image Obfuscations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-robustness-to-adversarial-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate 33 pretrained models on the benchmark and train models with different augmentations, architectures and training methods on subsets of the obfuscations to measure generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-robustness-to-adversarial-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALIP: Generative Adversarial CLIPs for Text-to-Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galip-generative-adversarial-clips-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The complex scene understanding ability of CLIP enables the discriminator to accurately assess the image quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galip-generative-adversarial-clips-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning with High-Cardinality Categorical Features in Actuarial Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-with-high-cardinality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The GLMMNet integrates a generalised linear mixed model in a deep learning framework, offering the predictive power of neural networks and the transparency of random effects estimates, the latter of which cannot be obtained from the entity embedding models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-with-high-cardinality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AudioLDM: Text-to-Audio Generation with Latent Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audioldm-text-to-audio-generation-with-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By learning the latent representations of audio signals and their compositions without modeling the cross-modal relationship, AudioLDM is advantageous in both generation quality and computational efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audioldm-text-to-audio-generation-with-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HeroNet: A Hybrid Retrieval-Generation Network for Conversational Bots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heronet-a-hybrid-retrieval-generation-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the retrieval performance is improved while the model size is reduced by training two lightweight, task-specific adapter modules that share only one underlying T5-Encoder model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heronet-a-hybrid-retrieval-generation-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Verifying the Geometric Robustness of Large-scale Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-verifying-the-geometric-robustness-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNNs) are known to be vulnerable to adversarial geometric transformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-verifying-the-geometric-robustness-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast-BEV: A Fast and Strong Bird's-Eye View Perception Baseline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-bev-a-fast-and-strong-bird-s-eye-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our Fast-BEV consists of five parts, We novelly propose (1) a lightweight deployment-friendly view transformation which fast transfers 2D image feature to 3D voxel space, (2) an multi-scale image encoder which leverages multi-scale information for better performance, (3) an efficient BEV encoder which is particularly designed to speed up on-vehicle inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-bev-a-fast-and-strong-bird-s-eye-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Accuracy-Robustness Trade-off of Classifiers via Adaptive Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-accuracy-robustness-trade-off</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide theoretical analyses to motivate the use of the adaptive smoothing procedure, certify the robustness of the smoothed classifier under realistic assumptions, and justify the introduction of the policy network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-accuracy-robustness-trade-off</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kernelized Cumulants: Beyond Kernel Mean Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernelized-cumulants-beyond-kernel-mean</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In $\mathbb R^d$, it is well-known that cumulants provide an alternative to moments that can achieve the same goals with numerous benefits such as lower variance estimators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernelized-cumulants-beyond-kernel-mean</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Dialogue Summarization with Topic-Aware Global- and Local- Level Centrality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-dialogue-summarization-with-topic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The global one aims to identify vital sub-topics in the dialogue and the local one aims to select the most important context in each sub-topic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-dialogue-summarization-with-topic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Regularization for Group Sparsity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-regularization-for-group-sparsity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the implicit regularization of gradient descent towards structured sparsity via a novel neural reparameterization, which we call a diagonally grouped linear neural network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-regularization-for-group-sparsity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pipe-BD: Pipelined Parallel Blockwise Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pipe-bd-pipelined-parallel-blockwise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this results in a high overhead of redundant teacher execution, low GPU utilization, and extra data loading.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pipe-bd-pipelined-parallel-blockwise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhyCV: The First Physics-inspired Computer Vision Library</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phycv-the-first-physics-inspired-computer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PhyCV is the first computer vision library which utilizes algorithms directly derived from the equations of physics governing physical phenomena.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phycv-the-first-physics-inspired-computer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confidence-Aware Calibration and Scoring Functions for Curriculum Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-aware-calibration-and-scoring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we integrate notions of model confidence and human confidence with label smoothing, respectively \textit{Model Confidence LS} and \textit{Human Confidence LS}, to achieve better model calibration and generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-aware-calibration-and-scoring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Subgraph Representation Learning for Scalable Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-subgraph-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Link prediction on graphs is a fundamental problem in graph representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-subgraph-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schema-Guided Semantic Accuracy: Faithfulness in Task-Oriented Dialogue Response Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/schema-guided-semantic-accuracy-faithfulness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that SGSAcc can be applied to evaluate utterances generated from a wide range of dialogue actions in the Schema Guided Dialogue (SGD) dataset with good agreement with human judgment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/schema-guided-semantic-accuracy-faithfulness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Mixer Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-mixer-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the attention mechanism has demonstrated superior performance in various tasks, leading to the emergence of GAT and Graph Transformer models that utilize this mechanism to extract relational information from graph-structured data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-mixer-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Datasets for Federated Survival Analysis Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-datasets-for-federated-survival</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the data needed to train survival models are often distributed, incomplete, censored, and confidential.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-datasets-for-federated-survival</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Optimal Features via Partial Invariance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-optimal-features-via-partial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose the notion of partial invariance as a relaxation of the IRM framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-optimal-features-via-partial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pragmatic Fairness: Developing Policies with Outcome Disparity Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pragmatic-fairness-developing-policies-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a causal framework for designing optimal policies that satisfy fairness constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pragmatic-fairness-developing-policies-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoPEFT: Automatic Configuration Search for Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopeft-automatic-configuration-search-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, it is non-trivial to make informed per-task design choices (i. e., to create PEFT configurations) concerning the selection of PEFT architectures and modules, the number of tunable parameters, and even the layers in which the PEFT modules are inserted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopeft-automatic-configuration-search-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selecting Models based on the Risk of Damage Caused by Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-models-based-on-the-risk-of-damage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In experiments, we demonstrate that the estimation results of our method have a clear and actionable interpretation and outperform conventional metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-models-based-on-the-risk-of-damage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutual Wasserstein Discrepancy Minimization for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-wasserstein-discrepancy-minimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wasserstein Discrepancy Measurement builds upon the 2-Wasserstein distance, which is more robust, more efficient in small batch sizes, and able to model the uncertainty of stochastic augmentation processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-wasserstein-discrepancy-minimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Decreases Editing Capability? Domain-Specific Hybrid Refinement for Improved GAN Inversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-decreases-editing-capability-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, we introduce Domain-Specific Hybrid Refinement (DHR), which draws on the advantages and disadvantages of two mainstream refinement techniques to maintain editing ability with fidelity improvement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-decreases-editing-capability-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Federated Learning Really Need Backpropagation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-federated-learning-really-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BAFFLE is 1) memory-efficient and easily fits uploading bandwidth; 2) compatible with inference-only hardware optimization and model quantization or pruning; and 3) well-suited to trusted execution environments, because the clients in BAFFLE only execute forward propagation and return a set of scalars to the server.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-federated-learning-really-need</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
