<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 21:06:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of Label-Description Training for Zero-Shot Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-benefits-of-label-description-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models have improved zero-shot text classification by allowing the transfer of semantic knowledge from the training data in order to classify among specific label sets in downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-benefits-of-label-description-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling-up Remote Sensing Segmentation Dataset with Segment Anything Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-remote-sensing-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of the Segment Anything Model (SAM) demonstrates the significance of data-centric machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-remote-sensing-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Glitch in the Matrix!": A Large Scale Benchmark for Content Driven Audio-Visual Forgery Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glitch-in-the-matrix-a-large-scale-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed baseline method, Boundary Aware Temporal Forgery Detection (BA-TFD), is a 3D Convolutional Neural Network-based architecture which efficiently captures multimodal manipulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glitch-in-the-matrix-a-large-scale-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>District-scale surface temperatures generated from high-resolution longitudinal thermal infrared images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/district-scale-surface-temperatures-generated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rooftop infrared thermography observatory with a multi-modal platform that is capable of assessing a wide range of dynamic processes in urban systems was deployed in Singapore.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/district-scale-surface-temperatures-generated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AttenWalker: Unsupervised Long-Document Question Answering via Attention-based Graph Walking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attenwalker-unsupervised-long-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate the problem, it might be possible to generate long-document QA pairs via unsupervised question answering (UQA) methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attenwalker-unsupervised-long-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Natural Language Watermarking through Invariant Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-natural-language-watermarking-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have witnessed a proliferation of valuable original natural language contents found in subscription-based media outlets, web novel platforms, and outputs of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-natural-language-watermarking-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NorQuAD: Norwegian Question Answering Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/norquad-norwegian-question-answering-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present NorQuAD: the first Norwegian question answering dataset for machine reading comprehension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/norquad-norwegian-question-answering-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding cirrus clouds using explainable machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-cirrus-clouds-using-explainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Their dependencies on meteorological and aerosol conditions are among the largest uncertainties in global climate models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-cirrus-clouds-using-explainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Synthetic Documents for Cross-Encoder Re-Rankers: A Comparative Study of ChatGPT and Human Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-synthetic-documents-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new dataset, ChatGPT-RetrievalQA, and compare the effectiveness of models fine-tuned on LLM-generated and human-generated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-synthetic-documents-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Contrastive Learning of Sentence Embeddings from AI Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-contrastive-learning-of-sentence-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method utilizes AI feedback from large pre-trained language models (LLMs) to construct sample pairs with fine-grained sample similarity scores to improve contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-contrastive-learning-of-sentence-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shotgun crystal structure prediction using machine-learned formation energies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shotgun-crystal-structure-prediction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stable or metastable crystal structures of assembled atoms can be predicted by finding the global or local minima of the energy surface with respect to the atomic configurations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shotgun-crystal-structure-prediction-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causality-aware Concept Extraction based on Knowledge-guided Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-aware-concept-extraction-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prompt adopts the topic of the given entity from the existing knowledge in KGs to mitigate the spurious co-occurrence correlations between entities and biased concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-aware-concept-extraction-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Encoding of Satellite Image Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-encoding-of-satellite-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representation learning of Satellite Image Time Series (SITS) presents its unique challenges, such as prohibitive computation burden caused by high spatiotemporal resolutions, irregular acquisition times, and complex spatiotemporal interactions, leading to highly-specialized neural network architectures for SITS analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-encoding-of-satellite-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Supervised Segmentation of Functional Tissue Units at the Cellular Level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-segmentation-of-functional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new method for functional tissue unit segmentation at the cellular level, which utilizes the latest deep learning semantic segmentation approaches together with domain adaptation and semi-supervised learning techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-segmentation-of-functional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Data Augmentation for Image Captioning using Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-data-augmentation-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image captioning, an important vision-language task, often requires a tremendous number of finely labeled image-caption pairs for learning the underlying alignment between images and texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-data-augmentation-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-train and Search: Efficient Embedding Table Sharding with Pre-trained Neural Cost Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-train-and-search-efficient-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore a "pre-train, and search" paradigm for efficient sharding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-train-and-search-efficient-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeGen2: Lessons for Training LLMs on Programming and Natural Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codegen2-lessons-for-training-llms-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we attempt to render the training of LLMs for program synthesis more efficient by unifying four key components: (1) model architectures, (2) learning methods, (3) infill sampling, and, (4) data distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codegen2-lessons-for-training-llms-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering ChatGPT's Capabilities in Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-chatgpt-s-capabilities-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The debut of ChatGPT has recently attracted the attention of the natural language processing (NLP) community and beyond.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-chatgpt-s-capabilities-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Neural Divide-and-Conquer Reasoning Framework for Image Retrieval from Linguistically Complex Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-divide-and-conquer-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the Divide-and-Conquer algorithm and dual-process theory, in this paper, we regard linguistically complex texts as compound proposition texts composed of multiple simple proposition sentences and propose an end-to-end Neural Divide-and-Conquer Reasoning framework, dubbed NDCR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-divide-and-conquer-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Sparse Training with Structured Sparsity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-sparse-training-with-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DST methods achieve state-of-the-art results in sparse neural network training, matching the generalization of dense models while enabling sparse training and inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-sparse-training-with-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Being Parameter-Efficient: A Stratified Sparsely Activated Transformer with Dynamic Capacity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-being-parameter-efficient-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, recent studies have established that MoE models are inherently parameter-inefficient as the improvement in performance diminishes with an increasing number of experts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-being-parameter-efficient-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysing the Impact of Audio Quality on the Use of Naturalistic Long-Form Recordings for Infant-Directed Speech Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysing-the-impact-of-audio-quality-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that the use of modest and high audio quality naturalistic speech data result in largely similar conclusions on IDS and ADS in terms of acoustic analyses and modelling experiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysing-the-impact-of-audio-quality-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zenseact Open Dataset: A large-scale and diverse multimodal dataset for autonomous driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zenseact-open-dataset-a-large-scale-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing datasets for autonomous driving (AD) often lack diversity and long-range capabilities, focusing instead on 360{\deg} perception and temporal reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zenseact-open-dataset-a-large-scale-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DocLangID: Improving Few-Shot Training to Identify the Language of Historical Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doclangid-improving-few-shot-training-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose DocLangID, a transfer learning approach to identify the language of unlabeled historical documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doclangid-improving-few-shot-training-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lightweight CNN-Transformer Model for Learning Traveling Salesman Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-cnn-transformer-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model consumes approximately 20% less GPU memory usage and has 45% faster inference time compared with other state-of-the-art Transformer-based models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-cnn-transformer-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Exploration of Conditioning Methods in Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-exploration-of-conditioning-methods-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The flexibility and effectiveness of message passing based graph neural networks (GNNs) induced considerable advances in deep learning on graph-structured data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-exploration-of-conditioning-methods-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Dataset Distillation via Deep Generative Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-dataset-distillation-via-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dataset Distillation aims to distill an entire dataset's knowledge into a few synthetic images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-dataset-distillation-via-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Type-enhanced Ensemble Triple Representation via Triple-aware Attention for Cross-lingual Entity Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/type-enhanced-ensemble-triple-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entity alignment(EA) is a crucial task for integrating cross-lingual and cross-domain knowledge graphs(KGs), which aims to discover entities referring to the same real-world object from different KGs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/type-enhanced-ensemble-triple-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Unleash the Power of Large Language Models for Few-shot Relation Extraction?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-unleash-the-power-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scaling language models have revolutionized widespread NLP tasks, yet little comprehensively explored few-shot relation extraction with large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-unleash-the-power-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Local to Global: Navigating Linguistic Diversity in the African Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-local-to-global-navigating-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The focus is on critical problems in NLP related to linguistic diversity and variation across the African continent, specifically with regards to African local di- alects and Arabic dialects that have received little attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-local-to-global-navigating-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expressive Mortality Models through Gaussian Process Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressive-mortality-models-through-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a flexible Gaussian Process (GP) framework for learning the covariance structure of Age- and Year-specific mortality surfaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressive-mortality-models-through-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Term Rhythmic Video Soundtracker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-term-rhythmic-video-soundtracker</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we present Long-Term Rhythmic Video Soundtracker (LORIS), a novel framework to synthesize long-term conditional waveforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-term-rhythmic-video-soundtracker</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pick-a-Pic: An Open Dataset of User Preferences for Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pick-a-pic-an-open-dataset-of-user</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using this web app we build Pick-a-Pic, a large, open dataset of text-to-image prompts and real users' preferences over generated images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pick-a-pic-an-open-dataset-of-user</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-ended search for environments and adapted agents using MAP-Elites</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-ended-search-for-environments-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We want to move one step closer to creating simulated environments similar to the diverse real world, where agents can both find solvable tasks, and adapt to them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-ended-search-for-environments-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Machine Learning for Science with PySR and SymbolicRegression.jl</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-machine-learning-for-science</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PySR was developed to democratize and popularize symbolic regression for the sciences, and is built on a high-performance distributed back-end, a flexible search algorithm, and interfaces with several deep learning packages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-machine-learning-for-science</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unpaired Downscaling of Fluid Flows with Diffusion Bridges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unpaired-downscaling-of-fluid-flows-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a method to downscale idealized geophysical fluid simulations using generative models based on diffusion maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unpaired-downscaling-of-fluid-flows-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stratified Adversarial Robustness with Rejection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stratified-adversarial-robustness-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We theoretically analyze the stratified rejection setting and propose a novel defense method -- Adversarial Training with Consistent Prediction-based Rejection (CPR) -- for building a robust selective classifier.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stratified-adversarial-robustness-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster OreFSDet : A Lightweight and Effective Few-shot Object Detector for Ore Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-orefsdet-a-lightweight-and-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the ore particle size detection, obtaining a sizable amount of high-quality ore labeled data is time-consuming and expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-orefsdet-a-lightweight-and-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single-model uncertainty quantification in neural network potentials does not consistently outperform model ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-model-uncertainty-quantification-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we examine multiple UQ schemes for improving the robustness of NN interatomic potentials (NNIPs) through active learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-model-uncertainty-quantification-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complex Logical Reasoning over Knowledge Graphs using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-logical-reasoning-over-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reasoning over knowledge graphs (KGs) is a challenging task that requires a deep understanding of the complex relationships between entities and the underlying logic of their relations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-logical-reasoning-over-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Neurons in a Haystack: Case Studies with Sparse Probing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-neurons-in-a-haystack-case-studies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite rapid adoption and deployment of large language models (LLMs), the internal computations of these models remain opaque and poorly understood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-neurons-in-a-haystack-case-studies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sentiment Perception Adversarial Attacks on Neural Machine Translation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentiment-perception-adversarial-attacks-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, adversarial attacks for NMT systems are explored from an output perception perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentiment-perception-adversarial-attacks-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-similarity-based super-resolution of photoacoustic angiography from hand-drawn doodles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-similarity-based-super-resolution-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose a novel approach that employs a super-resolution PAA method trained with forged PAA images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-similarity-based-super-resolution-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlimiformer: Long-Range Transformers with Unlimited Length Input</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlimiformer-long-range-transformers-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This way, we can index extremely long input sequences, while every attention head in every decoder layer retrieves its top-$k$ keys, instead of attending to every key.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlimiformer-long-range-transformers-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OTIEA:Ontology-enhanced Triple Intrinsic-Correlation for Cross-lingual Entity Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/otiea-ontology-enhanced-triple-intrinsic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, external resources are usually unavailable in some scenarios especially cross-lingual and cross-domain applications, which reflects the little scalability of these methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/otiea-ontology-enhanced-triple-intrinsic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARBEx: Attentive Feature Extraction with Reliability Balancing for Robust Facial Expression Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbex-attentive-feature-extraction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also employ learnable anchor points in the embedding space with label distributions and multi-head self-attention mechanism to optimize performance against weak predictions with reliability balancing, which is a strategy that leverages anchor points, attention scores, and confidence values to enhance the resilience of label predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbex-attentive-feature-extraction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Tailed Recognition by Mutual Information Maximization between Latent Features and Ground-Truth Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-recognition-by-mutual-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although contrastive learning methods have shown prevailing performance on a variety of representation learning tasks, they encounter difficulty when the training dataset is long-tailed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-recognition-by-mutual-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Factored Action Spaces for Efficient Offline Reinforcement Learning in Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-factored-action-spaces-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the theoretical properties of our approach, identifying scenarios where it is guaranteed to lead to zero bias when used to approximate the Q-function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-factored-action-spaces-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data valuation: The partial ordinal Shapley value for machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-valuation-the-partial-ordinal-shapley</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data valuation using Shapley value has emerged as a prevalent research domain in machine learning applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-valuation-the-partial-ordinal-shapley</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepAqua: Self-Supervised Semantic Segmentation of Wetlands from SAR Images using Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepaqua-self-supervised-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is particularly problematic in wetland detection, where water extent varies over time and space, necessitating multiple annotations for the same area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepaqua-self-supervised-semantic</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
