<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:06:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>RTQ: Rethinking Video-language Understanding Based on Image-text Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rtq-rethinking-video-language-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in video-language understanding have been established on the foundation of image-text models, resulting in promising outcomes due to the shared knowledge between images and videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rtq-rethinking-video-language-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaussian Grouping: Segment and Edit Anything in 3D Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-grouping-segment-and-edit-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose Gaussian Grouping, which extends Gaussian Splatting to jointly reconstruct and segment anything in open-world 3D scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-grouping-segment-and-edit-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weighted Riesz Particles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-riesz-particles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Markov chain Monte Carlo (MCMC) methods are simulated by local exploration of complex statistical distributions, and while bypassing the cumbersome requirement of a specific analytical expression for the target, this stochastic exploration of an uncertain parameter space comes at the expense of a large number of samples, and this computational complexity increases with parameter dimensionality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-riesz-particles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Transferability Estimation for Regression Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-transferability-estimation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider transferability estimation, the problem of estimating how well deep learning models transfer from a source to a target task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-transferability-estimation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object Detector Differences when using Synthetic and Real Training Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-detector-differences-when-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Collecting data while adhering to privacy legislation becomes increasingly difficult and annotating these large datasets is both a resource-heavy and time-consuming task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-detector-differences-when-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matching Weak Informative Ontologies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matching-weak-informative-ontologies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, these ontologies are named as weak informative ontologies (WIOs) and it is challenging for existing methods to matching WIOs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matching-weak-informative-ontologies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age-Based Scheduling for Mobile Edge Computing: A Deep Reinforcement Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/age-based-scheduling-for-mobile-edge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the traditional definition of AoI, it is assumed that the status information can be actively sampled and directly used.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/age-based-scheduling-for-mobile-edge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trained MT Metrics Learn to Cope with Machine-translated References</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trained-mt-metrics-learn-to-cope-with-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural metrics trained on human evaluations of MT tend to correlate well with human judgments, but their behavior is not fully understood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trained-mt-metrics-learn-to-cope-with-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Efficiency Spectrum of Large Language Models: An Algorithmic Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-efficiency-spectrum-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid growth of Large Language Models (LLMs) has been a driving force in transforming various domains, reshaping the artificial general intelligence landscape.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-efficiency-spectrum-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleCrafter: Enhancing Stylized Text-to-Video Generation with Style Adapter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylecrafter-enhancing-stylized-text-to-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we introduce StyleCrafter, a generic method that enhances pre-trained T2V models with a style control adapter, enabling video generation in any style by providing a reference image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylecrafter-enhancing-stylized-text-to-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-continual-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[General-purpose learning systems should improve themselves in open-ended fashion in ever-changing environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-continual-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIFT: Generative Interpretable Fine-Tuning Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gift-generative-interpretable-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the latter, in contrast to the prior art that directly introduce new model parameters (often in low-rank approximation form) to be learned in fine-tuning with downstream data, we propose a method for learning to generate the fine-tuning parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gift-generative-interpretable-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BCN: Batch Channel Normalization for Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bcn-batch-channel-normalization-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Normalization techniques have been widely used in the field of deep learning due to their capability of enabling higher learning rates and are less careful in initialization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bcn-batch-channel-normalization-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Score Distillation: When score distillation meets GAN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-score-distillation-when-score</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing score distillation methods are sensitive to classifier-free guidance (CFG) scale: manifested as over-smoothness or instability at small CFG scales, while over-saturation at large ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-score-distillation-when-score</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Out-Of-Distribution Robustness of Self-Supervised Representation Learning for Phonocardiogram Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-out-of-distribution-robustness-of-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results: We experimentally demonstrate that, depending on its training distribution, the effectiveness of a fully-supervised model can degrade up to 32% when evaluated on unseen data, while SSL models only lose up to 10% or even improve in some cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-out-of-distribution-robustness-of-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian causal discovery from unknown general interventions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-causal-discovery-from-unknown</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of learning causal Directed Acyclic Graphs (DAGs) using combinations of observational and interventional experimental data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-causal-discovery-from-unknown</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Removing Biases from Molecular Representations via Information Maximization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/removing-biases-from-molecular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-throughput drug screening -- using cell imaging or gene expression measurements as readouts of drug effect -- is a critical tool in biotechnology to assess and understand the relationship between the chemical structure and biological activity of a drug.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/removing-biases-from-molecular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstract Syntax Tree for Programming Language Understanding and Representation: How Far Are We?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstract-syntax-tree-for-programming-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To do so, we compare the performance of models trained with code token sequence (Token for short) based code representation and AST-based code representation on three popular types of code-related tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstract-syntax-tree-for-programming-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Clinical Prediction with Transparency: An Explainable AI Approach to Survival Modelling in Residential Aged Care</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-clinical-prediction-with-transparency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Objectives: Develop an interpretable survival model for elderly residential aged care residents using advanced machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-clinical-prediction-with-transparency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Transparency in Coreference Resolution: A Quantum-Inspired Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-transparency-in-coreference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous work extended the QNLP translation to discourse structure using points in a closure of Hilbert spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-transparency-in-coreference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summarization-based Data Augmentation for Document Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/summarization-based-data-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the prevalence of pretrained language models in natural language understanding tasks, understanding lengthy text such as document is still challenging due to the data sparseness problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/summarization-based-data-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Preconditioned Interior Point Method for Support Vector Machines Using an ANOVA-Decomposition and NFFT-Based Matrix-Vector Products</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-preconditioned-interior-point-method-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we consider the numerical solution to the soft-margin support vector machine optimization problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-preconditioned-interior-point-method-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Multimodal Semantic Segmentation via Dual-Prompt Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multimodal-semantic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing approaches often fully fine-tune a dual-branch encoder-decoder framework with a complicated feature fusion strategy for achieving multimodal semantic segmentation, which is training-costly due to the massive parameter updates in feature extraction and fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multimodal-semantic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effect of prolonged use of Smartphones on neck and wrist muscle fatigue using surface EMG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-prolonged-use-of-smartphones-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prolonged smartphone usage is prevalent among young adults in Lima, Peru, with potential implications for musculoskeletal health.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-prolonged-use-of-smartphones-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenStereo: A Comprehensive Benchmark for Stereo Matching and Strong Baseline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openstereo-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our extensive comparative analyses of StereoBase against numerous contemporary stereo matching methods on the SceneFlow dataset demonstrate its remarkably strong performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openstereo-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOT: Self-Training with Patch-Order Permutation for Object-Centric Learning with Autoregressive Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spot-self-training-with-patch-order</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised object-centric learning aims to decompose scenes into interpretable object entities, termed slots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spot-self-training-with-patch-order</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointBeV: A Sparse Approach to BeV Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointbev-a-sparse-approach-to-bev-predictions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose PointBeV, a novel sparse BeV segmentation model operating on sparse BeV cells instead of dense grids.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointbev-a-sparse-approach-to-bev-predictions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeaLLMs -- Large Language Models for Southeast Asia</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seallms-large-language-models-for-southeast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the remarkable achievements of large language models (LLMs) in various tasks, there remains a linguistic bias that favors high-resource languages, such as English, often at the expense of low-resource and regional languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seallms-large-language-models-for-southeast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temperature Balancing, Layer-wise Weight Analysis, and Neural Network Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temperature-balancing-layer-wise-weight-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, the learning rate, which can be interpreted as a temperature-like parameter within the statistical mechanics of learning, plays a crucial role in neural network training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temperature-balancing-layer-wise-weight-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Anatomically Consistent Embedding for Chest Radiography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-anatomically-consistent-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning (SSL) approaches have recently shown substantial success in learning visual representations from unannotated images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-anatomically-consistent-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Parameter-Free Robust Learning using Latent Bernoulli Variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-parameter-free-robust-learning-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an efficient parameter-free approach for statistical learning from corrupted training sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-parameter-free-robust-learning-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoLLiE: Collaborative Training of Large Language Models in an Efficient Way</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collie-collaborative-training-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces CoLLiE, an efficient library that facilitates collaborative training of large language models using 3D parallelism, parameter-efficient fine-tuning (PEFT) methods, and optimizers such as Lion, Adan, Sophia, LOMO and AdaLomo.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collie-collaborative-training-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-Temporal-Decoupled Masked Pre-training for Traffic Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-decoupled-masked-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate forecasting of multivariate traffic flow time series remains challenging due to substantial spatio-temporal heterogeneity and complex long-range correlative patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-decoupled-masked-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLLMs-Augmented Visual-Language Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mllms-augmented-visual-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual-language pre-training (VLP) has achieved remarkable success in multi-modal tasks, largely attributed to the availability of large-scale image-text datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mllms-augmented-visual-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Model Agents Suffer from Compositional Generalization in Web Automation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-model-agents-suffer-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that while existing prompted LMAs (gpt-3. 5-turbo or gpt-4) achieve 94. 0% average success rate on base tasks, their performance degrades to 24. 9% success rate on compositional tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-model-agents-suffer-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Negotiated Representations to Prevent Forgetting in Machine Learning Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/negotiated-representations-to-prevent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By evaluating our method on these challenging datasets, we aim to showcase its potential for addressing catastrophic forgetting and improving the performance of neural networks in continual learning settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/negotiated-representations-to-prevent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Robust Precipitation Forecaster by Temporal Frame Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-precipitation-forecaster-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This achievement not only underscores the effectiveness of our methodologies but also establishes a new standard for deep learning applications in weather forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-precipitation-forecaster-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt-Based Exemplar Super-Compression and Regeneration for Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-based-exemplar-super-compression-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Replay-based methods in class-incremental learning (CIL) have attained remarkable success, as replaying the exemplars of old classes can significantly mitigate catastrophic forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-based-exemplar-super-compression-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RaDialog: A Large Vision-Language Model for Radiology Report Generation and Conversational Assistance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radialog-a-large-vision-language-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational AI tools that can generate and discuss clinically correct radiology reports for a given medical image have the potential to transform radiology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radialog-a-large-vision-language-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAM-DETR: Boundary-Aligned Moment Detection Transformer for Temporal Sentence Grounding in Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bam-detr-boundary-aligned-moment-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, they suffer from the issue of center misalignment raised by the inherent ambiguity of moment centers, leading to inaccurate predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bam-detr-boundary-aligned-moment-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlignBench: Benchmarking Chinese Alignment of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignbench-benchmarking-chinese-alignment-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Alignment has become a critical step for instruction-tuned Large Language Models (LLMs) to become helpful assistants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignbench-benchmarking-chinese-alignment-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Diffusion Prior for Generalizable Pixel-Level Semantic Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-diffusion-prior-for-generalizable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contents generated by recent advanced Text-to-Image (T2I) diffusion models are sometimes too imaginative for existing off-the-shelf property semantic predictors to estimate due to the immitigable domain gap.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-diffusion-prior-for-generalizable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlgym: Large-Scale Safety-Critical Control Environments for Benchmarking Reinforcement Learning Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlgym-large-scale-safety-critical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This project serves the learning for dynamics & control (L4DC) community, aiming to explore key questions: the convergence of RL algorithms in learning control policies; the stability and robustness issues of learning-based controllers; and the scalability of RL algorithms to high- and potentially infinite-dimensional systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlgym-large-scale-safety-critical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advances in 3D Neural Stylization: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-3d-neural-stylization-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on such taxonomy, our survey first revisits the background of neural stylization on 2D images, and then provides in-depth discussions on recent neural stylization methods for 3D data, where we also provide a mini-benchmark on artistic stylization methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-3d-neural-stylization-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$\mathbb{Z}_2\times \mathbb{Z}_2$ Equivariant Quantum Neural Networks: Benchmarking against Classical Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathbb-z-2-times-mathbb-z-2-equivariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that the $\mathbb{Z}_2\times \mathbb{Z}_2$ EQNN and the QNN provide superior performance for smaller parameter sets and modest training data samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathbb-z-2-times-mathbb-z-2-equivariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the convergence of adaptive first order methods: proximal gradient and alternating minimization algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-convergence-of-adaptive-first-order</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon recent works on linesearch-free adaptive proximal gradient methods, this paper proposes AdaPG$^{\pi, r}$, a framework that unifies and extends existing results by providing larger stepsize policies and improved lower bounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-convergence-of-adaptive-first-order</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Routing-Guided Learned Product Quantization for Graph-Based Approximate Nearest Neighbor Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/routing-guided-learned-product-quantization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It suffers from the large-scale $\mathcal{X}$ because a PG with full vectors is too large to fit into the memory, e. g., a billion-scale $\mathcal{X}$ in 128 dimensions would consume nearly 600 GB memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/routing-guided-learned-product-quantization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ElasticDiffusion: Training-free Arbitrary Size Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elasticdiffusion-training-free-arbitrary-size</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose ElasticDiffusion, a novel training-free decoding method that enables pretrained text-to-image diffusion models to generate images with various sizes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elasticdiffusion-training-free-arbitrary-size</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compact3D: Compressing Gaussian Splat Radiance Field Models with Vector Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact3d-compressing-gaussian-splat-radiance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D Gaussian Splatting is a new method for modeling and rendering 3D radiance fields that achieves much faster learning and rendering time compared to SOTA NeRF methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact3d-compressing-gaussian-splat-radiance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Assessing and Benchmarking Risk-Return Tradeoff of Off-Policy Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-assessing-and-benchmarking-risk</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This efficient estimator is characterized by its capability to form the most advantageous policy portfolios, maximizing returns while minimizing risks during online deployment, a nuance that existing metrics typically overlook.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-assessing-and-benchmarking-risk</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
