<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 09:16:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-grained Hallucination Detection and Mitigation in Long-form Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-hallucination-detection-and-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces HaluQuestQA, the first hallucination dataset with localized error annotations for human-written and model-generated LFQA answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-hallucination-detection-and-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Background Shift in Class-Incremental Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-background-shift-in-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, in the case of the second approach, initializing the new class classifier with background knowledge triggers a similar background shift issue, but towards the new classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-background-shift-in-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporally Consistent Stereo Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporally-consistent-stereo-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this coherent state, we introduce a dual-space refinement module to iteratively refine the initialized result in both disparity and disparity gradient spaces, improving estimations in ill-posed regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporally-consistent-stereo-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOTUS: Enabling Semantic Queries with LLMs Over Tables of Unstructured and Structured Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lotus-enabling-semantic-queries-with-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce semantic operators, a declarative programming interface that extends the relational model with composable AI-based operations for semantic queries over datasets (e. g., sorting or aggregating records using natural language criteria).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lotus-enabling-semantic-queries-with-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isometric Representation Learning for Disentangled Latent Space of Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isometric-representation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The latent space of diffusion model mostly still remains unexplored, despite its great success and potential in the field of generative modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isometric-representation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VISA: Reasoning Video Object Segmentation via Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visa-reasoning-video-object-segmentation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a new task, Reasoning Video Object Segmentation (ReasonVOS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visa-reasoning-video-object-segmentation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Multi-Modal and Multi-Attribute Single-Cell Counts with CFGen</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-multi-modal-and-multi-attribute</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative modeling of single-cell RNA-seq data has shown invaluable potential in community-driven tasks such as trajectory inference, batch effect removal and gene expression generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-multi-modal-and-multi-attribute</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask-Free Neuron Concept Annotation for Interpreting Neural Networks in Medical Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-free-neuron-concept-annotation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in deep neural networks have shown promise in aiding disease diagnosis and medical decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-free-neuron-concept-annotation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Pretext Task Learning for Human Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-pretext-task-learning-for-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the final stage, the model aims to address the entire future trajectory task by taking full advantage of the knowledge from previous stages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-pretext-task-learning-for-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An AI System for Continuous Knee Osteoarthritis Severity Grading Using Self-Supervised Anomaly Detection with Limited Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ai-system-for-continuous-knee</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes a three stage approach for automated continuous grading of knee OA that is built upon the principles of Anomaly Detection (AD); learning a robust representation of healthy knee X-rays and grading disease severity based on its distance to the centre of normality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ai-system-for-continuous-knee</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monocular Occupancy Prediction for Scalable Indoor Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-occupancy-prediction-for-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a dataset size 40 times larger than the NYUv2 dataset, it facilitates future scalable research in indoor scene analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-occupancy-prediction-for-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNIT: Backdoor Mitigation via Automated Neural Distribution Tightening</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unit-backdoor-mitigation-via-automated-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While existing works have proposed various methods to mitigate backdoor effects in poisoned models, they tend to be less effective against recent advanced attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unit-backdoor-mitigation-via-automated-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKADA-Bench: Benchmarking Unsupervised Domain Adaptation Methods with Realistic Validation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skada-bench-benchmarking-unsupervised-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised Domain Adaptation (DA) consists of adapting a model trained on a labeled source domain to perform well on an unlabeled target domain with some data distribution shift.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skada-bench-benchmarking-unsupervised-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LRQ: Optimizing Post-Training Quantization for Large Language Models by Learning Low-Rank Weight-Scaling Matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lrq-optimizing-post-training-quantization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the commercialization of large language models (LLMs), weight-activation quantization has emerged to compress and accelerate LLMs, achieving high throughput while reducing inference costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lrq-optimizing-post-training-quantization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nowcasting R&amp;D Expenditures: A Machine Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nowcasting-r-d-expenditures-a-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we leverage the high frequency of our data to derive monthly estimates of R&D expenditures, which are currently unobserved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nowcasting-r-d-expenditures-a-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Guided Generation of Minority Samples Using Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-guided-generation-of-minority-samples</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on benchmark real datasets demonstrate that our approach can greatly improve the capability of creating realistic low-likelihood minority instances over the existing techniques without the reliance on costly additional elements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-guided-generation-of-minority-samples</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imitation of human motion achieves natural head movements for humanoid robots in an active-speaker detection task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imitation-of-human-motion-achieves-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Head movements are crucial for social human-human interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imitation-of-human-motion-achieves-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoFTI: Localization and Factuality Transfer to Indian Locales</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lofti-localization-and-factuality-transfer-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) encode vast amounts of world knowledge acquired via training on large web-scale datasets crawled from the internet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lofti-localization-and-factuality-transfer-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowd-SAM: SAM as a Smart Annotator for Object Detection in Crowded Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crowd-sam-sam-as-a-smart-annotator-for-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In computer vision, object detection is an important task that finds its application in many scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crowd-sam-sam-as-a-smart-annotator-for-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIC-BART-SSA: Controllable Image Captioning with Structured Semantic Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cic-bart-ssa-controllable-image-captioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use this Structured Semantic Augmentation (SSA) framework to augment existing image--caption datasets with the grounded controlled captions, increasing their spatial and semantic diversity and focal coverage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cic-bart-ssa-controllable-image-captioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Diffusion Transformers to 16 Billion Parameters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-diffusion-transformers-to-16-billion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present DiT-MoE, a sparse version of the diffusion Transformer, that is scalable and competitive with dense networks while exhibiting highly optimized inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-diffusion-transformers-to-16-billion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Weighted First Order Model Counting and Graph Polynomials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-weighted-first-order-model-counting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Third, the well-known Tutte polynomial can be recovered as a special case of the Weak Connectedness Polynomial, and the Strict and Non-Strict Directed Chromatic Polynomials can be recovered from the Strong Connectedness Polynomials, which allows us to show that these important graph polynomials can be computed in time polynomial in the number of vertices for any graph that can be encoded by a fixed $C^2$ sentence and a conjunction of an arbitrary number of ground unary literals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-weighted-first-order-model-counting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Feature Selection without Label or Feature Leakage for Interpretable Machine Learning Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-feature-selection-without-label-or</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Local feature selection in machine learning provides instance-specific explanations by focusing on the most relevant features for each prediction, enhancing the interpretability of complex models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-feature-selection-without-label-or</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Separable Video Transformer for Snapshot Compressive Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-separable-video-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have achieved the state-of-the-art performance on solving the inverse problem of Snapshot Compressive Imaging (SCI) for video, whose ill-posedness is rooted in the mixed degradation of spatial masking and temporal aliasing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-separable-video-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SFPNet: Sparse Focal Point Network for Semantic Segmentation on General LiDAR Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfpnet-sparse-focal-point-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although LiDAR semantic segmentation advances rapidly, state-of-the-art methods often incorporate specifically designed inductive bias derived from benchmarks originating from mechanical spinning LiDAR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfpnet-sparse-focal-point-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Refusal Training in LLMs Generalize to the Past Tense?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-refusal-training-in-llms-generalize-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We systematically evaluate this method on Llama-3 8B, GPT-3. 5 Turbo, Gemma-2 9B, Phi-3-Mini, GPT-4o, and R2D2 models using GPT-3. 5 Turbo as a reformulation model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-refusal-training-in-llms-generalize-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cDP-MIL: Robust Multiple Instance Learning via Cascaded Dirichlet Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdp-mil-robust-multiple-instance-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then perform bag-level prediction with another Dirichlet process model on the bags, which imposes a natural regularization on learning to prevent overfitting and enhance generalizability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdp-mil-robust-multiple-instance-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cover-separable Fixed Neural Network Steganography via Deep Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cover-separable-fixed-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image steganography is the process of hiding secret data in a cover image by subtle perturbation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cover-separable-fixed-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schema Matching with Large Language Models: an Experimental Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/schema-matching-with-large-language-models-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study shows that LLMs have potential in bootstrapping the schema matching process and are able to assist data engineers in speeding up this task solely based on schema element names and descriptions without the need for data instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/schema-matching-with-large-language-models-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Fair Graph Neural Networks from Re-balancing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-fair-graph-neural-networks-from-re</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We claim that the imbalance across different demographic groups is a significant source of unfairness, resulting in imbalanced contributions from each group to the parameters updating.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-fair-graph-neural-networks-from-re</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Utility-Preserving Text Anonymization Based on Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-utility-preserving-text-anonymization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text anonymization is crucial for sharing sensitive data while maintaining privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-utility-preserving-text-anonymization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibravox: A Dataset of French Speech Captured with Body-conduction Audio Sensors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vibravox-a-dataset-of-french-speech-captured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vibravox is a dataset compliant with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) containing audio recordings using five different body-conduction audio sensors : two in-ear microphones, two bone conduction vibration pickups and a laryngophone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vibravox-a-dataset-of-french-speech-captured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Theoretical Formulation of Many-body Message Passing Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-theoretical-formulation-of-many-body</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present many-body Message Passing Neural Network (MPNN) framework that models higher-order node interactions ($\ge 2$ nodes).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-theoretical-formulation-of-many-body</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TGIF: Text-Guided Inpainting Forgery Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tgif-text-guided-inpainting-forgery-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As such, this work demonstrates the inefficiency of state-of-the-art detectors on local manipulations performed by modern generative approaches, and aspires to help with the development of more capable IFL and SID methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tgif-text-guided-inpainting-forgery-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Segment Anything Model in Identifying Buildings within Refugee Camps (SAM4Refugee) from Satellite Imagery for Humanitarian Operations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-segment-anything-model-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study explores the utilization of the "Segment Anything Model" (SAM) and one of its branches, SAM-Adapter, for semantic segmentation tasks in the building extraction from satellite imagery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-segment-anything-model-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeedleBench: Can LLMs Do Retrieval and Reasoning in 1 Million Context Window?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/needlebench-can-llms-do-retrieval-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In evaluating the long-context capabilities of large language models (LLMs), identifying content relevant to a user's query from original long documents is a crucial prerequisite for any LLM to answer questions based on long text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/needlebench-can-llms-do-retrieval-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GV-Bench: Benchmarking Local Feature Matching for Geometric Verification of Long-term Loop Closure Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gv-bench-benchmarking-local-feature-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing feature matching methods focus on homography and pose estimation in long-term visual localization, lacking references for geometric verification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gv-bench-benchmarking-local-feature-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DreamCatalyst: Fast and High-Quality 3D Editing via Controlling Editability and Identity Preservation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamcatalyst-fast-and-high-quality-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing SDS-based 3D editing methods suffer from extensive training time and lead to low-quality results, primarily because these methods deviate from the sampling dynamics of diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamcatalyst-fast-and-high-quality-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not Another Imputation Method: A Transformer-based Model for Missing Values in Tabular Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-another-imputation-method-a-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Handling missing values in tabular datasets presents a significant challenge in training and testing artificial intelligence models, an issue usually addressed using imputation techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-another-imputation-method-a-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Confidence Bounds for Classification with Imbalanced Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-confidence-bounds-for-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Class imbalance poses a significant challenge in classification tasks, where traditional approaches often lead to biased models and unreliable predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-confidence-bounds-for-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relation DETR: Exploring Explicit Position Relation Prior for Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relation-detr-exploring-explicit-position</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results on the dataset illustrate that the proposed explicit position relation achieves a clear improvement of 1. 3% AP, highlighting its potential towards universal object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relation-detr-exploring-explicit-position</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying the Theory on Over-Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-the-theory-on-over-smoothing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph convolutions have gained popularity due to their ability to efficiently operate on data with an irregular geometric structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-the-theory-on-over-smoothing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDPT: Synchronous Dual Prompt Tuning for Fusion-based Visual-Language Pre-trained Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdpt-synchronous-dual-prompt-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing prompt tuning methods have not effectively addressed the modal mapping and aligning problem for tokens in different modalities, leading to poor transfer generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdpt-synchronous-dual-prompt-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Split Computing and Early Exit Applications through Predefined Sparsity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-split-computing-and-early-exit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel approach to address this challenge by combining the concept of predefined sparsity with Split Computing (SC) and Early Exit (EE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-split-computing-and-early-exit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Channel Masked Autoencoder and Comprehensive Evaluations for Reconstructing 12-Lead ECG from Arbitrary Single-Lead ECG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-channel-masked-autoencoder-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of cardiovascular diseases (CVD) that exhibit an elevated prevalence and mortality, the electrocardiogram (ECG) is a popular and standard diagnostic tool for doctors, commonly utilizing a 12-lead configuration in clinical practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-channel-masked-autoencoder-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperAggregation: Aggregating over Graph Edges with Hypernetworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperaggregation-aggregating-over-graph-edges</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate HyperAggregation in two models, GraphHyperMixer is a model based on MLP-Mixer while GraphHyperConv is derived from a GCN but with a hypernetwork-based aggregation function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperaggregation-aggregating-over-graph-edges</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Unsupervised Video Object Segmentation via Fake Flow Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-unsupervised-video-object-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised video object segmentation (VOS), also known as video salient object detection, aims to detect the most prominent object in a video at the pixel level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-unsupervised-video-object-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLMEvalKit: An Open-Source Toolkit for Evaluating Large Multi-Modality Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlmevalkit-an-open-source-toolkit-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the evaluation results obtained with the toolkit, we host OpenVLM Leaderboard, a comprehensive leaderboard to track the progress of multi-modality learning research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlmevalkit-an-open-source-toolkit-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Quantization for Efficient Pre-Training of Transformer Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-quantization-for-efficient-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While quantization has proven to be effective after pre-training and during fine-tuning, applying quantization in Transformers during pre-training has remained largely unexplored at scale for language modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-quantization-for-efficient-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Oscars of AI Theater: A Survey on Role-Playing with Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-oscars-of-ai-theater-a-survey-on-role</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This survey explores the burgeoning field of role-playing with language models, focusing on their development from early persona-based models to advanced character-driven simulations facilitated by Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-oscars-of-ai-theater-a-survey-on-role</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
