<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 09:11:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>UMMAFormer: A Universal Multimodal-adaptive Transformer Framework for Temporal Forgery Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ummaformer-a-universal-multimodal-adaptive-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach introduces a Temporal Feature Abnormal Attention (TFAA) module based on temporal feature reconstruction to enhance the detection of temporal differences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ummaformer-a-universal-multimodal-adaptive-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Multi Interest Process Pattern Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-multi-interest-process-pattern</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Process pattern discovery methods (PPDMs) aim at identifying patterns of interest to users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-multi-interest-process-pattern</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cognitive Effects in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cognitive-effects-in-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) such as ChatGPT have received enormous attention over the past year and are now used by hundreds of millions of people every day.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cognitive-effects-in-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoCutLER: Surprisingly Simple Unsupervised Video Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videocutler-surprisingly-simple-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing approaches to unsupervised video instance segmentation typically rely on motion estimates and experience difficulties tracking small or divergent motions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videocutler-surprisingly-simple-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MELT: Mining Effective Lightweight Transformations from Pull Requests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melt-mining-effective-lightweight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By leveraging code examples mined from the library source and automatically generated code examples based on the pull requests, we infer transformation rules in \comby, a language for structural code search and replace.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melt-mining-effective-lightweight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilled GPT for Source Code Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilled-gpt-for-source-code-summarization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A code summary is a brief natural language description of source code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilled-gpt-for-source-code-summarization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1st Place Solution for the 5th LSVOS Challenge: Video Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1st-place-solution-for-the-5th-lsvos</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video instance segmentation is a challenging task that serves as the cornerstone of numerous downstream applications, including video editing and autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1st-place-solution-for-the-5th-lsvos</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongBench: A Bilingual, Multitask Benchmark for Long Context Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longbench-a-bilingual-multitask-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce LongBench, the first bilingual, multi-task benchmark for long context understanding, enabling a more rigorous evaluation of long context understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longbench-a-bilingual-multitask-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the performance of object detection by preserving label distribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-performance-of-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We tested our proposed method not only on public datasets that typically exhibit balanced class distribution but also on custom datasets that may have imbalanced class distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-performance-of-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Referring Image Segmentation Using Text Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/referring-image-segmentation-using-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, we propose a novel weakly-supervised RIS framework to formulate the target localization problem as a classification process to differentiate between positive and negative text expressions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/referring-image-segmentation-using-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face Presentation Attack Detection by Excavating Causal Clues and Adapting Embedding Statistics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-presentation-attack-detection-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We excavate the causal factors hidden in the high-level representation via counterfactual intervention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-presentation-attack-detection-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Existing Out-Of-Distribution Techniques Suitable for Network Intrusion Detection?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-existing-out-of-distribution-techniques</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings suggest that existing detectors can identify a consistent portion of new malicious traffic, and that improved embedding spaces enhance detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-existing-out-of-distribution-techniques</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spoken Language Intelligence of Large Language Models for Language Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spoken-language-intelligence-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our focus is centered on evaluating the efficacy of LLMs in the realm of education, specifically in the areas of spoken language learning which encompass phonetics, phonology, and second language acquisition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spoken-language-intelligence-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Cross-task Protocol Inconsistency for Distillation in Dense Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-cross-task-protocol-inconsistency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, the optimum of the distillation loss does not necessarily lead to the optimal student classification scores for dense object detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-cross-task-protocol-inconsistency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in the Gray: Exploring Moderation Policies in Dialogic Large Language Models vs. Human Answers in Controversial Topics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-in-the-gray-exploring-moderation-policies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The introduction of ChatGPT and the subsequent improvement of Large Language Models (LLMs) have prompted more and more individuals to turn to the use of ChatBots, both for information and assistance with decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-in-the-gray-exploring-moderation-policies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Tradeoff between Privacy Preservation and Byzantine-Robustness in Decentralized Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-tradeoff-between-privacy-preservation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper jointly considers privacy preservation and Byzantine-robustness in decentralized learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-tradeoff-between-privacy-preservation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebalancing Social Feed to Minimize Polarization and Disagreement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rebalancing-social-feed-to-minimize</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Social media have great potential for enabling public discourse on important societal issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rebalancing-social-feed-to-minimize</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task-Aware Machine Unlearning and Its Application in Load Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-aware-machine-unlearning-and-its</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To balance between unlearning completeness and performance degradation, a performance-aware algorithm is proposed by evaluating the sensitivity of local model parameter change using influence function and sample re-weighting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-aware-machine-unlearning-and-its</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compositional Semantic Mix for Domain Adaptation in Point Cloud Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-semantic-mix-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce compositional semantic mixing for point cloud domain adaptation, representing the first unsupervised domain adaptation technique for point cloud segmentation based on semantic and geometric sample mixing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-semantic-mix-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANER: Arabic and Arabizi Named Entity Recognition using Transformer-Based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aner-arabic-and-arabizi-named-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present ANER, a web-based named entity recognizer for the Arabic, and Arabizi languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aner-arabic-and-arabizi-named-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Modification of the Upper Confidence Bound Algorithm by Generalized Weighted Averages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-modification-of-the-upper-confidence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In preliminary experiments, we investigated the optimal parameters of a simple generalized UCB1 (G-UCB1), prepared for comparison and GWA-UCB1, in a stochastic MAB problem with two arms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-modification-of-the-upper-confidence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaceChain: A Playground for Identity-Preserving Portrait Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facechain-a-playground-for-identity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present FaceChain, a personalized portrait generation framework that combines a series of customized image-generation model and a rich set of face-related perceptual understanding models (\eg, face detection, deep face embedding extraction, and facial attribute recognition), to tackle aforementioned challenges and to generate truthful personalized portraits, with only a handful of portrait images as input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facechain-a-playground-for-identity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Multiple Intent Detection and Slot Filling with Supervised Contrastive Learning and Self-Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-multiple-intent-detection-and-slot-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results also demonstrate the contributions of both bidirectional design and the training method to the accuracy improvement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-multiple-intent-detection-and-slot-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UMMAFormer: A Universal Multimodal-adaptive Transformer Framework for Temporal Forgery Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ummaformer-a-universal-multimodal-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach introduces a Temporal Feature Abnormal Attention (TFAA) module based on temporal feature reconstruction to enhance the detection of temporal differences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ummaformer-a-universal-multimodal-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffSmooth: Certifiably Robust Learning via Diffusion Models and Local Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffsmooth-certifiably-robust-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have been leveraged to perform adversarial purification and thus provide both empirical and certified robustness for a standard model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffsmooth-certifiably-robust-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Task Semantic Decomposition Framework with Task-specific Pre-training for Few-Shot NER</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-task-semantic-decomposition-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The objective of few-shot named entity recognition is to identify named entities with limited labeled instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-task-semantic-decomposition-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Visual Tracking and Reaching with Deep Reinforcement Learning on a UR10e Robotic Arm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-visual-tracking-and-reaching-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The report describes the reinforcement learning environments created to facilitate policy learning with the UR10e, a robotic arm from Universal Robots, and presents our initial results in training deep Q-learning and proximal policy optimization agents on the developed reinforcement learning environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-visual-tracking-and-reaching-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HRGCN: Heterogeneous Graph-level Anomaly Detection with Hierarchical Relation-augmented Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrgcn-heterogeneous-graph-level-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the problem, we propose HRGCN, an unsupervised deep heterogeneous graph neural network, to model complex heterogeneous relations between different entities in the system for effectively identifying these anomalous behaviour graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrgcn-heterogeneous-graph-level-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Light Control with Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-light-control-with-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A deep Q network structure with a "phase gate" component is used to simplify the model's learning task under different phases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-light-control-with-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-Aware Composition of Agent Policies by Markov Decision Process Entity Embeddings and Agent Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-composition-of-agent-policies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the environments in which agents operate can be stochastic and complex in terms of the number of states and feasible actions, activities are usually modelled in a simplified way by Markov decision processes so that agents with reinforcement learning are able to learn policies that help to capture the context and act accordingly to optimally perform activities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-composition-of-agent-policies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FonMTL: Towards Multitask Learning for the Fon Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fonmtl-towards-multitask-learning-for-the-fon</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multitask learning is a learning paradigm that aims to improve the generalization capacity of a model by sharing knowledge across different but related tasks: this could be prevalent in very data-scarce scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fonmtl-towards-multitask-learning-for-the-fon</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>360-Degree Panorama Generation from Few Unregistered NFoV Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/360-degree-panorama-generation-from-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[360$^\circ$ panoramas are extensively utilized as environmental light sources in computer graphics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/360-degree-panorama-generation-from-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the KB-Text Gap: Leveraging Structured Knowledge-aware Pre-training for KBQA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-kb-text-gap-leveraging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Base Question Answering (KBQA) aims to answer natural language questions with factual information such as entities and relations in KBs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-kb-text-gap-leveraging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Retrieval: A Systematic Review of Methods and Future Directions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-retrieval-a-systematic-review-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the exponential surge in diverse multi-modal data, traditional uni-modal retrieval methods struggle to meet the needs of users demanding access to data from various modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-retrieval-a-systematic-review-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniPT: Universal Parallel Tuning for Transfer Learning with Efficient Parameter and Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unipt-universal-parallel-tuning-for-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning pre-trained models has emerged as a powerful technique in numerous domains, owing to its ability to leverage enormous pre-existing knowledge and achieve remarkable performance on downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unipt-universal-parallel-tuning-for-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved learning theory for kernel distribution regression with two-stage sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-learning-theory-for-kernel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we improve the learning theory of kernel distribution regression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-learning-theory-for-kernel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balanced Representation Learning for Long-tailed Skeleton-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balanced-representation-learning-for-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, we design a detached action-aware learning schedule to further mitigate the bias in the representation space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balanced-representation-learning-for-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Contrastive Learning for Pattern-Generalizable Image Corruption Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-contrastive-learning-for-pattern</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting corrupted regions by learning the contrastive distinctions rather than the semantic patterns of corruptions, our model has well generalization ability across different corruption patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-contrastive-learning-for-pattern</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PECon: Contrastive Pretraining to Enhance Feature Alignment between CT and EHR Data for Improved Pulmonary Embolism Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pecon-contrastive-pretraining-to-enhance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous deep learning efforts have focused on improving the performance of Pulmonary Embolism(PE) diagnosis from Computed Tomography (CT) scans using Convolutional Neural Networks (CNN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pecon-contrastive-pretraining-to-enhance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The inverse problem for neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-inverse-problem-for-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of computing the preimage of a set under a neural network with piecewise-affine activation functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-inverse-problem-for-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Resolution Document Shadow Removal via A Large-Scale Real-World Dataset and A Frequency-Aware Shadow Erasing Net</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-document-shadow-removal-via-a-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We handle high-resolution document shadow removal directly via a larger-scale real-world dataset and a carefully designed frequency-aware network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-document-shadow-removal-via-a-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical Edge Detection via Robust Collaborative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-edge-detection-via-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Edge detection, as a core component in a wide range of visionoriented tasks, is to identify object boundaries and prominent edges in natural images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-edge-detection-via-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depth self-supervision for single image novel view synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-self-supervision-for-single-image-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we tackle the problem of generating a novel image from an arbitrary viewpoint given a single frame as input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-self-supervision-for-single-image-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconstructing Interacting Hands with Interaction Prior from Monocular Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructing-interacting-hands-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our key idea is to first construct a two-hand interaction prior and recast the interaction reconstruction task as the conditional sampling from the prior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructing-interacting-hands-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-aware Consistency Network for Cloth-changing Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-consistency-network-for-cloth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent progress in CC-ReID, existing approaches are still hindered by the interference of clothing variations since they lack effective constraints to keep the model consistently focused on clothing-irrelevant regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-consistency-network-for-cloth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Transfer Learning Capabilities of CLIP in Domain Generalization for Diabetic Retinopathy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-transfer-learning-capabilities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we investigate CLIP's transfer learning capabilities and its potential for cross-domain generalization in diabetic retinopathy (DR) classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-transfer-learning-capabilities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superpixels algorithms through network community detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superpixels-algorithms-through-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We follow this line of research by studying the efficiency of superpixels computed by state-of-the-art community detection algorithms on a 4-connected pixel graph, so-called pixel-grid.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superpixels-algorithms-through-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Unified Token Learning for Vision-Language Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-unified-token-learning-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a simple, flexible and effective vision-language (VL) tracking pipeline, termed \textbf{MMTrack}, which casts VL tracking as a token generation task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-unified-token-learning-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text Matching Improves Sequential Recommendation by Reducing Popularity Biases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-matching-improves-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TASTE alleviates the cold start problem by representing long-tail items using full-text modeling and bringing the benefits of pretrained language models to recommendation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-matching-improves-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Bloodstain Analysis Through AI-Based Segmentation: Leveraging Segment Anything Model for Crime Scene Investigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-bloodstain-analysis-through-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the application of pre-trained SAM and fine-tuned SAM on bloodstain image segmentation with diverse image backgrounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-bloodstain-analysis-through-ai</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
