<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 21:09:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Target Semantics Clustering via Text Representations for Robust Universal Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-semantics-clustering-via-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Universal Domain Adaptation (UniDA) focuses on transferring source domain knowledge to the target domain under both domain shift and unknown category shift.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-semantics-clustering-via-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BodyGen: Advancing Towards Efficient Embodiment Co-Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bodygen-advancing-towards-efficient-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Embodiment co-design aims to optimize a robot's morphology and control policy simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bodygen-advancing-towards-efficient-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Makes a Good Diffusion Planner for Decision Making?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-makes-a-good-diffusion-planner-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have recently shown significant potential in solving decision-making problems, particularly in generating behavior plans -- also known as diffusion planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-makes-a-good-diffusion-planner-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval Backward Attention without Additional Training: Enhance Embeddings of Large Language Models via Repetition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-backward-attention-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models can be viewed as functions that embed text into Euclidean space, where the quality of the embedding vectors directly determines model performance, training such neural networks involves various uncertainties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-backward-attention-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAMUT: A Novel Framework for Modifying Mathematical Formulas for the Generation of Specialized Datasets for Language Model Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamut-a-novel-framework-for-modifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mathematical formulas are a fundamental and widely used component in various scientific fields, serving as a universal language for expressing complex concepts and relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamut-a-novel-framework-for-modifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TomoSelfDEQ: Self-Supervised Deep Equilibrium Learning for Sparse-Angle CT Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tomoselfdeq-self-supervised-deep-equilibrium-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning has emerged as a powerful tool for solving inverse problems in imaging, including computed tomography (CT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tomoselfdeq-self-supervised-deep-equilibrium-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S4ConvD: Adaptive Scaling and Frequency Adjustment for Energy-Efficient Sensor Networks in Smart Buildings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s4convd-adaptive-scaling-and-frequency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting energy consumption in smart buildings is challenging due to dependencies in sensor data and the variability of environmental conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s4convd-adaptive-scaling-and-frequency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedConv: A Learning-on-Model Paradigm for Heterogeneous Federated Clients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedconv-a-learning-on-model-paradigm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) facilitates collaborative training of a shared global model without exposing clients' private data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedconv-a-learning-on-model-paradigm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRU-Adapter: Frame Recalibration Unit Adapter for Dynamic Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fru-adapter-frame-recalibration-unit-adapter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, the FRU-Adapter captures enhanced temporal dependencies by considering the irrelevant frames in a clip.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fru-adapter-frame-recalibration-unit-adapter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything, Everywhere, All at Once: Is Mechanistic Interpretability Identifiable?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/everything-everywhere-all-at-once-is</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work contributes to defining explanation standards in AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/everything-everywhere-all-at-once-is</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating convolutional layers and biformer network with forward-forward and backpropagation training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-convolutional-layers-and-biformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate molecular property prediction is crucial for drug discovery and computational chemistry, facilitating the identification of promising compounds and accelerating therapeutic development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-convolutional-layers-and-biformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved 3D Point-Line Mapping Regression for Camera Relocalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-3d-point-line-mapping-regression-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce a new architecture that learns to prioritize each feature independently before combining them for localization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-3d-point-line-mapping-regression-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniTok: A Unified Tokenizer for Visual Generation and Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitok-a-unified-tokenizer-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce UniTok, a discrete visual tokenizer that encodes fine-grained details for generation while also capturing high-level semantics for understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitok-a-unified-tokenizer-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exponential Topology-enabled Scalable Communication in Multi-agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exponential-topology-enabled-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fully unlock the potential of exponential graphs as communication topologies, we employ memory-based message processors and auxiliary tasks to ground messages, ensuring that they reflect global information and benefit decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exponential-topology-enabled-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Shot Multilingual Open-Domain QA from 5 Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-multilingual-open-domain-qa-from-5</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent approaches to multilingual open-domain question answering (MLODQA) have achieved promising results given abundant language-specific training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-multilingual-open-domain-qa-from-5</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINEREASON: Evaluating and Improving LLMs' Deliberate Reasoning through Reflective Puzzle Solving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finereason-evaluating-and-improving-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on this, we introduce two tasks: state checking, and state transition, for a comprehensive evaluation of how models assess the current situation and plan the next move.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finereason-evaluating-and-improving-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixtera: A Data Plane for Foundation Model Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixtera-a-data-plane-for-foundation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We build and present Mixtera, a data plane for foundation model training that enables users to declaratively express which data samples should be used in which proportion and in which order during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixtera-a-data-plane-for-foundation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Stance Detection via Small-Large Language Model Consistency Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-stance-detection-via-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, heavily relying on LLMs for stance detection, regardless of the cost, is impractical for real-world social media monitoring systems that require vast data analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-stance-detection-via-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision-Encoders (Already) Know What They See: Mitigating Object Hallucination via Simple Fine-Grained CLIPScore</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-encoders-already-know-what-they-see</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, Large Vision-Language Models (LVLMs) show remarkable performance across various domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-encoders-already-know-what-they-see</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanity Checking Causal Representation Learning on a Simple Real-World System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sanity-checking-causal-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate methods for causal representation learning (CRL) on a simple, real-world system where these methods are expected to work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sanity-checking-causal-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniDepthV2: Universal Monocular Metric Depth Estimation Made Simpler</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidepthv2-universal-monocular-metric-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the remarkable accuracy of recent MMDE methods is confined to their training domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidepthv2-universal-monocular-metric-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensing and Steering Stereotypes: Extracting and Applying Gender Representation Vectors in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensing-and-steering-stereotypes-extracting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are known to perpetuate stereotypes and exhibit biases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensing-and-steering-stereotypes-extracting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Collaborative Anti-Money Laundering Among Financial Institutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-collaborative-anti-money-laundering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results demonstrate that our methods can effectively identify cross-institution money laundering subgroups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-collaborative-anti-money-laundering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Search via Discrete Diffusion: A Study on Chess</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-search-via-discrete-diffusion-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, DiffuSearch demonstrates a notable 30% enhancement in puzzle-solving abilities compared to explicit search-based policies, along with a significant 540 Elo increase in game-playing strength assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-search-via-discrete-diffusion-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R2-T2: Re-Routing in Test-Time for Multimodal Mixture-of-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r2-t2-re-routing-in-test-time-for-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In large multimodal models (LMMs), the perception of non-language modalities (e. g., visual representations) is usually not on par with the large language models (LLMs)' powerful reasoning capabilities, deterring LMMs' performance on challenging downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r2-t2-re-routing-in-test-time-for-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your contrastive learning problem is secretly a distribution alignment problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/your-contrastive-learning-problem-is-secretly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the success of contrastive learning (CL) in vision and language, its theoretical foundations and mechanisms for building representations remain poorly understood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/your-contrastive-learning-problem-is-secretly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoBS: Autonomous Base Station Deployment Framework with Reinforcement Learning and Digital Twin Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autobs-autonomous-base-station-deployment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces AutoBS, a reinforcement learning (RL)-based framework for optimal base station (BS) deployment in 6G networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autobs-autonomous-base-station-deployment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HVI: A New color space for Low-light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hvi-a-new-color-space-for-low-light-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-Light Image Enhancement (LLIE) is a crucial computer vision task that aims to restore detailed visual information from corrupted low-light images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hvi-a-new-color-space-for-low-light-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SecureGaze: Defending Gaze Estimation Against Backdoor Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/securegaze-defending-gaze-estimation-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In such attacks, adversaries inject backdoor triggers by poisoning the training data, creating a backdoor vulnerability: the model performs normally with benign inputs, but produces manipulated gaze directions when a specific trigger is present.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/securegaze-defending-gaze-estimation-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlexVAR: Flexible Visual Autoregressive Modeling without Residual Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexvar-flexible-visual-autoregressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work challenges the residual prediction paradigm in visual autoregressive modeling and presents FlexVAR, a new Flexible Visual AutoRegressive image generation paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexvar-flexible-visual-autoregressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Learning in Latent Contextual Bandits with Covariate Shift Through Causal Transportability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-in-latent-contextual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that naively transferring all knowledge for classical bandit algorithms in this setting led to negative transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-in-latent-contextual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative augmentations for improved cardiac ultrasound segmentation using diffusion models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-augmentations-for-improved-cardiac</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work utilizes diffusion models to create generative augmentations that can significantly improve diversity of the dataset and thus the generalisability of segmentation models without the need for more annotated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-augmentations-for-improved-cardiac</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Fidelity Relightable Monocular Portrait Animation with Lighting-Controllable Video Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-fidelity-relightable-monocular-portrait</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address this limitation by distinguishing these feature types through dedicated subspaces within the feature space of a pre-trained image-to-video diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-fidelity-relightable-monocular-portrait</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SegLocNet: Multimodal Localization Network for Autonomous Driving via Bird's-Eye-View Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seglocnet-multimodal-localization-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on the nuScenes and Argoverse datasets demonstrate that our method outperforms the current state-of-the-art methods, and that our method can accurately estimate the ego pose in urban environments without relying on GNSS, while maintaining strong generalization ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seglocnet-multimodal-localization-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CirT: Global Subseasonal-to-Seasonal Forecasting with Geometry-inspired Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cirt-global-subseasonal-to-seasonal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate Subseasonal-to-Seasonal (S2S) climate forecasting is pivotal for decision-making including agriculture planning and disaster preparedness but is known to be challenging due to its chaotic nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cirt-global-subseasonal-to-seasonal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-distribution Generalization for Total Variation based Invariant Risk Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-generalization-for-total</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the autonomous TV penalty hyperparameter is exactly the Lagrangian multiplier.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-generalization-for-total</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Robust Graph Neural Networks by Modeling Noise Dependencies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-robust-graph-neural-networks-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In real-world applications, node features in graphs often contain noise from various sources, leading to significant performance degradation in GNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-robust-graph-neural-networks-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate and Scalable Graph Neural Networks via Message Invariance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-and-scalable-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Message passing-based graph neural networks (GNNs) have achieved great success in many real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-and-scalable-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QPM: Discrete Optimization for Globally Interpretable Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qpm-discrete-optimization-for-globally</link>
      <description><![CDATA[QPM represents every class with a binary assignment of very few, typically 5, features, that are also assigned to other classes, ensuring easily comparable contrastive class representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qpm-discrete-optimization-for-globally</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highly Parallelized Reinforcement Learning Training with Relaxed Assignment Dependencies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/highly-parallelized-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It relaxes assignment dependencies between subtask components and enables event-driven asynchronous communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/highly-parallelized-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Classifiers That Induce Markets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-classifiers-that-induce-markets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When learning is used to inform decisions about humans, such as for loans, hiring, or admissions, this can incentivize users to strategically modify their features to obtain positive predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-classifiers-that-induce-markets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The erasure of intensive livestock farming in text-to-image generative AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-erasure-of-intensive-livestock-farming-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While OpenAI introduced prompt revision to mitigate bias, in the case of farmed animal production systems, it paradoxically introduces a strong bias towards unrealistic farming practices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-erasure-of-intensive-livestock-farming-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A2-GNN: Angle-Annular GNN for Visual Descriptor-free Camera Relocalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a2-gnn-angle-annular-gnn-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual localization involves estimating the 6-degree-of-freedom (6-DoF) camera pose within a known scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a2-gnn-angle-annular-gnn-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Responsible AI in Education: Hybrid Recommendation System for K-12 Students Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-responsible-ai-in-education-hybrid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The growth of Educational Technology (EdTech) has enabled highly personalized learning experiences through Artificial Intelligence (AI)-based recommendation systems tailored to each student needs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-responsible-ai-in-education-hybrid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifiable Multi-View Causal Discovery Without Non-Gaussianity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifiable-multi-view-causal-discovery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel approach to linear causal discovery in the framework of multi-view Structural Equation Models (SEM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifiable-multi-view-causal-discovery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can a calibration metric be both testable and actionable?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-a-calibration-metric-be-both-testable-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Forecast probabilities often serve as critical inputs for binary decision making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-a-calibration-metric-be-both-testable-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models as Attribution Regularizers for Efficient Model Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-as-attribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose an attribution-matching regularization term that aligns the training dynamics of the smaller model with the insights provided by the LLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-as-attribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient-Guided Annealing for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-guided-annealing-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose alleviating domain conflicts in model optimization, by iteratively annealing the parameters of a model in the early stages of training and searching for points where gradients align between domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-guided-annealing-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Order-Robust Class Incremental Learning: Graph-Driven Dynamic Similarity Grouping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/order-robust-class-incremental-learning-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response, we first provide additional theoretical analysis, which reveals that when the similarity among a group of classes is lower, the model demonstrates increased robustness to the class order.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/order-robust-class-incremental-learning-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic DropConnect: Enhancing Neural Network Robustness through Adaptive Edge Dropping Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-dropconnect-enhancing-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dropout and DropConnect are well-known techniques that apply a consistent drop rate to randomly deactivate neurons or edges in a neural network layer during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-dropconnect-enhancing-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
