<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 21:07:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the Snapshot: Brain Tokenized Graph Transformer for Longitudinal Brain Functional Connectome Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-the-snapshot-brain-tokenized-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we proposed the first interpretable framework for brain FC trajectory embedding with application to neurodegenerative disease diagnosis and prognosis, namely Brain Tokenized Graph Transformer (Brain TokenGT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-the-snapshot-brain-tokenized-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Task Transferability in Large Pre-trained Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-task-transferability-in-large-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel Task Transfer Analysis approach that transforms the source distribution (and classifier) by changing the class prior distribution, label, and feature spaces to produce a new source distribution (and classifier) and allows us to relate the loss of the downstream task (i. e., transferability) to that of the source task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-task-transferability-in-large-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-level Anomaly Detection via Hierarchical Memory Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-level-anomaly-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One primary challenge is to learn normal patterns manifested in both fine-grained and holistic views of graphs for identifying graphs that are abnormal in part or in whole.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-level-anomaly-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Differentiable Logic Programs for Abstract Visual Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-differentiable-logic-programs-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to the memory intensity, most existing approaches do not bring the best of the expressivity of first-order logic, excluding a crucial ability to solve abstract visual reasoning, where agents need to perform reasoning by using analogies on abstract concepts in different scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-differentiable-logic-programs-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monte Carlo Policy Gradient Method for Binary Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-policy-gradient-method-for-binary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Binary optimization has a wide range of applications in combinatorial optimization problems such as MaxCut, MIMO detection, and MaxSAT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-policy-gradient-method-for-binary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVSegFormer: Audio-Visual Segmentation with Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avsegformer-audio-visual-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose AVSegFormer, a novel framework for AVS tasks that leverages the transformer architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avsegformer-audio-visual-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ImDiffusion: Imputed Diffusion Models for Multivariate Time Series Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imdiffusion-imputed-diffusion-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, ImDiffusion represents a pioneering approach that combines imputation-based techniques with time series anomaly detection, while introducing the novel use of diffusion models to the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imdiffusion-imputed-diffusion-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Explainable Deep Framework: Towards Task-Specific Fusion for Multi-to-One MRI Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-explainable-deep-framework-towards-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-sequence MRI is valuable in clinical settings for reliable diagnosis and treatment prognosis, but some sequences may be unusable or missing for various reasons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-explainable-deep-framework-towards-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Suicide Prevention from Bipolar Disorder with Temporal Symptom-Aware Multitask Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-suicide-prevention-from-bipolar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bipolar disorder (BD) is closely associated with an increased risk of suicide.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-suicide-prevention-from-bipolar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Instruction Tuning with Polite Flamingo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-instruction-tuning-with-polite</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This side effect negatively impacts the model's ability to format responses appropriately -- for instance, its "politeness" -- due to the overly succinct and unformatted nature of raw annotations, resulting in reduced human preference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-instruction-tuning-with-polite</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segment Anything Meets Point Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything-meets-point-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SAM-PT leverages robust and sparse point selection and propagation techniques for mask generation, demonstrating that a SAM-based segmentation tracker can yield strong zero-shot performance across popular video object segmentation benchmarks, including DAVIS, YouTube-VOS, and MOSE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything-meets-point-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sampling the lattice Nambu-Goto string using Continuous Normalizing Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampling-the-lattice-nambu-goto-string-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Effective String Theory (EST) represents a powerful non-perturbative approach to describe confinement in Yang-Mills theory that models the confining flux tube as a thin vibrating string.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampling-the-lattice-nambu-goto-string-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engression: Extrapolation for Nonlinear Regression?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/engression-extrapolation-for-nonlinear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental results indicate that this model is typically suitable for many real data sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/engression-extrapolation-for-nonlinear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Open-vocabulary Universal Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-open-vocabulary-universal-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-vocabulary image segmentation aims to partition an image into semantic regions according to arbitrary text descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-open-vocabulary-universal-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many tasks make light work: Learning to localise medical anomalies from multiple synthetic tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/many-tasks-make-light-work-learning-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a growing interest in single-class modelling and out-of-distribution detection as fully supervised machine learning models cannot reliably identify classes not included in their training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/many-tasks-make-light-work-learning-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TomatoDIFF: On-plant Tomato Segmentation with Denoising Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tomatodiff-on-plant-tomato-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence applications enable farmers to optimize crop growth and production while reducing costs and environmental impact.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tomatodiff-on-plant-tomato-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniFine: A Unified and Fine-grained Approach for Zero-shot Vision-Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifine-a-unified-and-fine-grained-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we find visual and textual fine-grained information, e. g., keywords in the sentence and objects in the image, can be fairly informative for semantics understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifine-a-unified-and-fine-grained-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trainable Transformer in Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trainable-transformer-in-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose an efficient construction, Transformer in Transformer (in short, TinT), that allows a transformer to simulate and fine-tune complex models internally during inference (e. g., pre-trained language models).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trainable-transformer-in-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-DA: UAV Tracks Anything at Night with SAM-Powered Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-da-uav-tracks-anything-at-night-with-sam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the state-of-the-art (SOTA) DA still lacks the potential object with accurate pixel-level location and boundary to generate the high-quality target domain training sample.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-da-uav-tracks-anything-at-night-with-sam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion-X: A Large-scale 3D Expressive Whole-body Human Motion Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-x-a-large-scale-3d-expressive-whole</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present Motion-X, a large-scale 3D expressive whole-body motion dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-x-a-large-scale-3d-expressive-whole</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worth of knowledge in deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/worth-of-knowledge-in-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model-agnostic framework can be applied to a variety of common network architectures, providing a comprehensive understanding of the role of prior knowledge in deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/worth-of-knowledge-in-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Building Self-Aware Object Detectors via Reliable Uncertainty Quantification and Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-building-self-aware-object-detectors-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The current approach for testing the robustness of object detectors suffers from serious deficiencies such as improper methods of performing out-of-distribution detection and using calibration metrics which do not consider both localisation and classification quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-building-self-aware-object-detectors-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuro-Symbolic Sudoku Solver</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-sudoku-solver</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our study, we showcase an NLM which is capable of obtaining 100% accuracy for solving a Sudoku with empty cells ranging from 3 to 10.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-sudoku-solver</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDC-HSDD-NDSA: Structure Detecting Cluster by Hierarchical Secondary Directed Differential with Normalized Density and Self-Adaption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdc-hsdd-ndsa-structure-detecting-cluster-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results verify its validity in structure detection, robustness over noises, as well as independence of granularities, and demonstrate that it could outperform previous ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdc-hsdd-ndsa-structure-detecting-cluster-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BioCPT: Contrastive Pre-trained Transformers with Large-scale PubMed Search Logs for Zero-shot Biomedical Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biocpt-contrastive-pre-trained-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results show that BioCPT sets new state-of-the-art performance on five biomedical IR tasks, outperforming various baselines including much larger models such as GPT-3-sized cpt-text-XL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biocpt-contrastive-pre-trained-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On efficient computation in active inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-efficient-computation-in-active-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite being recognized as neurobiologically plausible, active inference faces difficulties when employed to simulate intelligent behaviour in complex environments due to its computational cost and the difficulty of specifying an appropriate target distribution for the agent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-efficient-computation-in-active-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fourier-Mixed Window Attention: Accelerating Informer for Long Sequence Time-Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fourier-mixed-window-attention-accelerating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study a fast local-global window-based attention method to accelerate Informer for long sequence time-series forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fourier-mixed-window-attention-accelerating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Linear Inverse Problems Provably via Posterior Sampling with Latent Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-linear-inverse-problems-provably-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the first framework to solve linear inverse problems leveraging pre-trained latent diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-linear-inverse-problems-provably-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidirectional Looking with A Novel Double Exponential Moving Average to Adaptive and Non-adaptive Momentum Optimizers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-looking-with-a-novel-double</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SGD and Adam are two classical and effective optimizers on which researchers have proposed many variants, such as SGDM and RAdam.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-looking-with-a-novel-double</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pricing European Options with Google AutoML, TensorFlow, and XGBoost</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pricing-european-options-with-google-automl</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers have been using Neural Networks and other related machine-learning techniques to price options since the early 1990s.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pricing-european-options-with-google-automl</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A MIL Approach for Anomaly Detection in Surveillance Videos from Multiple Camera Views</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mil-approach-for-anomaly-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we tackle these typical problems of anomaly detection in surveillance video by combining Multiple Instance Learning (MIL) to deal with the lack of labels and Multiple Camera Views (MC) to reduce occlusion and clutter effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mil-approach-for-anomaly-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Text Unlearnable: Exploiting Effective Patterns to Protect Personal Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-text-unlearnable-exploiting-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the ethical concerns arising from the use of unauthorized public data in deep learning models and proposes a novel solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-text-unlearnable-exploiting-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text based Large Language Model for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-based-large-language-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel text-based large language model for recommendation (TBLLMR) that utilized the expressive power of LLM to generate personalized recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-based-large-language-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSP: Self-Supervised Post-training for Conversational Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssp-self-supervised-post-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational search has been regarded as the next-generation search paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssp-self-supervised-post-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intra- &amp; Extra-Source Exemplar-Based Style Synthesis for Improved Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intra-extra-source-exemplar-based-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using the proposed masked noise encoder to randomize style and content combinations in the training set, i. e., intra-source style augmentation (ISSA) effectively increases the diversity of training data and reduces spurious correlation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intra-extra-source-exemplar-based-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing protein fitness using Gibbs sampling with Graph-based Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-protein-fitness-using-gibbs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to design novel proteins with higher fitness on a given task would be revolutionary for many fields of medicine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-protein-fitness-using-gibbs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equal Confusion Fairness: Measuring Group-Based Disparities in Automated Decision Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equal-confusion-fairness-measuring-group</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalizing this intuition, this paper proposes a new equal confusion fairness test to check an automated decision system for fairness and a new confusion parity error to quantify the extent of any unfairness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equal-confusion-fairness-measuring-group</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TopicFM+: Boosting Accuracy and Efficiency of Topic-Assisted Feature Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topicfm-boosting-accuracy-and-efficiency-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating these topics, we can effectively capture comprehensive context information and obtain discriminative and high-quality features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topicfm-boosting-accuracy-and-efficiency-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IoT-Based Air Quality Monitoring System with Machine Learning for Accurate and Real-time Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iot-based-air-quality-monitoring-system-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the issue of air pollution awareness, Air Pollution Monitoring systems are used to measure the concentration of gases like CO2, smoke, alcohol, benzene, and NH3 present in the air.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iot-based-air-quality-monitoring-system-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WaveMixSR: A Resource-efficient Neural Network for Image Super-resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavemixsr-a-resource-efficient-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new neural network -- WaveMixSR -- for image super-resolution based on WaveMix architecture which uses a 2D-discrete wavelet transform for spatial token-mixing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavemixsr-a-resource-efficient-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse-Input Neural Network using Group Concave Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-input-neural-network-using-group</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this limitation, we propose a framework of sparse-input neural networks using group concave regularization for feature selection in both low-dimensional and high-dimensional settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-input-neural-network-using-group</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filter Pruning for Efficient CNNs via Knowledge-driven Differential Filter Sampler</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filter-pruning-for-efficient-cnns-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel Knowledge-driven Differential Filter Sampler~(KDFS) with Masked Filter Modeling~(MFM) framework for filter pruning, which globally prunes the redundant filters based on the prior knowledge of a pre-trained model in a differential and non-alternative optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filter-pruning-for-efficient-cnns-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CasTGAN: Cascaded Generative Adversarial Network for Realistic Tabular Data Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/castgan-cascaded-generative-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative adversarial networks (GANs) have drawn considerable attention in recent years for their proven capability in generating synthetic data which can be utilized for multiple purposes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/castgan-cascaded-generative-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residual-based attention and connection to information bottleneck theory in PINNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/residual-based-attention-and-connection-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driven by the need for more efficient and seamless integration of physical models and data, physics-informed neural networks (PINNs) have seen a surge of interest in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/residual-based-attention-and-connection-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using joint training speaker encoder with consistency loss to achieve cross-lingual voice conversion and expressive voice conversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-joint-training-speaker-encoder-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Voice conversion systems have made significant advancements in terms of naturalness and similarity in common voice conversion tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-joint-training-speaker-encoder-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variation-aware Vision Transformer Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variation-aware-vision-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also find that the variations in ViTs cause training oscillations, bringing instability during quantization-aware training (QAT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variation-aware-vision-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SyMFM6D: Symmetry-aware Multi-directional Fusion for Multi-View 6D Object Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symfm6d-symmetry-aware-multi-directional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting objects and estimating their 6D poses is essential for automated systems to interact safely with the environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symfm6d-symmetry-aware-multi-directional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-Resource Cross-Lingual Adaptive Training for Nigerian Pidgin</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-resource-cross-lingual-adaptive-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we target on improving upon both text classification and translation of Nigerian Pidgin (Naija) by collecting a large-scale parallel English-Pidgin corpus and further propose a framework of cross-lingual adaptive training that includes both continual and task adaptive training so as to adapt a base pre-trained model to low-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-resource-cross-lingual-adaptive-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recursive Algorithmic Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recursive-algorithmic-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning models that execute algorithms can enable us to address a key problem in deep learning: generalizing to out-of-distribution data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recursive-algorithmic-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Sample Size Determination in Natural Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-sample-size-determination-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowing exactly how many data points need to be labeled to achieve a certain model performance is a hugely beneficial step towards reducing the overall budgets for annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-sample-size-determination-in</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
