<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 09:11:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Gramian Attention Heads are Strong yet Efficient Vision Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gramian-attention-heads-are-strong-yet-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel architecture design that enhances expressiveness by incorporating multiple head classifiers (\ie, classification heads) instead of relying on channel expansion or additional building blocks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gramian-attention-heads-are-strong-yet-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diversity Enhanced Narrative Question Generation for Storybooks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diversity-enhanced-narrative-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To validate the answerability of the generated questions, we employ a SQuAD2. 0 fine-tuned question answering model, classifying the questions as answerable or not.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diversity-enhanced-narrative-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DreamCraft3D: Hierarchical 3D Generation with Bootstrapped Diffusion Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamcraft3d-hierarchical-3d-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The score distillation from this 3D-aware diffusion prior provides view-consistent guidance for the scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamcraft3d-hierarchical-3d-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive importance sampling for heavy-tailed distributions via $α$-divergence minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-importance-sampling-for-heavy-tailed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then show that the $\alpha$-divergence can be approximated by a generalized notion of effective sample size and leverage this new perspective to adapt the tail parameter with Bayesian optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-importance-sampling-for-heavy-tailed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MotionAGFormer: Enhancing 3D Human Pose Estimation with a Transformer-GCNFormer Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motionagformer-enhancing-3d-human-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed GCNFormer module exploits the local relationship between adjacent joints, outputting a new representation that is complementary to the transformer output.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motionagformer-enhancing-3d-human-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AccoMontage-3: Full-Band Accompaniment Arrangement via Sequential Style Transfer and Multi-Track Function Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accomontage-3-full-band-accompaniment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first component is a piano arranger that generates piano accompaniment for the lead sheet by transferring texture styles to the chords using latent chord-texture disentanglement and heuristic retrieval of texture donors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accomontage-3-full-band-accompaniment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DECWA : Density-Based Clustering using Wasserstein Distance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decwa-density-based-clustering-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A method is then proposed to agglomerate similar sub-clusters by using both their density ($p. d. f$) and their spatial distance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decwa-density-based-clustering-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic Latent Transformer: Efficient Modelling of Stochastically Forced Zonal Jets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-latent-transformer-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the 'Stochastic Latent Transformer', a probabilistic deep learning approach for efficient reduced-order modelling of stochastic partial differential equations (SPDEs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-latent-transformer-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSLCL: An Efficient Model-Agnostic Supervised Contrastive Learning Framework for Emotion Recognition in Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sslcl-an-efficient-model-agnostic-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose an efficient and model-agnostic SCL framework named Supervised Sample-Label Contrastive Learning with Soft-HGR Maximal Correlation (SSLCL), which eliminates the need for a large batch size and can be seamlessly integrated with existing ERC models without introducing any model-specific assumptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sslcl-an-efficient-model-agnostic-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISCO: A Large Scale Human Annotated Corpus for Disfluency Correction in Indo-European Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disco-a-large-scale-human-annotated-corpus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Towards the goal of multilingual disfluency correction, we present a high-quality human-annotated DC corpus covering four important Indo-European languages: English, Hindi, German and French.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disco-a-large-scale-human-annotated-corpus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XFEVER: Exploring Fact Verification across Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xfever-exploring-fact-verification-across</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results show that the multilingual language model can be used to build fact verification models in different languages efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xfever-exploring-fact-verification-across</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple, Scalable and Effective Clustering via One-Dimensional Projections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-scalable-and-effective-clustering-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also believe that our theoretical analysis is of independent interest, as we show that the approximation ratio of a $k$-means algorithm is approximately preserved under a class of projections and that $k$-means++ seeding can be implemented in expected $O(n \log n)$ time in one dimension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-scalable-and-effective-clustering-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DualMatch: Robust Semi-Supervised Learning with Dual-Level Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dualmatch-robust-semi-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel SSL method called DualMatch, in which the class prediction jointly invokes feature embedding in a dual-level interaction manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dualmatch-robust-semi-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Optimization in Deep Learning: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-optimization-in-deep-learning-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consequently, a huge number of studies in the existing literature have focused on the data aspect in deep learning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-optimization-in-deep-learning-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Self-Interpretable Graph-Level Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-self-interpretable-graph-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate a new challenging problem, explainable GLAD, where the learning objective is to predict the abnormality of each graph sample with corresponding explanations, i. e., the vital subgraph that leads to the predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-self-interpretable-graph-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Particle-based Variational Inference with Generalized Wasserstein Gradient Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/particle-based-variational-inference-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particle-based variational inference methods (ParVIs) such as Stein variational gradient descent (SVGD) update the particles based on the kernelized Wasserstein gradient flow for the Kullback-Leibler (KL) divergence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/particle-based-variational-inference-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unraveling Feature Extraction Mechanisms in Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-feature-extraction-mechanisms-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The underlying mechanism of neural networks in capturing precise knowledge has been the subject of consistent research efforts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-feature-extraction-mechanisms-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperparameter Optimization for Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameter-optimization-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, prior research has explored hyperparameter optimization in RL to address this concern.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameter-optimization-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Continuous Network Emerging Dynamics from Scarce Observations via Data-Adaptive Stochastic Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-continuous-network-emerging-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning network dynamics from the empirical structure and spatio-temporal observation data is crucial to revealing the interaction mechanisms of complex networks in a wide range of domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-continuous-network-emerging-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoDet: Co-Occurrence Guided Region-Word Alignment for Open-Vocabulary Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codet-co-occurrence-guided-region-word</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CoDet then leverages visual similarities to discover the co-occurring objects and align them with the shared concept.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codet-co-occurrence-guided-region-word</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamics Generalisation in Reinforcement Learning via Adaptive Context-Aware Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamics-generalisation-in-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce a neural network architecture, the Decision Adapter, which generates the weights of an adapter module and conditions the behaviour of an agent on the context information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamics-generalisation-in-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperHF: Supervised Iterative Learning from Human Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superhf-supervised-iterative-learning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we focus on two prevalent methods used to align these models, Supervised Fine-Tuning (SFT) and Reinforcement Learning from Human Feedback (RLHF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superhf-supervised-iterative-learning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sum-of-Parts Models: Faithful Attributions for Groups of Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sum-of-parts-models-faithful-attributions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An explanation of a machine learning model is considered "faithful" if it accurately reflects the model's decision-making process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sum-of-parts-models-faithful-attributions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Conversational Recommendation Systems via Bias Analysis and Language-Model-Enhanced Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-conversational-recommendation-5</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational Recommendation System (CRS) is a rapidly growing research area that has gained significant attention alongside advancements in language modelling techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-conversational-recommendation-5</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning COVID-19 Regional Transmission Using Universal Differential Equations in a SIR model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-covid-19-regional-transmission-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compared the proposed model using a simulated COVID-19 outbreak against a single-region SIR and a fully data-driven model composed only of a DNN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-covid-19-regional-transmission-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CommonCanvas: An Open Diffusion Model Trained with Creative-Commons Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/commoncanvas-an-open-diffusion-model-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This task presents two challenges: (1) high-resolution CC images lack the captions necessary to train text-to-image generative models; (2) CC images are relatively scarce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/commoncanvas-an-open-diffusion-model-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving through the Concept Gridlock: Unraveling Explainability Bottlenecks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/driving-through-the-concept-gridlock</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of human-assisted or autonomous driving, explainability models can help user acceptance and understanding of decisions made by the autonomous vehicle, which can be used to rationalize and explain driver or vehicle behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/driving-through-the-concept-gridlock</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BabyStories: Can Reinforcement Learning Teach Baby Language Models to Write Better Stories?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/babystories-can-reinforcement-learning-teach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These insights highlight the potential benefits of RLHF fine-tuning for language models within limited data, enhancing their ability to maintain narrative focus and coherence while adhering better to initial instructions in storytelling tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/babystories-can-reinforcement-learning-teach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HI-TOM: A Benchmark for Evaluating Higher-Order Theory of Mind Reasoning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hi-tom-a-benchmark-for-evaluating-higher</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Theory of Mind (ToM) is the ability to reason about one's own and others' mental states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hi-tom-a-benchmark-for-evaluating-higher</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photometric Redshifts with Copula Entropy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/photometric-redshifts-with-copula-entropy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we propose to apply copula entropy (CE) to photometric redshifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/photometric-redshifts-with-copula-entropy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention Lens: A Tool for Mechanistically Interpreting the Attention Head Information Retrieval Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-lens-a-tool-for-mechanistically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based Large Language Models (LLMs) are the state-of-the-art for natural language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-lens-a-tool-for-mechanistically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Efficient Surrogate Dynamic Models with Graph Spline Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-efficient-surrogate-dynamic-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While complex simulations of physical systems have been widely used in engineering and scientific computing, lowering their often prohibitive computational requirements has only recently been tackled by deep learning approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-efficient-surrogate-dynamic-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Near-Optimal Pure Exploration in Matrix Games: A Generalization of Stochastic Bandits &amp; Dueling Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-optimal-pure-exploration-in-matrix-games</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We design a near-optimal algorithm whose sample complexity matches the lower bound, up to log factors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-optimal-pure-exploration-in-matrix-games</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redco: A Lightweight Tool to Automate Distributed Training of LLMs on Any GPU/TPUs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redco-a-lightweight-tool-to-automate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Redco, a lightweight and user-friendly tool crafted to automate distributed training and inference for LLMs, as well as to simplify ML pipeline development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redco-a-lightweight-tool-to-automate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Robust Deep Visual Representations from EEG Brain Recordings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-deep-visual-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstruction of visual images from brain Electroencephalography (EEG) signals has garnered a lot of interest due to its applications in brain-computer interfacing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-deep-visual-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMURF-THP: Score Matching-based UnceRtainty quantiFication for Transformer Hawkes Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smurf-thp-score-matching-based-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct extensive experiments in both event type prediction and uncertainty quantification of arrival time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smurf-thp-score-matching-based-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Early Evaluation of GPT-4V(ision)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-early-evaluation-of-gpt-4v-ision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we evaluate different abilities of GPT-4V including visual understanding, language understanding, visual puzzle solving, and understanding of other modalities such as depth, thermal, video, and audio.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-early-evaluation-of-gpt-4v-ision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Simple to Complex: A Progressive Framework for Document-level Informative Argument Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-simple-to-complex-a-progressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These methods extract events according to their appearance order in the document, however, the event that appears in the first sentence does not mean that it is the easiest to extract.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-simple-to-complex-a-progressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QMoE: Practical Sub-1-Bit Compression of Trillion-Parameter Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qmoe-practical-sub-1-bit-compression-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) architectures offer a general solution to the high inference costs of large language models (LLMs) via sparse routing, bringing faster and more accurate models, at the cost of massive parameter counts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qmoe-practical-sub-1-bit-compression-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChimpACT: A Longitudinal Dataset for Understanding Chimpanzee Behaviors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chimpact-a-longitudinal-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ChimpACT is both comprehensive and challenging, consisting of 163 videos with a cumulative 160, 500 frames, each richly annotated with detection, identification, pose estimation, and fine-grained spatiotemporal behavior labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chimpact-a-longitudinal-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RDBench: ML Benchmark for Relational Databases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdbench-ml-benchmark-for-relational-databases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Benefiting from high-quality datasets and standardized evaluation metrics, machine learning (ML) has achieved sustained progress and widespread applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdbench-ml-benchmark-for-relational-databases</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Simultaneous Machine Translation with Word-level Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-simultaneous-machine-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have seen remarkable advances in the field of Simultaneous Machine Translation (SiMT) due to the introduction of innovative policies that dictate whether to READ or WRITE at each step of the translation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-simultaneous-machine-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flow-Attention-based Spatio-Temporal Aggregation Network for 3D Mask Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-attention-based-spatio-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose a novel 3D mask detection framework, called FASTEN (Flow-Attention-based Spatio-Temporal aggrEgation Network).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-attention-based-spatio-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Explain: A Model-Agnostic Framework for Explaining Black Box Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-explain-a-model-agnostic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Learning to Explain (LTX), a model-agnostic framework designed for providing post-hoc explanations for vision models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-explain-a-model-agnostic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCB-ST-Dataset4: Extending the Spatio-Temporal Behavior Dataset in Student Classroom Scenarios Through Image Dataset Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scb-st-dataset4-extending-the-spatio-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we proposed a method for extending the spatio-temporal behavior dataset in Student Classroom Scenarios (SCB-ST-Dataset4) through image dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scb-st-dataset4-extending-the-spatio-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metrically Scaled Monocular Depth Estimation through Sparse Priors for Underwater Robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metrically-scaled-monocular-depth-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address the problem of real-time dense depth estimation from monocular images for mobile underwater vehicles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metrically-scaled-monocular-depth-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interferometric Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interferometric-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate their applicability for combinatorial optimization, image classification, and image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interferometric-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nighttime Driver Behavior Prediction Using Taillight Signal Recognition via CNN-SVM Classifier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nighttime-driver-behavior-prediction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper aims to enhance the ability to predict nighttime driving behavior by identifying taillights of both human-driven and autonomous vehicles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nighttime-driver-behavior-prediction-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Potential Field for Obstacle-Aware Local Motion Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-potential-field-for-obstacle-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiment on Husky UGV mobile robot showed that our approach allows real-time and safe local planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-potential-field-for-obstacle-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Uncertainty Estimation via High-Dimensional Testing on Latent Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-uncertainty-estimation-via-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experiments on the OOD detection task also show satisfactory performance of our method when the OOD data are unseen in the training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-uncertainty-estimation-via-high</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
