<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 09:13:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Competing for Shareable Arms in Multi-Player Multi-Armed Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/competing-for-shareable-arms-in-multi-player</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In reality, agents often have to learn and maximize the rewards of the resources at the same time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/competing-for-shareable-arms-in-multi-player</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E-PANNs: Sound Recognition Using Efficient Pre-trained Audio Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-panns-sound-recognition-using-efficient-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sounds carry an abundance of information about activities and events in our everyday environment, such as traffic noise, road works, music, or people talking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-panns-sound-recognition-using-efficient-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing and combining some popular NER approaches on Biomedical tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-and-combining-some-popular-ner</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lastly, we implement a system that learns to combine the predictions of SEQ and SpanPred, generating systems that consistently give high recall and high F1 across all 4 datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-and-combining-some-popular-ner</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preserving Pre-trained Features Helps Calibrate Fine-tuned Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-pre-trained-features-helps</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In light of these observations, we evaluate the calibration of several methods that preserve pre-trained features and show that preserving pre-trained features can improve the calibration of fine-tuned language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-pre-trained-features-helps</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleAvatar3D: Leveraging Image-Text Diffusion Models for High-Fidelity 3D Avatar Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styleavatar3d-leveraging-image-text-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent advancements in image-text diffusion models have stimulated research interest in large-scale 3D generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styleavatar3d-leveraging-image-text-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Node Embedding from Neural Hamiltonian Orbits in Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/node-embedding-from-neural-hamiltonian-orbits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the graph node embedding problem, embedding spaces can vary significantly for different data types, leading to the need for different GNN model types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/node-embedding-from-neural-hamiltonian-orbits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jointly Reparametrized Multi-Layer Adaptation for Efficient and Private Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jointly-reparametrized-multi-layer-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This can be a drawback for low-resource applications and training with differential-privacy constraints, where excessive noise may be introduced during finetuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jointly-reparametrized-multi-layer-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Processes for Spatio-Temporal Extrapolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-processes-for-spatio-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the task of spatio-temporal extrapolation that generates data at target locations from surrounding contexts in a graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-processes-for-spatio-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Weakly Supervised Audio-Visual Violence Detection in Hyperbolic Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-weakly-supervised-audio-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this, we propose HyperVD, a novel framework that learns snippet embeddings in hyperbolic space to improve model discrimination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-weakly-supervised-audio-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NUNO: A General Framework for Learning Parametric PDEs with Non-Uniform Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nuno-a-general-framework-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The neural operator has emerged as a powerful tool in learning mappings between function spaces in PDEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nuno-a-general-framework-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Does Information Bottleneck Help Deep Learning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-does-information-bottleneck-help-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide the first rigorous learning theory for justifying the benefit of information bottleneck in deep learning by mathematically relating information bottleneck to generalization errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-does-information-bottleneck-help-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subequivariant Graph Reinforcement Learning in 3D Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subequivariant-graph-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning a shared policy that guides the locomotion of different agents is of core interest in Reinforcement Learning (RL), which leads to the study of morphology-agnostic RL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subequivariant-graph-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockwise Stochastic Variance-Reduced Methods with Parallel Speedup for Multi-Block Bilevel Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blockwise-stochastic-variance-reduced-methods</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we consider non-convex multi-block bilevel optimization (MBBO) problems, which involve $m\gg 1$ lower level problems and have important applications in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blockwise-stochastic-variance-reduced-methods</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnoOnly: Semi-Supervised Anomaly Detection without Loss on Normal Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anoonly-semi-supervised-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike existing SSAD methods that resort to strict loss supervision, AnoOnly suspends it and introduces a form of weak supervision for normal data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anoonly-semi-supervised-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shuo Wen Jie Zi: Rethinking Dictionaries and Glyphs for Chinese Language Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shuo-wen-jie-zi-rethinking-dictionaries-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce CDBERT, a new learning paradigm that enhances the semantics understanding ability of the Chinese PLMs with dictionary knowledge and structure of Chinese characters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shuo-wen-jie-zi-rethinking-dictionaries-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrapped Cauchy Distributed Angular Softmax for Long-Tailed Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wrapped-cauchy-distributed-angular-softmax</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The class-wise distribution of angular representation becomes a sum of these kernels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wrapped-cauchy-distributed-angular-softmax</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-based Multi-ODE Neural Networks for Spatio-Temporal Traffic Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-multi-ode-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current works primarily rely on road networks with graph structures and learn representations using graph neural networks (GNNs), but this approach suffers from over-smoothing problem in deep architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-multi-ode-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Template-free Articulated Neural Point Clouds for Reposable View Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/template-free-articulated-neural-point-clouds</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the versatility of our representation on a variety of articulated objects from common datasets and obtain reposable 3D reconstructions without the need of object-specific skeletal templates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/template-free-articulated-neural-point-clouds</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HQDec: Self-Supervised Monocular Depth Estimation Based on a High-Quality Decoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hqdec-self-supervised-monocular-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a high-quality decoder (HQDec), with which multilevel near-lossless fine-grained information, obtained by the proposed adaptive axial-normalized position-embedded channel attention sampling module (AdaAxialNPCAS), can be adaptively incorporated into a low-resolution feature map with high-level semantics utilizing the proposed adaptive information exchange scheme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hqdec-self-supervised-monocular-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empirical Sufficiency Lower Bounds for Language Modeling with Locally-Bootstrapped Semantic Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-sufficiency-lower-bounds-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we build upon negative results from an attempt at language modeling with predicted semantic structure, in order to establish empirical lower bounds on what could have made the attempt successful.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-sufficiency-lower-bounds-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intrinsic shape analysis in archaeology: A case study on ancient sundials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsic-shape-analysis-in-archaeology-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By performing regression in shape space, we find that for Roman sundials, the bend of the sundials' shadow-receiving surface changes with the location's latitude.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsic-shape-analysis-in-archaeology-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyPOTS: A Python Toolbox for Data Mining on Partially-Observed Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pypots-a-python-toolbox-for-data-mining-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PyPOTS is an open-source Python library dedicated to data mining and analysis on multivariate partially-observed time series, i. e. incomplete time series with missing values, A. K. A.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pypots-a-python-toolbox-for-data-mining-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Performance Analysis for Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-performance-analysis-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Joint vision-language models have shown great performance over a diverse set of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-performance-analysis-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Align, Perturb and Decouple: Toward Better Leverage of Difference Information for RSI Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/align-perturb-and-decouple-toward-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we revisit the importance of feature difference for change detection in RSI, and propose a series of operations to fully exploit the difference information: Alignment, Perturbation and Decoupling (APD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/align-perturb-and-decouple-toward-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Known by the Company it Keeps: Proximity-Based Indexing for Physical Content in Archival Repositories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/known-by-the-company-it-keeps-proximity-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the plethora of born-digital content, vast troves of important content remain accessible only on physical media such as paper or microfilm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/known-by-the-company-it-keeps-proximity-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design and implementation of intelligent packet filtering in IoT microcontroller-based devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/design-and-implementation-of-intelligent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our evaluation shows that T800 is an efficient solution that increases device computational capacity by excluding unsolicited malicious traffic from the processing pipeline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/design-and-implementation-of-intelligent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encouraging Divergent Thinking in Large Language Models through Multi-Agent Debate</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/encouraging-divergent-thinking-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the DoT problem, we propose a Multi-Agent Debate (MAD) framework, in which multiple agents express their arguments in the state of "tit for tat" and a judge manages the debate process to obtain a final solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/encouraging-divergent-thinking-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concise Answers to Complex Questions: Summarization of Long-form Answers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concise-answers-to-complex-questions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long-form question answering systems provide rich information by presenting paragraph-level answers, often containing optional background or auxiliary information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concise-answers-to-complex-questions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Magic of IF: Investigating Causal Reasoning Abilities in Large Language Models of Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-magic-of-if-investigating-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal reasoning, the ability to identify cause-and-effect relationship, is crucial in human thinking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-magic-of-if-investigating-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Information Retrieval Experiment Platform</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-information-retrieval-experiment-platform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Standardization is achieved when a retrieval approach implements PyTerrier's interfaces and the input and output of an experiment are compatible with ir_datasets and ir_measures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-information-retrieval-experiment-platform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Promise and Limits of Real-Time Recurrent Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-promise-and-limits-of-real-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To scale to such challenging tasks, we focus on certain well-known neural architectures with element-wise recurrence, allowing for tractable RTRL without approximation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-promise-and-limits-of-real-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sit Back and Relax: Learning to Drive Incrementally in All Weather Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sit-back-and-relax-learning-to-drive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose to store these affine parameters as a memory bank for each weather condition and plug-in their weather-specific parameters during driving (i. e. test time) when the respective weather conditions are encountered.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sit-back-and-relax-learning-to-drive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asymptotic Characterisation of Robust Empirical Risk Minimisation Performance in the Presence of Outliers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymptotic-characterisation-of-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We examine in detail how performance depends on the loss function and on the degree of outlier corruption in the training set and identify a region of parameters where the optimal performance of the Huber loss is identical to that of the $\ell_2$ loss, offering insights into the use cases of different loss functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymptotic-characterisation-of-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Occ-BEV: Multi-Camera Unified Pre-training via 3D Scene Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occ-bev-multi-camera-unified-pre-training-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed multi-camera unified pre-training framework demonstrates promising results in key tasks such as multi-camera 3D object detection and semantic scene completion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occ-bev-multi-camera-unified-pre-training-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Client: Cross-variable Linear Integrated Enhanced Transformer for Multivariate Long-Term Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/client-cross-variable-linear-integrated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long-term time series forecasting (LTSF) is a crucial aspect of modern society, playing a pivotal role in facilitating long-term planning and developing early warning systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/client-cross-variable-linear-integrated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambient Diffusion: Learning Clean Distributions from Corrupted Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambient-diffusion-learning-clean</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the first diffusion-based framework that can learn an unknown distribution using only highly-corrupted samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambient-diffusion-learning-clean</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the feasibility of using Generative Models to generate Chest X-Ray Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-feasibility-of-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore the feasibility of using generative models, specifically Progressive Growing GANs (PG-GANs) and Stable Diffusion fine-tuning, to generate synthetic chest X-ray images for medical diagnosis purposes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-feasibility-of-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Optimization of Class-Specific Training- and Test-Time Data Augmentation in Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-optimization-of-class-specific-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the effectiveness of our method on four medical image segmentation tasks across different scenarios with two state-of-the-art segmentation models, DeepMedic and nnU-Net.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-optimization-of-class-specific-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reduced Precision Floating-Point Optimization for Deep Neural Network On-Device Learning on MicroControllers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduced-precision-floating-point-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Enabling On-Device Learning (ODL) for Ultra-Low-Power Micro-Controller Units (MCUs) is a key step for post-deployment adaptation and fine-tuning of Deep Neural Network (DNN) models in future TinyML applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduced-precision-floating-point-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edge-MoE: Memory-Efficient Multi-Task Vision Transformer Architecture with Task-level Sparsity via Mixture-of-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge-moe-memory-efficient-multi-task-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computer vision researchers are embracing two promising paradigms: Vision Transformers (ViTs) and Multi-task Learning (MTL), which both show great performance but are computation-intensive, given the quadratic complexity of self-attention in ViT and the need to activate an entire large MTL model for one task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge-moe-memory-efficient-multi-task-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wide &amp; deep learning for spatial &amp; intensity adaptive image restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wide-deep-learning-for-spatial-intensity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The wide & deep architecture in DparNet enables the learned parameters to directly modulate the final restoring results, boosting spatial & intensity adaptive image restoration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wide-deep-learning-for-spatial-intensity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Annotated Dataset for Explainable Interpersonal Risk Factors of Mental Disturbance in Social Media Posts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-annotated-dataset-for-explainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a surge in identifying suicidal risk and its severity in social media posts, we argue that a more consequential and explainable research is required for optimal impact on clinical psychology practice and personalized mental healthcare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-annotated-dataset-for-explainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fighting Bias with Bias: Promoting Model Robustness by Amplifying Dataset Biases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fighting-bias-with-bias-promoting-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We suggest that in order to drive the development of models robust to subtle biases, dataset biases should be amplified in the training set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fighting-bias-with-bias-promoting-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dotears: Scalable, consistent DAG estimation using observational and interventional data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dotears-scalable-consistent-dag-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extend previous work to show, both empirically and analytically, that the inferences of previous methods are driven by exogenous variance structure, but $\texttt{dotears}$ is robust to exogenous variance structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dotears-scalable-consistent-dag-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Computation with Emerging Covariance: towards efficient uncertainty quantification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-computation-with-emerging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building robust, interpretable, and secure artificial intelligence system requires some degree of quantifying and representing uncertainty via a probabilistic perspective, as it allows to mimic human cognitive abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-computation-with-emerging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards single integrated spoofing-aware speaker verification embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-single-integrated-spoofing-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, competitive performance should be demonstrated compared to the fusion of automatic speaker verification (ASV) and countermeasure (CM) embeddings, which outperformed single embedding solutions by a large margin in the SASV2022 challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-single-integrated-spoofing-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-scale Ridesharing DARP Instances Based on Real Travel Demand</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-ridesharing-darp-instances-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rise of large MoD systems and the availability of open travel demand datasets for many US cities, there is now an opportunity to evaluate these algorithms on standardized, realistic, and representative instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-ridesharing-darp-instances-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing for the Markov Property in Time Series via Deep Conditional Generative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testing-for-the-markov-property-in-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, we propose a nonparametric test for the Markov property in high-dimensional time series via deep conditional generative learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testing-for-the-markov-property-in-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-World Image Variation by Aligning Diffusion Inversion Chain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-world-image-variation-by-aligning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, a domain gap exists between generated images and real-world images, which poses a challenge in generating high-quality variations of real-world images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-world-image-variation-by-aligning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating with Confidence: Uncertainty Quantification for Black-box Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-with-confidence-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate uncertainty quantification in NLG for $\textit{black-box}$ LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-with-confidence-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
