<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:11:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>RSpell: Retrieval-augmented Framework for Domain Adaptive Chinese Spelling Check</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rspell-retrieval-augmented-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a retrieval-augmented spelling check framework called RSpell, which searches corresponding domain terms and incorporates them into CSC models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rspell-retrieval-augmented-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Neural Network Generalization for Grammar Induction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-neural-network-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How well do neural networks generalize?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-neural-network-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaBrowse: Adaptive Video Browser for Efficient Continuous Sign Language Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adabrowse-adaptive-video-browser-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then these features are fed into a policy network to intelligently select a subsequence to process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adabrowse-adaptive-video-browser-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Visual and Semantic Similarity Using Hierarchies for Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-visual-and-semantic-similarity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most of the research in content-based image retrieval (CBIR) focus on developing robust feature representations that can effectively retrieve instances from a database of images that are visually similar to a query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-visual-and-semantic-similarity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising Diffusion Probabilistic Model for Retinal Image Generation and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-probabilistic-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We developed a Retinal Trees (ReTree) dataset consisting of retinal images, corresponding vessel trees, and a segmentation network based on DDPM trained with images from the ReTree dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-probabilistic-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inherent Redundancy in Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inherent-redundancy-in-spiking-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we pose and focus on three key questions regarding the inherent redundancy in SNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inherent-redundancy-in-spiking-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expressivity of Graph Neural Networks Through the Lens of Adversarial Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressivity-of-graph-neural-networks-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We perform the first adversarial robustness study into Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) that are provably more powerful than traditional Message Passing Neural Networks (MPNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressivity-of-graph-neural-networks-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Independent Distribution Regularization for Private Graph Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/independent-distribution-regularization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we introduce a novel regularization to enforce the independence of the encoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/independent-distribution-regularization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ref-DVGO: Reflection-Aware Direct Voxel Grid Optimization for an Improved Quality-Efficiency Trade-Off in Reflective Scene Reconstructio</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ref-dvgo-reflection-aware-direct-voxel-grid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we investigate an implicit-explicit approach based on conventional volume rendering to enhance the reconstruction quality and accelerate the training and rendering processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ref-dvgo-reflection-aware-direct-voxel-grid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoencoding a Soft Touch to Learn Grasping from On-land to Underwater</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoding-a-soft-touch-to-learn-grasping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robots play a critical role as the physical agent of human operators in exploring the ocean.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoding-a-soft-touch-to-learn-grasping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detoxify Language Model Step-by-Step</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detoxify-language-model-step-by-step</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detoxification for LLMs is challenging since it requires models to avoid generating harmful content while maintaining the generation capability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detoxify-language-model-step-by-step</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeDoDe: Detect, Don't Describe -- Describe, Don't Detect for Local Feature Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dedode-detect-don-t-describe-describe-don-t</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To train a descriptor, we maximize the mutual nearest neighbour objective over the keypoints with a separate network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dedode-detect-don-t-describe-describe-don-t</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diagnosing Human-object Interaction Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnosing-human-object-interaction-detectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although we have witnessed significant progress in human-object interaction (HOI) detection with increasingly high mAP (mean Average Precision), a single mAP score is too concise to obtain an informative summary of a model's performance and to understand why one approach is better than another.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnosing-human-object-interaction-detectors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Membrane Potential Batch Normalization for Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membrane-potential-batch-normalization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[All these BNs are suggested to be used after the convolution layer as usually doing in CNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membrane-potential-batch-normalization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety Filter Design for Neural Network Systems via Convex Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-filter-design-for-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increase in data availability, it has been widely demonstrated that neural networks (NN) can capture complex system dynamics precisely in a data-driven manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-filter-design-for-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endogenous Macrodynamics in Algorithmic Recourse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/endogenous-macrodynamics-in-algorithmic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing work on Counterfactual Explanations (CE) and Algorithmic Recourse (AR) has largely focused on single individuals in a static environment: given some estimated model, the goal is to find valid counterfactuals for an individual instance that fulfill various desiderata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/endogenous-macrodynamics-in-algorithmic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPA-3D: Geometry-aware Prototype Alignment for Unsupervised Domain Adaptive 3D Object Detection from Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpa-3d-geometry-aware-prototype-alignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LiDAR-based 3D detection has made great progress in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpa-3d-geometry-aware-prototype-alignment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeViS: A Large-scale Benchmark for Video Segmentation with Motion Expressions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mevis-a-large-scale-benchmark-for-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To investigate the feasibility of using motion expressions to ground and segment objects in videos, we propose a large-scale dataset called MeViS, which contains numerous motion expressions to indicate target objects in complex environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mevis-a-large-scale-benchmark-for-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S-Mixup: Structural Mixup for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-mixup-structural-mixup-for-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing studies for applying the mixup technique on graphs mainly focus on graph classification tasks, while the research in node classification is still under-explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-mixup-structural-mixup-for-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Reference Deep Adaptive Curve Estimation for Low-Light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-reference-deep-adaptive-curve-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a 2-stage low-light image enhancement method called Self-Reference Deep Adaptive Curve Estimation (Self-DACE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-reference-deep-adaptive-curve-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Multi-View Deep Networks Methodology for Experimental Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-multi-view-deep-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we suggest different multi-view architectures for the vision domain, each suited to another problem, and we also present a methodology for explaining these models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-multi-view-deep-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KernelWarehouse: Towards Parameter-Efficient Dynamic Convolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernelwarehouse-towards-parameter-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic convolution learns a linear mixture of $n$ static kernels weighted with their sample-dependent attentions, demonstrating superior performance compared to normal convolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernelwarehouse-towards-parameter-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering User Interest from Biased and Noised Watch Time in Video Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-user-interest-from-biased-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the video recommendation, watch time is commonly adopted as an indicator of user interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-user-interest-from-biased-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Cap: Leveraging a Frozen Vision-Language Model for Hateful Meme Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pro-cap-leveraging-a-frozen-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we prompt a frozen PVLM by asking hateful content-related questions and use the answers as image captions (which we call Pro-Cap), so that the captions contain information critical for hateful content detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pro-cap-leveraging-a-frozen-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALIP: Adaptive Language-Image Pre-training with Synthetic Caption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alip-adaptive-language-image-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the presence of intrinsic noise and unmatched image-text pairs in web data can potentially affect the performance of representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alip-adaptive-language-image-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EQ-Net: Elastic Quantization Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eq-net-elastic-quantization-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore a one-shot network quantization regime, named Elastic Quantization Neural Networks (EQ-Net), which aims to train a robust weight-sharing quantization supernet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eq-net-elastic-quantization-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Commit Message Generation to History-Aware Commit Message Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-commit-message-generation-to-history</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use this dataset to evaluate the completion setting and the usefulness of the historical context for state-of-the-art CMG models and GPT-3. 5-turbo.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-commit-message-generation-to-history</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Identify Critical States for Reinforcement Learning from Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-identify-critical-states-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work on deep reinforcement learning (DRL) has pointed out that algorithmic information about good policies can be extracted from offline data which lack explicit information about executed actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-identify-critical-states-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Genetic Algorithm Meta-Heuristic for a Generalized Quadratic Assignment Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-genetic-algorithm-meta-heuristic-for-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The GQAP addressed in this work is defined as the task of minimizing the assignment and transportation costs of assigning a set of facilities to a set of locations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-genetic-algorithm-meta-heuristic-for-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ske2Grid: Skeleton-to-Grid Representation Learning for Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ske2grid-skeleton-to-grid-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents Ske2Grid, a new representation learning framework for improved skeleton-based action recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ske2grid-skeleton-to-grid-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Machine Unlearning Without Retraining Through Selective Synaptic Dampening</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-machine-unlearning-without-retraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Selective Synaptic Dampening (SSD), a novel two-step, post hoc, retrain-free approach to machine unlearning which is fast, performant, and does not require long-term storage of the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-machine-unlearning-without-retraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anaphoric Structure Emerges Between Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anaphoric-structure-emerges-between-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pragmatics is core to natural language, enabling speakers to communicate efficiently with structures like ellipsis and anaphora that can shorten utterances without loss of meaning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anaphoric-structure-emerges-between-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Low-Rank Instance Adaptation for Universal Neural Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-low-rank-instance-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We thus introduce a dynamic gating network on top of the low-rank adaptation method, in order to decide which decoder layer should employ adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-low-rank-instance-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complete Instances Mining for Weakly Supervised Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complete-instances-mining-for-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we propose a novel approach for WSIS that focuses on the online refinement of complete instances through the use of MaskIoU heads to predict the integrity scores of proposals and a Complete Instances Mining (CIM) strategy to explicitly model the redundant segmentation problem and generate refined pseudo labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complete-instances-mining-for-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Dataset Distillation for Image-Text Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-dataset-distillation-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dataset distillation methods offer the promise of reducing a large-scale dataset down to a significantly smaller set of (potentially synthetic) training examples, which preserve sufficient information for training a new model from scratch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-dataset-distillation-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handwritten Stenography Recognition and the LION Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handwritten-stenography-recognition-and-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods: A state-of-the-art text recognition model is trained to establish a baseline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handwritten-stenography-recognition-and-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dyadic Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dyadic-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This presents opportunities in mobile health to design interventions that target the dyadic relationship -- the relationship between a target person and their care partner -- with the aim of enhancing social support.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dyadic-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EduSAT: A Pedagogical Tool for Theory and Applications of Boolean Satisfiability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edusat-a-pedagogical-tool-for-theory-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Boolean Satisfiability (SAT) and Satisfiability Modulo Theories (SMT) are widely used in automated verification, but there is a lack of interactive tools designed for educational purposes in this field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edusat-a-pedagogical-tool-for-theory-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do We Fully Understand Students' Knowledge States? Identifying and Mitigating Answer Bias in Knowledge Tracing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-we-fully-understand-students-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing models tend to memorize the answer bias as a shortcut for achieving high prediction performance in KT, thereby failing to fully understand students' knowledge states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-we-fully-understand-students-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Temporal Edge Regression: A Case Study on Agriculture Trade Between Nations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-temporal-edge-regression-a-case-study</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore the application of GNNs to edge regression tasks in both static and dynamic settings, focusing on predicting food and agriculture trade values between nations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-temporal-edge-regression-a-case-study</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Phase Labeling and Lattice Refinement for Autonomous Material Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-phase-labeling-and-lattice</link>
      <description><![CDATA[X-ray diffraction (XRD) is an essential technique to determine a material's crystal structure in high-throughput experimentation, and has recently been incorporated in artificially intelligent agents in autonomous scientific discovery processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-phase-labeling-and-lattice</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Zero-Shot Reasoning with Role-Play Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-zero-shot-reasoning-with-role-play</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This highlights its potential to augment the reasoning capabilities of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-zero-shot-reasoning-with-role-play</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness and Privacy in Federated Learning and Their Implications in Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-and-privacy-in-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper endeavors to outline the typical lifecycle of fair federated learning in research as well as provide an updated taxonomy to account for the current state of fairness in implementations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-and-privacy-in-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoDeF: Content Deformation Fields for Temporally Consistent Video Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codef-content-deformation-fields-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the content deformation field CoDeF as a new type of video representation, which consists of a canonical content field aggregating the static contents in the entire video and a temporal deformation field recording the transformations from the canonical image (i. e., rendered from the canonical content field) to each individual frame along the time axis. Given a target video, these two fields are jointly optimized to reconstruct it through a carefully tailored rendering pipeline. We advisedly introduce some regularizations into the optimization process, urging the canonical content field to inherit semantics (e. g., the object shape) from the video. With such a design, CoDeF naturally supports lifting image algorithms for video processing, in the sense that one can apply an image algorithm to the canonical image and effortlessly propagate the outcomes to the entire video with the aid of the temporal deformation field. We experimentally show that CoDeF is able to lift image-to-image translation to video-to-video translation and lift keypoint detection to keypoint tracking without any training. More importantly, thanks to our lifting strategy that deploys the algorithms on only one image, we achieve superior cross-frame consistency in processed videos compared to existing video-to-video translation approaches, and even manage to track non-rigid objects like water and smog. Project page can be found at https://qiuyu96. github. io/CoDeF/.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codef-content-deformation-fields-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffGuard: Semantic Mismatch-Guided Out-of-Distribution Detection using Pre-trained Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffguard-semantic-mismatch-guided-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a recent work that directly applies it to OOD detection, which employs a conditional Generative Adversarial Network (cGAN) to enlarge semantic mismatch in the image space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffguard-semantic-mismatch-guided-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time Automatic M-mode Echocardiography Measurement with Panel Attention from Local-to-Global Pixels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-automatic-m-mode-echocardiography</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motion mode (M-mode) recording is an essential part of echocardiography to measure cardiac dimension and function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-automatic-m-mode-echocardiography</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-Aware Pseudo-Label Refinement for Source-Free Domain Adaptive Fundus Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-pseudo-label-refinement-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a context-aware pseudo-label refinement method for SF-UDA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-pseudo-label-refinement-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ImbSAM: A Closer Look at Sharpness-Aware Minimization in Class-Imbalanced Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imbsam-a-closer-look-at-sharpness-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this bottleneck, we leverage class priors to restrict the generalization scope of the class-agnostic SAM and propose a class-aware smoothness optimization algorithm named Imbalanced-SAM (ImbSAM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imbsam-a-closer-look-at-sharpness-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICAFusion: Iterative Cross-Attention Guided Feature Fusion for Multispectral Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icafusion-iterative-cross-attention-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Effective feature fusion of multispectral images plays a crucial role in multi-spectral object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icafusion-iterative-cross-attention-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffV2S: Diffusion-based Video-to-Speech Synthesis with Vision-guided Speaker Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffv2s-diffusion-based-video-to-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In doing so, the rich speaker embedding information can be produced solely from input visual information, and the extra audio information is not necessary during the inference time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffv2s-diffusion-based-video-to-speech</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
