<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 09:15:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>xJailbreak: Representation Space Guided Reinforcement Learning for Interpretable LLM Jailbreaking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xjailbreak-representation-space-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safety alignment mechanism are essential for preventing large language models (LLMs) from generating harmful information or unethical content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xjailbreak-representation-space-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JRE-L: Journalist, Reader, and Editor LLMs in the Loop for Science Journalism for the General Audience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jre-l-journalist-reader-and-editor-llms-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Science journalism reports current scientific discoveries to non-specialists, aiming to enable public comprehension of the state of the art.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jre-l-journalist-reader-and-editor-llms-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Code Runtime Performance through Context-Aware Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-code-runtime-performance-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimizing software performance through automated code refinement offers a promising avenue for enhancing execution speed and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-code-runtime-performance-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VeriFact: Verifying Facts in LLM-Generated Clinical Text with Electronic Health Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifact-verifying-facts-in-llm-generated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods to ensure factual accuracy of text generated by large language models (LLM) in clinical medicine are lacking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifact-verifying-facts-in-llm-generated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RDMM: Fine-Tuned LLM Models for On-Device Robotic Decision Making with Enhanced Contextual Awareness in Specific Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdmm-fine-tuned-llm-models-for-on-device</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research introduces a framework that utilizes RDMM (Robotics Decision-Making Models), which possess the capacity for decision-making within domain-specific contexts, as well as an awareness of their personal knowledge and capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdmm-fine-tuned-llm-models-for-on-device</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Roughly Forced Nonlinear PDEs via Misspecified Kernel Methods and Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-roughly-forced-nonlinear-pdes-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the use of Gaussian Processes (GPs) or Neural Networks (NNs) to numerically approximate the solutions to nonlinear partial differential equations (PDEs) with rough forcing or source terms, which commonly arise as pathwise solutions to stochastic PDEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-roughly-forced-nonlinear-pdes-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FactCG: Enhancing Fact Checkers with Graph-Based Multi-Hop Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factcg-enhancing-fact-checkers-with-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior research on training grounded factuality classification models to detect hallucinations in large language models (LLMs) has relied on public natural language inference (NLI) data and synthetic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factcg-enhancing-fact-checkers-with-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mamba-Shedder: Post-Transformer Compression for Efficient Selective Structured State Space Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-shedder-post-transformer-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large pre-trained models have achieved outstanding results in sequence modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-shedder-post-transformer-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A General Bayesian Framework for Informative Input Design in System Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-bayesian-framework-for-informative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We tackle the problem of informative input design for system identification, where we select inputs, observe the corresponding outputs from the true system, and optimize the parameters of our model to best fit the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-bayesian-framework-for-informative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scanning Trojaned Models Using Out-of-Distribution Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scanning-trojaned-models-using-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TRODO leverages the concept of "blind spots"--regions where trojaned classifiers erroneously identify out-of-distribution (OOD) samples as in-distribution (ID).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scanning-trojaned-models-using-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model Critics for Execution-Free Evaluation of Code Changes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-critics-for-execution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Importantly, we assume access to the gold test patch for the problem (i. e., reference-aware) to assess both semantics and executability of generated patches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-critics-for-execution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHiP: Cross-modal Hierarchical Direct Preference Optimization for Multimodal LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chip-cross-modal-hierarchical-direct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, in this work, we propose a Cross-modal Hierarchical Direct Preference Optimization (CHiP) to address these limitations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chip-cross-modal-hierarchical-direct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Rollouts in Model-Based Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-rollouts-in-model-based-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model-based reinforcement learning (MBRL) seeks to enhance data efficiency by learning a model of the environment and generating synthetic rollouts from it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-rollouts-in-model-based-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SliceOcc: Indoor 3D Semantic Occupancy Prediction with Vertical Slice Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliceocc-indoor-3d-semantic-occupancy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To utilize these slice features, we propose SliceOcc, an RGB camera-based model specifically tailored for indoor 3D semantic occupancy prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliceocc-indoor-3d-semantic-occupancy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exponential Family Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exponential-family-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The self-attention mechanism is the backbone of the transformer neural network underlying most large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exponential-family-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RODEO: Robust Outlier Detection via Exposing Adaptive Out-of-Distribution Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rodeo-robust-outlier-detection-via-exposing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce RODEO, a data-centric approach that generates effective outliers for robust outlier detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rodeo-robust-outlier-detection-via-exposing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream to Drive with Predictive Individual World Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dream-to-drive-with-predictive-individual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is still a challenging topic to make reactive driving behaviors in complex urban environments as road users' intentions are unknown.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dream-to-drive-with-predictive-individual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Phenology Modeling for Predicting Temperature Effects on Tree Dormancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-phenology-modeling-for-predicting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Biophysical models offer valuable insights into climate-phenology relationships in both natural and agricultural settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-phenology-modeling-for-predicting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polyp-Gen: Realistic and Diverse Polyp Image Generation for Endoscopic Dataset Expansion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyp-gen-realistic-and-diverse-polyp-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advancements in generating synthetic images for dataset expansion, existing endoscopic image generation algorithms failed to accurately generate the details of polyp boundary regions and typically required medical priors to specify plausible locations and shapes of polyps, which limited the realism and diversity of the generated images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyp-gen-realistic-and-diverse-polyp-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-Differentiating Any LLM Workflow: A Farewell to Manual Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-differentiating-any-llm-workflow-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have reshaped natural language processing, powering applications from multi-hop retrieval and question answering to autonomous agent workflows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-differentiating-any-llm-workflow-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HateBench: Benchmarking Hate Speech Detectors on LLM-Generated Content and Hate Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hatebench-benchmarking-hate-speech-detectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose HateBench, a framework for benchmarking hate speech detectors on LLM-generated hate speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hatebench-benchmarking-hate-speech-detectors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outlier Synthesis via Hamiltonian Monte Carlo for Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-synthesis-via-hamiltonian-monte-carlo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Hamiltonian Monte Carlo with sampling acceptance rate almost close to 1 also makes our framework enjoy great efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-synthesis-via-hamiltonian-monte-carlo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CascadeV: An Implementation of Wurstchen Architecture for Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascadev-an-implementation-of-wurstchen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, with the tremendous success of diffusion models in the field of text-to-image (T2I) generation, increasing attention has been directed toward their potential in text-to-video (T2V) applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascadev-an-implementation-of-wurstchen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixture-of-Mamba: Enhancing Multi-Modal State-Space Models with Modality-Aware Sparsity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-mamba-enhancing-multi-modal-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the Chameleon setting, Mixture-of-Mamba reaches similar image loss with just 42. 50% of the FLOPs at the 1. 4B scale, and similar text loss with just 65. 40% of the FLOPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-mamba-enhancing-multi-modal-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIM: Surface-based fMRI Analysis for Inter-Subject Multimodal Decoding from Movie-Watching Experiments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim-surface-based-fmri-analysis-for-inter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key obstacle to model generalisation is the degree of variability of inter-subject cortical organisation, which makes it difficult to align or compare cortical signals across participants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim-surface-based-fmri-analysis-for-inter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Diverse Perspectives: A Multi-Agent Framework for Enhanced Error Detection in Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-diverse-perspectives-a-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For specific industrial scenarios, our framework can facilitate the training of specialized agents using domain-specific knowledge graphs for error detection, which highlights the potential industrial application value of our framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-diverse-perspectives-a-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Formal Verification of Markov Processes with Learned Parameters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/formal-verification-of-markov-processes-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the problem of formally verifying properties of Markov processes where the parameters are the output of machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/formal-verification-of-markov-processes-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-powered Multi-agent Framework for Goal-oriented Learning in Intelligent Tutoring System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-powered-multi-agent-framework-for-goal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After identifying the skill gap, it schedules an efficient learning path using an evolving optimization approach, driven by a comprehensive and dynamic profile of learners' multifaceted status.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-powered-multi-agent-framework-for-goal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficiency Bottlenecks of Convolutional Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks: A Comprehensive Scrutiny with ImageNet, AlexNet, LeNet and Tabular Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiency-bottlenecks-of-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Algorithmic level developments like Convolutional Neural Networks, transformers, attention mechanism, Retrieval Augmented Generation and so on have changed Artificial Intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiency-bottlenecks-of-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-View Attention Syntactic Enhanced Graph Convolutional Network for Aspect-based Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-attention-syntactic-enhanced-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aspect-based Sentiment Analysis (ABSA) is the task aimed at predicting the sentiment polarity of aspect words within sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-attention-syntactic-enhanced-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upside Down Reinforcement Learning with Policy Generators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/upside-down-reinforcement-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method, dubbed Upside Down Reinforcement Learning with Policy Generators (UDRLPG), streamlines comparable techniques by removing the need for an evaluator or critic to update the weights of the generator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/upside-down-reinforcement-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UDBE: Unsupervised Diffusion-based Brightness Enhancement in Underwater Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/udbe-unsupervised-diffusion-based-brightness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A major challenge in this domain is the depth at which images are captured, with increasing depth resulting in a darker environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/udbe-unsupervised-diffusion-based-brightness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TopoNets: High Performing Vision and Language Models with Brain-Like Topography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toponets-high-performing-vision-and-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neurons in the brain are organized such that nearby cells tend to share similar functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toponets-high-performing-vision-and-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LCTG Bench: LLM Controlled Text Generation Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lctg-bench-llm-controlled-text-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LCTG Bench provides a unified framework for assessing control performance, enabling users to select the most suitable model for their use cases based on controllability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lctg-bench-llm-controlled-text-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CENSOR: Defense Against Gradient Inversion via Orthogonal Subspace Bayesian Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/censor-defense-against-gradient-inversion-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing gradient inversion attacks can exploit this vulnerability to recover private training instances from a client's gradient vectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/censor-defense-against-gradient-inversion-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Retinal V2: Transfer an Elite Knowledge Spark into Fundus Vision-Language Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-retinal-v2-transfer-an-elite-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language pretraining (VLP) has been investigated to generalize across diverse downstream tasks for fundus image analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-retinal-v2-transfer-an-elite-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Structural Convolution Network for Domain-Invariant Point Cloud Recognition of Autonomous Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-structural-convolution-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present the Multi-View Structural Convolution Network (MSCN) designed for domain-invariant point cloud recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-structural-convolution-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe Gradient Flow for Bilevel Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-gradient-flow-for-bilevel-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bilevel optimization is a key framework in hierarchical decision-making, where one problem is embedded within the constraints of another.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-gradient-flow-for-bilevel-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing Out-of-Label Hazard Detection in Dashcam Videos: Insights from the COOOL Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-out-of-label-hazard-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel approach for hazard analysis in dashcam footage, addressing the detection of driver reactions to hazards, the identification of hazardous objects, and the generation of descriptive captions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-out-of-label-hazard-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWIFT: Mapping Sub-series with Wavelet Decomposition Improves Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swift-mapping-sub-series-with-wavelet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose $\textit{SWIFT}$, a lightweight model that is not only powerful, but also efficient in deployment and inference for Long-term Time Series Forecasting (LTSF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swift-mapping-sub-series-with-wavelet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPECIAL: Zero-shot Hyperspectral Image Classification With CLIP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/special-zero-shot-hyperspectral-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperspectral image (HSI) classification aims at categorizing each pixel in an HSI into a specific land cover class, which is crucial for applications like remote sensing, environmental monitoring, and agriculture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/special-zero-shot-hyperspectral-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting clinician implicit biases in diagnoses using proximal causal inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-clinician-implicit-biases-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a causal inference approach to detect the effect of clinician implicit biases on patient outcomes in large-scale medical data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-clinician-implicit-biases-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Tropical Cyclone Forecasting With Video Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-tropical-cyclone-forecasting-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tropical cyclone (TC) forecasting is crucial for disaster preparedness and mitigation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-tropical-cyclone-forecasting-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Attention-Sharing Information Distillation Transformer for Lightweight Single Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-attention-sharing-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose the Attention-Sharing Information Distillation (ASID) network, a lightweight SR network that integrates attention-sharing and an information distillation structure specifically designed for Transformer-based SR methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-attention-sharing-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconciling Predictive Multiplicity in Practice</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconciling-predictive-multiplicity-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This issue is exemplified by the model multiplicity (MM) phenomenon, where a set of comparable models yield inconsistent predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconciling-predictive-multiplicity-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DepoRanker: A Web Tool to predict Klebsiella Depolymerases using Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deporanker-a-web-tool-to-predict-klebsiella</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Objective: To develop a machine learning model for identifying and ranking potential phage depolymerases targeting Klebsiella.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deporanker-a-web-tool-to-predict-klebsiella</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Quantum Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-quantum-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Benchmarking and establishing proper statistical validation metrics for reinforcement learning (RL) remain ongoing challenges, where no consensus has been established yet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-quantum-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoCoNUT: Structural Code Understanding does not fall out of a tree</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coconut-structural-code-understanding-does</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we demonstrate that high performance on such benchmarks does not correlate to humans' innate ability to understand structural control flow in code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coconut-structural-code-understanding-does</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parametric Retrieval Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parametric-retrieval-augmented-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce Parametric retrieval-augmented generation (Parametric RAG), a new RAG paradigm that integrates external knowledge directly into the parameters of feed-forward networks (FFN) of an LLM through document parameterization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parametric-retrieval-augmented-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUCY: Linguistic Understanding and Control Yielding Early Stage of Her</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lucy-linguistic-understanding-and-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The film Her features Samantha, a sophisticated AI audio agent who is capable of understanding both linguistic and paralinguistic information in human speech and delivering real-time responses that are natural, informative and sensitive to emotional subtleties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lucy-linguistic-understanding-and-control</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
