<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 09:12:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Factorized Inverse Path Tracing for Efficient and Accurate Material-Lighting Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factorized-inverse-path-tracing-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inverse path tracing has recently been applied to joint material and lighting estimation, given geometry and multi-view HDR observations of an indoor scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factorized-inverse-path-tracing-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALADIN-NST: Self-supervised disentangled representation learning of artistic style through Neural Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aladin-nst-self-supervised-disentangled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representation learning aims to discover individual salient features of a domain in a compact and descriptive form that strongly identifies the unique characteristics of a given sample respective to its domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aladin-nst-self-supervised-disentangled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proximity Forest 2.0: A new effective and scalable similarity-based classifier for time series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proximity-forest-2-0-a-new-effective-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series classification (TSC) is a challenging task due to the diversity of types of feature that may be relevant for different classification tasks, including trends, variance, frequency, magnitude, and various patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proximity-forest-2-0-a-new-effective-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unicom: Universal and Compact Representation Learning for Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unicom-universal-and-compact-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further enhance the low-dimensional feature representation, we randomly select partial feature dimensions when calculating the similarities between embeddings and class-wise prototypes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unicom-universal-and-compact-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rail Detection: An Efficient Row-based Network and A New Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rail-detection-an-efficient-row-based-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the growth of lane detection, we propose a rail database and a row-based rail detection method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rail-detection-an-efficient-row-based-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Local Features All You Need for Cross-Domain Visual Place Recognition?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-local-features-all-you-need-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advances, recognizing the same place when the query comes from a significantly different distribution is still a major hurdle for state of the art retrieval methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-local-features-all-you-need-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scale-Equivariant Deep Learning for 3D Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-equivariant-deep-learning-for-3d-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability of convolutional neural networks (CNNs) to recognize objects regardless of their position in the image is due to the translation-equivariance of the convolutional operation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-equivariant-deep-learning-for-3d-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard Patches Mining for Masked Image Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-patches-mining-for-masked-image-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that the reconstruction loss can naturally be the metric of the difficulty of the pre-training task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-patches-mining-for-masked-image-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Image Quality Assessment Dataset for Portraits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-image-quality-assessment-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This costly procedure can be partially replaced by automated learning-based methods for image quality assessment (IQA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-image-quality-assessment-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Understanding How Data Augmentation Works with Imbalanced Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-understanding-how-data-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data augmentation forms the cornerstone of many modern machine learning training pipelines; yet, the mechanisms by which it works are not clearly understood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-understanding-how-data-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Aware Mixup for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-mixup-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the hard-fitting issue, we propose to perform a semantic-aware mixup (SAM) for domain generalization, where whether to perform mixup depends on the semantic and domain information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-mixup-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPr-Net: Geometric Prototypical Network for Point Cloud Few-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpr-net-geometric-prototypical-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of 3D-computer vision applications, point cloud few-shot learning plays a critical role.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpr-net-geometric-prototypical-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP Surgery for Better Explainability with Enhancement in Open-Vocabulary Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-surgery-for-better-explainability-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive Language-Image Pre-training (CLIP) is a powerful multimodal large vision model that has demonstrated significant benefits for downstream tasks, including many zero-shot learning and text-guided vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-surgery-for-better-explainability-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DynamicDet: A Unified Dynamic Architecture for Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamicdet-a-unified-dynamic-architecture-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also present a novel optimization strategy with an exiting criterion based on the detection losses for our dynamic detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamicdet-a-unified-dynamic-architecture-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Aligned Pseudo-Supervision from Non-Aligned Data for Image Restoration in Under-Display Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-aligned-pseudo-supervision-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the difficulty in collecting large-scale and perfectly aligned paired training data for Under-Display Camera (UDC) image restoration, previous methods resort to monitor-based image systems or simulation-based methods, sacrificing the realness of the data and introducing domain gaps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-aligned-pseudo-supervision-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Dense Retrieval's Few-Shot Ability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-dense-retrieval-s-few-shot-ability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, the dataset is disjointed into base and novel classes, allowing DR models to be continuously trained on ample data from base classes and a few samples in novel classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-dense-retrieval-s-few-shot-ability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precise localization of corneal reflections in eye images using deep learning trained on synthetic data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precise-localization-of-corneal-reflections</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method outperformed state-of-the-art algorithmic methods on real eye images with a 35% reduction in terms of spatial precision, and performed on par with state-of-the-art on simulated images in terms of spatial accuracy. We conclude that our method provides a precise method for CR center localization and provides a solution to the data availability problem which is one of the important common roadblocks in the development of deep learning models for gaze estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precise-localization-of-corneal-reflections</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InterGen: Diffusion-based Multi-human Motion Generation under Complex Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intergen-diffusion-based-multi-human-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we propose a novel representation for motion input in our interaction diffusion model, which explicitly formulates the global relations between the two performers in the world frame.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intergen-diffusion-based-multi-human-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying and Personalizing Weakly-supervised Federated Medical Image Segmentation via Adaptive Representation and Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-and-personalizing-weakly-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The statistical heterogeneity (e. g., non-IID data and domain shifts) is a primary obstacle in FL, impairing the generalization performance of the global model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-and-personalizing-weakly-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosted Prompt Ensembles for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosted-prompt-ensembles-for-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods such as chain-of-thought prompting and self-consistency have pushed the frontier of language model reasoning performance with no additional training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosted-prompt-ensembles-for-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance-Aware Domain Generalization for Face Anti-Spoofing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-aware-domain-generalization-for-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose a novel perspective for DG FAS that aligns features on the instance level without the need for domain labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-aware-domain-generalization-for-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMM (Segment Any Medical Model): A 3D Slicer Integration to SAM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samm-segment-any-medical-model-a-3d-slicer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To assist with the development, assessment, and utilization of SAM on medical images, we introduce Segment Any Medical Model (SAMM), an extension of SAM on 3D Slicer, a widely-used open-source image processing and visualization software that has been extensively used in the medical imaging community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samm-segment-any-medical-model-a-3d-slicer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FALQU: Finding Answers to Legal Questions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/falqu-finding-answers-to-legal-questions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new test collection for Legal IR, FALQU: Finding Answers to Legal Questions, where questions and answers were obtained from Law Stack Exchange (LawSE), a Q&A website for legal professionals, and others with experience in law.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/falqu-finding-answers-to-legal-questions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of Differentially Constrained Motion Models for Graph-Based Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-differentially-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research investigates the performance of various motion models in combination with numerical solvers for the prediction task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-differentially-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CamDiff: Camouflage Image Augmentation via Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camdiff-camouflage-image-augmentation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we leverage the latent diffusion model to synthesize salient objects in camouflaged scenes, while using the zero-shot image classification ability of the Contrastive Language-Image Pre-training (CLIP) model to prevent synthesis failures and ensure the synthesized object aligns with the input prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camdiff-camouflage-image-augmentation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actually Sparse Variational Gaussian Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actually-sparse-variational-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For large datasets, sparse GPs reduce these demands by conditioning on a small set of inducing variables designed to summarise the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actually-sparse-variational-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task Difficulty Aware Parameter Allocation &amp; Regularization for Lifelong Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-difficulty-aware-parameter-allocation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the Parameter Allocation & Regularization (PAR), which adaptively select an appropriate strategy for each task from parameter allocation and regularization based on its learning difficulty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-difficulty-aware-parameter-allocation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OccFormer: Dual-path Transformer for Vision-based 3D Semantic Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occformer-dual-path-transformer-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The vision-based perception for autonomous driving has undergone a transformation from the bird-eye-view (BEV) representations to the 3D semantic occupancy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occformer-dual-path-transformer-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAL: Evaluation and Interpretation of Active Learning Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openal-evaluation-and-interpretation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the vast body of literature on Active Learning (AL), there is no comprehensive and open benchmark allowing for efficient and simple comparison of proposed samplers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openal-evaluation-and-interpretation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automaton-Guided Curriculum Generation for Reinforcement Learning Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automaton-guided-curriculum-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments in gridworld and physics-based simulated robotics domains show that the curricula produced by AGCL achieve improved time-to-threshold performance on a complex sequential decision-making problem relative to state-of-the-art curriculum learning (e. g, teacher-student, self-play) and automaton-guided reinforcement learning baselines (e. g, Q-Learning for Reward Machines).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automaton-guided-curriculum-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biological Factor Regulatory Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biological-factor-regulatory-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BFReg-NN starts from gene expression data and is capable of merging most existing biological knowledge into the model, including the regulatory relations among genes or proteins (e. g., gene regulatory networks (GRN), protein-protein interaction networks (PPI)) and the hierarchical relations among genes, proteins and pathways (e. g., several genes/proteins are contained in a pathway).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biological-factor-regulatory-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Learning for News Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-learning-for-news-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some recent \textit{news recommendation} (NR) methods introduce a Pre-trained Language Model (PLM) to encode news representation by following the vanilla pre-train and fine-tune paradigm with carefully-designed recommendation-specific neural networks and objective functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-learning-for-news-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Efficient Fine-tuning of Pre-trained Code Models: An Experimental Study and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-fine-tuning-of-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental study shows that (1) lexical, syntactic and structural properties of source code are encoded in the lower, intermediate, and higher layers, respectively, while the semantic property spans across the entire model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-fine-tuning-of-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HRS-Bench: Holistic, Reliable and Scalable Benchmark for Text-to-Image Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrs-bench-holistic-reliable-and-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A human evaluation aligned with 95% of our evaluations on average was conducted to probe the effectiveness of HRS-Bench.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrs-bench-holistic-reliable-and-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum-Based Imitation of Versatile Skills</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-based-imitation-of-versatile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning skills by imitation is a promising concept for the intuitive teaching of robots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-based-imitation-of-versatile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SportsMOT: A Large Multi-Object Tracking Dataset in Multiple Sports Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sportsmot-a-large-multi-object-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We expect SportsMOT to encourage the MOT trackers to promote in both motion-based association and appearance-based association.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sportsmot-a-large-multi-object-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGXplain: Rule-Based Deep Neural Network Explanations Using Dual Linear Programs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cgxplain-rule-based-deep-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rule-based surrogate models are an effective and interpretable way to approximate a Deep Neural Network's (DNN) decision boundaries, allowing humans to easily understand deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cgxplain-rule-based-deep-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selecting Robust Features for Machine Learning Applications using Multidata Causal Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-robust-features-for-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply our framework to the statistical intensity prediction of Western Pacific Tropical Cyclones (TC), for which it is often difficult to accurately choose drivers and their dimensionality reduction (time lags, vertical levels, and area-averaging).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-robust-features-for-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did we personalize? Assessing personalization by an online reinforcement learning algorithm using resampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/did-we-personalize-assessing-personalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use a working definition of personalization and introduce a resampling-based methodology for investigating whether the personalization exhibited by the RL algorithm is an artifact of the RL algorithm stochasticity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/did-we-personalize-assessing-personalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TodyNet: Temporal Dynamic Graph Neural Network for Multivariate Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/todynet-temporal-dynamic-graph-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, the existing deep learning-based methods neglect the hidden dependencies in different dimensions and also rarely consider the unique dynamic features of time series, which lack sufficient feature extraction capability to obtain satisfactory classification accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/todynet-temporal-dynamic-graph-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable graph-structured models for inverse design of lattice materials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-graph-structured-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Materials possessing flexible physico-chemical properties that adapt on-demand to the hostile environmental conditions of deep space will become essential in defining the future of space exploration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-graph-structured-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnCRtainTS: Uncertainty Quantification for Cloud Removal in Optical Satellite Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncrtaints-uncertainty-quantification-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clouds and haze often occlude optical satellite images, hindering continuous, dense monitoring of the Earth's surface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncrtaints-uncertainty-quantification-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Graph Neural Networks for Charged Particle Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-graph-neural-networks-for-charged</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) have gained traction in high-energy physics (HEP) for their potential to improve accuracy and scalability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-graph-neural-networks-for-charged</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The MONET dataset: Multimodal drone thermal dataset recorded in rural scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-monet-dataset-multimodal-drone-thermal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MONET is different from previous thermal drone datasets because it features multimodal data, including rural scenes captured with thermal cameras containing both person and vehicle targets, along with trajectory information and metadata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-monet-dataset-multimodal-drone-thermal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DartsReNet: Exploring new RNN cells in ReNet architectures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dartsrenet-exploring-new-rnn-cells-in-renet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present new Recurrent Neural Network (RNN) cells for image classification using a Neural Architecture Search (NAS) approach called DARTS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dartsrenet-exploring-new-rnn-cells-in-renet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Learning Across Heterogeneous Features For Efficient Tensor Program Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-across-heterogeneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tuning tensor program generation involves searching for various possible program transformation combinations for a given program on target hardware to optimize the tensor program execution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-across-heterogeneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable Textual Inversion for Personalized Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-textual-inversion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent large-scale generative modeling has attained unprecedented performance especially in producing high-fidelity images driven by text prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-textual-inversion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRHF: Rank Responses to Align Language Models with Human Feedback without tears</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rrhf-rank-responses-to-align-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning from Human Feedback (RLHF) facilitates the alignment of large language models with human preferences, significantly enhancing the quality of interactions between humans and these models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rrhf-rank-responses-to-align-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Recommender Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-recommender-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In light of the impressive advantages of Diffusion Models (DMs) over traditional generative models in image synthesis, we propose a novel Diffusion Recommender Model (named DiffRec) to learn the generative process in a denoising manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-recommender-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards preserving word order importance through Forced Invalidation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-preserving-word-order-importance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large pre-trained language models such as BERT have been widely used as a framework for natural language understanding (NLU) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-preserving-word-order-importance</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
