<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 09:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Graph neural network outputs are almost surely asymptotically constant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-network-outputs-are-almost</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results apply to a broad class of random graph models, including the (sparse) Erd\H{o}s-R\'enyi model and the stochastic block model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-network-outputs-are-almost</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear and nonlinear system identification under $\ell_1$- and group-Lasso regularization via L-BFGS-B</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-and-nonlinear-system-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an approach for identifying linear and nonlinear discrete-time state-space models, possibly under $\ell_1$- and group-Lasso regularization, based on the L-BFGS-B algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-and-nonlinear-system-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From One to Many: Expanding the Scope of Toxicity Mitigation in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-one-to-many-expanding-the-scope-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To date, toxicity mitigation in language models has almost entirely been focused on single-language settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-one-to-many-expanding-the-scope-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Photographic Image Layout Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-photographic-image-layout</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This shortfall makes the learning process for photographic image layouts suboptimal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-photographic-image-layout</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AcceleratedLiNGAM: Learning Causal DAGs at the speed of GPUs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acceleratedlingam-learning-causal-dags-at-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing causal discovery methods based on combinatorial optimization or search are slow, prohibiting their application on large-scale datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acceleratedlingam-learning-causal-dags-at-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Geolocated Realtime Data of Interfleet Urban Transit Bus Idling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-geolocated-realtime-data-of-interfleet-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Urban transit bus idling is a contributor to ecological stress, economic inefficiency, and medically hazardous health outcomes due to emissions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-geolocated-realtime-data-of-interfleet-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apollo: Lightweight Multilingual Medical LLMs towards Democratizing Medical AI to 6B People</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apollo-lightweight-multilingual-medical-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the vast repository of global medical knowledge predominantly being in English, local languages are crucial for delivering tailored healthcare services, particularly in areas with limited medical resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apollo-lightweight-multilingual-medical-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Invariant Representations of Graph Neural Networks via Cluster Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-invariant-representations-of-graph-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose the Cluster Information Transfer (CIT) mechanism (Code available at https://github. com/BUPT-GAMMA/CITGNN), which can learn invariant representations for GNNs, thereby improving their generalization ability to various and unknown test graphs with structure shift.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-invariant-representations-of-graph-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Heuristic Core: Understanding Subnetwork Generalization in Pretrained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-heuristic-core-understanding-subnetwork</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of finding competing subnetworks, we find that all subnetworks -- whether they generalize or not -- share a set of attention heads, which we refer to as the heuristic core.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-heuristic-core-understanding-subnetwork</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GaLore: Memory-Efficient LLM Training by Gradient Low-Rank Projection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galore-memory-efficient-llm-training-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach reduces memory usage by up to 65. 5% in optimizer states while maintaining both efficiency and performance for pre-training on LLaMA 1B and 7B architectures with C4 dataset with up to 19. 7B tokens, and on fine-tuning RoBERTa on GLUE tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galore-memory-efficient-llm-training-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slot Abstractors: Toward Scalable Abstract Visual Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slot-abstractors-toward-scalable-abstract</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Abstract visual reasoning is a characteristically human ability, allowing the identification of relational patterns that are abstracted away from object features, and the systematic generalization of those patterns to unseen problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slot-abstractors-toward-scalable-abstract</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backtracing: Retrieving the Cause of the Query</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backtracing-retrieving-the-cause-of-the-query</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While information retrieval (IR) systems may provide answers for such user queries, they do not directly assist content creators -- such as lecturers who want to improve their content -- identify segments that _caused_ a user to ask those questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backtracing-retrieving-the-cause-of-the-query</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance Evaluation of Semi-supervised Learning Frameworks for Multi-Class Weed Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-evaluation-of-semi-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we assess the effectiveness of a semi-supervised learning framework for multi-class weed detection, employing two well-known object detection frameworks, namely FCOS and Faster-RCNN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-evaluation-of-semi-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Efficient and Effective Unlearning of Large Language Models for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-and-effective-unlearning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in order to protect user privacy and optimize utility, it is also crucial for LLMRec to intentionally forget specific user data, which is generally referred to as recommendation unlearning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-and-effective-unlearning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PPTC-R benchmark: Towards Evaluating the Robustness of Large Language Models for PowerPoint Task Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pptc-r-benchmark-towards-evaluating-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The growing dependence on Large Language Models (LLMs) for finishing user instructions necessitates a comprehensive understanding of their robustness to complex task completion in real-world situations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pptc-r-benchmark-towards-evaluating-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Diffusion Policy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-diffusion-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Imitation learning provides an efficient way to teach robots dexterous skills; however, learning complex skills robustly and generalizablely usually consumes large amounts of human demonstrations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-diffusion-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Language Models Puzzle Prodigies? Algorithmic Puzzles Unveil Serious Challenges in Multimodal Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-language-models-puzzle-prodigies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new dataset, AlgoPuzzleVQA designed to challenge and evaluate the capabilities of multimodal language models in solving algorithmic puzzles that necessitate both visual understanding, language understanding, and complex algorithmic reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-language-models-puzzle-prodigies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEAD: Learning Decomposition for Source-free Universal Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lead-learning-decomposition-for-source-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, LEAD is also appealing in that it is complementary to most existing methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lead-learning-decomposition-for-source-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Geolocated Realtime Data of Interfleet Urban Transit Bus Idling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-geolocated-realtime-data-of-interfleet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Urban transit bus idling is a contributor to ecological stress, economic inefficiency, and medically hazardous health outcomes due to emissions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-geolocated-realtime-data-of-interfleet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-based Generative Prior for Low-Complexity MIMO Channel Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-generative-prior-for-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes a novel channel estimator based on diffusion models (DMs), one of the currently top-rated generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-generative-prior-for-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing the dimensionality and granularity in hierarchical categorical variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-the-dimensionality-and-granularity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply our methodology on a real dataset and find that the reduced hierarchy is an improvement over the original hierarchical structure and reduced structures proposed in the literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-the-dimensionality-and-granularity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German also Hallucinates! Inconsistency Detection in News Summaries with the Absinth Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/german-also-hallucinates-inconsistency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advent of Large Language Models (LLMs) has led to remarkable progress on a wide range of natural language processing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/german-also-hallucinates-inconsistency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Hallucination in Large Language Models based on Unanswerable Math Word Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-hallucination-in-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new method for evaluating LLM hallucination in Question Answering (QA) based on the unanswerable math word problem (MWP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-hallucination-in-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Multilingual Dense Retrieval via Generative Pseudo Labeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-multilingual-dense-retrieval-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dense retrieval methods have demonstrated promising performance in multilingual information retrieval, where queries and documents can be in different languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-multilingual-dense-retrieval-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A&amp;B BNN: Add&amp;Bit-Operation-Only Hardware-Friendly Binary Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-b-bnn-add-bit-operation-only-hardware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A&B BNN is proposed to directly remove part of the multiplication operations in a traditional BNN and replace the rest with an equal number of bit operations, introducing the mask layer and the quantized RPReLU structure based on the normalizer-free network architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-b-bnn-add-bit-operation-only-hardware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Decode Collaboratively with Multiple Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-decode-collaboratively-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method to teach multiple large language models (LLM) to collaborate by interleaving their generations at the token level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-decode-collaboratively-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Topic Modelling with Transformer Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-topic-modelling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rise of transformers in Natural Language Processing, however, several successful models that rely on straightforward clustering approaches in transformer-based embedding spaces have emerged and consolidated the notion of topics as clusters of embedding vectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-topic-modelling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probing the Robustness of Time-series Forecasting Models with CounterfacTS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-the-robustness-of-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because most of the training data does not reflect such changes, the models present poor performance on the new out-of-distribution scenarios and, therefore, the impact of such events cannot be reliably anticipated ahead of time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-the-robustness-of-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Environmental Insights: Democratizing Access to Ambient Air Pollution Data and Predictive Analytics with an Open-Source Python Package</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/environmental-insights-democratizing-access</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ambient air pollution is a pervasive issue with wide-ranging effects on human health, ecosystem vitality, and economic structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/environmental-insights-democratizing-access</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedMamba: Vision Mamba for Medical Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medmamba-vision-mamba-for-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image classification is a very fundamental and crucial task in the field of computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medmamba-vision-mamba-for-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECAP: Extensive Cut-and-Paste Augmentation for Unsupervised Domain Adaptive Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecap-extensive-cut-and-paste-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We implement ECAP on top of the recent method MIC and boost its performance on two synthetic-to-real domain adaptation benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecap-extensive-cut-and-paste-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MolNexTR: A Generalized Deep Learning Model for Molecular Image Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molnextr-a-generalized-deep-learning-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, it employs a series of novel augmentation algorithms to significantly enhance the robustness and performance of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molnextr-a-generalized-deep-learning-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KG-TREAT: Pre-training for Treatment Effect Estimation by Synergizing Patient Data with Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kg-treat-pre-training-for-treatment-effect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the challenges, we introduce a novel pre-training and fine-tuning framework, KG-TREAT, which synergizes large-scale observational patient data with biomedical knowledge graphs (KGs) to enhance TEE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kg-treat-pre-training-for-treatment-effect</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-Shot: A Unified System to Handle Frequent, Few-shot and Zero-shot Learning Simultaneously in Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-shot-a-unified-system-to-handle-frequent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, few-shot and zero-shot learning, which learn to predict labels with limited annotated instances, have garnered significant attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-shot-a-unified-system-to-handle-frequent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint multi-task learning improves weakly-supervised biomarker prediction in computational pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-multi-task-learning-improves-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Learning (DL) can predict biomarkers directly from digitized cancer histology in a weakly-supervised setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-multi-task-learning-improves-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Language and Items for Retrieval and Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-language-and-items-for-retrieval-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces BLaIR, a series of pretrained sentence embedding models specialized for recommendation scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-language-and-items-for-retrieval-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRCoder: Intermediate Representations Make Language Models Robust Multilingual Code Generators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ircoder-intermediate-representations-make</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, most mainstream Code-LMs have been pre-trained on source code files alone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ircoder-intermediate-representations-make</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Attention Empowered Graph Convolutional Network for Structure Learning and Node Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-attention-empowered-graph-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed GCN-SA contains two enhancements corresponding to edges and node features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-attention-empowered-graph-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformal prediction for multi-dimensional time series by ellipsoidal sets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-prediction-for-multi-dimensional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conformal prediction (CP) has been a popular method for uncertainty quantification because it is distribution-free, model-agnostic, and theoretically sound.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-prediction-for-multi-dimensional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extend Your Own Correspondences: Unsupervised Distant Point Cloud Registration by Progressive Distance Extension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extend-your-own-correspondences-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Registration of point clouds collected from a pair of distant vehicles provides a comprehensive and accurate 3D view of the driving scenario, which is vital for driving safety related applications, yet existing literature suffers from the expensive pose label acquisition and the deficiency to generalize to new data distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extend-your-own-correspondences-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Effectiveness of Distillation in Mitigating Backdoors in Pre-trained Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-distillation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Distillation aims to distill knowledge from a given model (a. k. a the teacher net) and transfer it to another (a. k. a the student net).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-distillation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RouteExplainer: An Explanation Framework for Vehicle Routing Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/routeexplainer-an-explanation-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the explainability for VRP is significant for improving the reliability and interactivity in practical VRP applications, it remains unexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/routeexplainer-an-explanation-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>gaHealth: An English-Irish Bilingual Corpus of Health Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gahealth-an-english-irish-bilingual-corpus-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However in the context of low-resource languages, there is a paucity of parallel data datasets available for developing translation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gahealth-an-english-irish-bilingual-corpus-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task Attribute Distance for Few-Shot Learning: Theoretical Analysis and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-attribute-distance-for-few-shot-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we try to understand FSL by delving into two key questions: (1) How to quantify the relationship between \emph{training} and \emph{novel} tasks?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-attribute-distance-for-few-shot-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Configuration Performance Learning: A Systematic Survey and Taxonomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-configuration-performance-learning-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Performance is arguably the most crucial attribute that reflects the behavior of a configurable software system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-configuration-performance-learning-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Learning Approaches for Identifying ICU Patient Subgroups: Do Results Generalise?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-approaches-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, it is unclear whether common patient subgroups exist across different ICUs, which would determine whether ICU restructuring could be operationalised in a standardised manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-approaches-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards General Computer Control: A Multimodal Agent for Red Dead Redemption II as a Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-general-computer-control-a-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies have demonstrated the success of foundation agents in specific tasks or scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-general-computer-control-a-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Mean-Teacher: An Unbiased Semi-Supervised Framework for Audio-Visual Source Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-mean-teacher-an-unbiased-semi-supervised-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Audio-Visual Source Localization (AVSL) aims to locate sounding objects within video frames given the paired audio clips.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-mean-teacher-an-unbiased-semi-supervised-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrackNex: a Few-shot Low-light Crack Segmentation Model Based on Retinex Theory for UAV Inspections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cracknex-a-few-shot-low-light-crack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LCSD consists of 102 well-illuminated crack images and 41 low-light crack images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cracknex-a-few-shot-low-light-crack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brand Visibility in Packaging: A Deep Learning Approach for Logo Detection, Saliency-Map Prediction, and Logo Placement Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brand-visibility-in-packaging-a-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the third step, by integrating logo detection with a saliency map generation, the framework provides a comprehensive brand attention score.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brand-visibility-in-packaging-a-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
