<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 21:07:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hunyuan3D 2.0: Scaling Diffusion Models for High Resolution Textured 3D Assets Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunyuan3d-2-0-scaling-diffusion-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This system includes two foundation components: a large-scale shape generation model -- Hunyuan3D-DiT, and a large-scale texture synthesis model -- Hunyuan3D-Paint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunyuan3d-2-0-scaling-diffusion-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoGERNN: An Inductive Traffic Predictor for Unobserved Locations in Dynamic Sensing Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mogernn-an-inductive-traffic-predictor-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a partially observed road network, how can we predict the traffic state of unobserved locations?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mogernn-an-inductive-traffic-predictor-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utilising Deep Learning to Elicit Expert Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilising-deep-learning-to-elicit-expert</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work [ 14 ] has introduced a method for prior elicitation that utilizes records of expert decisions to infer a prior distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilising-deep-learning-to-elicit-expert</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating High Quality RT Planning at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-high-quality-rt-planning-at-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Radiotherapy (RT) planning is complex, subjective, and time-intensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-high-quality-rt-planning-at-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MirrorCBO: A consensus-based optimization method in the spirit of mirror descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mirrorcbo-a-consensus-based-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we propose MirrorCBO, a consensus-based optimization (CBO) method which generalizes standard CBO in the same way that mirror descent generalizes gradient descent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mirrorcbo-a-consensus-based-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabularARGN: A Flexible and Efficient Auto-Regressive Framework for Generating High-Fidelity Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabularargn-a-flexible-and-efficient-auto</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthetic data generation for tabular datasets must balance fidelity, efficiency, and versatility to meet the demands of real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabularargn-a-flexible-and-efficient-auto</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternVideo2.5: Empowering Video MLLMs with Long and Rich Context Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internvideo2-5-empowering-video-mllms-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper aims to improve the performance of video multimodal large language models (MLLM) via long and rich context (LRC) modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internvideo2-5-empowering-video-mllms-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAC++: Towards 100X Compression of 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hac-towards-100x-compression-of-3d-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) has emerged as a promising framework for novel view synthesis, boasting rapid rendering speed with high fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hac-towards-100x-compression-of-3d-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALoFTRAG: Automatic Local Fine Tuning for Retrieval Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aloftrag-automatic-local-fine-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) systems have been shown to improve the accuracy of Large Language Model (LLM) outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aloftrag-automatic-local-fine-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Accurate Unified Anomaly Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-accurate-unified-anomaly-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised anomaly detection (UAD) from images strives to model normal data distributions, creating discriminative representations to distinguish and precisely localize anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-accurate-unified-anomaly-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panoramic Interests: Stylistic-Content Aware Personalized Headline Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panoramic-interests-stylistic-content-aware-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prevailing methods focus on user-oriented content preferences, but most of them overlook the fact that diverse stylistic preferences are integral to users' panoramic interests, leading to suboptimal personalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panoramic-interests-stylistic-content-aware-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HERITAGE: An End-to-End Web Platform for Processing Korean Historical Documents in Hanja</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heritage-an-end-to-end-web-platform-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, anyone interested in these documents can get a general understanding from the model predictions and the interactive glossary, especially MT outputs in Korean and English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heritage-an-end-to-end-web-platform-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternLM-XComposer2.5-Reward: A Simple Yet Effective Multi-Modal Reward Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internlm-xcomposer2-5-reward-a-simple-yet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the promising performance of Large Vision Language Models (LVLMs) in visual understanding, they occasionally generate incorrect outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internlm-xcomposer2-5-reward-a-simple-yet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedS$^3$: Towards Medical Small Language Models with Self-Evolved Slow Thinking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meds-3-towards-medical-small-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a deployable, small-scale medical language model, \mone, designed for long-chain reasoning in clinical tasks using a self-evolution paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meds-3-towards-medical-small-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fact-Preserved Personalized News Headline Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fact-preserved-personalized-news-headline-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a framework Fact-Preserved Personalized News Headline Generation (short for FPG), to prompt a tradeoff between personalization and consistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fact-preserved-personalized-news-headline-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise-Resilient Point-wise Anomaly Detection in Time Series Using Weak Segment Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-resilient-point-wise-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting anomalies in temporal data has gained significant attention across various real-world applications, aiming to identify unusual events and mitigate potential hazards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-resilient-point-wise-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cinepro: Robust Training of Foundation Models for Cancer Detection in Prostate Ultrasound Cineloops</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cinepro-robust-training-of-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, prostate ultrasound images lack pixel-level cancer annotations, introducing label noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cinepro-robust-training-of-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabularARGN: A Flexible and Efficient Auto-Regressive Framework for Generating High-Fidelity Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabularargn-a-flexible-and-efficient-auto-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthetic data generation for tabular datasets must balance fidelity, efficiency, and versatility to meet the demands of real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabularargn-a-flexible-and-efficient-auto-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics of Skill Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-of-skill-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim to understand physics of skill learning, i. e., how skills are learned in neural networks during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-of-skill-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An End-to-End Approach for Korean Wakeword Systems with Speaker Authentication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-end-to-end-approach-for-korean-wakeword</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an end-to-end approach that trains wakewords for Non-English languages, particulary Korean, and uses this to develop a Voice Authentication model to protect user privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-end-to-end-approach-for-korean-wakeword</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VARGPT: Unified Understanding and Generation in a Visual Autoregressive Multimodal Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vargpt-unified-understanding-and-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present VARGPT, a novel multimodal large language model (MLLM) that unifies visual understanding and generation within a single autoregressive framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vargpt-unified-understanding-and-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RALAD: Bridging the Real-to-Sim Domain Gap in Autonomous Driving with Retrieval-Augmented Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ralad-bridging-the-real-to-sim-domain-gap-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RALAD features three primary designs, including (1) domain adaptation via an enhanced Optimal Transport (OT) method that accounts for both individual and grouped image distances, (2) a simple and unified framework that can be applied to various models, and (3) efficient fine-tuning techniques that freeze the computationally expensive layers while maintaining robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ralad-bridging-the-real-to-sim-domain-gap-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network-informed Prompt Engineering against Organized Astroturf Campaigns under Extreme Class Imbalance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-informed-prompt-engineering-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, through prompt engineering and the proposed Balanced RAG method, it effectively detects coordinated disinformation campaigns on X (Twitter).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-informed-prompt-engineering-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coarse-to-Fine Lightweight Meta-Embedding for ID-Based Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse-to-fine-lightweight-meta-embedding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The state-of-the-art recommendation systems have shifted the attention to efficient recommendation, e. g., on-device recommendation, under memory constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse-to-fine-lightweight-meta-embedding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EmbodiedEval: Evaluate Multimodal LLMs as Embodied Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embodiedeval-evaluate-multimodal-llms-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose EmbodiedEval, a comprehensive and interactive evaluation benchmark for MLLMs with embodied tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embodiedeval-evaluate-multimodal-llms-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Drafts to Answers: Unlocking LLM Potential via Aggregation Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-drafts-to-answers-unlocking-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scaling data and model size has been proven effective for boosting the performance of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-drafts-to-answers-unlocking-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Uncertainties in Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning through Integration of Agent Termination Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-uncertainties-in-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning (MARL) has gained significant traction for solving complex real-world tasks, but the inherent stochasticity and uncertainty in these environments pose substantial challenges to efficient and robust policy learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-uncertainties-in-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MyDigiTwin: A Privacy-Preserving Framework for Personalized Cardiovascular Risk Prediction and Scenario Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mydigitwin-a-privacy-preserving-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cardiovascular disease (CVD) remains a leading cause of death, and primary prevention through personalized interventions is crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mydigitwin-a-privacy-preserving-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can open source large language models be used for tumor documentation in Germany? -- An evaluation on urological doctors' notes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-open-source-large-language-models-be-used</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Examples from a different medical domain than urology could also improve the outcome in few-shot prompting, which demonstrates the ability of LLMs to handle tasks needed for tumor documentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-open-source-large-language-models-be-used</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community-Aware Temporal Walks: Parameter-Free Representation Learning on Continuous-Time Dynamic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/community-aware-temporal-walks-parameter-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic graph representation learning plays a crucial role in understanding evolving behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/community-aware-temporal-walks-parameter-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Communication Gap: Evaluating AI Labeling Practices for Trustworthy AI Development</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-communication-gap-evaluating-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[They see benefits for alleviating communication gaps and aiding non-expert decision-makers, however limitations, misunderstandings, and suggestions for improvement were also discussed (RQ2).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-communication-gap-evaluating-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EDoRA: Efficient Weight-Decomposed Low-Rank Adaptation via Singular Value Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edora-efficient-weight-decomposed-low-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parameter-efficient fine-tuning methods, such as LoRA, reduces the number of trainable parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edora-efficient-weight-decomposed-low-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMVU: Measuring Expert-Level Multi-Discipline Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmvu-measuring-expert-level-multi-discipline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce MMVU, a comprehensive expert-level, multi-discipline benchmark for evaluating foundation models in video understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmvu-measuring-expert-level-multi-discipline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expertise elevates AI usage: experimental evidence comparing laypeople and professional artists</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expertise-elevates-ai-usage-experimental</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Novel capacities of generative AI to analyze and generate cultural artifacts raise inevitable questions about the nature and value of artistic education and human expertise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expertise-elevates-ai-usage-experimental</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UI-TARS: Pioneering Automated GUI Interaction with Native Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ui-tars-pioneering-automated-gui-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces UI-TARS, a native GUI agent model that solely perceives the screenshots as input and performs human-like interactions (e. g., keyboard and mouse operations).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ui-tars-pioneering-automated-gui-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-aware Censored Gaussian Processes for Demand Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-aware-censored-gaussian-processes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inferring the true demand for a product or a service from aggregate data is often challenging due to the limited available supply, thus resulting in observations that are censored and correspond to the realized demand, thereby not accounting for the unsatisfied demand.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-aware-censored-gaussian-processes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FNIN: A Fourier Neural Operator-based Numerical Integration Network for Surface-form-gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fnin-a-fourier-neural-operator-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional methods encounter significant challenges in achieving high accuracy and handling high-resolution inputs, particularly facing the complex nature of discontinuities and the inefficiencies associated with large-scale linear solvers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fnin-a-fourier-neural-operator-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LASER: Lip Landmark Assisted Speaker Detection for Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laser-lip-landmark-assisted-speaker-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Active Speaker Detection (ASD) aims to identify speaking individuals in complex visual scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laser-lip-landmark-assisted-speaker-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ComposeAnyone: Controllable Layout-to-Human Generation with Decoupled Multimodal Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composeanyone-controllable-layout-to-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on the success of diffusion models, significant advancements have been made in multimodal image generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composeanyone-controllable-layout-to-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Uncertainty Estimation in Semantic Segmentation via Monte-Carlo Frequency Dropout</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-uncertainty-estimation-in-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monte-Carlo (MC) Dropout provides a practical solution for estimating predictive distributions in deterministic neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-uncertainty-estimation-in-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finer-CAM: Spotting the Difference Reveals Finer Details for Visual Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finer-cam-spotting-the-difference-reveals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite its simplicity and computational efficiency, CAM often struggles to identify discriminative regions that distinguish visually similar fine-grained classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finer-cam-spotting-the-difference-reveals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Randomized Kaczmarz Methods with Beyond-Krylov Convergence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randomized-kaczmarz-methods-with-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Kaczmarz++, an accelerated randomized block Kaczmarz algorithm that exploits outlying singular values in the input to attain a fast Krylov-style convergence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randomized-kaczmarz-methods-with-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explain-Query-Test: Self-Evaluating LLMs Via Explanation and Comprehension Discrepancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explain-query-test-self-evaluating-llms-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable proficiency in generating detailed and coherent explanations of complex concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explain-query-test-self-evaluating-llms-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PD-SORT: Occlusion-Robust Multi-Object Tracking Using Pseudo-Depth Cues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pd-sort-occlusion-robust-multi-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-object tracking (MOT) is a rising topic in video processing technologies and has important application value in consumer electronics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pd-sort-occlusion-robust-multi-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimLabel: Consistency-Guided OOD Detection with Pretrained Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simlabel-consistency-guided-ood-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We thus investigate the ability of image-text comprehension among different semantic-related ID labels in VLMs and propose a novel post-hoc strategy called SimLabel.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simlabel-consistency-guided-ood-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent-R: Training Language Model Agents to Reflect via Iterative Self-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-r-training-language-model-agents-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further explore the scalability of this self-improvement paradigm, we investigate iterative refinement of both error correction capabilities and dataset construction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-r-training-language-model-agents-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early evidence of how LLMs outperform traditional systems on OCR/HTR tasks for historical records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-evidence-of-how-llms-outperform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore the ability of two LLMs -- GPT-4o and Claude Sonnet 3. 5 -- to transcribe historical handwritten documents in a tabular format and compare their performance to traditional OCR/HTR systems: EasyOCR, Keras, Pytesseract, and TrOCR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-evidence-of-how-llms-outperform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPL: Training-Free Medical Knowledge Mining of Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kpl-training-free-medical-knowledge-mining-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these challenges, we introduce the Knowledge Proxy Learning (KPL) to mine knowledge from CLIP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kpl-training-free-medical-knowledge-mining-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITCFN: Incomplete Triple-Modal Co-Attention Fusion Network for Mild Cognitive Impairment Conversion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/itcfn-incomplete-triple-modal-co-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose an innovative multimodal approach for predicting MCI conversion, focusing specifically on the issues of missing positron emission tomography (PET) data and integrating diverse medical information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/itcfn-incomplete-triple-modal-co-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Block Flow: Learning Straight Flow on Data Blocks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/block-flow-learning-straight-flow-on-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that the variance of the prior distribution can control the curvature upper bound of forward trajectories in flow-matching models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/block-flow-learning-straight-flow-on-data</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
