<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 09:17:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Siren: A Learning-Based Multi-Turn Attack Framework for Simulating Real-World Human Jailbreak Behaviors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siren-a-learning-based-multi-turn-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are widely used in real-world applications, raising concerns about their safety and trustworthiness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siren-a-learning-based-multi-turn-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating and Improving Graph to Text Generation with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-and-improving-graph-to-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although we explored the optimal prompting strategies and proposed a novel and effective diversity-difficulty-based few-shot sample selection method, we found that the improvements from tuning-free approaches were incremental, as LLMs struggle with planning on complex graphs, particularly those with a larger number of triplets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-and-improving-graph-to-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funzac at CoMeDi Shared Task: Modeling Annotator Disagreement from Word-In-Context Perspectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/funzac-at-comedi-shared-task-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we evaluate annotator disagreement in Word-in-Context (WiC) tasks exploring the relationship between contextual meaning and disagreement as part of the CoMeDi shared task competition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/funzac-at-comedi-shared-task-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the (De)Composition Capabilities of Large Language Models in Natural-to-Formal Language Conversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-de-composition-capabilities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve generalized and robust natural-to-formal language conversion (N2F), large language models (LLMs) need to have strong capabilities of decomposition and composition in N2F when faced with an unfamiliar formal language and be able to cope with compositional gaps and counter-intuitive symbolic names.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-de-composition-capabilities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When GNNs meet symmetry in ILPs: an orbit-based feature augmentation approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-gnns-meet-symmetry-in-ilps-an-orbit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate the properties of permutation equivariance and invariance in GNNs, particularly in relation to the inherent symmetry of ILP formulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-gnns-meet-symmetry-in-ilps-an-orbit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing Action Space for Deep Reinforcement Learning via Causal Effect Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-action-space-for-deep-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a method to improve exploration efficiency by estimating the causal effects of actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-action-space-for-deep-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Time-Aware Mixture of Experts for Multi-Modal Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-time-aware-mixture-of-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these limitations, we propose a Hierarchical time-aware Mixture of experts for multi-modal Sequential Recommendation (HM4SR) with a two-level Mixture of Experts (MoE) and a multi-task learning strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-time-aware-mixture-of-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Online Olympiad-Level Math Problems for LLMs Training and Contamination-Resistant Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-online-olympiad-level-math</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advances in Large Language Models (LLMs) have sparked interest in their ability to solve Olympiad-level math problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-online-olympiad-level-math</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TrajFlow: A Generative Framework for Occupancy Density Estimation Using Normalizing Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajflow-a-generative-framework-for-occupancy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the same time, the motion of traffic participants is inherently uncertain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajflow-a-generative-framework-for-occupancy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Expansion: Parameter-Efficient Modules as Building Blocks for Composite Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-expansion-parameter-efficient-modules</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning (PEFT) is an efficient alternative to full scale fine-tuning, gaining popularity recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-expansion-parameter-efficient-modules</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HorNets: Learning from Discrete and Continuous Signals with Routing Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hornets-learning-from-discrete-and-continuous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose HorNets (Horn Networks), a neural network architecture with state-of-the-art performance on synthetic and real-life data sets from scarce-data tabular domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hornets-learning-from-discrete-and-continuous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fat-to-Thin Policy Optimization: Offline RL with Sparse Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fat-to-thin-policy-optimization-offline-rl</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse continuous policies are distributions that can choose some actions at random yet keep strictly zero probability for the other actions, which are radically different from the Gaussian.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fat-to-thin-policy-optimization-offline-rl</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-LN: A Lightweight Framework for Efficient Point Cloud Classification Using Non-Parametric Positional Encoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-ln-a-lightweight-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Point-LN, a novel lightweight framework engineered for efficient 3D point cloud classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-ln-a-lightweight-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-scale and Fine-grained Vision-language Pre-training for Enhanced CT Image Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-and-fine-grained-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a fine-grained vision-language model (fVLM) for anatomy-level CT image interpretation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-and-fine-grained-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RealCritic: Towards Effectiveness-Driven Evaluation of Language Model Critiques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realcritic-towards-effectiveness-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a new benchmark designed to assess the critique capabilities of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realcritic-towards-effectiveness-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correlation-Based Band Selection for Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-based-band-selection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a correlation-based band selection approach for hyperspectral image classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-based-band-selection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Think-on-Graph: Wider, Deeper and Faster Reasoning of Large Language Model on Knowledge Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-think-on-graph-wider-deeper-and-faster</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Retrieval Augmented Generation (GRAG) is a novel paradigm that takes the naive RAG system a step further by integrating graph information, such as knowledge graph (KGs), into large-scale language models (LLMs) to mitigate hallucination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-think-on-graph-wider-deeper-and-faster</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HERMES: A Unified Self-Driving World Model for Simultaneous 3D Scene Understanding and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hermes-a-unified-self-driving-world-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driving World Models (DWMs) have become essential for autonomous driving by enabling future scene prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hermes-a-unified-self-driving-world-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-rank Prompt Interaction for Continual Vision-Language Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-rank-prompt-interaction-for-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering that the training parameters scale to the number of layers and tasks, we propose low-rank interaction-augmented decomposition to avoid memory explosion while enhancing the cross-modal association through sharing and separating common-specific low-rank factors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-rank-prompt-interaction-for-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic detection and prediction of nAMD activity change in retinal OCT using Siamese networks and Wasserstein Distance for ordinality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-detection-and-prediction-of-namd</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we proposed deep learning models for the two tasks of the public MARIO Challenge at MICCAI 2024, designed to detect and forecast changes in nAMD severity with longitudinal retinal OCT. For the first task, we employ a Vision Transformer (ViT) based Siamese Network to detect changes in AMD severity by comparing scan embeddings of a patient from different time points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-detection-and-prediction-of-namd</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BrainGuard: Privacy-Preserving Multisubject Image Reconstructions from Brain Activities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brainguard-privacy-preserving-multisubject</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these challenges, we introduce BrainGuard, a privacy-preserving collaborative training framework designed to enhance image reconstruction from multisubject fMRI data while safeguarding individual privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brainguard-privacy-preserving-multisubject</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Benchmarking and Robust Learning for Noise-Free Ego-Motion and 3D Reconstruction from Noisy Video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-benchmarking-and-robust-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim to redefine robust ego-motion estimation and photorealistic 3D reconstruction by addressing a critical limitation: the reliance on noise-free data in existing models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-benchmarking-and-robust-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whisper D-SGD: Correlated Noise Across Agents for Differentially Private Decentralized Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whisper-d-sgd-correlated-noise-across-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decentralized learning enables distributed agents to train a shared machine learning model through local computation and peer-to-peer communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whisper-d-sgd-correlated-noise-across-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoShield: Regulating Diffusion-based Video Generation Models via Watermarking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videoshield-regulating-diffusion-based-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence Generated Content (AIGC) has advanced significantly, particularly with the development of video generation models such as text-to-video (T2V) models and image-to-video (I2V) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videoshield-regulating-diffusion-based-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Automated Self-Supervised Learning for Truly Unsupervised Graph Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-automated-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning (SSL) is an emerging paradigm that exploits supervisory signals generated from the data itself, and many recent studies have leveraged SSL to conduct graph anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-automated-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedAgentBench: Dataset for Benchmarking LLMs as Agents in Medical Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medagentbench-dataset-for-benchmarking-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, a standardized dataset to benchmark the agent capabilities of LLMs in medical applications is currently lacking, making the evaluation of LLMs on complex tasks in interactive healthcare environments challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medagentbench-dataset-for-benchmarking-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Zero-Shot LLM Framework for Automatic Assignment Grading in Higher Education</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-zero-shot-llm-framework-for-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated grading has become an essential tool in education technology due to its ability to efficiently assess large volumes of student work, provide consistent and unbiased evaluations, and deliver immediate feedback to enhance learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-zero-shot-llm-framework-for-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>coverforest: Conformal Predictions with Random Forest in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coverforest-conformal-predictions-with-random</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conformal prediction provides a framework for uncertainty quantification, specifically in the forms of prediction intervals and sets with distribution-free guaranteed coverage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coverforest-conformal-predictions-with-random</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Vessel Segmentation with Symmetric Rotation-Equivariant U-Net</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-vessel-segmentation-with-symmetric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While existing equivariant learning approaches attempt to mitigate these issues, they substantially increase learning cost, model size, or both.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-vessel-segmentation-with-symmetric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing MRI Reconstruction: A Systematic Review of Deep Learning and Compressed Sensing Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-mri-reconstruction-a-systematic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we summarize key results and trends in DL-based MRI reconstruction, including quantitative metrics, the dataset, acceleration factors, and the progress of and research interest in DL techniques over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-mri-reconstruction-a-systematic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRESSing Up LLM: Efficient Stylized Question-Answering via Style Subspace Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dressing-up-llm-efficient-stylized-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach leverages the over-parameterized nature of LLMs to disentangle a style-relevant subspace within the model's representation space to conduct representation editing, ensuring a minimal impact on the original semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dressing-up-llm-efficient-stylized-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exact Soft Analytical Side-Channel Attacks using Tractable Circuits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-soft-analytical-side-channel-attacks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By leveraging sparse belief messages, this performance is achieved with little more computational cost than SASCA, and about 3 orders of magnitude less than exact inference via exhaustive enumeration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-soft-analytical-side-channel-attacks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointOBB-v3: Expanding Performance Boundaries of Single Point-Supervised Oriented Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointobb-v3-expanding-performance-boundaries</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the views, a scale augmentation module and an angle acquisition module are constructed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointobb-v3-expanding-performance-boundaries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting CLIP: Efficient Alignment of 3D MRI and Tabular Data using Domain-Specific Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-clip-efficient-alignment-of-3d-mri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal models require aligned, shared embedding spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-clip-efficient-alignment-of-3d-mri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedSlice: Fine-Tuned Large Language Models for Secure Clinical Note Sectioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medslice-fine-tuned-large-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We fine-tuned three open-source LLMs to extract sections using a curated dataset of 487 progress notes, comparing results relative to proprietary models (GPT-4o, GPT-4o mini).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medslice-fine-tuned-large-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Multimodal Open-set Test-time Adaptation via Adaptive Entropy-aware Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-multimodal-open-set-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This task becomes more challenging when multiple modalities are involved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-multimodal-open-set-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OstQuant: Refining Large Language Model Quantization with Orthogonal and Scaling Transformations for Better Distribution Fitting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ostquant-refining-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We complement QSUR with mathematical derivations that examine the effects and limitations of various transformations, guiding our development of Orthogonal and Scaling Transformation-based Quantization (OSTQuant).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ostquant-refining-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-Alignment Influences the Utility of AI-assisted Decision Making</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-alignment-influences-the-utility-of-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Whenever an AI model is used to predict a relevant (binary) outcome in AI-assisted decision making, it is widely agreed that, together with each prediction, the model should provide an AI confidence value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-alignment-influences-the-utility-of-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIDDA: SInkhorn Dynamic Domain Adaptation for Image Classification with Equivariant Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sidda-sinkhorn-dynamic-domain-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern neural networks (NNs) often do not generalize well in the presence of a "covariate shift"; that is, in situations where the training and test data distributions differ, but the conditional distribution of classification labels remains unchanged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sidda-sinkhorn-dynamic-domain-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensuring Medical AI Safety: Explainable AI-Driven Detection and Mitigation of Spurious Model Behavior and Associated Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensuring-medical-ai-safety-explainable-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks are increasingly employed in high-stakes medical applications, despite their tendency for shortcut learning in the presence of spurious correlations, which can have potentially fatal consequences in practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensuring-medical-ai-safety-explainable-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCRL4OR: Multimodal Contrastive Representation Learning for Off-Road Environmental Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcrl4or-multimodal-contrastive-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In experiments, we pre-train the MCRL4OR with a large-scale off-road driving dataset and adopt the learned multimodal representations for various downstream perception tasks in off-road driving scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcrl4or-multimodal-contrastive-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLO11-JDE: Fast and Accurate Multi-Object Tracking with Self-Supervised Re-ID</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo11-jde-fast-and-accurate-multi-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce YOLO11-JDE, a fast and accurate multi-object tracking (MOT) solution that combines real-time object detection with self-supervised Re-Identification (Re-ID).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo11-jde-fast-and-accurate-multi-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M3PT: A Transformer for Multimodal, Multi-Party Social Signal Prediction with Person-aware Blockwise Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3pt-a-transformer-for-multimodal-multi-party</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding social signals in multi-party conversations is important for human-robot interaction and artificial social intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3pt-a-transformer-for-multimodal-multi-party</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Sample Relations for Few-Shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-sample-relations-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MGRCL categorizes sample relations into three types: intra-sample relation of the same sample under different transformations, intra-class relation of homogenous samples, and inter-class relation of inhomogeneous samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-sample-relations-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse identification of nonlinear dynamics and Koopman operators with Shallow Recurrent Decoder Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-identification-of-nonlinear-dynamics-6</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatiotemporal modeling of real-world data poses a challenging problem due to inherent high dimensionality, measurement noise, and expensive data collection procedures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-identification-of-nonlinear-dynamics-6</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentRec: Agent Recommendation Using Sentence Embeddings Aligned to Human Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentrec-agent-recommendation-using-sentence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel architecture for recommending which LLM agent out of many should perform a task given a natural language prompt by extending the Sentence-BERT (SBERT) encoder model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentrec-agent-recommendation-using-sentence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EgoHand: Ego-centric Hand Pose Estimation and Gesture Recognition with Head-mounted Millimeter-wave Radar and IMUs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egohand-ego-centric-hand-pose-estimation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advanced Virtual Reality (VR) headsets, such as the Apple Vision Pro, employ bottom-facing cameras to detect hand gestures and inputs, which offers users significant convenience in VR interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egohand-ego-centric-hand-pose-estimation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can We Generate Images with CoT? Let's Verify and Reinforce Image Generation Step by Step</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-generate-images-with-cot-let-s-verify</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope our study provides unique insights and paves a new path for integrating CoT reasoning with autoregressive image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-generate-images-with-cot-let-s-verify</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pix2Cap-COCO: Advancing Visual Comprehension via Pixel-Level Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pix2cap-coco-advancing-visual-comprehension</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results demonstrate that Pix2Cap-COCO is a particularly challenging dataset, as it requires models to excel in both fine-grained visual understanding and detailed language generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pix2cap-coco-advancing-visual-comprehension</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Prompt-One-Story: Free-Lunch Consistent Text-to-Image Generation Using a Single Prompt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-prompt-one-story-free-lunch-consistent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Drawing inspiration from the inherent context consistency, we propose a novel training-free method for consistent text-to-image (T2I) generation, termed "One-Prompt-One-Story" (1Prompt1Story).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-prompt-one-story-free-lunch-consistent</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
