<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 21:05:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing detection of left bundle branch block by means of electrocardiogram’s signals using Machine Learning algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-detection-of-left-bundle-branch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LBBB is a cardiovascular disease that affects the heart’s electrical conduction system and may indicate the presence of underlying diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-detection-of-left-bundle-branch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Good Are Synthetic Medical Images? An Empirical Study with Lung Ultrasound</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-good-are-synthetic-medical-images-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adding synthetic training data using generative models offers a low-cost method to deal effectively with the data scarcity challenge, and can also address data imbalance and patient privacy issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-good-are-synthetic-medical-images-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLAIM: AIM-based Synthetic Data Generation in the Federated Setting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flaim-aim-based-synthetic-data-generation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we initiate the study of federated synthetic tabular data generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flaim-aim-based-synthetic-data-generation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network Alignment with Transferable Graph Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-alignment-with-transferable-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Network alignment is the task of establishing one-to-one correspondences between the nodes of different graphs and finds a plethora of applications in high-impact domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-alignment-with-transferable-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Representation Learning via Asymmetric Negative Contrast and Reverse Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-representation-learning-via-asymmetric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks are vulnerable to adversarial noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-representation-learning-via-asymmetric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Procedural Text Mining with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procedural-text-mining-with-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in the field of Natural Language Processing, particularly the development of large-scale language models that are pretrained on vast amounts of knowledge, are creating novel opportunities within the realm of Knowledge Engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procedural-text-mining-with-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-dimensional Bayesian Optimization with Group Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-bayesian-optimization-with-6</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a group testing approach to identify active variables to facilitate efficient optimization in these domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-bayesian-optimization-with-6</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSI: Enhancing the Robustness of 3D Point Cloud Recognition against Corruption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csi-enhancing-the-robustness-of-3d-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we harness the inherent set property of point cloud data to introduce a novel critical subset identification (CSI) method, aiming to bolster recognition robustness in the face of data corruption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csi-enhancing-the-robustness-of-3d-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plug-and-Play Posterior Sampling under Mismatched Measurement and Prior Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-posterior-sampling-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Posterior sampling has been shown to be a powerful Bayesian approach for solving imaging inverse problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-posterior-sampling-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Zero Level-Set Extraction from Unsigned Distance Fields Based on Double Covering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-zero-level-set-extraction-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the computed iso-surface is the boundary of the $r$-offset volume of the target zero level-set $S$, which is an orientable manifold, regardless of the topology of $S$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-zero-level-set-extraction-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can pre-trained models assist in dataset distillation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-pre-trained-models-assist-in-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dataset Distillation (DD) is a prominent technique that encapsulates knowledge from a large-scale original dataset into a small synthetic dataset for efficient training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-pre-trained-models-assist-in-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeaTMOSS: Mining Pre-Trained Models in Open-Source Software</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peatmoss-mining-pre-trained-models-in-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Developing and training deep learning models is expensive, so software engineers have begun to reuse pre-trained deep learning models (PTMs) and fine-tune them for downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peatmoss-mining-pre-trained-models-in-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Large Language Models As AI Research Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-language-models-as-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Can we build AI research agents to perform these long-horizon tasks?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-language-models-as-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAPES: Learning to Sample Graphs for Scalable Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grapes-learning-to-sample-graphs-for-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) learn the representation of nodes in a graph by aggregating the neighborhood information in various ways.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grapes-learning-to-sample-graphs-for-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LESSON: Learning to Integrate Exploration Strategies for Reinforcement Learning via an Option Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesson-learning-to-integrate-exploration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, a unified framework for exploration in reinforcement learning (RL) is proposed based on an option-critic model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesson-learning-to-integrate-exploration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of learning a flow-based generative model from limited sample complexity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-learning-a-flow-based-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of training a flow-based generative model, parametrized by a two-layer autoencoder, to sample from a high-dimensional Gaussian mixture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-learning-a-flow-based-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kandinsky: an Improved Text-to-Image Synthesis with Image Prior and Latent Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kandinsky-an-improved-text-to-image-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image generation is a significant domain in modern computer vision and has achieved substantial improvements through the evolution of generative architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kandinsky-an-improved-text-to-image-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RL-based Stateful Neural Adaptive Sampling and Denoising for Real-Time Path Tracing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-based-stateful-neural-adaptive-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monte-Carlo path tracing is a powerful technique for realistic image synthesis but suffers from high levels of noise at low sample counts, limiting its use in real-time applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-based-stateful-neural-adaptive-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Long Way to Go: Investigating Length Correlations in RLHF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-long-way-to-go-investigating-length</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we find that even running RLHF with a reward based solely on length can reproduce most of the downstream improvements over the initial policy model, showing that reward models in these settings have a long way to go.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-long-way-to-go-investigating-length</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSPy: Compiling Declarative Language Model Calls into Self-Improving Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dspy-compiling-declarative-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ML community is rapidly exploring techniques for prompting language models (LMs) and for stacking them into pipelines that solve complex tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dspy-compiling-declarative-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tractable Bounding of Counterfactual Queries by Knowledge Compilation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tractable-bounding-of-counterfactual-queries</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discuss the problem of bounding partially identifiable queries, such as counterfactuals, in Pearlian structural causal models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tractable-bounding-of-counterfactual-queries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Energy-Based Prior Model with Diffusion-Amortized MCMC</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-energy-based-prior-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To remedy this sampling issue, in this paper we introduce a simple but effective diffusion-based amortization method for long-run MCMC sampling and develop a novel learning algorithm for the latent space EBM based on it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-energy-based-prior-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Know2BIO: A Comprehensive Dual-View Benchmark for Evolving Biomedical Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/know2bio-a-comprehensive-dual-view-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge graphs (KGs) have emerged as a powerful framework for representing and integrating complex biomedical information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/know2bio-a-comprehensive-dual-view-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certifiably Robust Graph Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certifiably-robust-graph-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on real-world datasets demonstrate the effectiveness of our proposed method in providing effective certifiable robustness and enhancing the robustness of any GCL model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certifiably-robust-graph-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relational Convolutional Networks: A framework for learning representations of hierarchical relations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-convolutional-networks-a-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on the problem of learning representations of hierarchical relations, proposing an architectural framework we call "relational convolutional networks".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-convolutional-networks-a-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Personalized Story Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-personalized-story-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further develop a personalized story evaluation model PERSE to infer reviewer preferences and provide a personalized evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-personalized-story-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DED: Diagnostic Evidence Distillation for acne severity grading on face images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ded-diagnostic-evidence-distillation-for-acne</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose an acne diagnosis method, Diagnostic Evidence Distillation (DED), that suitably adapts the characteristics of acne diagnosis and can be applied to diagnose under different acne criteria.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ded-diagnostic-evidence-distillation-for-acne</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GENER: A Parallel Layer Deep Learning Network To Detect Gene-Gene Interactions From Gene Expression Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gener-a-parallel-layer-deep-learning-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting and discovering new gene interactions based on known gene expressions and gene interaction data presents a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gener-a-parallel-layer-deep-learning-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Text-to-Image Diffusion Models with Reward Backpropagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-text-to-image-diffusion-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to their unsupervised training, controlling their behavior in downstream tasks, such as maximizing human-perceived image quality, image-text alignment, or ethical image generation, is difficult.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-text-to-image-diffusion-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoLLIE: Annotation Guidelines improve Zero-Shot Information-Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gollie-annotation-guidelines-improve-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous attempts to leverage such information have failed, even with the largest models, as they are not able to follow the guidelines out-of-the-box.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gollie-annotation-guidelines-improve-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MathCoder: Seamless Code Integration in LLMs for Enhanced Mathematical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathcoder-seamless-code-integration-in-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a method to fine-tune open-source language models, enabling them to use code for modeling and deriving math equations and, consequently, enhancing their mathematical reasoning abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathcoder-seamless-code-integration-in-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent Instructs Large Language Models to be General Zero-Shot Reasoners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-instructs-large-language-models-to-be</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For instance, our method boosts the performance of state-of-the-art large language models by a large margin, including Vicuna-13b (13. 3%), Llama-2-70b-chat (23. 2%), and GPT-3. 5 Turbo (17. 0%).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-instructs-large-language-models-to-be</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Baselines with Visual Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-baselines-with-visual-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large multimodal models (LMM) have recently shown encouraging progress with visual instruction tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-baselines-with-visual-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeReg: Image-to-Point Cloud Registration Leveraging Pretrained Diffusion Models and Monocular Depth Estimators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freereg-image-to-point-cloud-registration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Matching cross-modality features between images and point clouds is a fundamental problem for image-to-point cloud registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freereg-image-to-point-cloud-registration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreshLLMs: Refreshing Large Language Models with Search Engine Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freshllms-refreshing-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce FreshQA, a novel dynamic QA benchmark encompassing a diverse range of question and answer types, including questions that require fast-changing world knowledge as well as questions with false premises that need to be debunked.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freshllms-refreshing-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-Based Radiance Fields for Controllable Human Motion Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-based-radiance-fields-for-controllable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel controllable human motion synthesis method for fine-level deformation based on static point-based radiance fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-based-radiance-fields-for-controllable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memoria: Hebbian Memory Architecture for Human-Like Sequential Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memoria-hebbian-memory-architecture-for-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have demonstrated their success in various domains and tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memoria-hebbian-memory-architecture-for-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoLiDE: Concomitant Linear DAG Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colide-concomitant-linear-dag-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We deal with the combinatorial problem of learning directed acyclic graph (DAG) structure from observational data adhering to a linear structural equation model (SEM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colide-concomitant-linear-dag-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Training of a Neural HMM with Label and Transition Probabilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-training-of-a-neural-hmm-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate recognition results and additionally Viterbi alignments of our models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-training-of-a-neural-hmm-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GET: Group Event Transformer for Event-Based Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/get-group-event-transformer-for-event-based-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event cameras are a type of novel neuromorphic sen-sor that has been gaining increasing attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/get-group-event-transformer-for-event-based-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-FP: An Experimental Study of Automated Feature Preprocessing for Tabular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-fp-an-experimental-study-of-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This observation enables us to extend a variety of HPO and NAS algorithms to solve the Auto-FP problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-fp-an-experimental-study-of-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Language Models Employ the Socratic Method? Experiments with Code Debugging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-language-models-employ-the-socratic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When employing the Socratic method of teaching, instructors guide students toward solving a problem on their own rather than providing the solution directly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-language-models-employ-the-socratic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaMerging: Adaptive Model Merging for Multi-Task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adamerging-adaptive-model-merging-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach aims to autonomously learn the coefficients for model merging, either in a task-wise or layer-wise manner, without relying on the original training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adamerging-adaptive-model-merging-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Prototype-Based Neural Network for Image Anomaly Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-prototype-based-neural-network-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes ProtoAD, a prototype-based neural network for image anomaly detection and localization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-prototype-based-neural-network-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOLA: Networks as Linear Combination of Low Rank Random Basis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nola-networks-as-linear-combination-of-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For instance, in larger models, even a rank one decomposition might exceed the number of parameters truly needed for adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nola-networks-as-linear-combination-of-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delving into CLIP latent space for Video Anomaly Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delving-into-clip-latent-space-for-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We tackle the complex problem of detecting and recognising anomalies in surveillance videos at the frame level, utilising only video-level supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delving-into-clip-latent-space-for-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Stability of Expressive Positional Encodings for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-stability-of-expressive-positional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite many attempts to address non-uniqueness, most methods overlook stability, leading to poor generalization on unseen graph structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-stability-of-expressive-positional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering General Reinforcement Learning Algorithms with Adversarial Environment Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-general-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, it has been shown that it is possible to meta-learn update rules, with the hope of discovering algorithms that can perform well on a wide range of RL tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-general-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOMINO: A Dual-System for Multi-step Visual Language Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domino-a-dual-system-for-multi-step-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By fine-tuning the System-2 module (LLaMA-2 70B) on only a small amount of data on multi-step reasoning, the accuracy of our method is further improved and surpasses the best fully-supervised end-to-end approach by 5. 7% and a pipeline approach with FlanPaLM (540B) by 7. 5% on a challenging dataset with human-authored questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domino-a-dual-system-for-multi-step-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Vision Anomaly Detection with the Guidance of Language Modality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-vision-anomaly-detection-with-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To learn a more compact latent space for the vision anomaly detector, CMLE learns a correlation structure matrix from the language modality, and then the latent space of vision modality will be learned with the guidance of the matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-vision-anomaly-detection-with-the</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
